My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years on a hellish island,
I have come home with only one goal...
to save my city.
But to do so,I can't be the killer I once was.
To honor my friend's memory,I must be someone else.
I must be something else.
Previously on "Arrow"...
The defendant is found not guilty.
Hello,Moira.
What do you want,Malcolm?
Thea is my daughter.
What do these guys want with a seven year old sub?
What's on it,it'll save the human race.
Will it save him?
Sir,there's been a development.
Brother Cyrus...
How do you feel?
Stronger.
What was that?
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly Presents
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-收音机头
ARROW Season2Episode 08
Mrs.Queen,welcome back to the company.
Thank you.
- You look fabulous. - Really,better than ever.
Did you do something to your hair?
Yes,I shampooed it without eight women and a guard watching me.
Is it ok to laugh?
Because I was ordered not to say anything about you being in prison,
just to avoid any awkward...exchanges.
Like that one.
Right.
We need to drill down on these numbers before the earnings call.
Oliver.I didn't realize your mother was stopping by for a visit today.
Well,it's not a visit.
This is her company,too.
Of course.
How are you,Moira?
Back,Isabel.
Mr.Queen,may I speak to you for a minute?
What sort of message does it send to the investment committee,to the city,
if we hand Queen Consolidated right back to your mother?
- She was acquitted. - By a jury.Not by the city.
Oliver.Stop thinking like a son and start thinking like a CEO.
Oliver.There's been a break-in.
Damn!
This door was made of expanded reinforced titanium.
What did they use to do this?
Not sure yet.No sign of any explosives.
Maybe a crane,maybe a forklift.
I'm guessing there was at least three of them,maybe four.
And given how quick they got in and out of here...
They were fast.
Whoa,hey,stop,wait!You don't even have a fare!
Any idea what these guys were so hot to break in here for?
You didn't happen to leave a spare earthquake machine lying around,did you?
Sorry.
This is what we're able to pull off the security cameras.
He was the only guy we got on video.
The rest of the crew must have come in after him.
Actually,it was only one guy.
Ah,sorry I'm late.
But actually,my train was late.
Well,the second one.The first one I did miss,
but that was my cab driver's fault.
I've got this great traffic app,and...
But he thought that he was right.
I'm here now,though.So.
Great.Who the hell are you?
And do your parents know that you're here?
I'm Barry Allen.
I'm from the Central City police department.
I'm with the crime scene investigation unit.
We're working on a case with some similar unexplained elements in Central City,
so when the report of your robbery came over the wire,my captain sent me up here.
And you think one guy ripped through this door like it was tin foil?
One very strong guy,yeah.
Uh,it takes about 1,250 foot pounds of torque to break someone's neck.
You see the marks on the guard's neck?
The bruising pattern suggests the killer used only one hand.
I'm guessing you don't know how hard it is to break someone's neck.
Hmm?No.No idea.
Uh,we're going to need a list of the entire inventory here to figure out exactly what was stolen.
Actually,I think I know what was stolen.
A centrifuge.
An industrial centrifuge.
Probably the Cord Enterprises 2BX 900.Maybe the six series.
Both have a three column base.
Here,you can see the three sets of broken bolts where the thief just...
ripped it out of the ground.
And what exactly is a centrifuge?
It separates liquids.
The centripetal acceleration causes denser substances to separate out along the radial direction.
And lighter objects move to the top.
What did you say your name was again?
Barry.Allen.
Felicity.Smoak.
Um,you can see the cracks heading towards the door.
Footsteps.
One guy.
Anyway,it's just a theory.
One backed by a lot of evidence.
There has to be another explanation.
Yeah.I'm sure you're right.
You might want to fill our mutual friend in on this.
Yeah.Don't worry.
I'm sure he's already on it.
We need to change directions 10 degrees north.
We need to rest.
If Ivo and any of his men survived that blast,they'll be tracking us.
We keep moving.
Five minutes.
- You watch him,please. - Of course.
Do you believe them?
That this Hosen will lead us to a wrecked Japanese sub?
Ivo seems to think so.
I just hope whatever miracle serum they're after is actually onboard.
For his sake.
How do you know that girl?
Sara was on my father's boat...
with me.
What about the girl in the picture?
Laurel?
The girl you told me you were in love with.
Sara is her sister.
I feel like taking a walk.
Anyone care to join me?
I guess a lot's happened in the last year.
Oliver.
Got the final inventory from applied sciences.
That CSI from Central City was right.
The only thing missing is a centrifuge.
You have to see this.
I pulled up CC traffic camera footage from across the street of applied sciences.
This is three minutes after the alarm went off.
Can we help you with something,Detective?
Oh,CSIs aren't actually detectives.
We don't even carry guns.
Just some plastic baggies.
- Uh,where should I set up my equipment? - I'll show you.
What's going on?
Your assistant said that you preferred to keep the investigation in house,
so I cleared it with my captain to give you a hand.
What are you doing?
We need to find this intruder.
And he seems to know more about it than any of us.
Forensic science isn't exactly my forte,so...
I'd say we need him.
Wouldn't you?
Mm-hmm.
I'll show you around.
Why am I getting the feeling you know more about this than Felicity's new friend?
Pray I'm wrong.
Hi.
I'm sorry about what happened at the office this morning.
There are a lot of people who think I got away with murder,Oliver.
Maybe I did.
Mom,the trial,the Undertaking,Malcolm Merlyn,all of that is behind us now.
And we need everyone to see that.
How are we going to do that?
We throw a party.
Thea.
Roy.
Did I hear you guys say something about a party?
A welcome back to Queen Consolidated party for mom.
I don't think so.
If things are going to get back to normal,then we need to start acting normal.
Normal for us is a lavish party.
Oh.I'm sorry,Mrs.Queen,I can't stay for brunch.
I guess we got to go.
Bye.
I'll take care of everything.
What exactly are you looking for?
Your thief's shoes touched the ground,
which means he tracked in dozens of clues as to where he's been the past few days.
Got ya.
Shouldn't take long.
So you've seen him,right?
The Vigilante?
I read that he saved you.
What was he like?
- Green. - Green.
That's interesting,right?
I mean,why green?
Black would be better for stealth,and urban camouflage.
Me,personally,I think that he trained in some sort of like forest or jungle environment,
and the green is a nod to that.
I don't give the vigilante much thought.
Police reports show that he uses carbon arrows,
but if he switched to an aluminum carbon composite,
he would have far better penetration.
Maybe he thinks he penetrates just fine.
Do you want to know something else?
I think that he has partners.
Definitely someone with a background in computer sciences.
Yeah.
Why are you so interested in the Vigilante?
When I was 11,my mom was murdered.
I'm so sorry.
They never caught the guy who did it.
Maybe he would have.
The soil...
there's a crystalline structure in it.
That's weird.
What's weird?
It's sugar.
Sin,you said this was an emergency.
No offense,but Thea,you shouldn't be here.
In the alleyway of the club I own?
It's my friend Max.He's missing.
I haven't seen him for a week,no one has.
Something happened to him.
I figured you knew someone who could help.
Roy can help you.
I thought you wanted me to stay out of trouble.
I kind of like that you never turn away from someone who needs help.
I'll just get someone to cover the club.
What do you mean?
Oh,I'm coming with you.
I hear you're throwing a party.
I didn't get my invite.
Where exactly should I have addressed it?
Starling City cemetery?
I know that's where you wish I was right now.
Lying beside my son.
Am I supposed to feel sorry for you,Malcolm?
You killed Tommy.
You killed your son.
You cannot have my daughter.
Our daughter.
I think we both needed someone that night.
I felt so bad about betraying Rebecca's memory
that I left Starling.
Left Tommy behind.
That's when I made my way to Nanda Parbat,
where I found my new purpose.
In a way,Moira,
you made me the man I am today.
Thea is innocent.
She loved Robert.
Please don't take that away from her,I'm begging you.
Thea is all I have left.
Tell her the truth,and tell her soon.
You found something?
We found something.
There were trace amounts of sucrose and a spec of dirt the killer dragged in here on his boot.
Which got me thinking.
There is a sugar refinery two miles from here.
The land around it is suffused in waste sugar.
So I checked.
They had a delivery truck stolen a few days ago.
Their truck matches the make and model of the truck the thief used to steal the centrifuge.
Can you track the vehicle?
We've been trying.
What was that?
You're not going to believe this.
The truck,it was just used to rob a blood bank.
Are you sure?
Yeah.Our guy just made off with 30,000 ccs of O-negative.
What,he has super strength,likes blood?
Please don't tell me we suddenly believe in vampires.
We should give this information to the local police.
I'll...take care of that.
Did you say that you were working a similar case in Central City?
Oh,yeah,um...
Yeah,you know,it's similar.
Has similar elements.
A lot of similarities.
Right.
Yeah.I want you to look into this Allen kid.
There's more to him than he's letting on.
His intentions seem pretty clear to me.
Just do it,please.
Oliver,when are you going to tell me what exactly we're up against?
Yeooww!
Sorry.
Thank you.
You were right to ask if I knew more than I was letting on.
I've seen men with abilities like that before.
You have?
Where?
The island.
My second year marooned there,we...
I came across the remains of a Japanese World War II military project.
It was a serum designed to create human weapons.
Human weapons.
My God,what's next,aliens?
This is real,Diggle.
Those five years that I was away,I came across things that just...
defy explanation.
There's a doctor,his name is Ivo,
and he came to the island to test the serum on people.
The ones that survived,their endurance,reflexes and strength were all enhanced.
And you think this Ivo's in Starling City?
He's dead.
And so is everyone that he injected with the serum.
The last of which...
I burned.
You think someone found the recipe.
The centrifuge and a large supply of blood.
I think someone wants to make more of it.
A lot more.
Why couldn't you have been marooned on Aruba?
There's a third component...
a strong sedative.
I think I preferred it when you left these in people.
I need you to analyze the blood on the arrowhead.
If we can figure out which sedative they're using...
We can figure out where the next robbery will be.
Barry and I will get right on it.
I think our Miss Smoak is smitten.
Diggle,what did you find out about Mr.Allen?
He's not who he says he is.
How are you holding up?
I could do with a better looking crutch.
You two seem like you've gotten pretty chummy.
We're here.
There must be a fissure in the island below the waterline for it to come that far inland.
Unbelievable.
They have nitric acid next to hydrazine?
Permanganates on top of acetone?
This is the definition of dangerous.
If it's so dangerous,maybe you shouldn't be touching them.
- Barry. - Yeah.
I managed to get a sample of the perpetrator's blood from the police department.
We need to isolate a sedative in the blood.
It could lead us to the thief.
How did the police get it?
Apparently the Vigilante shot him with an arrow.
You're kidding.
You know what this means,right?
This means the Vigilante's working the same case we are!
Heh.Go figure.
How did you get it?
Oliver has a lot of connections.
Wow.Pays to work for a billionaire.
Actually my take home's nothing special.
Especially given I am rarely at home,since I'm with him every night.
Well,I didn't realize you and he were...
Oh,no.
Work.He...
and I are not,no,I do not like Oliver.
Um,I was invited to a work function.
It's a party.
And I have a plus-one.
I was thinking you would make a really good...
plus one.
There's not going to be dancing,is there?
I'm not just not too good on my feet.
It reeks in here.
I guess your friend wasn't too into painting seascapes.
Max is like any starving artist...
starving.
But I could always crash here when I didn't have a place to stay.
Hey,this blood drive was a week ago.
When did you say he went missing?
That day.
It's Daily.
Someone's looking for Maxwell Stanton.
And they should find him.
Yes,brother blood.
Blood provides life.
Blood provides power.
And with power...
There's no limit to what I can do.
Central City is just a day away from making history
when the controversial S.T.A.R.Lab's particle accelerator is finally turned on.
Pretty cool,right?
You know there's been a hundred percent increase in earthquakes
since they've turned on the Large Hadron Collider.
That data is misleading.
Oh,do tell.
You know about misleading,don't you?
What are you talking about?
He's not from CSI,he's an assistant.
Whose bosses don't know you're in Starling.
And there is no similar case in Central City.
So tell me,Barry...
What are you really doing here?
I told you my mom was murdered.
By your father.
He didn't do it.
You said that the police didn't find the man who killed her.
The police think they did.
My dad has been serving a life sentence.
They didn't believe me.
About what?
I was 11.
One night...
something just came into our house,like a tornado.
A blur.
Somewhere inside The Blur,I saw a person.
My dad went to fight it.
I tried to get 'em when suddenly...
I was 20 blocks away from our house.
Nobody believed me.
They thought I was trying to cover for my father.
But what I saw that night was real.
As real as the man that ripped down that metal door with his bare hands.
That's why I look into cases like this.
The ones nobody believes are possible.
Maybe if I can just make sense of one,
I might be able to find out who really killed my mother.
And free my dad.
I am sorry I lied to you.
Better find another plus one.
He did lie about who he really was.
And what do we do every day?
Hey.
How's everything going in there?
Good evening,Queens.
Can I have a word?
Yeah.
I'm sorry if I overreacted a little bit earlier.
Oh,you think?
Look,right now you need to apologize to your mother.
Not me.
- For what? - Your being wrong.
I guess these days,I only draw a crowd when I'm on trial for murder.
Mom,you don't have to...
We have guests.
However few of them there are.
This is not your fault,Ollie.
How's your mom doing?
Oh,you know us Queen women...
nothing gets to us.
You must take after your dad.
Sorry.
Sin.What's up?
I found Max.
Where?
I'm on my way.
They find Max?
Um,no.
She just wants me to stop by.
I can come with you.
You should stay here.
Your mom needs you.
Ok,I'll call you later.
Time for a dance?
Not really feeling like dancing with you,Oliver.
I know.
And that is why I called him.
Fyi... they will card him at the bar.
- Hi. - Hi.
I was serious about not being able to dance.
But I'll hold your hands and sway.
Sold.
Ok.
I tried to warn you.
I tried to ignore you.
I am sorry,Oliver.
Yeah.
Oliver threw you a lovely party.
Oliver's a good son,if not the best judge of character.
Is everything ok?
Everything's going perfectly.
He doesn't have long.
If this miracle drug is onboard,then we need to find it now.
Slade,be back in a few minutes,ok?
I'll just get comfortable.
Come on.
There.
Mirakuru.
Miracle.
I was never sure it was real.
What happens if we give it to Slade?
He needs a sedative in his bloodstream first.
They might have potassium bromide or barbital.
Ohh.It's empty.
What happens if we give it to him without the sedative?
Sarah!
He'll die,for sure.
He's going to die anyway.
What was that?
Ivo and his men.
They're on the sub.
Have you made contact?
Yes.
He said to tell you that your information was gratefully accepted.
Thank you.
- Who was that? - Nothing to worry about.
Thank you for tonight,Oliver.
It was a lovely party.
I'm so sorry that I put you through that.
Oh,listen,I don't care what anyone else in this city thinks of me.
I only care what you two think.
And I have to get back to the office.
Excuse me.
Thea.
There's something I need to tell you.
Sure.What is it?
I love you.
I love you,too.
Yes.
Yes,sir.I...
yes,director,I know that this is not the first time.
Yes,sir,I do value my job,very much.
Look,I will be on the next train.
Mm-hmm.I'll be back tonight.
Ok.Thank...
Well,my boss found out I don't have food poisoning.
I need to get back to Central City if I still want to be employed.
Which I do.
Tell the SCPD that the sedative in the thief's blood is Ketamine.
It's a schedule three controlled substance.
It shouldn't be too hard to track.
Yeah,I'll make sure they get it.
Thank you.
- It was really nice...  - thank you for...
- working with you. - everything,We couldn't have done it...
Without you.
Good-bye,Felicity.
Good-bye.
Max!Get off,let go!
- Max!Get off of me! - Hey!Let her go.
Cut it out!
Stupid cops.
They're saying Max ODed.
- Was he using? - No!
He made extra cash donating blood.
You really think the hospital would let him be a donor if he was an addict?
Hey.Can't be here,kid.
They found trace amounts of Ketamine in the thief's blood.
It's a common surgical anesthesia derived from hydrochloric salt.
Can you use that to track him?
With the current concentration ratio in the blood sample,
there's only one possible location with a large enough quality of the sedative
that correlates with the amount of blood the stolen centrifuge can process.
What is it?There's no sign.
A.R.G.U.S.doesn't like to advertise.
It's a disaster bunker.
Right on the edge of the Glades.
A.R.G.U.S.has them all over the country.
They store relief supplies... food,clothing...
Medicine.
I'm on my way.
Oliver...
I can't believe I'm actually saying this.
The way this arrowhead is bent...
It means our thief's muscle density is at least 120 pounds per cubic foot.
That's almost the same density as common concrete.
Your arrows may cut this guy,but they will not stop him.
Well,I've beat someone like this before,Felicity.
I can do it again.
What if you can't?
Oliver.
Now this,it could save you...
Or it could kill you.
By the looks on your faces,I'm going to die anyway.
Sorry.
For what?
For not telling you how I really feel.
Do it.
No!
What?
I need your help.
A friend of mine's friend,well,
the cops think he ODed,but we think he was murdered.
Why?
Well,he wasn't an addict,for starters.And this...
This doesn't look like any OD I've ever seen.
Stay away from that.
You know something?
What happened to him?
You're the one who told me to be your eyes and ears on the streets.
You know what,that is not good enough for me anymore.
Fine.
Then we're done altogether.
I don't need you!
I have friends that can help me.
You can't stop us.
Slow you down.
And I thought it couldn't hurt to add extra security guards.
It hurt them.
Badly.
Have you prepared Thea?
No.
You will not go near Thea,
you will not speak to her and you will never set foot in this house again.
I set you free,Moira.
Your life belongs to me.
I am through being afraid of you.
You think you can stop me?
Even the Vigilante couldn't kill me.
No,he couldn't.
But I know someone who can.
Ra's al Ghul.
How do you know that name?
Well,I didn't.
Until you mentioned Nanda Parbat.
The League of Assassins,however twisted their aims,
believes very deeply in a code of honor.
Your undertaking betrayed that code.
You told Ra's I'm still alive?
He was so grateful to hear it.
Because he so very much wants to kill you himself.
So my advice to you,Malcolm...
Run.
This isn't finished,Moira.
Who are you?
Merely a follower.
Of who?!
My brother.
Did he give you the mirakuru?
Did he inject you with it?!
No.
He saved me with it.
Please.Please!
Oliver!Oliver!Oliver!Oliver!
Is he alive?
His pulse is weak,but it's there.
Oliver!
Can you hear me?
His pupils are dilated!
What the hell was that?
I don't know,it's coded.
Damn it.Damn it!
I can't break into the dispensary files.
I have no idea what he was injected with!
Poisoned with.
All right,we have no choice.
What are you doing?
Calling 9-1-1.
- Dig,wait! - Can't wait!
How are we supposed to explain this?
Everyone's going to find out Oliver's the Vigilante!
Which won't matter if he's dead.
Felicity,we can't save him!
I know,you're right...
We can't.
One way to Central City.
It left ten minutes ago.
Of course it did.
When is the next one?
In the morning.
Ohh.Please save my friend.
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly Presents
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-收音机头
ARROW Season2Episode 08