3 percent rise in domestic violence calls.
So the Thanksgiving week always brings an uptick.
Families starting to gather. In-laws in town.
If the pilgrims and indians could find a way.
Maybe the first Thanksgiving was cause they were just to worn out to fight anymore.
- Where's the file I asked you for?
- It's on your desk, sir.
Thank you Baker.
What about this Raymond thing?
Corporation counsel was served today with a lawsuit., alleging police brutality.
It claims, that two days ago, Raymond assaulted an eight-year-old boy
living on the same block as his partner, Officer Donohue.
- Is the boy ok?
- After two hour in ER, and multiple stitches.
His father, an attorney, named Preston Morris, says his son is
"totally traumatized by the attack,"
and went straight to the media after filing the suit.
- And we have no idea why it happened.
- Not even from his partner.
Far as anyone can tell, Raymond just snapped.
Goes without saying, the optics are bad on this.
Sterling record, decorated twice for heroism.
This is not that.
He is entitled to the same presumption of innocence afforded any other member of my department.
- You'll let Legal handle it?
- Yes, Mrs. Reagan.
Moving on.
Vic was a hell of a cop.
But he would be the first to say he wasn't the best in the family.
That would belong to Colleen over there.
In fact, we partnered for a while.
And then she was assigned to Vic,
who said that that was the happiest day of his life.
Until, of course, Brendan and Meara
came along.
May the Lord bless Vic McGuire
and keep his family in His heart.
- You did good, Reagan.
- Thanks, Roy.
- Fly was open the entire time though.
- Up yours, Roy.
Thank you, Henry.
- How you doing?
- I'm hanging in there.
This place already seems so empty without him.
You'll see him again one day.
Don't be a stranger.
Okay.
- This doesn't make sense.
- Brendan, I am not imagining things.
- What you're saying is crazy.
- I'm...
Hi, kids.
Hey, Mr. Reagan.
Look...
I've been through this a little bit.
You got to go day by day.
But it will get better.
Go on. Say it.
Say what?
Unless Dad didn't just die.
What do you mean?
I think Mom might've had something to do with his death.
Meara, your father died of cancer.
- He's been sick for the last eight months.
- No, but he was better last week.
- Mr. Reagan, she is just upset.
- And you're not?
Listen to what you're saying, Meara. It's your mother.
I know how it sounds, and maybe she didn't do anything to Dad.
But I think she did.
How the hell can you not love Thanksgiving?
Six hours of cooking, ten minutes of eating and then a food coma?
- What's wrong with a food coma?
- Give me any other holiday, please.
- Detectives.
- What do you got, Sarge?
Hispanic male, stabbed to death, found by the owner of this bar over there.
Yeah, I came out to take out some empties, and I almost stepped on him.
- You ever seen him before?
- Just inside, watching the football.
I'm missing a football game tonight?
- I think he means soccer.
- Yeah, Venezuela versus Chile!
Right! Soccer's not football.
And it looks like the game is officially over for this guy.
Wallet...
appears to be intact.
Wasn't a robbery.
Single stab wound to the chest.
Judging by the angle, the killer is left-handed.
Gabriel Vega, 26 years old.
He lives about three blocks from here.
I'd say Mr. Vega came out for a smoke, killer approached to bum one,
stabbed him before he lit up.
- You psychic?
- 'Cause I only see the one.
Uh, no. There's another one right there.
Saw it on the way in.
You got security cameras here?
No, I don't but other businesses in the area do.
All right. Uh, Sarge, can you have your guys round 'em all up, everything within
- a five-block radius?
- Of course.
Well, if this isn't a robbery, you got a motive for why somebody wanted him dead?
Maybe he was cheering for the wrong soccer team.
Step aside. Kill those TVs.
Please, sir, this is one of my biggest nights of the year.
- Not anymore it isn't.
- Por favor...
Terry Giondo here for Master Blend 3000.
Hey! A minute left in the half!
- Shut up!
- And we're kicking their asses!
Shut up! Now, here's how it's gonna go down.
I want Chile fans over there on the bench, Venezuela fans over here on the bar.
Move your asses. Let's go. Let's go!
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
警脉相承 第四季第9集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
时间轴：光影
20 possibles in that bar and not a suspect among 'em.
- Remember when staying up all night was fun?
- Oh, yeah.
Reagan, Baez. How's your Spanish Harlem slaying?
- Ask me after my nap, Sarge.
- Not till you go through those.
- Security tapes?
- Mm-hmm.
- Maybe we'll get a look at our killer.
- TARU just dropped 'em off so get crackin'.
I'll divvy 'em up, you make the coffee?
- Okay.
- Oh, and, uh... good morning!
- Mr. Reagan.
- Hi, Meara.
- I'm so glad you called.
- Your mom isn't here?
No, she's at the store.
Okay.
Are you, uh... you feeling any better?
I tried. Brendan says I'm wrong.
But he didn't see what I saw.
- Which was?
- The way Mom's been recently.
I saw her reading Dad's life insurance policy over and over.
And a week ago Saturday, I swear to God,
she was on this computer doing a search on euthanasia.
Well, people look up all kinds of things online.
Even when your husband is dying?
Meara, what you're describing
- is a crime and a mortal sin.
- I know that.
I'm neither a cop nor a priest.
Well, you better show me.
She searched "euthanasia"
and clicked on this link.
"Last Exit Collective, helping you face the end with dignity. "
"Doctor consultation. How to order pentobarbital and methaqualone. "
Oh, my God.
Did your dad ever talk about ending it all?
Never. You saw him last week.
He was sitting up, he was making jokes.
Has she received any parcels recently?
She got a box last week. It had a U.S. Customs stamp on it.
Then she was shredding something.
Oh, Meara.
I'm not sure what you want from me here.
Please prove to me my mom didn't do this.
Meara?
- You home?
- In here, Mom.
Honey, I wanted you to help me with this...
Henry. What are you doing here?
Well, I got all the way home last night and realized
that I left my glasses right here on your kitchen counter.
Henry,
I sweated enough perps in my life to know when I'm getting fed a line.
You told me not to be a stranger.
Did I tell you he was the flirtiest partner I ever had?
- And that includes your father.
- Doesn't surprise me.
Come on. Help me unload the car, Romeo.
- That's not Raymond.
- Commissioner Reagan.
- Officer Donohue.
- Raymond's kenneled, per protocol.
I'm just helping out with Kurtis here and... trying to stay busy.
Pretty serious lawsuit we got on our hands.
It's a load of crap, respectfully.
Raymond's the best partner I've ever had.
He's never gone after anyone other than perps and, then, only on my orders. And he loves kids.
Plays with my niece Annie all the time. Maybe that boy provoked him.
- We're not gonna blame the victim here.
- Yes, sir.
How did Raymond get out of your yard?
Sir, I have no idea. He's getting up there.
His days of jumping the fence to get laid are over.
And I keep that gate padlocked, always.
Yet he got out.
Well, there's no evidence of that. But the padlock had disappeared.
He also had points deducted last year
at the National Field Trials after making
a secondary bite on the simulated attacker.
Raymond got kicked in the takedown.
But he's never had a negative incident with the public.
He's given his life to service. He deserves a happy retirement,
not some shyster says he's a killer. It's not right.
I want to see your partner.
This way.
Fuss!
(QUARANTINED ANIMAL)
Five more days like this.
If the rabies and behavior evaluations come back on time.
May I?
Sir, he's confined to kennel. I...
I'm the police commissioner.
You use "Ray" for command purposes?
- Yes, sir.
- Ray.
Come.
You know something about this.
I do.
Down.
Stay.
Come!
Heel.
Good boy.
He didn't do it.
- Anything?
- Nothing.
All I got are a bunch of dark, empty streets.
Well, I'll trade you for the cross-dresser that looks just like Sergeant Gormley.
Come on, killer, killer,
where is our killer?
Hold on.
I found a guy running out of that alley.
Time code matches Vega's T.O.D.
- Hello, dirtbag.
- You mean, hello, Tic-Tac.
- What, you know the guy?
- Wish I didn't.
- Why do they call him Tic-Tac?
- Because if it looks like a pill, he'll swallow it, along with any other drug.
Uh-huh. So he's a junkie.
- Is he capable of murder?
- Tic-Tac's capable of anything.
Nice neighborhood.
Tic-Tac lives in one of these dumps when he's not nodding off in some shooting gallery.
Yeah. You seem to know a lot about this guy.
- What's your history with him?
- There he is.
All right, I'll go around.
- Flush him out to me.
- Actually, can you do the flushing?
Tic-Tac!
Where you going?
Look what the cat coughed up, huh?
What do you want with me?
Put it down.
- I'm clean!
- Put it down!
- I didn't do anything!
- I don't give a damn! I said drop it!
What is this, Baez? Something I'm missing here?
I guess I should've said- his real name is Javi.
He's my brother.
Really?
Come on.
- In a cell; lock it twice.
- Yeah, I gotcha.
All right, this way. To the back.
When were you gonna tell me he was your brother?
- You do realize I almost shot him, right?
- You would've done me a favor.
Whoa, whoa. What's the story with you?
What do you want to know? How me and Javi were best friends growing up?
How he wanted to stay back a grade so we could be in all the same classes?
Or how that all ended when he met a new best friend in a bag of dope?
- You know, maybe you ought to sit this one out.
- Excuse me?
- You're his sister.
- Not as far as I'm concerned.
No, you are, and you proved it by pushing him through a glass door.
You're busting me on how I took down a hump? You?
- Oh, come on...
- Everything okay out here?
No, Sarge... the guy we like for Vega's murder happens to be Baez's older brother.
Which is irrelevant,
unless family is now outlawed around here- which means Danny's gonna get pretty lonely
without somebody from his dropping by every other day.
My family members aren't murder suspects who I pushed through a door.
It doesn't matter who Javi is. It only matters that he killed Vega.
- No, it matters how you handle the situation...
- All right, listen up, listen up.
Both of you talk to him. But I'll be nearby.
I figured since you used to work in the lab...
that you might help me piece this thing together.
Does Colleen know you went digging in her shredder?
Nah, I had to grab it when she wasn't looking.
Okay.
- Let's start sorting this mess.
- By hand?
Whatever it takes to prove to Meara that her mother didn't do this.
What I mean is, they got computer programs now
that use algorithms to put these together.
- Match shred marks, predict word patterns.
- I didn't know you kept up.
Some of us stay young, Reagan.
Says the guy who's taken three leaks since he got here.
Now I just send this scan to the laptop,
and let the program do its thing.
(PROCESSING)
I'll be damned.
So, you don't think she offed Vic.
No. Not the Colleen I know.
I always wanted to ask you about that.
Yeah. I know.
There was talk.
Can't say I'm surprised.
Colleen and I... Not that we ever acted on it...
So what are you telling me for?
I don't know. I never told anyone.
Family, friends.
- No one.
- She feel the same way?
Not that she ever came out and said.
But I had the boss reassign her.
That's how she and Vic got partnered?
That's how Betty and I stayed together for 46 years.
It's a drug receipt.
She bought a bottle of pentobarbital.
You hang back.
Your homework assignment in 1,000 words or less is to write down why you killed Gabriel Vega.
- Who is Gabriel Vega?
- The guy you stabbed in an alley in Spanish Harlem last night.
You're out of your mind.
And you're high as a kite. Just go ahead and confess, Javi.
We got you coming out of the alley on video moments after Vega was stabbed and killed.
I already told you, I didn't kill anyone.
- And why should I believe a junkie like you?
- Because I'm clean.
Three months. Look. I don't have any fresh marks.
So, where are you shooting up now, between your toes?
- People change.
- Not you.
- What were you doing in the alley?
- I was coming home from work.
- Where do you work?
- Who the hell would hire you?
You want to know? Huh?
CZE Tech. You always knew I was good with computers.
- Oh, so what now, you're hacking people's credit card numbers and buying drugs?
- I don't...
I don't do drugs.
That's enough, all right?
What were you doing in the alley?
The gu..
um, Vega, he's smoking,
and I-I bummed a smoke from him.
- Some other guy comes out of nowhere, and he just starts stabbing him.
- This other guy, what'd he look like?
I don't know. I was... I was running.
- Just like you ran from us.
- You think I want to talk to a bitch like you?
What did you call me?
You cut me off two years ago.
- Yeah, it was 20 years too late,
- All right, all right...
- you stupid piece of crap!
- Officer! Step outside.
You. Hey.
Start writing. Everything you remember, put it down.
You know, you two are worse than my kids.
- You didn't buy any of that.
- Actually, I did buy it.
Look, your brother's no angel, but he looks clean and his work I.D. seems legit.
- You kidding me?
- Did you see him catch the pen with his right hand?
- The stab wounds on the victim were consistent with a left-handed killer.
- Hey, boss,
- you were listening- you can't agree with him.
- Actually, I do.
And I just called Javi's boss at CZE Tech, and he's confirmed
he's been employed for three months and passed every blood test.
He's not our guy.
- Innocent people don't run from the cops.
- Your brother might be guilty of something; he's not guilty of murder.
Get his statement; cut him loose.
I'll but him loose.
You see if you can come up with some reason why someone would want to kill Gabriel Vega.
- You talked to the dog's handler.
- Yes, I did.
- After you said you'd stay away.
- Cut it out.
You cut it out. I can't do my job if you're gonna undermine me.
How is getting a firsthand field report undermining you?
- You talk to the kid who got bit?
- No.
Dog bites boy, Reagan checks in on dog?
What's wrong with this picture?
"Oh"? That's all you got?
- It's a shakedown, Garrett.
- Well, score one for their side.
Well... we got the truth on our side.
They've got the optics on theirs!
Does the name Greta mean anything?
Yes, it does.
It's also my job to know things, Frank. Like, motivation?
You ran a dog named Greta in K-9 back in the '80s.
But only that one. Why?
I couldn't cut it.
And that has nothing to do with Greta being shot and killed by the burglar
you sent her in after?
Let's just leave it at that- I couldn't cut it.
I know you're not gonna let this go, but...
let me do my job.
I know how these things are supposed to go.
It is cheaper and quieter to settle out of court.
But any settlement would include an order to put that dog down.
And that can't happen.
Gabriel worked at my tire shop.
He was a good boy.
He loved soccer.
So no enemies you know of?
Who wouldn't want to be his friend?
The only bad thing he did was smoke.
I'm very sorry for your loss, Mr. Vega.
This officer is gonna take you to identify your son.
And if there's anything else, here's my card.
No enemies, no debts. Why is this not making any sense?
Hmm. Maybe we're looking at it wrong.
- How so?
- What if Vega wasn't the target?
But then who? Javi?
The killer was going after your brother,
and somehow Vega got himself in the way.
- Who would want to kill my brother?
- He's a nobody.
Well, all your brother's cases are connected to one man- Benny Russo.
- Who is...?
- Mid-level heroin dealer.
Narcotics has never been able to pin a case on him.
Launders everything through a legit business- this lumberyard.
And my brother was in bed with him.
Your brother was a cross-town mule in exchange for drugs.
Seems this Russo's a bit of a hothead, and is a little paranoid
when it comes to his ex-employees. He thinks they're all gonna rat on him.
Like... his former accountant here, who was shot point blank in the forehead a year ago.
- Well, that's a different M.O. than stabbing.
- No.
Both crimes are up-close and personal, which would indicate rage or revenge.
So, maybe your brother gets clean, walks out on Russo, he gets paranoid, thinking,
Javi might run to his sister, the cop.
Russo decides to go after him.
And Gabriel Vega was just a good Samaritan who tried to stop it?
- Sounds right.
- I'm gonna kick his ass for not telling us any of this.
Yeah, well, now you're gonna have to wait in line.
Coming in, Javi!
Javi?
Son of a bitch.
- Call a bus!
- Oh, my God.
Call a bus!
Is... Is he alive?
Barely.
This is Detective Reagan.
We need a bus forthwith, re apparent overdose.
I knew he wouldn't be able to stay clean.
- Yeah, and I knew this was gonna be too personal for you.
- What?
Partner, you've been screwing up since we got started,
and I'm not letting either one of us get killed 'cause you're too close to this.
Not everyone has a family where the worst thing that happens is someone's late to Sunday dinner.
Just try to understand.
Javi tore our family apart.
The lies, the stealing, the money my parents spent trying to keep him clean.
They split up because of what he put us all through.
That's why you don't like Thanksgiving.
After everything Javi did, there was nothing to celebrate or anyone who wanted to.
'Least I saw a lot of cops growing up.
- Made me want to become one.
- Yeah, well, something good came of it, I guess.
Can we just go nail Benny Russo?
I don't know, partner? Can we?
I'm fine, Reagan.
All right.
Go sit with your brother till he wakes up.
I'll see if I can't make some traction with Benny Russo.
Go ahead.
Mr. Irving to Volunteer Services.
So, who's Benny Russo?
Benny Russo is a drug dealer who laughs in our face every time he skates,
- which is every time he gets pinched.
- Okay, so, what do you need from me?
- -I need a warrant from your bosses.
- Off of what evidence?
He tried to have my partner's brother killed. He's a customer.
And this guy killed an innocent bystander instead.
For the record, I do love this song you always sing.
I don't sing any song. What song are you talking about?
It's called "I'm Danny Reagan and I Know Someone's Guilty
Even if I Don't Have Any Evidence to Back It Up. "
- I do have evidence to back it up!
- So, you have a murder weapon?
I don't have a murder weapon, no!
Legitimate threats against the brother?
Baez's brother said that Russo tried to kill him.
Any witnesses that are not junkies?
Listen, Russo is a murderer. He killed his accountant!
And he skated because there was no evidence.
- He's a nut!
- And you are halfway there, if you think I'm gonna bring charges on a he said/he said
between one guy who's never spent a day in jail,
and another who's been in and out his whole life, when he's not too busy OD'ing.
You know, I need to find a new sister.
You need to find me... when you have more.
So I didn't die.
Not for lack of trying.
Did you get Benny Russo?
My partner went to talk to his sister.
She's an ADA.
So...
siblings can get along, huh?
Weird, huh?
I'm sorry...
I didn't...
I didn't tell you that it was Russo who was after me.
I just thought that...
it would be one more thing for you to hate me for.
Stranger,
you know, he does a, uh...
good thing...
and I ran like a coward.
Maybe we can go talk to Vega's family
and tell them how he tried to help you, after we get Russo.
Which may not happen any time soon.
You're not the only one with a difficult sibling.
My sister says we got no case, unless, of course, we catch Russo in the act
- with about 50 witnesses and 12 video cameras.
- So we're screwed?
Unless we give him another chance to finish the job.
What?
We use your brother to flush him out.
Like, dangle him like bait? No!
- Russo's gonna come after him again anyway.
- Unless he's cooled off.
- Do you think that guy's gonna cool off?
- He's right, Maria.
No, you shut up. You're still groggy.
No. I... I still know people.
So I get the word out to Russo that I'm gonna be where I used to score, tonight-
Tenth and Butler. It's secluded.
And he'll think he has the drop on me.
- It's a good plan, partner.
- It's crazy.
It's the only way we can make sure your brother's protected.
He's got to go down, Maria.
And I... and I could help. And I want to help.
Least I can do, right?
- Mr. Morris, Frank Reagan.
- I know who you are.
But I can't imagine what you're doing here.
I just like to get out of the office once in a while.
So, the department is settling our suit?
Depends on what you mean by "settle. "
Well, by settle, I mean monetary compensation for physical injury and emotional stress.
Then, no.
But we are prepared to forego a countersuit.
- Then this conversation's over.
- Not quite.
We looked you up.
Good for you.
You go after deep pockets, but always settle for less.
But a lot of less adds up nicely.
Your dog bit my boy.
A dog bit your boy.
I saw Raymond do it.
Well, you told the investigating sergeant that you were inside at the time.
What I mean is...
I heard my son scream, and by the time I got outside,
I saw your police dog running off down the street.
There were no witnesses that saw Raymond get out of Officer Donohue's yard.
So, you're saying, I framed Raymond?
No. You just said that.
And if it wasn't him, what dog bit my kid? I don't even have a dog.
I don't know.
The dog at your mother's house in Queens?
The rescue dog that you've tried repeatedly to get them to take back?
I don't know.
Okay.
We're done here.
I've got a big megaphone, Mr. Morris, and I know how to use it.
Know one thing.
We will not settle.
I know you love your son.
Do you really want to put him on the stand to tell your lies?
You're a real piece of work, Reagan.
Oh, please call me by my first name- Commissioner.
What's going on?
Tell me Vic was in on this.
I knew you didn't come here to find your glasses.
Was he?
It was a decision we made together.
Check the seal.
Unbroken.
Last Tuesday...
he was in so much pain.
Oh, Henry,
I, I came so close.
But you didn't need to.
I was going to say, I,
I don't know if I could have had the courage.
Not sure that's the word for it.
Oh, believe me, Henry, I've been there,
and that is the word.
We still friends?
From the first day we met.
Henry, I want to thank you... for caring,
and I mean for all of us.
When the time is right and you want to have a meal,
- go see a movie...
- I'll know who to call.
You okay up there, Javi?
It's cold here, man.
I still don't see Russo.
Same here. Just sit tight.
Ghosts 1 and 2, when Russo shows up, do not make a move until he makes a move first.
- You copy?
- Copy that.
Reagan, I don't know about this.
Javi's got a stab vest on under his jacket. He'll be fine.
In fact, here he comes now.
Hey, Javi.
How you doing, my man?
Okay, Javi, stay calm, stay in the light.
Now act surprised to see him.
Hey, Benny. What you doing out here?
Well, a little bird told me you might be out and about tonight.
Don't worry, I just want to talk. Won't take long.
- All right, wait for my command.
- Copy that.
Tell 'em to move in. He's going to stab him.
Give it a second.
Hey, you tried to kill me, man.
Oh... yeah,
you- but you know I get nuts sometimes.
Little bird told me that you also fell off the wagon
last night.
Sucks being clean, huh?
Look, I just want to know everything's good between me and you.
- Come on.
- Sure.
I don't want to kill you, Javi.
- But I am going to make you disappear.
- What the hell is this?
????
- No!
- Get in the van!
Move in, move in!
Move your car! Where the hell did they come from?
Are they giving you anything?
We don't even know if they're still going in this direction.
Sarge, you locate the GPS signal on my brother's cell phone yet?
Hold on, still trying.
Got it- the cell phone's signal is pinging off a cell tower in Queens.
East on 73rd Avenue.
East on 73rd Ave. Must be headed out of the city.
Hollis Hills- Russo's lumberyard is in Hollis Hills.
That's where they're taking your brother. Tell the sarge to send backup.
- Come on, let's go.
- I didn't rat on you!
- Let's go.
- Hey!
What are you doing?
You're a junkie and your sister's a cop.
Turn that thing on.
I didn't do it, I didn't do it.
No... no, no, what are you doing? Listen to me.
- Chop you up...
- No!
... hose off the back of that truck...
- ... and it'll be like you never existed.
- Let go of me!
- Police! Let him go!
Let him go!
He's my brother, I'm the only one that gets to kill him.
Hey, look at me.
Don't waste a bullet on that scumbag, all right? Me maybe but not you.
It's not you.
Then there's that.
You okay, Javi?
You saved me, Maria.
Sit.
He's coming along.
Commissioner.
About Raymond...
Yes, sir.
The lawsuit is dropped.
I want the two of you back on the job forthwith.
For those who are about to die, we salute you.
He's already dead, Pop.
It's the thought that counts.
- How's Colleen holding up?
- About how you would expect.
You know, I don't think we ever really talked about it.
I was only 11 or 12 when you two were partners.
Yeah, so?
And I certainly wasn't going to bring it up in front of Mom.
What's to bring up?
- Oh, come on.
- Come on, what?
I had the biggest crush on her. She was a babe.
Yes, she, uh, she did have her admirers.
I'll bet.
There we go.
Everything looks so good.
Smells even better.
Wait, do we give thanks before or after grace?
Always before, Sean.
- Linda, go ahead.
- Oh, okay.
this Thanksgiving I am thankful for...
Why do I have to go first?
- You always go first.
- I'll go.
No, no, it's okay.
- Okay, um...
- Time's up.
Uh, my boys.
Eh, you said that last year.
- I did?
- Yeah.
Well, let me do another.
No, no, that was lovely, and the food's getting cold.
- Okay.
- Next.
I'm thankful to have Drew Brees on my fantasy football team this year.
I'm thankful I have the 2013
- New York Jets as my real football team this year. Go, Gang Green!
- Go, Gang Green!
And I'm thankful that I have a beautiful wife and two sons who put up with me
'cause, believe me, it's not that way in every family, and
I'm also thankful for that drumstick on the right, which has my name on it.
Me- I'm just thankful for what I'm always thankful for:
to be happy to be kicking around this place with all of you.
I'm thankful for all the ordinary citizens who have come up to me
on the beat over the past year and thanked me for my service-
all two of 'em. Also, bulletproof vests.
I'm thankful I only have a year and a half left before I go to college.
I'm thankful that she still has a year and a half left
before she goes to college.
And I'm thankful for four generations of this family at this table,
safe and sound and starving.
Bless us, O Lord, for these, thy gifts which we are about to receive from thy bounty.
Through Christ, our Lord, amen.
Amen.
Who wants sweet potatoes?
- I'll take some.
- The turkey looks amazing.
I????
Yeah, keep your hands off the drumstick- that one's mine.
Yes????
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入