I need to be assured thatthis means that 51 is safe.
Yes,it does.
Previously on chicago fire.
I didn't campaign for your job,wally.
I'm giving up my job to save 51.
I'm benny's wife.The boys miss him.
He hasn't been home in months.
They need to see their father.
I saw your name on the applicant list.
I was in a bad place,man.
You'd make a hell of a cop though.
My wife moved out back in august.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- Yeah,what are you gonna do?
This is torture.
The point is,they talkabout you all the time.They miss you.
I think i know what you're going through.
You can twist yourself up inknots trying to understand it,
But ultimately i don't thinkit's for us to figure out.
There's a protein in ourblood called osteopontin.
- Your levels are higher than expected.
- Meaning what?
Sometimes it's an indicatorfor asbestos poisoning.
The scans will be read by a radiologist,
And they'll get backto you with the results.
I thought the results were instant.
Let's see,you're beingscreened for lung cancer.
I'm sure someone willlet you know by tomorrow.
Go long,go long.
Touchdown.
Broken glass,flag on play.
No way.That was a touchdown.
Of course it was.
Should i come back later,or.
Nope,we were just,uh,cleaning.
Yeah,just dusting.
Why do you need afootball to help you clean?
Busted.
My house.I decide who's busted,all right?
Ben,i'm sorry.
Wait,hold on.Give me a look.
Maybe it's time g.i.joe goes into retirement.
- No!
- Wait,wait,okay,okay.
listen,gabby sees thiskind of thing every day.
If you guys can do the dishes,then she'll get himback into fighting shape.
What do you say?
Okay.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah?
Weren't you here beforewith benny severide?
yeah,i was.Why?
Ii just wanted to know if you were aware that he has a wife and kids.
Yeah,of course i do. I.Who are you?
So it doesn't bother youbreaking up a family and.
Wait,wait,wait,do youthink i'm dating benny?
To be generous,yeah.
I'm his daughter,katie.
You three make quite a crew.
Yeah.
Which reminds me.
A cabin on lake carroll,
two days pulling largemouthout of crystal clear water.
man,they're going to love that.
So will you.
Yes,i will.
Matt,i have some news.
Boys,i'm coming home.
- What,really?
- yeah
Mom's coming home!
Because of overcrowding,they're letting me out early.
I told you she'd come back.
Mom's coming home!Mom's coming home!
Mom's coming home!
I told you she'd come back.
Your wife beth came to see me.
Yeah,well,she's got a flairfor the dramatic,that woman.
Now you understand why it'sbest i give her some space.
Always the martyr.
Hold on,you don't know the whole story.
And i never do.
It's like i didn't know the story of my 21yearold sister.
Yeah,i talked to her.
21 years old,
which is exactly how long ago you left meAnd mom to fend for ourselves.
Tell me this.Do youeven know who her mom is?
Of course i do.
And have you been takingcare of her all these years?
How could i?I just metkatie when i got to town.
You're unbelievable.
Yeah,well,alert the press.
I had some issues when i was younger.
But don't forget,i'm comingout of a happy retirement
To save your dysfunctional firehouse.
That's an excuse!
You're just running from another family,leaving the kids with the bill.
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Proudly Presents
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Sync: YTET-天外飞砖
chicago.fire.207.
herrmann,lieutenanttests are coming up.
How many times you take that thing?
Capp,really?
You mean how many times did i fail it?
The answer is three,but not since the '90s.
Five kids is all theaggravation that i need.
I know my place.
Lady in the house.
Mama!
Now here's a sight i love to see.
What,me or the groceries?
There's more in the car.
- You got it.
- Guys.
Baby,how are you?
Wallace,hi.
I will help with the rest of the groceries.
chief,you have a call.
I'm no foodie per se,
But having two millses in the kitchen bodes well for lunch?
I thought mcleod burnedall of our old logbooks in the town square.
What year you got there?
'85.
I don't suppose you'rejust cruising memory lane.
Factory fire on haskell,high heat,
asbestos falling like snow.
No masks back then.
Three of these men are dead.
Lung cancer.
severide,roll call's in five minutes.Where's shay?
I don't know,dawson.
I'm not her babysitter.
Yeah,well,someone needs to be.
Looks like the engine is losing water.
A couple of seals are cracked.
We put in a request,
and the wizard said it'sgoing to be a couple of weeks.
You sure we've got that long?
Excuse me.
I'm looking for jeff clarke.
Yeah. Who should i say is,
his wife.
Yeah.
- Something wrong?
- Just slow down for a second.
I'm here in peace.
What do you want,lisa?
To talk to you.
I've been going to a group.
Good for you.
It's a place to hearother people's stories,
To connect and find outwhat's going on in your head.
Here's what's going on inside my head.
A month after i got back,you were sleeping at your sister's house.
When i needed you most,you left.
Jeff,you treated melike the day's garbage.Worse.
Is that what they tell you in that group?
You left me,lisa.
I did.
And i'm sorry,okay?
I'm here to say i'm sorry.
- Wish it was that easy.
- It could be if you'd let it.
Let's just spend some time together.
I got to get back.
Okay,see you later.
Look,before you start with the heavy breathing,i know.
I'm more than happy to get a reliever.
I'm good. I'm good.
Ijust got a lot going on.
Yeah,i see you got your hands full.
Our house has been underthe microscope lately.
Everyone in this room hashandled the various intrusions
Like the professionals i know you to be,
And that is why 51 is still going strong.
It's your commitment to the house
That allows me in good conscience to announce
my retirement from the c.f.d.
It's been an honor to servewith every single one of you.
Chief.
Let's go to work.
Engine 51,truck 81,squad3,
ambulance 61,battalion 25.
Railroad incident.South homan and 75th.
Did you know?
Mcleod's been pressuring him.
We just got to get this call over with and talk him out of it.
This will be quick.
5 bucks says just anothercell phone on the tracks.
50 says it's not.
What the hell?
Chief,i'm seeing multiplecommuter cars derailed,
At least a hundred fleeing passengers and several fires,
Includingcars and a building.
Did that train go into that building?
We're gonna need more alarms,chief.
45 and main.We got multiple commuter trains derailed
and at least a hundred victims.
I need a 211 alarm and an e.m.s. Plan 2,the rail corridor on 75th.
Chief,we'll take the passenger car.
Recon the tanker and geta handle on the car fires.
Copy that.
- Shay,dawson.
- Yep.
Set up triage.Call it as you see it.
You got it.
That thing just plowed right into us.
- Come with me.
- There's more guys in the warehouse.
Check the cars for victims.
We got more in the warehouse.
Liquid propane.Liquid propane,chief.
All companies be awarethat the overturned tanker is filled with propane.
Work quickly,and let's get those peopleout of those train cars.
Help,please!
Let's go.Get that plug open.
Engine 51,water's flowing.
- Come on.Come on,come.
- Where's the water?
- Pump's not working.
- Come on.
All right.All right,here we go.
Herrmann,water coming your way.
It's coming.
Here it comes.
25,be advised closest units are currently respondingto a highrise fire.
Relief companies are enroute from battalion 32.
32 is across town.
Yeah,mcleod's cutbacks at work.
Clear!
This one's empty too.
That propane tanker'stoo close for comfort.
Knock those fires down!
XXXXXXXXXXXX
Sir,you're hurt.
Let's get you out of here.
My daughter.She just went to therear to get her backpack.
If you didn't see her inside,she's on her way to triage.
We'll take you.
All the doors are jammed.
Get 'em open.
Tony and i are gonna clear the warehouse.Tony!
All right.
- Hello?
- This way.
Right there.
Step back.
- In here!
- Get us out!
Hang on,guys.
We need more triage tags.
We need more everything.
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah,i'm fine.
There's a.There's more tags in the ambo.
I. I'm gonna get those.Finish bandaging her.
- Shay.
- Dawson,leg wound.He's losing blood.
My daughter,anna,is she here?
She's ten,she's wearing a striped sweater.
No,sir,but i'll let you know as soon as we see her,all right?
- What's your name?
- Marcus.
Marcus? Marcus,there are a lot ofothers who are in worse shape.
Can you hang on?
Find my daughter!
Striped sweater.
Here you go.
What are the different colors for?
Just be glad you'renot wearing a black one.
Remind me to thank this guyfor topping off his tank.
Just keep the wet stuff on the hot stuff.
you okay?
You okay?
Come here,come here.
All right,hey,stick with me.
Here we go.Watch your step.
Hold,one second,stop.Go!
Careful,ma'am.Go slow,watch your step.
Keep walking,keep moving.
Sir,what the hell are you doing?
Her eye.
An epidermal hemorrhage is pushing on her brain.
I have to release the pressure.
A wine opener isn't ideal,but when is life ideal,right?
She should be okay.
Thanks.
You canexit the way we came in.We'll take it from here.
No,there are at least ten more back there.Let me help.
I've got some medical experience.
- Obviously.What's your name?
- Westin.
All right,westin,i appreciate the hand.
Capp,let this guy go first.
Typical?We ask for more ambos andthey send us police cars.
Mills,need a hand?
Yeah.
I saw you signed up foranother c.p.d. Ridealong.
Might as well get yourselffitted for a uniform.
Just help me get him to the tarp,man.
Dawson!
She's got a hole in her head.
Red.Chief,we need some more hands here.
45 to main,we can't wait for those ambos.
Activate the emergencyresponse team from lakeshore.
Okay,there you go.Can you walk?
Come on.
- You got him,tone?
- Yeah.
Capp,there's still two in the back.
All right,sir,you're gonnahave to keep pressure on it.
I'll be right back.Westin.
Hand me that strip of cloth over there.
It lets the paramedicsknow he's got a tourniquet.
Here.
Combat medic,huh?
You coming or going?
Between.
Heading home for a week to see the family.
What about you,marine?When did they cut you loose?
come on,man,i cansmell jarhead a mile away.
First recon.
So basically you'reworking on your golf game?
Brought myhandicap down five strokes.
- I'll be right back.
- Yes,sir.
Okay.
Easy,all right.Here.
Marcus.I told you to stay.
Anna's not in triage.
I won't go back until i find her.
Marcus!
You're not gonna be much good on that leg.
She lost her mother tobreast cancer last year.
She's got to be so scared.
Are you a father,lieutenant?
Yeah.
So you know how i feel.
Where were you guys sitting?
There.
All right,i'll find her as long as you don't bleed out on me.
Back to triage.
Redirect the lines,81!
We got to get water on that tanker now!
Herrmann,you got this?
Got it,lieutenant.
Let's go,move those lines!
Cool that propane!
Give me one line on the firewith two sheeting off the top.
We got to keep this rig cool!
Anna!
Anna?
Severide,how many still trapped?
There's less than tenstill in the warehouse
But a bunch more stillin the passenger car.
sir,you need to get backin your car and drive away.
It's tempting,but you lookto be about ten hands short of what you need.
David arata,chief of trauma lakeshore.
Okay,yeah,you'll do.
What's your head count?
we're at 30 so far,but we got more coming in.
Sir,move that man to the black tarp.
No,wait.We haven't assessed him yet.
Unless you have plasma,which you don't,he's dead.
I need any injured who canstill walk to keep walking.
We need space to work.
Let's go.
Sheet off the top.
Hit it from the other side!
- You okay?
- I'm okay.
What the hell is that?
The pressure relief valve's venting.
Without it,this thing's blowing sky high!
You better get these attack lines back.
We're going defensive!Go back.
Come on!
Back here.Something's wrong.
He was wrapping my legthen he just fell back.
Come on,westin.
What's wrong,marine?
You've never seen a little bruise before?
You,of all people,shouldknow how serious this is.
You,of all people,know that no army medic walks out on the wounded.
Severide,help me out.
Okay,hold on.
You're gonna be okay.
Damn it.
Something wrong?
- No.
- Good.
Head down,task at hand.
Okay.
Anna!
This candle ever gonna go out?
That propane's got to go someplace.
If it goes out,then we got to worry.
Chief,pressure's falling on the pumper.
- Floor it.
- I think the seal's going bad.
We're losing pressure.
Son of a bitch.
Seals just popped,so we've lost pressure.
Herrmann,set up an ariel pipe.
We got to squeeze every dropof water onto that tanker or it'll blow.
Got it,let's go!Get out of here!
25 to main,where's that backup?
Delay,25.Still 15 minutes out.
Let's go!
Internal bleeding.I'm not sure how bad.
- Let me help.
- I got it,shay.Right here.Red.
All right.
Black.We need the space.
No. Dawson.You take care of him.
It's okay.
Red.
Okay,fine.
You all right?
No.
You can do this.
Just get through the day,all right?
Breathe in for me.
Line's charged.
Here comes the water,chief!
Let's hope it lasts.
Anna?
We finished the primary searchfor warehouse workers.
- How many?
- 22.
There were 24 cars in the lot by my count.
Today's payday.
Our two bookkeepers use the back office.
chief,there's possibly two workers still in the back office.
Mills,grab your irons.
Let's go,go!
Fire department!If you can hear me,call out!
Chief,warehouse guy said the bookkeepers work
In the third office towards the back.
Chicago fire department.
Call out if you can hear me.
Up ahead on the left.
Chief,wait!
Mills?
Yeah,here,here.
- You okay?
- Yeah,yeah,i think so.You?
I'm good,i'm just.I'm just trapped.
Me too.
Let me try and.
No,no!
There could be a few tons above us.
Let's just not push our luck,okay?
- Yeah.
- This is boden.I'm with mills.
We're in the north end of the warehouse.
There's been a collapse.
On our way,chief.
That's it on the water.
Engine's fried.Watch that tanker!
chief,the heat destroyedthe pressure release valve.
What do you want us to do?
The tanker's gonna blow and it's gonna take the block with it.
This is battalion 25 to allfire and police personnel.
Evacuate the area to a 1/4mile perimeter.
Repeat evacuate the area.
It's the right thing to do.
I'm gonna need confirmation
That all first responders havepulled back to a safe distance.
I got a job to finish.
We're on the tanker.
Chief ain't going out like this.
Let's move.
All right everybody,let's go.
People,if you can move,let's do it.
We need to evacuate.
Sir,let's go.
Not a chance.
negative on that confirmation,chief.
Herrmann,you listen to me.
Chief,you know they aren't going anywhere.
- Where'd you come from?
- Back office.
- How'd you get out?
- Around back.
But everything came down right behind us.
Let's go.
We got to release and divert the gas flow.
Will that coupling fit one of our hoses?
Yeah,let's try it.
Anna!
Anna,can you hear me?
guys,secure the end of this hose.
Got it.
Let's attach it to the track.
Move,guys.Let's move.I need a chain.
Coming in.
Westin?Westin,stay with me.
Stay with me,buddy.
We have more incoming.
You need to ration your supplies.
His vitals are 80 over50.He needs a second line.
keep moving.I'll handle this one.
Well,i guess this isn't a good time to ask if you're claustrophobic.
I spent the better part ofyesterday trapped in an m.r.i.
All i could think ofwhen i was in that machine is
What i was gonna do when i got out.
This wasn't on the list.
So you got your test results in?
No,not yet.
Maybe it's better i stayin here,not knowing.
But if the results are clear,and.
You don't have to retire.
Men who usually stay on thejob longer than
They should live to regret that choice.
You have any regrets?
I'm done talking about me.
Let's talk about you and p.d.
Marcus!
No.
I'm not giving up.
Is there someplace else she could be?
Our meal vouchers were in her backpack.
She wanted to see ifthey were good for lunch.
Where do they sell food on the train?
I know you think that iwalked into police academy
Because i got pushed over for squad.
It's not the reason why.
I wanted out because i foundout about you and my mom.
Come on,quit lyingaround and get out of there
Before this whole thingblows to smithereens.
Hose secure.
Opening the valve.
Coming out with the chief and mills.
Severide,how's that valve?
Son of a bitch.
i need a vice grips up here.
Chief.
Go.
Damn it!Hurry.
Clear!
Mills,how's your arm?
Anna!
Anna?
I need a backboard over here.
Can you hear me?
My dad.
He's waiting for you.
- Why aren't you treating him?
- What?
He saved lives in there,and you're gonna let him die in the dirt?
Even if i had an ambulance,
he wouldn't make it to the hospital alive.
I'm sorry.
Jarhead.
You get the rest?
Yeah,man,i did.
Could have got you tooif you'd told me earlier.
And let you be the hero?
Go to hell.
All passengers alive anddead have been accounted for.
You disobeyed orders.
Yep.
I suppose you taught us that.
Chief,just know if it were up to me,
you wouldn't be going anywhere.
Thanks.
Dawson,shay,i remember you were doingroundsWith hallie thomas
over at lakeshore,right,designs on being a surgeon.
Yeah,that's right.
You were extraordinary today,both of you.
Call me anytime.
I'm always willing to help out good people.
I understand you had quite a day today.
It's calls like that thatreflect very well on this house.
I don't give a damn how it reflects.
We can't operate withoutthe support that we need.
But you did today,didn't you?
You worked with what youhad,and you saved lives.
So whether you like it ornot,chief,the system works.
But that's not your problem anymore.
This is for your exit interview tomorrow.
Please fill it out andremember to bring your badge.
I actually missed this place.
Heather.
Why didn't you call?Iwould have picked you up.
I wasn't gonna stay there aminute longer than necessary.
I was hoping i could get the keys so i can be there when the boys wake up.
Sure,yeah.
They are going to lose theirminds when they see you.
Matt,this whole thing.
Has made me realize i need to make some changes in my life.
Whatever you need.
I know that.I do.
But i also know thatwhen i wake up tomorrow,
Everything i see,everywhere i go,
will remind me of losing andy and jen.
I've got this old friend in florida.
She owns an apartmentbuilding and needs a manager.
It's rent free,and it's a steady job.
Heather.
Take a little time.
I've cleared it withthe probation department.
shay.Can you give me a minute?
We really need to talk.
Not now,i.I'm fine.
Lover's quarrel?
Just go.
Mr.boden,this is dr. Kerry.
Your test results came back negative.
I'd still like to getyou tested every year,
But there's no reason youshouldn't get out and celebrate.
Congratulations.
You sure picked a hellof a call to go out on.
Sure did.
Peter.We should talk.
Before.
I was so mad at you,icould barely look at you.
And day after day i've watched you put yourself
On the line for this house,for me.
And now you're leaving,and.
I realize what a waste oftime it was to be so mad.
I regret that,and i wish i had that time back.
What's up?
You were right.
Let's face it,when it comes to women i'm a world class screwup.
Something goes wrong for me,
And i make sure i scorchthe earth as i leave town.
I did that to your mother.
I did it to katie's mom.
And now i'm doing it again to beth.
She's probably gonna divorce me,
But at least i can be around for the boys.
I'm sorry i wasn't around for you.
Anyway,they got soccer,so.
If i hit the road now,ishould be able to make the game.
That's good.Good.
Yeah.
Do me a favor,will you?
Would you tell wally,chief boden,that.
51 is his house.
one last thing.
Your sister katie.
I haven't spent much time with her,but.
She seems like a nice person.
No promises.
I'll see you,kelly.
It's difficult for me to accept
That the department i'vealways known is changing.
That makes me somewhat of a dinosaur.
But as difficult as those changes are.
Letting go of a lifetime'swork,that isn't easy.
Jeff.
I'm sorry.
I am so sorry.
There isn't a single man i've served with
Who hasn't been brought to his knees because of what he's seen on the job.
Different endeavors in life change people.
Only the strongest are up for that.
What makes them exceptional?
No matter how hard they fall,
they never give upWhen there'ssomething worth fighting for.
You'd make a great lieutenant.
Yeah,i don't know if i canhandle waiting
By the mailbox for another rejection letter.
I'm pretty sure it'dcome by email nowadays.
Yeah,thanks so much,sweetie.
When i was buried under two tons of rubble,
My men risked their lives to pull me out.
Even an extinct old dinosaur like me.
So to think about saddlingthem with a broken system
That strips away the essentials so they can barely do their job,
A broken system that mightkeep one of my men and women
From going home to their families,i will not. Allow that.
And i don't give a damn.
I will have no regrets.
You. Are not taking my house.
Not without a fight.
Do me a favor and take careof your mom and brother,okay?
You know.
Your dad always used to tell me
That we didn't become menuntil we got our badges.
His original badge will alwayshang on the academy wall,but.
Made this one for you.
Is this his number?
I was in line right after him,
so our badges are onlyone number apart,see?
Can i keep yours too?
Absolutely.
This is for you so you don't forget us.
Not a chance.
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Proudly Presents
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Sync: YTET-天外飞砖
chicago.fire.207.