Hello,I'm America's Jane Lynch
In October 2012, on the
Paramount soundstages,
the cast and crew of Glee filmed a Christmas
episode entitled "Rough Trade Santa"
Upon viewing the director's cut,
Fox executivesrecoiled in horror,
and then locked the episodein a lead
vault, where it languishedfor an entire year
A new,less-controversialChristmas
episode
containing an entire act
dedicated to biracial Judaism
was rushed into productionand
aired in its place
After a year of pleasfrom
fans all over the world,
the episode will now
air... with several edits
Gone is an entire subplot involving
Blaine and hisobsession with Yule logs
Lost forever areseveral
scenes explaining
why Will Schuester abandoned his
Washington dreams to come back
and teach his merry band
of miscreants and losers
So,sit back,relax, have
some eggnog and enjoy,
if you dare-- the never-aired
Glee Christmas episode
We're going green,guys
I refuse to give up my wig and
weave-aerosolizedluster spray
Okay,you're fine,Unique
This year's theme for the 50th Annual McKinley
Classroom Decorating contest is... "Green is Good"
Sam,Tina
All right,well,as seniors,Mr Shue asked us to
take over the ,decorating committee this year,
so we're gonna need everyone'shelp
in order to win this thing
Oh,and we will win
Because first prize is an antique glass
angel, hand-blown thousandsof years ago
This holy glass ornament issaid to
have magical powers to bring good luck,
and possibly a boyfriend or prom
queen dreamsto whoever she oversees
And that person will be me
don't we all getto share the prize
We're going au naturelthis year
We're gonna get pine cones,LED lights
Are we getting those
from the LED bush out back
This is exactlythe kind of
in-fighting that will make us lose,
and I'm not gonna stand for it
Guys,this is serious
Cancel your plansfor the entire month
I don't want to hear about any
of you caroling in nursing homes
or feeding the homeless
or giving toys to tots
Every waking thought willbe spent figuring
out how to win me that stupid angel
- Got it
- Well
Merry Christmas,everyone
- Joy to the...
- Shut up,Blaine
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET-可可与可心
Glee
5 Episode 08
The McKinley HighNon-Denominational
Christmas Club meetingis now called to order
Vice President Artie
Abrams has the floor
This Christmas club looksan
awful lot like Glee Club
Nobody panic
But Principal Figginsjust informed me
that McKinley's outdoor
mangerscene has been defaced
with swastikasand with Satanic symbols
And Baby Jesus was found
stuffeddown Figgins' chimney
Oh,my God,that's horrible
Christmas is canceled
Not quite yet,Tina
Figgins askedthe Christmas Club to
step in... and do a living nativity
Christmas is saved
And Artie and I have decided
that Jake should play Joseph
I mean... Joseph was a darkly tanned Jew
Thank you
I call dibs on arguablythe most important
female role in the history of the world
- The Virgin Mary
- You can't
You're black,and you'd crush the donkey
I'm a virgin
That's a shocker
To think nobody's tickled inside of
your musty,mildewed granny panties
except for the familyof
crickets that nest in there
Yeah,well... you weara
smaller bra than me
All right,girls,come on,okay
It's Christmas,andwe've got a show to do
Wait,are manger scenes
evenallowed on school property
Auditions are tomorrow
Mmm,what is it.What is it.Oh,my gosh
It's My Pretty Princess
Deluxe-All-Jazzed-UpStyling Head
Aw,Santana,I love it.Thank you so much
Oh,I had one of these when I was ten
And I was obsessed with her
I-I gave this ladysmoky eyes every day
Well,merry Christmas,Lady Hummel
Now you can relive allyour Jeffrey Dahmer
fantasies in the privacy of your own home
But that's not it
because additionally I am giving you
an all-expense-paid trip to Dildo Island
It's a real place,it's in Canada
I got you the deluxebachelor package
- I think this calls for anotherglass
of my world-famous eggnog - Yes
I'm using Giada's recipe, but you
tell me if it'stoo much all-spice
You know what I will tell youis
that I think that you've actuallybecome more
of a Grandma Moses since moving to New York
I mean,you just hada traumatic
break-up with Princess Valiant,
and you're single, you
should be living it up
Oh,like you
Breezing through hereunannounced,
with a sleigh fullof Christmas
decorations and presents la Auntie Mame
By the way,all of
thesearen't for us,are they
Oh,no,no,no,I mean,you
got your decapitated head
And one of theseis for Berry
A gallon jug ofProActiv solution
and a booklet ofJetBlue vouchers
The rest are for me
After what happenedwith Brittany, I
prescribed myself alittle retail therapy
Couldn't be in Limaright now,you know
Not with her there,it's too soon
But now I have tobook myself a hotel
In New York Cityduring
the holidays.Are you crazy
Do you knowhow expensive that will be
Calm down,Joyce
DeWitt.Okay.It's gonna be fine
Don't you remember that money
that my mom gave me for graduation
Your college fund
Please tell meyou didn't spend it
all on post-breakup giftsfor yourself
No,no,just half
Kurt
Oh,my God,Santana
What are you doing here
We have our firstholiday house guest
Feliz Navidad
I decided that I wanted to dosomething a
little different for the holidays this year
In that case,you're in luck
Because I justgot Kurt and I the greatest
gig,and you can get in on it,too,if you want
We are gonna beChristmas elves
in Santa Land atthe Midtown Mall
I know what you're thinking,
but I've done my research
And this is where allof the Broadway
luminaries bring their children,
so we'll have tons of exposure
It's gonna be great,pleasesay you're in
Are you in
Come on,we'll alldo it together
- Sure,yeah -
Yeah - Cheers
I am gonna bethe best Jewish elf ever
I'm serious,okay
What could be greenerthan foraging
in the woodsfor Christmas decorations
Our Christmas tree will
have,like,a zero carbon footprint
Except for cutting downa perfectly healthy
tree and throwing it awaytwo weeks later
Well...exactly
I'll go intothe West Lima Forest
Preserve and get pine cones,deer antlers,
fallen branchesand
make them into wreaths,
and you'd be surprisedat how many Hispanic
families throw birthday parties in there
I'm even gonna collectall the,uh,
deflated mylar "feliz cumpleaos" balloons
- and then I'm gonna maketinsel
out of it.- Perfect - Yeah
Hold it right there,sluts.Hey,Becky
This is mistletoe
I'm super horny,so
youbetter give me some tongue
- What
- Whoa
I mean it,bitch
I want to lickthose Asian tonsils
And then once she'sgot me all warmed up,
I'm gonna make you French me
because it's Christmasand I'm loose
Oh,dear God
Becky,you can't just
make usFrench kiss you
Yes,I can,stripper
I have special needs,and one of my
special needs is mouth sex with your face
No,Becky.This is not okay
You get away with murderat this school
because Sue has made you believe
that the rulesdon't apply to you
It's discrimination
no,it's not,honey
Becky.That's poison sumac
That's not mistletoe
Get your little buttto the nurse's
office for a Silkwood shower,stat
Can I take the LeCar
Of course you can takethe LeCar
Oh,Asian Number One
Stupid Trouty Joethe
Happy Strippin' Hobo
You're exactly right
I have been treating Becky differently
than allthe other kids at this school
when I probably should'vejust
treated her like everybody else
You've made your point,fair is fair
And I will adjustmy behavior accordingly
Geez,I just think she needs to be
treated for somesort of sex addiction
Yeah,okay,I got it,got it
I'm here to inform you that Principal
Figgins has made mein charge of judging
the 50th Annual Christmas
TreeDecorating Contest
A longstanding traditionhere at McKinley
High even thoughwe didn't do it last year
Or the year before
Or the year before that
Anyhoo,I'm just thrilledto be able
to judge the GleeChristmas tree
so I can rank it dead last
Because I'm sureit's covered
with condoms and dental dams
and suicide hotlinepamphlets
and at-home-sex-change kits
I know that sounds harsh
But maybe it's justthe motivation that
poor little Christmas tree needs to go out
and conquer its dreams to hop
out of thatChristmas tree stand,
fly to New Yorkand audition for NYADA
We want Santa.We want Santa.We
want Santa.We want Santa
I'm seriously regrettingthese tights
They smell like Williamstown, and
they're giving meserious mangina
And I am seriously sensing some
workplace sexismhappening over here
All these little ladyelves are
dressed like candy-striped hookers
Do you think they'll let
mekeep this when we're done
Because I am lovingthis look on me
Lord of the Bling
We want Santa.We want Santa
Has anyone seen Santa
These Manhattan kids
aren'tgonna wait much longer
Uh,there he is
Merry Christmas.Calm
down.Calm down,here I am
No flash photos before I
geton my throne,though,okay
Ho,ho,ho.Oh
Lady elves
Santa,great
well,can we getthis line moving for you
Don't ever look directlyat
me again,Keebler.Ever
I don't like you and
your Equity card attitude
So I'm gonna hit the men's roomand
craft services, aka my flask
Why don't you take careof
keeping these kids busy
Maybe you could do that Rent medley that
you learned at the lastopen mic cabaret night
Ho,ho,ho,ho,ho
Okay,this crowdis about to get fugly
Do we have a plan
There is always a plan
We are gonna worksome NYADA magic
Santana,graba candy cane.Kurt,hit it
Here comes Santa
Claus,here comes Santa Claus
Right down Santa Claus Lane
Vixen and Blitzenand all his reindeer
Are pulling on the reins
Bells are ringing,children singing
All is merry and bright
Hang your stockingsand say your prayers
'Cause Santa Clauscomes tonight
Here comes Santa
Claus,here comes Santa Claus
Right down Santa Claus Lane
He's got a bagthat's filled with toys
For the boys and girls again
Hear those sleigh bellsjingle jangle
What a beautiful sight
Jump in bed,cover up your head
'Cause Santa Clauscomes tonight,tonight
Santa Claus comes tonight
Happy days,happy times
Listen to the bellsand chimes
As Santa Claus comesyour way today
Here comes Santa
Claus,here comes Santa Claus
Right down Santa Claus Lane
He doesn't careif you're rich or poor
For he loves youjust the same
Santa knowsthat we're God's children
And that makeseverything right
Fill your hearts withthe Christmas cheer
'Cause Santa Claus comestonight
Tonight
Santa Claus comes tonight
Peace on Earthwill come to all
If we just follow the light
Let's give thanksto the Lord above
'Cause Santa Clauscomes tonight
Happy days,happy times
Listen to thebells and chimes
Here comes Santa Claus
just goes to show you,even in New
York, all you need is justa little magic
Let's go already
You guys suck eggs
Oh,my God.Hey
Us girls were talking andwe figured
that since all of us obviously want to
playthe Virgin Mary in the nativity scene,
we should all audition together
- No,thanks
- Okay
I was justtrying to be nice
I have a very low tolerancefor nice
I may seem really cooland
loving for a week or two,
but then my body rejects itlike a virus
and I move backinto my natural
state of cruel, selfishinsensitivity
The fact is,that between lady-man
and his junk flapping around on stage,
you probably passing out atsome
point during the audition,
and the basic truththat there is no way
they're going to leta Chinese girl play Mary
I think Tina's Korean
I would get that part
hands downif I wanted it
But I don't
What.Where are you
I'm takinga much-needed break,okay
It is exhaustingplaying a slutty elf
Get back here
Santa passed outin his own vomit
and probablycrapped his pants
And until the mall can finda replacement,
we need you to come backand play Mrs Claus
No,no,you play Mrs Claus,Lady Hummel
You were born to play Mrs Claus and Mrs
Butterworth and Bea Arthurand Barbara Bush
The mob's gettingrestless out there
Oh,my God,we are begging you
Please come hereand help us
Rocking aroundthe Christmas tree
At the Christmas party hop
Mistletoe hungwhere you can see
Every couple tries to stop
Rocking aroundthe Christmas tree
Let the Christmasspirit ring
Later we'll havesome pumpkin pie
And we'll do some caroling
You will geta sentimental feeling
When you hear
Voices singing,"Let's be jolly
Deck the halls withboughs of holly"
Rocking aroundthe Christmas tree
Have a happy holiday
Everyone dancing merrily
In the newold-fashioned way
You will geta sentimental feeling
When you hear
Voices singing,"Let's be jolly
Deck the halls withboughs of holly"
Rocking aroundthe Christmas tree
At the Christmas party hop
Mistletoe hungwhere you can see
Every couple tries to stop
Rocking aroundthe Christmas tree
Have a happy holiday
Everyone dancing merrily
In the new old-fashioned... Way...
We want Santa.We want Santa
Merry Christmas,shoppers
Well,it turns outSanta has
got a bit of a drinking problem
Got into the schnappslast night, and
he was a little hardto get out of bed
But-but... but it is actually Mrs Claus
who's been writing the list of
who's been naughtyand who's been nice
and forcing us elvesto
work at the sweatshop,
and she has madea special
trip to Santa Land,
and you guys get to tell
herwhat you want for Christmas
Who's excited.Who's excited
So here she is,Mrs Claus
Merry Christmas
Who's ready to sit on my lap
And what would youlike for Christmas
I want a Doc
McStuffinsTime-for-Your-Check-up Doll
Ooh,so cute
Well,that soundsa little molesty
I mean,I didn't startplaying
doctor till I was nine
I'll see whatI can do
I think that somebody needsto
freeze the fat for Christmas
because somebody
weighsmore than Mrs Claus
Whoa,stop right there
You look a littleJewish,right
Rachel,you think
Okay,bye
I think...Did you...
I think he poopedin his pants
I want a Kinder CollegeLearning Laptop
Why don't we justget you an iPad
You can't evenget porn on
whatever you justasked me for,okay
Hey,how's it going
You look exactlylike a young
Brittany SPierce,doesn't she
Brittany is my ex-girlfriend,and
she just dumped me,
which is why I'm even
hereand why I have this job
And we're lesbians
You know,and,like,I'd never
been with... Okay,great job
What would you likefor Christmas
I'd like... Oh,no,you know what
I think that youshould ask Santa to get
your daddy a jobwith some dental benefits,
because your grillis freaking jacked up
Do you see this
I think that Mrs Clausneeds a break
This is going well,right
You guys,she's coming
And one,two...
What's this ornament made of
It's a suet cakefor migratory songbirds,
and it's loadedwith
wildflower seeds for the birds
to poop outin their deforested wintering
groundsin the Amazon River Basin
- What species
- Douglas fir
- Which is the primary habitat of
- Red tree vole
And what happened to the voleyou left
homeless when you cut down this tree
Um,do you mean Richie
Because he came hereto live with us
Well,Glee Club,I gotta hand it to you
I thought Becky Jacksonwas going
to take first prize this year,
but shedidn't really get the
concept of "green decorations
" Here it is,Coach
See.Everything's green
Green apples,green bananas,peas, an Apple
Jacks box, grass clippings,moldy bread
I won't be announ...
You're still humming.Okay
I won't be announcing the
winneruntil tomorrow morning,
but I have to admit,for once,Glee Club,
you haven't totally screwedeverything up
Happy holidays
Since this year'sliving nativity
has a singing element to it,
and since I'm no expertwhen it comes
to judging show choir star power...
I am,in fact,sitting right here
I asked Mr Shueto help
out with our auditions
- for the Virgin Mary
- Thanks,Coach
I'm happy to help
judgeyour potential virgins
And it looks likefirst up we
have - a group audition - Yes
Ladies,wheneveryou're
ready, the manger is yours
Mary's boy childJesus Christ
Was born on Christmas Day
Long time ago in Bethlehem
So the Holy Bible said
Mary's boy childJesus Christ
Was born on Christmas Day
***
And man will liveforevermore
Because of Christmas Day
For a momentthe world was aglow
All the bells rang out,therewere
tears of joy and laughter
People shouted,"Let everyone know
There is hopefor all to find peace"
Hark now,hearthe angels sing
A king was born today
And man will liveforevermore
Because of Christmas Day
Oh,my Lord,you sentyour son to save us
Oh,my Lord,your very self you gave us
Oh,my Lord,that sinmay not enslave us
And love may reign once more
Oh,my Lord
Oh,praise the Lord
You sent your sonto save us
Oh,my Lord
This day will live forever
***
Oh,my Lord Ladies,I'm breathless
And I've got a littleJamaican in me,
and thattouched home in a very real way
Are there any other
last-minuteauditions for the Virgin Mary
***
No,but I'm afraidwe're gonna get killed
There's,like,a mobof
angry parents out there
We're never gonna get hiredas
holiday retail temps again
It's over,it's all over
No,it's not
How you doing
Cody Tolentino
But you can justcall me "Sexy Claus
" Heard somechatter about
there was sometrouble over here
Us Santastend to keep
- pretty close ranks
- Okay,listen
Even I'll admit thatmy girl-loving vagina
is feeling a littlejingle bell from you,
but we don'tneed your help
Okay,well,then... I'll just go
But if I were you guys,I would...
I would leave out the back door
I mean,these places tendto turn
people into animals when 'tisthe season
You mess with somebody's Yule,
and they will trample your ass
Okay,no,pleaseI'm sorry,we-we don't.we don't
want to betrampled,so... what do weneed to do
Yes.Anything.Truly
I'm Kurt,by the way.Newly single
Well,it's not a one-day fix
I can calm things down for today,
but if you truly want to save
Christmasfor this store and all of you,
it's gonna takethe rest of the week
I hereby deputizeeach of you as my elves
Ooh,we're deputized.Sounds fun
What are ourresponsibilities
Well,let's not getinto that just yet
I like to get to knowmy elves first
So what doyou guys say
Maybe dinner
- Your place. -
How's 8:00. - Right on
Merry Christmas,everybody
And that's whyancient Egyptians
regarded dung beetlesas sacred
- Attention,McKinley idiots.
- Come on
Here are your morningannouncements that were
obviously too unimportantto be mentioned until now
The three runners-up in the
politically-correct green-themed Christmas Tree
Decorating Contest are... the Biology
Club... ...the 420 Club... Oh,sick
and Beisteand the football team
What about me,Coach.What about me
Inside voice,Becky
And the winner of the tacky
plastic angelmade in the Philippines
by a 12-year-old child slave
is... bah,humbug...the glee club
Don't,Becky.Becky,don't.Becky,no
Everything's fine
- That's it
- Yep
Shocker
The virgin Marley gets
to playthe Virgin Mary
Aren't you worriedabout typecasting
What's with the snark
I asked you to audition, and
you said...I didn't want it
You obviously do
I don't get it
If this is somethingthat is important
to you, maybe we can talk to Mr
Shue... Don't you get it
I'm a Christian,and I know what it means to
have the Virgin Mary'sspirit in your heart
I don't have it
And I don't deserveto be her
To tell youthe truth, I'm
more likeMary Magdalene
Hey... Do we really have to
take downall of the ornaments
Rachel,yes
I thought it'd be niceto
have a tree-trimming party to,
you know,get us in the holiday spirit
We all set in there
If,by "all set," you mean did I light the candy-canescented
candles on the toilet, then yes,we are all set
- Good,perfect - Now,here.Try
this.I added some nutmeg. - No
I think thatneeds some kick
I mean,come on,Kurt
Don't all you gayslove Julia Child
Didn't she,like,spike everything
Well,I guessI could add - some
cooking sherry in here - Yes
Merry Christmas.Merry Christmas
this is unbelievable.
I mean... for struggling actors,
geez,you guys gota great apartment
- Is that vintage.yeah.I-I
love vintage - Yeah. - Albums
Well,you gottahave vintage
- Wow
- Yep
So,you got any tricks
- in that bag,Santa
- Oh... Well,you know,I
do do all kinds of parties
Kids,bachelorette...
bachelor... Well,let's see
I got balloons and helium... Costumes
All kinds of stuff
So how did you guys all meet
We were in,um,high
school glee club together
Kurt and I first, and then...it's
just... it's complicated
Glee club,huh
Do you guys take requests
'Cause I just thoughtof
something truly amazing
All right,you chipmunks
Ready to sing your song
I'll say we are
Yeah,let's sing it now
-Okay,Rachel
- Okay
- Okay,Santana
- Okay,Kurt.Kurt.Kurt.
- Okay
Christmas,Christmas time is near
Time for toys
And time for cheer
We've been goodbut we can't last
Hurry,Christmas,hurry fast
Want a planethat loops the loop
Me,I want a hula hoop
We can hardly stand the wait
Please,Christmas,don't be late
okay,fellas,take it away.Very good
Very good,Santana
Now,Kurt,you werea little flat.Watch me
- Kurt Kurt...Kurt
- Okay
Want a planethat loops the loop
I still want a hula hoop
We can hardly stand the wait
Please,Christmas,don't be late
- That is good...
- Oh,my gosh... Tickle me
This is the bestChristmas present ever
- Besides curing cancer and peace on Earth,of course
- True
Hey,Trouty Mouth
Hey,Tokyo Rose
Merry Christmas
Are these teeth
Not any teeth
My baby teeth
To remind you of the
pure,innocent love of Baby Jesus
Thanks,Becky
That's... verysweet of you
We were sorry youdidn't,you
know, win the contest
Tell me about it
I'm still recovering
fromCoach Sue's critique
Well,I appreciate your
literalinterpretation of "green,"
but it looks like you fishedall this
stuff right out ofthe school Dumpster
It's recycled
What it is,is lazy
Okay,okay
I wanted to go home and
watch Gigolos on Showtime
So I did it half-assed
I feel like you guys
Losers
Anyways,happy holidays
- I love Christmas
- Me,too
- And I love New York
You know what.You
should totallymove here
- No.No way
- Yeah
I mean,what aboutmy scholarship
to the Universityof Louisville
There's no way thatI could just leave in the middle
ofthe school year for no good reasonand come here
Look,I know thatit's impossible, but you
could,like,live here with me and Kurt... Where
Where's Kurt
- Yeah,and Studly Claus
- Kurt.Kurt.Kurt
- Oh,my God
- Oh,hell no
That is not happening
Oh,don't worry,ladies
Santa swings both ways
- What.What's the matter,Santana
- Jealous
No,I am disgusted and also impressed
Who knew the Queen of
Englandcould be so trashy
Aren't you the one who's
always callingme Miss Priss
And telling me that I
needto live it up a bit
Well,you're right
I'm in New York, I'm
single,I'm available,
and your hot butteredrum concoction
is dangerouslylowering my inhibitions
So why not throw cautionto the wind
In that case,let's drink up.Let's do it
Ladies,join us for a toast
Here's to being naughtythis Christmas
To being naughty
Oh... Santana Santana,wake up
Oh,my God.Oh,my God
Oh,the last timeI felt like this
was when I was roofiedat Lilith Fair
Oh,my God
- Oh,my God,help me up
- Come here
Oh,my God,Rachel... Oh,my God
Where's all our nice things
I don't know,I don't know
The last thing I rememberwas Lady Hummel
bouncing quartersoff of Santa's abs
- Kurt
- Kurt.Oh,my God
Take that outof his mouth
- What happened Are you okay
- What is this
- It was rough-trade Santa,that's
what happened - Oh,God
We were role-playing, and he
wantedme to be his Rudolph,
and when I said no,well,he
stopped being so jolly
Oh,God,he took offhis
suspenders and he tied me up
And-And,well,he did sayit was sexy kissing
me because it was likeI had no teeth
That's disgusting.This is disgusting
But then he just admittedthat-that he
was only here to rob us blind anyway
Oh,I think I'mgonna be sick
Wait... Did Kittyreally
say she wasn't worthy
You sure she wasn't justbeing snarky
- Or
body-snatched - No
In that moment,she
wastotally,like,a real person
If we can get Kitty to take
the role of the Virgin Mary,
get into those vestmentsand stand in the middle
of that nativity scene holding the Baby Jesus,
maybe she'll realize she is worthy, and
she'll stop beingso insanely horrible
Oh,a Christmas presentto us all
I tried to offer herthe
part, but she wouldn'ttake it
I know how tomake her take it
Sam,the Christmas angelis
not like the Stanley Cup
- You can't take it home with you
- Oh,this
Yeah,um... we decidedto give it away
Uh,to Becky
Becky'slike a sad little... Hermey the
Elf waddlingaimlessly into a snow drift,
and we thoughtthat giving her the angel
might light her uplike Rudolph's nose
Well,that walksa dangerously fine line between
being really sweetand horribly condescending
Don't worry,Artie,we've
gotsomething else for her,too
Remember,guys,you'retired,you're
hungry but ironically excited
- All right,dress rehearsal.
- Places.Let's go
Wait,Marley,why aren'tyou
dressed as the Virgin Mary
We all decidedthat the only girl who could
do the partjustice is... The black one
Joseph,honey,get meto the
stable.I'm about to pop
You think thatI don't feel love
But what I feel for youis real love
In others' eyesI see reflected
A hurt,scorned,rejected
Love child
Never meant to be
***
Is worth the pain of waiting,we'll only
End up hating The
child we may be creating
Love child
Never meant to be
Scorned by
Society
Love child
Always second best
Love child,different from the rest
Hold on,hold on,just a little bit longer
Mmm,baby
Hold on,hold on
Just a little bit longer
Don't thinkthat I don't need you
Don't thinkI don't want to please you
No child of mine'llbe bearing
The name of shameI've been wearing
Love child,love child
Never quite as good
Afraid,ashamed
Misunderstood
But I'll always love you
Always love you
Love child
Wait just a little bit
I'll always,I'll always
I'll always love
you,love child Love child
- Yes All right
- Not bad,not bad,guys
- just a few notes
- Wow
- Ryder,deliver the baby
- a few bars earlier
- You got it.
- Wait.N-No
That wasthe most sacrilegious and
profane horror showI have ever seen
Racist
Mr Shue,you can not letthis abomination
happen to the most beautiful storyever told
We have to do this the
right wayor not at all
- i will play the virginary.
- not so fast
Um,is that okaywith you,Unique
Happy holidays.You get the part
Hey,Becky,there you are
- Uh,didn't you hear the news
- What are you talking about
There was a recounton the tree decorating
contest, and it turns outyou actually won
But my tree was a bagof diapers
It's Ohio,Becky.It's a swing state
You know,the votescan
always go either way
the angel's yours
Merry Christmas Congratulations
I love you,plastic angel
Oh,and there's something else
There's a,um,part left in the living
nativitythat no one else can play
Do you thinkyou can help us out
Santana,I feellike such a fool
I just wanted to get
outsideof myself,you know,
let myself be free for
once,and look what happened
Everything,includingmy collection
of Broadway Playbills,was stolen
I've never felt so ashamed
That's why I couldnever live here
Bushwick is worsethan Lima Heights
You can't tellanyone about this
Even though Blaineand I are
broken up, you can never tellhim
- Promise me
- I promise
Okay,so I justgot back from the mall
Turns out that Codyransacked
Santa Land as well
He even took all of the moneyfrom
the Salvation Army bucket
The police said that we
werelucky that we weren't hurt
More hurt
But,needless to say,our services at
the Midtown Mall are no longer required
This is gonna follow us
The fact that we were fired fromour jobs as Christmas
elves is gonna be a black markon our acting rsums
for the rest of our lives
Not if we have something else
to make upfor it,which I do
So,I was getting offof the subway
and I was passing Fifth Avenue...
No,Rachel,another oneof your crazy jobs
We barely survivedthe first one
Trust me,Santana
This jobwill not only test
our mettle as performers,
but we will beprotected by
the safety of bulletproof glass
- This is obviously myrrh,not frankincense
- No,no,no
That's-that's frankincense
Guys,can we just talk
abouthow great everybody looks
Look at you guys.You guyslook
phenomenal.Where's Becky
This hay is making mehave a rash
- Becky,you're a genius
- Genius
All you have to do is
just kneel right here
- It's gonna look perfect
- Yes
- You look amazing
- Great job
How did you think of that
Kitty... Virgin in the house,bitches
You look beautiful
Places,everyone
Away in a manger
No crib for a bed
The little Lord Jesus
Lay down his sweet head
The stars in the sky
Looked down where he lay
The little Lord Jesus
Asleep on the hay
The cattle are lowing
The poor baby wakes
But little Lord Jesus
No crying he makes
I love thee,Lord Jesus
Look down from the sky
And stay by my cradle
Till morning is nigh
Be near me,Lord Jesus
Ooh...I ask thee to stay
Close by me forever
And love me,I pray
Bless all the dear children
In thy tender care
And take us to Heaven
To live with thee there