I'm still not comfortable with this.
Steve,everyone on this
rock knows you and Five-O.
So if you guys show up,the
clientele's gonna be out the back door
before you even step foot in
the front,but they don't know me.
Maybe we do a different location.
No,no,no.This guys doesn't want
anyone to know that he's in the casino,
So it's the only place where he's
not gonna have security with him.
I've surveilled it; I know how to
get in,I know how to get out.Boom.
- What if you get compromised?
- I'll improvise.
You're the one who told me to get back
up on the horse,okay?And you were right.
So you're just gonna
have to let me do this.
What,are you deputizing me?
Just in case,all right?
Don't worry,it's gonna be
fine.I've got this covered,okay?
It's gonna be fine.
P*****
Six,pass line wins.
Betting against the table
hasn't been working for you,huh?
Maybe you can get lucky some other way.
Haven't we met before,miss?
What do you want?
Riku Sato,where is he?
Who the hell are you?
Five-O.
Now where the hell is Sato?
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly
Presents
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET-静静的生活
Hawaii Five-0
2010 Season 04Episode 07
BABY*****
Hey,bro,any good sets out there?
Picking up.
If we're lucky,we'll get swell.
B***
How***
You****
that***
G***
Anything else,lover boy?
Nani,you reading over my shoulder?
Only the dirty parts.More coffee?
Just the check,please.
Oh,it's already taken care
of.Gentleman at the counter.
- Thanks,Nani.
- Sure.
What's that for?
Well,Captain Grover,let's just say
I've been around long enough to know
that when someone pays for your
meal they usually want something.
Come on.Are you really that cynical?
Where I'm from,cops
do that for each other.
Besides,I figured it was the least I could
do after pointing a shotgun in your face.
Yeah,well,that hostage
crisis was rough on everyone.
I think it's fair to say that
there was fault on both sides.
Lieutenant,I realize the governor
gives you guys a free pass,
but to be honest,that behavior I saw
out there in the field the other day,
that's a surefire way to get yourself
alienated from your brothers in blue.
I mean,I'd hate to see you in a situation
where you call for backup and it doesn't show.
I think you need to be having
this conversation with McGarrett.
I don't think so.
I'm not having this conversation with
McGarrett.McGarrett's not a real cop.
He doesn't think like a
cop,he doesn't act like a cop.
You,on the other hand...I did
my homework; you're a good cop.
Got your badge back after going through
a rough patch.I know what that's like.
Have a nice day,Captain.
I'm coming,I'm coming.I said
I'm coming!All right,all right.
IT'A GITL!c*****
Mary,what...
- You should see your face.
- What are you doing here?
- Who's baby is this?
- Mine.
- No,it's not.
- She's mine.
I adopted her.
What are you talking
about?How could it be yours?
It's been in the works for a while,
but I kept in on the DL in case a certain
someone was gonna be critical about it.
I don't believe it.
Isn't she cute?I named her after Dad.
- Oh,you named her John?
- No,Joan.
Mary,I don't want to be critical,
but you have difficulty
managing your own life.
How you gonna look after the baby?
I think I took care of a
90-year-old man pretty well.
For three weeks,and he died.
He died of natural causes,okay?
Okay.You got to give her back,Mary.
Steve,I can't return
her like she's an Xbox.
She's not an Xbox.She's
a little baby person,okay,
and this is a responsibility you're
gonna have for the rest of your life.
You're really killing my
buzz being a new mom.Thanks.
Yeah?Okay.I'm on the way.
I got to go.All right,listen,we'll
talk about this when I get back.
Bye.
Buddy,listen to me,the way I see
it,Mary didn't adopt a kid; you did.
All right,'cause it's only a
matter of time before that poor,
unfortunate child is looking for some suckling
at 3:00 a.m.,is gonna be looking to you.
No,there's gonna be no suckling,okay?
- No?
'Cause that baby is going back.
Oh,you're gonna send it
back,what,to the orphanage?
- With a bunch of other kids that nobody wants?
- What?
Yeah,no,it's a good idea.
I mean,it's probably a better idea
than leaving it with your sister.
Wait a minute,I thought
you didn't approve?
I don't approve.
Okay,whose side are you on then?
I'm on the side where the kid
has a chance of being loved.
If you think Mary is capable of
doing that,then I'm all for it,okay?
Gentlemen,what we have
here is a male victim.
C.O.D. is quite evident based
on the multiple stab wounds.
He was most likely
attacked in the water.
Maybe a couple of guys got territorial
over this break,and then it got out of hand.
A reasonable theory,but highly unlikely.
The victim's hands are noticeably
free of defensive wounds,
which suggests that the attack
was sudden and unexpected.
Okay,do we get an ID?
I was just getting to that.
Just spoke to a lifeguard
who patrols this area.
He said our vic's a regular,here every
Monday 9:00 a.m.,swell or no swell.
Okay,so predictable schedule,
he's hit up close and
personal,no defensive wounds.
Our victim could've been
attacked by somebody who knew him.
Our victim has been
identified as Bryan Carpenter.
Pinches for assault,drug
charges,grand larceny,
guy's been in and out
of trouble for years.
Looks like his troubles
followed him out to sea.
B******
Got signs of a break-in.
Place has been tossed.
Clear.
I wonder if they found
what they were looking for.
What is that?
Something under this drain.
This could be what
they were looking for.
There's something else in there.
- Oh,my God.
- Chin,what is it?
Our victim wasn't Bryan Carpenter.
M*****
His name is Matt Hutchins.
He was a cadet at the Police Academy
when I was teaching a class on executing
search warrants a few years ago.
Normally,I don't remember students,but
Matt asked a lot of really smart questions.
One day,he cornered me after class and
asked me what the job was really like.
The kid wanted to make a difference,but
wasn't even sure it was possible.
He grew up in a rough
neighborhood,drug dealing,gangs.
When I asked him,"Why be a cop?
" he said that "The game"
was the only thing he knew,
and that he would end up on
one side of it or the other.
He wanted to take the right path.
So he became a cop.
Well,Matt never got his badge.
He was busted for heroin possession.He
got kicked out of the Academy.
I was disappointed.
Special Agent Blake
Kennedy,ATF.I just got a call?
What happened to my guy?
Sorry.Your guy?
Matt,uh,Hutchins was working a
long-term undercover op for ATF.
I was his handler.
So he was never kicked
out of the Academy.
Kicked out?Hell no.That
was all part of his cover.
What was the op?
We had him infiltrate
a gang of gunrunners.
A network with ties to
Asia and the mainland.
Matt's job was to ID the
players and record transactions,
and we were just about to
drop the net on these guys.
Another few weeks and Matt
would've a career bust.
If you guys were that close,we
have to assume one thing...
Matt's cover was compromised.
How?
He was attacked this morning.
We believe he was deliberately targeted.
- Where?
- Baby Makapu'u Beach.
We were just there today.
A witness told us that he
surfed there every Monday.
My son and I go there every Monday.
Well,he couldn't break cover,but I'm sure
that was his way of keeping an eye on you.
Do you know who did this?
We believe it had something to
do with his undercover assignment.
Those people he was
investigating,he hated them.
- How often did you two speak?
- Every few weeks.
A text here,a quick phone call there.
Always from a different number.
But the last time,his
tone was different...
- How so?
- I don't know.
He sounded happy.
So I was under the impression that maybe
it was coming all coming to an end and...
he'd be home soon.
My husband sacrificed
everything for that job.
Lieutenant,you need to find
the bastards who did this.
This is the guy we're after,J.C.Dekker.
He spent his wayward youth on the North Shore
making a name for himself in the ice trade.
Now,ten years ago,he moved
his operation into town
and he upgraded his clientele,focusing
primarily on weapons distribution.
Guys right below him have been
there since the first dollar.
Everyone else has been
recruited along the way.
Looks like Matt worked his
way up the chain of command.
Well,like I said:
That was Matt's talent.
He was able to talk the
talk,and that earned him respect.
And when it came time,he wasn't
afraid to use some muscle.
When I first sent him in,we
didn't know what to expect.
We thought it was a
six-month op at most.
But Matt's intel was so good,we soon
realized we were sitting on a major case.
Right,now that Matt's gone,so are
the chances of taking these guys out.
That's why I like Dekker for this.
Motive,means,opportunity.
What about these
guys?What happened to them?
KIA.
As tight as Dekker's operation
is,he has his problems.
In the last few months,these dirtbags
have been robbed a number of times
by a three-man crew we
have yet to identify.
How were these robberies going down?
It wasn't any
street-level,crime-of-opportunity stuff.
I mean,we're talking
well-coordinated hit-and-runs.
Cash drops,they were there.Guns
in storage,they were there.
All right,well,maybe Dekker
thought Matt was selling 'em out.
Giving information to the guys
who were ripping off his boys.
Or maybe Dekker figured
out Matt was a cop.
I mean,either way,Dekker had at
least two motives to kill this kid.
- We're gonna need everything on this case.
- Yeah.
Linda,can you come
over here for a moment?
Linda Davies,this is Steve
McGarrett,Detective Danny Williams.
They're with Five-O.
Now,Linda transcribed
all of Matt's reports.
She'll get you everything you need.
Of course.Right this way.
This is everything.
Ms.Davies,do you mind if we ask
you how well did you know Matt?
We actually never met.
I've listened to his voice
for the past four years.
I transcribed every one of his reports.
So I could tell when he was having
a good week and when,when it was bad.
How did he sound in his last
few reports?Anything unusual?
Did he mention any threats?
If you're asking me if his cover
was blown,I can tell you this:
the longer you leave an undercover out
there,they get tired and depressed,sloppy.
They start making mistakes.
It's not my place to say this,but I,
I really think we had enough to
take these guys down months ago.
What makes you say that?
I've been working this
job for a while now,
and I've seen this department
take people down for much less.
If we would have done
what we normally do,
I-I just can't help but wonder
if Matt would still be alive.
All right,are you gonna say it or am I?
I'm not saying anything.I'm not
ready to start pointing fingers.
Okay,I'll say it.
If the ATF could have made an
arrest months ago,why didn't they?
Keeping Matt out there past his sell-by
date could have compromised his cover.
Dismantling an operation like
this,it is not as easy as it sounds.
Think about Matt,all right?
This guy,maybe he,uh,maybe he got
tired,maybe he missed his family,
maybe somewhere he slipped up.
Maybe he slipped up,and maybe
Kennedy kept Matt out there too long
because he cared more about making his case
than he did about looking after his boy.
Maybe,but like I said,
I am not ready for pointing fingers
until we have something that is real,okay?
I'll tell you what's real: J.C.Dekker.
And let me tell you something else.
If he suspected for one second that Matt
was a cop,he would take care of business.
I agree.But to go rattle that
cage right now is a terrible idea
because we could blow the ATF's
entire three-year operation.
So we'll tread lightly.
Got your attention now or what?
Hey,hey,hey,what happened
to "tread lightly," huh?
I'm giving you three seconds
to get your hands off my throat.
Or what?
How's your girlfriend look in black?
Sit.
Now listen to me very carefully:
You're done mouthing off.
I'm gonna ask the questions from now on.
You're just gonna nod yes or no.
Bryan Carpenter,do you know him?
That's not technically a yes or a no.
I'm gonna take it as a yes.I'm
also gonna assume that you did this.
What happened?
This morning,where were you?
Complying with the state's unconstitutional
invasion of my physical sovereignty.
Come again?
I was peeing in a cup for
my P.O.You can ask him.
Okay,well,that still doesn't
mean you didn't order the hit.
Why would I do that?
Bryan was my friend.
Let's assume that you're telling
the truth again for two seconds.
Why would somebody want to kill him?
I have no idea.
And why do you care
about one of mines anyway?
Shouldn't you be celebrating at a
donut shop or something right now?
That sounds excellent.
Get up.
Now here's your itinerary for
the next couple of days: nothing.
You don't move from here,you understand?
HPD's gonna sit on your place
until we straighten this out.
If I hear that you leave,even
to take your library books back,
Detective Williams and I,we're gonna come back
and we're not gonna be as courteous next time.
Well,that was very subtle.
I'm sure he's calling whoever killed
Matt right now and telling 'em to lay low.
What are you talking?He
didn't order the hit.
Did you see the look on his
face?He didn't know anything.
Okay,well,if that's the case,
then we have to consider the
possibility that Matt was dirty,okay?
- Dirty.
- Yes,dirty,okay?
If he was selling information to the crew that
ripped off Dekker and he slipped off somewhere,
it would've gotten him killed.
Danny,Matt was a cop.
I know he was a cop,okay?
I knew plenty of guys back in New
Jersey that were undercover for so long,
they ended up slipping; they
didn't know what the line was.
Just-Just wait.Just wait.
Yes,Mary?Wait...what?
And so it begins.
Salmonella?Really?
- I shouldn't have eaten that egg salad on the plane.
- Yeah.
Mary,this is exactly what
we were talking about before.
Steve,bad eggs have nothing to
do with my parenting skills,okay?
I could be a good
mother,just not right now.
I really need you to watch Joan for
me 'cause I have to stay her overnight.
- No!No,no,no!I can't do that.
- Steve,you have to.
- Mary,no,Mary...
- I don't have anybody else to call!I have to stay here over...
Mary,I'm in the middle,I'm in the
middle of a homicide investigation.
Okay.I'll just call
Child Protective Services.
And Joan will have to be placed with
a foster care family for a while.
I just hope that the trauma doesn't
affect her cognitive development.
Cognitive?You don't even
know what that word means.
You're a horrible uncle,you know that?
- This funny to you?
- Yeah!
So when you're through amusing yourself,
I need you to wipe down
her changing pad,please.
Not at all.I'm retired,you see.
And it's gonna be way too entertaining to
see Uncle Steve on diaper duty.So go ahead.
Hey,why is there a baby
attached to your chest?
- Mary.- Say no
more.Yeah.Mazel tov.- Thanks.
Anyway,I was able to track down
- the manufacturer of the key we found at Matt's house.
- Oh,good.
It traces back to a set of locks
that they sold to Honolulu Zoo.
Oh,let me see that.
Actually,you know
what?Here,just for a second.
- What?
- Thank you.
- Take care of it.
- Yeah,yeah.
- Okay,Danny,let's go.
- Okay.
- Wait.
- If she gets hungry,bottle in here.You got it?Let's go.
Wait...how am I supposed
to know if she's hungry?
Oh,you'll know.Trust me,you'll know.
Sato?
I don't know any Sato.
You know for somebody who likes to
gamble,you don't have a very good poker face.
Your name is Hideaki
Kuroda.You're Sato's moneyman.
You have a wife.You have
two children.Rosie and Kin.
Now,Rosie,she's very
talented at the piano.
And Kin,well,he aced math,but
he needs a science tutor.Right?
Oh,and you just brought,um,a
brand-new sports car.For your mistress.
So far,so good?
I also know that you
want out of Sato's crew.
But you can't because you've been
gambling with your boss' money.
And you've been losing.
Trying to cover it up,moving the money
around from place to place.But that hole?
Yeah,that hole just keeps
getting deeper.And deeper.
Now if I know this,Then really it's only a
matter of time before Sato figures it out.
And when he realizes that
he can't get his money back
because you lost it at blackjack
and craps,and roulette and horses,
he is gonna hurt you in
the worst way that he can.
Now,we can help you,Mr.Kuroda,
but you first you got to
tell me where I can find Sato.
What business do you have with Sato?
I don't give a damn about Sato.
I just want to ask him where
I can find Adam Noshimuri.
HO******
There it is.There are the lockers.
B-24.
You still think Matt's not dirty?
FIVE*****
Okay.We got over a $100,000 cash.
Explain to me how is it that an
undercover cop has this kind of money?
I can't.Okay?I can't.But
that doesn't make him dirty.
Steve,he had the key to that
locker hidden in a shower drain.
He did not want anyone
to see this cash...why?
Maybe he was getting paid for inside information
by the guys that were ripping off Decker.
That's a big maybe for
a guy who put his wife
and his son's lives on the backburner
for three years to take Dekker down.
Don't mind the smell.Yeah,I
know.Strained peas.
Only partially digested.Here,could
you,uh...Thanks.
- Did you,uh,get anything besides throw up?
- Funny.
I ran the credit histories
on Matt and his wife.
Nothing unusual...they
live paycheck to paycheck
just like most honest hard-working
civil servants on the island.
Can we focus over here?
Yeah,you ran the finances,no
surprises.Good,what else we got?
I dumped Matt's phone.
The only thing of note
was a series of phone calls
to a local real estate
agent all in the last week.
Name of Cherie Tranton.
Real estate agent?That
seem strange to you?
Maybe the lease is
up on,uh,on his place.
Ah,yeah,or maybe he was looking to buy
some property and launder some of this cash.
I'll check in with Agent Kennedy.
See if he knows anything about
the money or the real estate agent.
You know what,Chin?Hold
off on that for now.
Let's take a look at
Matt's field reports first.
I want to keep ATF out
of the loop for now.
Well,Kennedy had all the
same intel Matt did.You know?
Oh,I see.So I'm crazy,my-my theory
is nuts thinking that Matt went bad,
but your new amazing idea is Matt's
handler was the one giving information
to the guys that ripped off Dekker.
Well,I'm just saying it's possible,okay?
We all heard what
Kennedy's transcriber said.
Kennedy could've pulled Matt out
and taken the case down weeks ago.
That would explain why Kennedy
kept Matt out in the field so long.
Right.So let's just take a
closer look at the transcripts.
See if we're missing anything.All right?
- What are we doing?
- It's your turn.
- My turn for what?
- We're a team.
Danny,everybody's got to put in 110%.
Look at this...that's 110% right there.
Chin and I,we're gonna go talk to Dekker
see if he can shed some light on this cash.
In the meantime,while
you're on babysitting duty,
run background on
this real estate agent.
See if there's any connection between
Dekker's crew and Cherie Tranton.
And try not to let her drool on
the evidence.We're gonna need it.
Smart kid.Uh,I got an idea.
Uh,why don't I step up for the
team and,uh,Chin and I will go out.
You stay here,make those calls,and
deal with,your soiled niece here?
Change her soon.You
understand?Or she gets a rash.
Oh,does she?
Diaper bag's in Steve's office.
Bottles are in the fridge.
You're gonna need that.
Why was this in a storage locker
belonging to your dead friend?
Let me guess.There's a
hundred grand in there.
How did you know that?
'Cause I gave it to him.
Bryan asked me for a loan.Said he'd
get it back to me by the weekend.
Wait a minute...a guy asks you
for a hundred thousand dollars
and you just give it to him?
Yeah,I trust my friends.
What he want the money for?
I don't ask for details,man.
What I don't know won't put me in a box.
Now if you're done harassing me,I'm gonna
get some fish tacos with my police escort.
If Matt didn't steal that money...
Yeah,it throws some cold water on the
theory that he was dirty.Hey,Dekker?
I'm done talking until
I get my money back.
Oh,you mean this donation to the Widows and
Orphans Fund?That's very generous of you.
Now,listen,why don't you tell me about
this crew that's been ripping you off...
who are they?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Those guys that have been hitting you are
probably the guys that killed your friend.
Well,then I sincerely
hope you catch them.
Okay,listen to me.
I know you've been taking
some big financial hits lately.
Okay?So I want to do you a favor.
I'm going to extend our police presence.
You and everybody in your life is
gonna be protected by HPD 24-seven.
Just to make sure you feel safe.
We're gonna have eyes
on you day and night.
Yeah,good luck in the import/export biz.
Enjoy your tacos.
Wait.
I got something that might help.
This is an in-house surveillance video from a
local gang getting ripped off by another crew.
What's in the crates?
Guns,drugs and other party favors.
I'm more interested in
the guys behind the masks.
Is there any way we can
ID these guys,Charlie?
There's always a way.
I'll call you when I got something.
All right,thanks,buddy.
Hey,Charlie?It's good to have you back.
Once upon a time there
was a very handsome prince.
And this,uh,handsome prince had
a very beautiful black stallion.
And this black stallion was,uh,was
admired by everybody in the kingdom.
He was the fastest and
fairest stallion in the land,
about 528 horsepower,very
nice stallion,anyway.
Uh,one day,uh,this
incredibly handsome prince...
Yeah,he was,he was out
of sight,let me tell you.
He was partnered up with a mean ogre.
A disgusting,hairy ogre.
It was not a match made in heaven.
They would slay dragons
together from time to time.
And they'd argue all
the time and,of course,
the brilliant charming prince would-would win
those arguments because the ogre was a dope.
Despite their,uh,victories,there
was a dark cloud that loomed.
Because...the dopey ogre coveted
the handsome prince's stallion,okay?
And he was a very greedy,selfish
ogre with-with major control issues.
And he would never let the handsome
prince ride his own stallion.
Hold on,we're gonna
pick this up in a second.
Great,it's the real estate agent.
Hello.Yes,yes it is.
Uh,that's perfect.I can,uh,I can meet
you there.What's,uh,what's the address?
That was fast.
Making up for lost time.Check it out.
I got a clean screen
capture on one of your guys.
We can estimate height,weight,shoe size.
If we run those traits through
the HPD arrest database?
We're gonna get dozens of matches
and then lots of possible suspects.
But...if we measure Pupillary distance,which
in this case is 63.2 millimeters,
and we combine it with
all of the other traits,
it narrows the field considerably.
Aloha,Joey Tillman.
Okay,what do we
got?Robbery,guns,assault,more robbery.
This has to be our guy.
You know,SWAT's on its way.Maybe I don't
need to ask this,but should we wait?
That's what I thought.
Cover!
Looks like we got three shooters.
These guy move weapons for a
living.They're gonna be armed to the teeth.
We're gonna need more guns.
You should've waited for SWAT.
You really want to do this now?
Hold fire!
This is HPD SWAT!
Drop your weapons and come
out.You are outnumbered.
This is your one warning.
That's Tillman.
Clear!
Hey,yo.You'll want to
come take a look at this.
Same crates we saw in
the surveillance videos.
These have got to be the guys
that've been ripping off Dekker.
All right,let's get an
alert out right away.
I thought you said there
were three shooters.
There were.Third guy
must've slipped out the back.
Oh,he slipped out the back.
Well,that's exemplary work,Commander.
Steve.Take a look at this.
Entry wound's in the back of the head.
We didn't kill these guys.
The third shooter did.
Oh,you mean the guy that
escaped on your watch?
On my watch?You were standing right
next to me when this went down.
See,it wouldn't have gone down if you just
waited a little bit and let SWAT do its job.
But,hey,like I
said,exemplary work,Commander.
- All right,listen up.We got a shooter on the run.
- So why does he shoot his own guys?
Well,maybe he's tying up loose ends.
Which could be the same
motive for killing Matt.
Maybe this third shooter knew that
Matt was getting close to the crew.
We need to work out what
Matt wanted that money for.
All new construction,brand-new
carpeting,engineered quartz countertops.
And there's a great school district
for your little girl,when she's ready.
Oh,no,that's,uh...that's very nice.
She's,uh...she's actually a friend
of mine's.I'm just babysitting.
I'm,uh...I'm single.
Oh,my.Well...
So refreshing to meet
somebody who's so...giving.
You must be a very warm person.
And you're so fit.
Oh,thank you very much.
I just appreciate a man who
can wear a pair of pants.
- Okay.
- Well...
Now,this condo's got a great layout.
Although...there's
only one bedroom.Wink.
Look at that.She said
"wink,wink," and then she winked.
So tell me...
what winds of fortune have blown
your little ship into my harbor?
Matt Hutchins,actually recommended you.
- Mr. Hutchins!
- Yeah.
- Oh,did he rent the apartment for you?
- Yes,he did.
I have to say,this was a first for me.
I mean,I have people who
come and want to window shop,
but I've never had someone want
to rent a condo for just one day.
Well,uh,yeah,one day.That's
all we need it for.
- Today's that day,so...here we are.
- Tomorrow,silly.
Tomorrow,yes,of course.Tomorrow's
that day,that's what I meant.
You know,for $1,000,you boys must
have something scintillating planned,
so you better keep Cherie's
number in your phone.
Homeowner's association doesn't
like little side deals like this,
so it's our little secret,okay?
All right.Cherie,you're very naughty.
Honey...you have no idea.
You are gonna love this view.
Wow,very nice.
I know.
Hey,Steve.Something you
gotta see.Come down here.
It seems like Matt was running surveillance
on the lockers where we found the money.
You know what,if you're gonna
hold the baby in the sun,okay,
just ask me and I'll
put a sunhat on her.
You know what,though?The question is,why
would he be doing surveillance on the lockers?
Okay,Matt recorded all the times and
dates of Dekker's weapons transactions.
- Right?
- Yeah.
The crew that was ripping Dekker
off had all that information.
Are you thinking that Matt thought
that someone in the ATF leaked it?
I think he was building a case.
I mean,he could have borrowed
the money off of Dekker,
planted it in the lockers to set up
whoever was leaking that information.
If that were the case,he would have planted
the misinformation in one of his reports.
Now look at this...Here's an entry
about the money drop at Honolulu Zoo.
Set to be dropped off at 9:00
a.m.,picked up at 11:00 a.m. tomorrow.
All right,that's a two hour
window for the money to be stolen.
Yep,we were right.Matt was
setting someone up at the ATF.
Kennedy.
He could have been selling information
to Tillman about Dekker's operation.
That's why he kept the case open
and Matt undercover for so long.
He was onto a good thing,he
didn't want it to end.
Well,he keeps his hands clean,and
he gets a cut of the profits.
And then when he found out
that Matt was on to him,
Kennedy got one of
Tillman's guys to kill him.
Where are you going?
I'm going to finish what Matt started.
You want to come?Let's do it.
All right,so listen up.
Grab whoever picks up this money
the second they open the locker.
I want this entire place locked down.
I want men on every exit,and I want two men
every 30 yards around the perimeter.Let's go.
I wouldn't have done it this way.
Yeah,you don't say?
McGarrett,we should wait.
Let your suspect exit the
zoo,then you take him down.
That way,we don't get into a firefight
in the middle of all these civilians.
I want to secure the perimeter.Okay?
He's not going to escape this time.
He wouldn't have escaped last time
if you'd have just waited for SWAT.
I could've been dead
if I waited for SWAT.
Maybe.But there's a right way
and a wrong way to do things.
You don't like me.All right?I get that.
But I'm in command and control of this
operation I'm also the team leader,okay?
So you and your team,you can come
aboard with us or you can stand down.
Whatever you say,uh...Commander.
Nothing.Did you remember
to give Joan her bottle?
Of course I did.
You're texting Max right now,aren't you?
MAX *****
No,I'm not.
You're a terrible liar.
I got something.
Black hoodie,straight ahead.Moving
fast,heading straight for the lockers.
Hold it right there.
- Took you long enough.
- Traffic.
Don't move a muscle.
Why?
Take a look around,Linda.
Look at where you are.
You see this room?You don't get
to this room by accident.It's over.
We know you were feeding Matt's
intel to your boyfriend here.
And we know that with that information,
he and two of his associates were able
to systematically rip off Dekker's crew.
Yesterday,this guy right here,
he put two bullets in the back of their
heads to make sure they kept quiet.
Now,who's to say he wouldn't have done the same
thing to you after you collected that money?
Matt trusted us.
No,we were his lifeline.
And y-you betrayed him.For what?Money?
- No.We just didn't want to go to jail.
- Shut up,Linda!
You make me understand.
Why'd you have to kill him?
Matt called a few weeks ago.
He wanted to know who had
access to his transcripts.
He suspected that his
reports had been compromised.
It was only a matter of time
until he traced that back to us.
I'm... sorry. I'm... so sorry.
You done here?
Now I am.
Maybe I should've...pulled Matt out.
You know,if I-I'd just
pushed the button sooner...
What say we go push it now?
What the hell is this?
There was nothing incriminating
on that tape I gave you.
- Where's my money?
- Where's your money?
Good news is,we got
your money and your guns.
Bad news is,we got your
money and your guns.
Allison,there's
something you need to see.
Hey,Matty.
You know,I often dream about
the kind of man you'll become...
your strength and courage,your
sense of right and wrong.
There are so many things a
father wants to teach his son,
and sometimes you
gotta teach by example.
In accepting this assignment,
I hope I've helped make this world the
kind of place you deserve to grow up in.
Son,there's always hard choices in
life,sacrifices that need to be made.
I just want you to know Daddy made this one
out of the love I have for you and your mother.
You take care of her,kid.
You're the man of the house now.
There we go.Come on.
Aw,no dings or scratches.
Looks like Uncle Steve did a good job.
I had a job to do,I did it.That's all.
Oh,admit it.You had a little
bit of fun.I just saw you.
I-I definitely had a lot of fun.
Yeah,she's a great kid,Mary.
Aw,thank you.Well,next time I
need a sitter I'll call on you two.
Excuse me for a minute here,please.
Yes,we all contributed,but I was
primary on this one,I'd like to say.
Okay,tough guy.
Say goodbye to your uncles!
Where-where you going?
You don't...what?You don't
need to rush off,do you?
Just stick around for a bit.
Yeah,we just,uh,wrapped up this case.
We got nothing on the
board,so we could...
- go out and get a bite to eat?
- Right.
Got plenty of strained peas.
Sorry,but we have Bouncy Baby Story
Time at the library in ten minutes.
- So say,bye,Uncle Steve!
- Bye...
Bye,Uncle Danny!Bye,Uncle Chin!
All right.Thank you.Bye,guys.
- Okay.- See
you.- Bye.
- What?- You're such
a softy.- Nothing.
- You okay?
- Never better.
Got a location on Sato.
Full surveillance package...address,structural
blueprints,security system,
activity logs for his
staff...Everything's there.It's all good.
You,uh...do all that by yourself?
What,you trying to put us out of a job?
No,just helping out a friend.
- Okay.
- Oh,and,uh...Here.
Thanks for the loaner.
You know what?
- Why don't you keep it?
- What?
Go ahead.
You need a job.We need some help.
Yeah.Trust me,this,uh,animal,he
needs all the help that he can get.
Don't think about it.Just say yes.
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly
Presents
Okay.Yes.
Welcome to Five-O.
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET-静静的生活
Hawaii Five-0
2010 Season 04Episode 07