Air and naval forces of the United States
launched a series of strikes against terrorist facilities...
Pan Am Flight 103 crashed into the town of Lockerbie.
He has sanctioned acts of terror in Africa, Europe and the Middle East.
This will not stand, this aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
This relentless pursuit of terror. We will make no distinction...
The USS Cole was attacked while refueling in the port of Aden.
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable and cowardly act.
The next samba we're going to swing for you is one of the good old favorites.
...until something stops him.
It was right in front of my eyes, and I never saw it coming.
That plane crashed into the World Trade Center.
Thousands of people running.
We must and we will remain vigilant at home and abroad.
You're the smartest and the dumbest fucking person
I've ever known.
I'm not the one who got it wrong.
I'm the only one who got it right.
Take 'em. Take 'em all.
Previously on Homeland...
I got plans for you. What plans?
I'm gonna play you back into Iran.
From now on, you work for us.
The Senator's made some serious allegations.
That you had Majid Javadi in a safe house on American soil and let him go.
We debriefed him, turned him. He's ours.
I've made a decision to give the marriage another chance.
So I told him something before you left... about the Langley bomber.
You mean Brody.
No, that's just it. It's not him.
The bomber's the only way to prove that Brody's innocent.
Carrie, what the fuck are you doing?
Carrie, turn around now.
This is your last warning.
Got a gunshot wound to the upper left bicep.
significant bleeding. Might have clipped an artery.
Where the fuck is Saul?
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
国土 第三季第9集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
时间轴：RoyJames
You're awake.
Where am I? The Naval hospital.
They brought you here after you were shot.
Careful, you don't want to rip the sutures. Quite a few of them.
It was a through and through. Missed the bone.
Some muscle and tissue damage but no nerve involvement.
You're lucky.
No, he's just a great shot.
How long will I be in here? As long as you need to be.
For me to heal or for the CIA to figure out what to do with me?
You'd have to talk to them.
Are you aware you're 13 weeks pregnant?
Yes.
The baby should be fine. In case you're wondering.
Pupils reactive to light.
BP of 60 over 40. Too fucking low.
Lay down.
He started going cold turkey on the flight,
so they knocked him out - with a half pint of vodka. - Idiots.
Pulse is thready.
Take it easy.
Where's my stuff, you fucking thieves?!
Fuck! Where is my stuff?! Calm down, goddamn it!
Where's my stuff?
Don't move now.
You've got seven days till Lockhart's confirmed.
You think this guy's gonna be ready by then?
He's not what we expected...
but he's what we've got. If he agrees to do it.
He's a mess...
anemic...
severely dehydrated, probably hep C.
HIV isn't a stretch.
If you're suggesting a hospital, it's out of the question.
I'm pretty sure I can keep him stable, but the guy's a junkie, sir.
How far is he into withdrawal? Hardly started.
What he's feeling now, it's gonna get a hell of a lot worse.
Methadone would make it easier. Has to be cold turkey.
Where he's going, we need him functional.
Even if it kills him? It won't.
'Cause you will keep him alive. Do you understand?
Sir.
You all right?
Whoa, whoa!
Stop! What are you doing?
I need it! There's nothing there for you.
- No, I need it now! - No.
Give it to me, give it to me, give me...
Hey, grab him!
Where's the needle? Got it.
Cover him up. Stay down.
Please...
How are you feeling?
The doctor says you're progressing nicely.
You'll be up and walking in no time.
Though, not necessarily out of here.
There are two armed guards outside your door.
You know it never ceases to amaze me how you people close ranks.
Here you are,
a casualty of some CIA op gone very, very wrong,
basically a prisoner, and still, somehow, I'm the enemy.
You are aware that the CIA charter does not include
operations on US soil?
You know, I'm on painkillers.
I can barely understand anything you're saying.
Well...
I've been going through your file.
The fact is,
you need someone you can trust.
And why is that?
You're lying there shot and you need to ask?
The man who did this to you,
he's on his way out.
But I need to know...
what's he up to?
Ask him.
What was he doing in Caracas?
You didn't even know he was there, did you?
I got another message from Carrie.
Is she calming down at all? No, the opposite.
Senator Lockhart just paid her a visit.
Somehow, he knows about Caracas.
It's impossible. Well, he does.
You think he suspects? I'm sure he doesn't have a clue.
She does now.
So what do we do about that? Same as before;
keep her under guard at the hospital.
Away from Brody. And Lockhart?
I don't know how the hell he found out.
No one knew besides us.
Have our houses and offices swept.
Every room, top to bottom.
What happened? Shat himself.
Jesus Christ.
Who are you?
Don't talk.
You're soldiers, aren't you? Don't talk.
It's burning! It's burning.
It's not hot.
It's burning!
It'll continue as bad as this, or worse, another three days.
And at least a week after that before the stuff's out of his system.
So you're saying ten days. We have six.
Plus, at the end of all this, he's gonna be weak as a fuckin' kitten.
There is another option.
What?
Ibogaine.
It's a drug based on a Nigerian plant.
It dramatically accelerates the withdrawal process and kills the addiction.
The side effects are brutal, which is why it's outlawed here.
Nausea, vomiting, some hallucinations.
Violent, mind-bending hallucinations.
Does it work?
It does.
Take my word.
Say something, you motherfucker.
Don't just stand there.
Say something...
Of United States Marine.
God...
Get out.
Get out!
What the fuck did you give me?!
No...
Give me that! Get off me!
Get off!
Get off of me! Get off!
Get off me, no!
He'll sleep now.
For a while.
Maybe we should just call Saul's landline, trigger the voice activation,
double-check our tracking program. We could.
But...?
This house is leased to a shipping consortium out of Tel Aviv.
- It's got Mossad written all over it. - Yeah,
but what if it's just a monitoring station, or a dead drop?
Then we're wasting our fucking time.
Are you gettin' this?
You're alive.
That wasn't a given.
Want some water?
Why couldn't you have just left me there to die?
I think you know that wasn't really an option.
So...
what now?
That'll be up to you.
A trial?
'Cause I didn't do it.
You talking about bombing the CIA?
I'm inclined to agree.
But your transgressions don't begin or end there.
And I'm not about to engage in a back and forth where you somehow end up the victim.
We both know what you've done.
We both know what you are.
A man who's dug himself into a hole so deep,
common sense'd tell you there's no way out.
I am telling you, though, that there might be.
How?
I'm offering you a chance to be a Marine again.
The man you were...
before they broke you.
Please.
No more.
I'm done.
You are not.
You will do this one last thing.
No.
So kill me. Kill me now.
You want to die, huh?
We'll see about that.
Put him overboard.
Fuck this shit. I'm going in.
Don't. He'll come up.
I don't believe this.
Fuck it. Let's go.
Pull him...
He went down like a stone.
No attempt to save himself whatsoever.
Now he's refusing to eat. Make him.
How do you expect us to do that? It's called force-feeding.
All due respect, sir, the guy's a waste of space.
Now, I suggest whatever you've got in mind for him, just push it six months.
Let us do this thing right.
You done letting us in on your thought process?
Yes, sir.
Get him to eat.
He's right, you know. Our window's closing fast.
It's now or never, Saul.
How you feeling? As if you actually cared.
You know, I've had time to think here.
And I keep coming back to the fact that this bullet in my shoulder
would never have happened without your okay.
You were about to compromise the mission.
I was about to clear Brody. You said you were behind that.
"Clear Brody. " What does that even mean?
So you lied to me.
I don't think you want to go there-
who lied to whom.
Brody slipping out of the country while you were unconscious for 14 hours.
You think I believed that for a second?
You know I was in Caracas, you left me a message.
Don't you want to know how he is?
How is he?
He's not well.
What did you do to him?
You know, the assumptions behind that question are so misguided, it frightens me.
I found him in a bad way.
Believe me.
It wasn't something I wanted.
Where is he?
In Virginia.
At Dam Neck.
Got a special ops team trying to get him in shape.
In shape for what? That's what I wanted to talk about.
I have a play.
It involves Brody.
And I'm hoping you'll convince him it's in everyone's interest.
You told me Javadi was the play. He is.
Brody's the next phase.
And you need me why?
I'm assuming he already turned you down. We didn't get that far.
Like I said, he's not well.
So, what is it? What's your big idea?
Darnish Akbari.
Head of Iran's Revolutionary Guard.
Right.
Javadi's boss.
And the single greatest impediment to peace.
I want him gone.
Well, good luck with that.
Brody can get to him.
How?
As the Langley bomber.
Brody seeks political asylum there.
Gets an audience with Akbari, takes him out.
Javadi's the heir apparent.
He ascends the throne, and he goes from being
one of the 20 most important people in Iran to one of three.
Only he's working for us.
Brody takes him out?
Yes. Come on, Saul, you're reaching.
Akbari's better protected than the Ayatollah.
Brody's got a knack for getting into tight places.
He's done it before. At best it's a suicide mission.
No, he'll have a team on the ground.
And you expect me to convince him of this?
I expect you to consider deeply the upside of placing a US asset at the very top of the Iranian food chain.
That's what I expect.
Javadi won't be just an intelligence source.
He'll be in control of the entire Iranian security apparatus.
That doesn't mean he'll roll over and play dead.
I know.
But he can do something.
Something to break the long jump.
Something besides another war.
Something that'll change the facts on the ground...
just enough...
so two countries that haven't been able to communicate
for over 30 years except through terrorist actions and threats...
can sit down and talk.
That's the play, Carrie.
Tell me it's not worth your time.
Brody, I want you to know that I didn't know you were here until today.
I came as soon as I heard.
Tell me if there's anything I can do for you.
Anything.
When do you need him ready by?
27th of this month.
Why so soon?
It's the day Senator Lockhart's confirmation hearings begin.
Right.
Tell me what happened to him in Caracas.
A world of shit as far as we know.
He was gut-shot at the Colombian border.
Nearly died.
Got hooked on the painkillers, I guess.
There was also an incident at a mosque.
An imam and his wife were murdered.
Because of him?
Because of him.
I need a vehicle.
What happened to your arm? Hang gliding accident.
For real? Fucking CIA, Baraz.
What are you asking her questions for? Just making conversation.
It's the next left.
What now?
Now we wait.
We sat on the house for 24 hours.
And this is the only person who ever came in or out.
Oh, Christ.
You know him?
Yeah, I'm afraid so. Who is he?
A friend of my wife's.
His name is Alain Bernard.
She met him in Mumbai.
They struck up a relationship there, which may or may not be ongoing.
I hate to ask this, Saul, but do you think Mira's aware?
That he's an Israeli intelligence officer?
No.
Falling for the guy is her only crime.
What do you want me to do? For the time being?
Pick him up.
Put him in a dark fucking hole.
What about Lockhart? How does he fit into the equation?
I think I buried a lead. Meaning what?
After our guy left the safe house, I followed him to Pete's Diner,
Capitol Hill.
Dana?
Dan...
Hey, assholes, let me out! Brody...
Get off me! Oh... God...
- Let me the hell out! - Relax!
Brody! Motherfucker!
Dana, it's me! Dana!
- Get back... - Get off of me...
Dana!
Fuck. Dana!
She can't hear you, Brody.
You... you bitch.
You fucking bitch.
Is he in? Is he expecting you? Sir, you can't go in there.
I'm hosting a fund-raiser that night anyway.
Listen, I got to go. What the hell, Saul?
What is this? Open it.
Care to explain?
Alain Bernard is writing a profile on me for Le Monde.
20 minutes ago, Alain Bernard admitted to being an asset of Israeli intelligence.
And I should be concerned about this... why?
Because he claims he passed you information obtained
from a listening device planted in my home.
That's preposterous. Is it?
One call to Ambassador Benayoun, it would be an international incident.
A second call to The Post,
and your picture'd be on the front page of every newspaper in the country.
What do you want?
Time.
Time?
Postpone your confirmation until the middle of next month,
and these'll never see the light of day.
I don't understand.
It's a simple request. Give me a few more weeks.
That's not what I meant.
You could destroy me with this.
You could guarantee your own tenure as director.
Why are you letting me off the hook?
Because it would humiliate my wife, Senator.
And because it would damage the Agency.
Badly.
We have a deal?
We do.
I was hoping you've calmed down enough to talk.
What's Dana doing cleaning motel rooms - in the middle of nowhere? - Why?
Is something wrong with that?
- Being a maid? - There's nothing wrong with that, goddamn it-
I just want to know what's going on with my daughter!
Drink it, and I'll tell you about Dana.
Slowly, or you'll be sick.
There.
Now, what's going on? Well, she's had a rough time, Brody.
She dropped out of school.
She moved out of the house.
She changed her last name.
Take me back to the motel. That's not gonna happen.
For Christ's sake, Carrie. I told you.
if you want to see her again you have to...
Quit your fucking games, Carrie! I need to look her in the eye.
I want her to know I'm innocent!
If you keep yelling, this conversation is over.
Now I would like to tell these two men to leave, can I do that?
What do you want?
The same thing as Saul Berenson, I'm guessing.
Some bullshit about me being a Marine again?
What do you want, Brody?
What have you always wanted?
A chance at redemption.
For the last time, Carrie. I didn't do the bombing.
You of all people should know that. I'm not talking about the bombing.
I'm talking about the suicide vest.
I'm talking about the death of Elizabeth Gaines
and those two Secret Service agents outside the State Department.
I'm talking about what happened to that imam and his wife in Caracas.
Do what Saul is asking.
- What you're asking? - All right, what I'm asking.
If not for your sake, then for Dana's.
Otherwise, telling her you're innocent is just...
is just one more lie.
Look at me, Carrie.
You couldn't send me out for a pack of cigarettes right now.
We'll get you ready.
You just have to be willing.
Well, look who's come out to play.
About fucking time. Did you get Mommy's permission?
Hey, shut the fuck up, everybody.
We're going this way.
You ready?
Come on. On your feet.
No. He needs to do it by himself.
Tell me when you're good to go again. Now.
Go.
Sixteen Days Later
Find Maputo, Mozambique.
What's the frequency?
KHZ 3265.
What language are they speaking?
Portuguese.
Bottom three cards? Eight of clubs.
Ten of hearts.
Jack of spades?
Spell her last name.
Uh, B-A-C-Z-
E- W-S-K-I. Baczewski.
It says here she's hotter than what?
- Georgia asphalt? - And who said that?
Lula Fortune to Sailor Ripley in Wild at Heart.
Fucking-A right.
Yeah.
So, you guys got something going on?
No. Come on, man,
I've seen the way she's checking you out when you're not looking.
There's nothing.
Seriously?
Seriously.
So, you don't mind if I... if I hit that shit then, right?
See? There is something.
I knew it.
No, go ahead. Really.
Nah, man, I'm just fucking with you.
I'm married.
And, uh, we just had our first kid.
It's a boy. Name's Devon.
How come I didn't know that?
Just...
I don't like talking about my family.
Superstitious.
Hey, we're on in five. In the briefing room.
Iranian patrols in the area are intermittent.
But they are well-trained and equipped.
Also, there is also an IRIAF base
in Bijar, 70 miles away,
which means they can call in air support.
What kind of planes are we talking?
Uh, some French-built F-1 Mirages impounded from Iraq after the First Gulf War
and six Chinese SU-24s.
Excuse me, can we back up a minute? Sure.
The guys gets me to the border... where I surrender myself?
Correct.
We chose Marivan because several Al-Qaeda commanders also asked for political asylum there.
What happens then? I get flown to Tehran?
After a period of vetting, yeah, that's our expectation.
Okay, but what makes you think I'll ever get close enough to General Akbari to take him out?
You'll be treated as a hero of the Revolution.
The senior members of the regime, like the general,
want to take advantage of your propaganda value.
Plus Javadi's on the ground to facilitate a meeting between the two of you.
But if we don't know where or when the assassination goes down...?
You're concerned about our extraction plan. How we're gonna get you out of there once it's done?
Yeah.
I was just getting to that.
Once you're inserted at the border,
four members of your team will continue south to Nodesheh,
where they cross the mountains and make their way overland to Lavasan,
a small city just outside Tehran.
Opposition groups there have provided us with a safe house.
We've already gone ahead
and put in secure Satcom.
Our code there is...
Since when do you smoke? I don't.
I'm not.
It just looks like I'm smoking.
There. It never happened. You saw nothing.
Nothing.
Look... I did what you asked.
I'm doing what you want.
Now you told me you'd take me to see Dana again.
I meant after you get back. Come on, Carrie.
We both know that's a long shot.
We made it this far.
That's true.
I admit, I had my doubts.
Is that why you've kept your distance?
Hey, it's fine. You're entitled.
You're loading out in six hours.
I'm not sure I can get you off the base and back in time.
Well, I'm not leaving until I see Dana again.
It's there. 119.
Brody, there's something you need to know.
Before she changed her name, before she left home...
Dana was hospitalized.
About two weeks after the bombing...
she tried to kill herself.
Who is it?
Dana, it's me.
It's your dad.
How did you find me?
Carrie.
Can I come in?
Dana, please?
Thank you.
I had to see you.
Okay.
You have.
Oh, my baby, I'm so sorry.
Don't be.
How are you now?
Why are you here?
I just wanted to tell you that all those things those people said I did, I didn't do.
Fine. Fine, good.
I didn't kill all those people.
It wasn't me.
I didn't do it.
And I have to leave soon. In a few hours.
But I just wanted to see you before I go.
You did.
Did you ever, for one second,
think about if I wanted to see you?
What... what do you want to hear?
That you were a good dad?
That despite everything, it's all okay?
What do you want me to say?
Look...
look, here... here, just write it down.
Really, just write it down and I will say it to you...
as long as you promise I will never have to see you again.
Either of you.
I will come back from Tehran.
I know you will.
And not just for her.
Where the fuck were you? He wanted to talk.
He's got 45 minutes to load out. He's all set.
You took him off base. He threatened to pull out, Saul.
Anything could've happened out there. But it didn't.
I am truly at a fuckin' loss with you.
Have a little faith, Saul.
Two weeks ago, there was no operation. Now there is, because of me.
I really need you to get that.
Because in order for us to pull this thing off,
we're gonna have to find a way to trust each other again.
Or at least come up with a really great plan for faking it.
Brody...
See you on the other side.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入
All he has to do tonight is walk across the border and ask for asylum.
And in the unlike event that anything goes wrong? We have it covered.