Previously on Hostages...
My name is Agent Hoffman. I'm with the Secret Service.
I think someone is threatening your family.
This is Vanessa Moore. My sister.
Vanessa, have you met Colonel Blair?
Not in person, but I read about your appointment to the NSA.
I loved your brother very much. He would have been President someday.
He would have been President now.
Our mutual friend is here.
I wanted to keep her in the loop.
Hello, Quentin.
This is a conspiracy that goes way beyond Duncan.
What makes you believe him?
Open your eyes, Brian, the FBI, the Secret Service this is bigger than any one man.
We need to know exactly when Kincaid plans to go public, and that is on you.
And what if that's before the scheduled surgery?
Well, we re-evaluate where we stand with everything.
I say we start with his family.
- He warned you to stay away from his daughter. - That's why I'm going after his wife.
Your wife is a very sick woman.
I took the safety valve off.
I can dump 20 cc of morphine into her before you take another step.
- She's innocent. - So is my family.
Ellen, I know you're upset, that you want answers.
- Why are you doing this? - The reason doesn't matter.
- It does to me. - Put down the morphine.
Please.
You don't want to kill an innocent woman.
Like Angela?
- Like the President? - He's not innocent.
You get to decide who's innocent and who's guilty. Who gets to live.
Who are you? God?
Excuse me? What are you doing?
- Why are you touching her IV? - Henry, it's okay, I uh...
I ran into Dr. Sanders in the hallway, and asked her to check on the drip.
Nina was complaining of pain earlier in the evening.
- Is there a problem with her drip line? - No.
It's all working fine now.
You said the President is not innocent, what did you mean?
We can discuss that later.
Right now, you need to get home to your daughter.
- Why? - Morgan's boyfriend came by the house.
He brought a gun.
Oh, my God.
What are you talking about? Why would you think my family is being threatened?
Let's just say your wife is the common denominator
in a series of coincidences that all connect to the President.
What are you suggesting?
Your wife is a respected doctor.
An exemplary citizen.
And she has no reason to assassinate the President, unless she's being coerced.
No one else knows that you're here.
So this is your chance to speak openly.
I...
I don't know what you're talking about.
Everything's fine. Nobody's threatening us.
Okay. Sorry to have taken up your time, Mr. Sanders.
You can go.
Thank you.
Boyd loved me.
I know.
I know, sweetheart. I am so sorry.
- You did this. - No.
He protected me.
You okay?
Yeah.
The vest stops the bullet, but it still hurts like a son of a bitch.
But I've been through worse.
You could have been killed.
Secret Service Headquarters
You need to start collecting stamps or something.
I thought the interview with the husband was a bust last night.
I'm not looking at Dr. Sanders right now, but I am looking at the hospital.
You have to ask yourself, "Why would the White House
"pick Maryland College Hospital?"
There was a rigorous selection process. We looked into all this.
I started over last night.
- I think somebody might have rigged the game. - What are you talking about?
"Maryland College Hospital incident report.
"Filed September 4th with the joint commissioner. "
Hospitals file these things annually. They report fatalities, injuries.
Now this one, the White House copy, shows 245 negative incidents.
The Maryland College Hospital copy shows 479.
Why would someone change the number?
To make sure the President wound up at this particular hospital.
I have a Bill Jones on the line. He says it's urgent.
- Hello. - We need to talk. Now.
I'll call you back.
You have to be kidding me. He's cross-referencing hospital filings?
Like I said, he's thorough.
He thinks someone on the inside influenced the decision to use Dr. Sanders.
- Did he mention my name? - Not yet, but it's only a matter of time.
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
人质 第一季第9集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
时间轴：奶酪站住
So, what, Hoffman just brought you into his office to ask questions?
He wanted to know if anyone was threatening us.
He's a smart guy. Pretty much figured out what's going on.
- What did you say? - I said everything is great.
Did he believe you?
I think so, but...
- He's relentless. - Maybe it's a good thing.
We've been through this.
If we talk to any kind of law enforcement, it's basically suicide.
Look, I know what we agreed to but maybe we're wrong.
Maybe it's smarter to bet on Hoffman to get us out of this.
I'd rather bet on myself.
Ellen. We need to talk.
I just got word, you'll be using the OR on the fourth floor.
Fourth? My surgeries are always on the fifth.
Not this one. Rules have changed.
You need to deposit this in the scrub room on the fourth floor, locker 715.
By 11:30.
After that, the fourth floor will be on lockdown.
Full body searches.
An associate will make sure it's not discovered.
Locker 715, fourth floor.
11:30.
TEXT MESSAGE
From Washington DC:
Park. 10 minutes.
Hoffman. He's obsessed.
He's been sleeping in the office.
Analyzing documents, statistics.
How close is he?
Close enough that he needs to go.
Go?
That's what I've been told.
- You think that's the right move? - Doesn't matter what I think.
6 Months Ago
Carlisle?
I think we have a mutual friend.
- Oh, yeah? Who's that? - The guy who plays tennis.
Once the President flatlines, we're going to need five minutes alone.
- For what? - Not your concern.
Five minutes is a long time.
Our friend said you could make it happen.
I'll work on it. Is this going to be an issue?
- Yes or no? - No.
It's not easy to take out a Secret Service agent.
We'll need your help with this.
Is there going to be a problem with that?
No.
- Hey! - Hey, how are you?
Good.
But things are crazy at home with college applications.
Where's Morgan applying?
Columbia and Dartmouth are her favorites, so...
- We'll see. - Oh, she was always so smart.
How's she doing these days? I bet she's absolutely beautiful.
She is terrific.
Listen, I gotta run, huh?
- Good to see you. - Good to see you, hon.
How you holding up?
Okay.
Look, I'm sorry I got you into this.
No. You didn't. I asked to be a part of it.
I'd just never thought it would get to this. The nurse.
The limo driver.
Now that kid, Boyd.
- Let's just hope it ends there. - It won't.
They're gonna take out Hoffman.
Well, if that's what they want.
There's nothing we can do about it.
Unless I can convince him to drop the case.
We're not criminals.
I've been chasing a few leads, but I haven't found anything interesting.
Not yet, but I'll keep digging.
Good, because the answer's out there somewhere.
We just need to find it.
You disagree?
In my experience, when I have to work too hard to find an answer,
there isn't one.
Maybe the reason we can't crack this case is because there's nothing to crack.
What if Angela really did commit suicide?
She was depressed, she jumped off the bridge into the Chesapeake,
- and her body washed out to sea. - So, you think I've lost my mind?
I think certain people never know when to give up.
You're probably right. I can be stubborn. But not on this one.
I have a new lead and it points to someone in the White House.
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah.
Excuse me.
(Incoming
Laura)
Hello, sweetheart. Hey, listen, I can't talk right now.
Great. I'll see you when I get home.
Yeah, I love you.
My wife.
She gets nervous whenever we don't touch base a few times a day.
- How's she doing? - Not too good.
Can't really blame her.
It was him or you.
You did the right thing.
What else is going on?
That guy still after you for the money?
- You want some help with him? - Thanks, but I'm good for now.
I paid off a large chunk of my debt.
Kramer hooked me up.
Really? Tell me more.
I'd rather not.
Well, now I'm really intrigued.
Sandrine, come with me, we need to run an errand for Duncan.
You stay here and keep an eye on Brian and the kids.
Oh, you giving orders now, huh?
I'm passing them along.
It's some type of poison. A patient ingested it.
She presented with nausea, vomiting... I just need you to analyze it for me.
- Sure, I'll get right on it. - Great.
What's up, little man?
I heard you met up with Kramer and his father yesterday.
Uh, yeah.
I just want to say I think you did the right thing.
Kramer told me all about your conversation.
I just did what they asked.
I know.
That's why I stopped by.
- Say thanks. - Uh, yeah. No problem.
But, look, just so I'm straight.
Tell me your version of the story.
- What the hell you want? - Who the hell are you?
I'm looking for a friend.
- Your friend got a name? - Yeah.
Herman. Goes by Hip.
Found him.
I got a call that you'd be coming.
- What's your name? - My name doesn't matter.
You ready to talk business?
So, what's the deal with you and Archer?
Did we ever sleep together? Yes. Long time ago.
Are we sleeping together now? No.
That's her. That's the target.
Okay.
- Agent Hoffman. - Stan, it's Duncan Carlisle.
I just got a tip from an informant,
says she's got some information about Angela Nix.
I'm gonna meet her in 30 minutes on the corner of Anacostia and Third.
- A place called The New Dawn restaurant. - Okay, I'll meet you there.
We're all set. He'll be here soon.
He'll be at the location in 25 minutes.
You'll move on my signal. Understand?
It's all good.
Just make it look like a random shooting.
Good. Let me know the second it's done.
Your timing is impeccable.
I just spoke to our friend.
- Our problem's about to disappear. - Good.
Well?
That was our friend, the Chief of Staff.
Things are in motion.
Are you sure this is absolutely necessary?
The risk of not doing it outweighs the risk of doing it.
So, yes. It's necessary.
"We sleep safely at night because
"rough men stand ready to visit violence against those who would harm us. "
Patton. Churchill.
You know, you are going to make a great...
President, one day.
Target is in position.
Game time.
- Get ready. - Copy that, boss.
- Agent Carlisle. - I just got here.
I'm stuck in a little traffic, I'll be there in about five minutes.
Okay.
These guys know the target is a Fed?
They don't know. They wouldn't care anyway.
You sure it won't come back to us?
Positive.
It'll look like what it is. Hoffman was in the wrong place at the wrong time.
A victim of gang violence. His wife gets a pension.
- What the hell is he doing? - What's with this guy?
Call Hoffman. Keep him there.
- Hello? - Stan.
It's me. I'm pretty close.
Hey listen, no worries. I'm just enjoying the beautiful scenery here.
- I bet. - By the way, this informant...
- Is she credible? - Yeah, she's solid.
Oh, there you are. I see you up ahead.
Yo! Move out the way!
Incoming
Laura
- Hey, sweetheart, I can't talk right now. - I'm sorry, sir, there's been a car accident.
This phone was found next to the victim.
- What? - You need to come to the emergency room at GW Medical Center right away.
Yo! Move out of the way!
Are you deaf? Move out of the way!
Where the hell did he go?
Find him. Now.
No sign of him, man. He's gone.
Keep looking.
What the hell happened? Where did he go?
I don't know. Call him.
Maybe he just went around the corner to take a leak or something.
Maybe he's still close by.
Hoffman.
We missed our chance.
(From Hoffman:
Had to take off. Family emergency. Call you later.)
Now what?
Ah, Ellen, I was just about to come to your office.
I thought I'd save you a trip.
Did you get a chance to analyze that sample I gave you?
I, I did.
Tell me again. Where did you get this from?
The patient's father brought it to me. He was concerned.
- Thought it might be toxic. Why? - It's not poison.
It's dimethyl sulfoxide.
Dimethyl sulfoxide, isn't that a preservative?
It's a bone marrow preservative.
Mostly, it's for leukemia patients.
You would need to ingest an awful lot of this to cause a reaction.
Are you sure that this is what made your patient ill?
Uh, well, apparently not.
Well, thank you. This information is very helpful.
All right, gentlemen, let's get down to business.
Where are we on the exit plan for OTI?
If you are going to distance yourself from this program,
- you're gonna need a fall guy. - More than one.
We'll need some time to get our ducks in a row, sir.
This thing could blow up in our faces. The sooner, the better.
Excuse me a moment, Mr. President.
- I assume you're calling with good news? - You assume wrong.
- What happened? - It doesn't matter, we didn't get it done.
- What now? - Not sure.
I'll get back to you in a few hours.
Sorry, Mr. President.
My wife.
Sometimes she forgets that you're the leader of the free world.
That's all right. So does mine.
- Where you been? - Running an errand for Duncan.
What sort of errand?
I guess if Duncan wanted you to know he'd have told you.
I wasn't talking to you.
We were making a delivery. No big deal.
- Duncan didn't tell us what it was. - Relax, tough guy.
- We're on the same team, remember? - Then why are you so worried about where we were?
I just want to make sure my partners aren't out there doing anything stupid.
Like killing a limo driver.
- Why'd you drag him into this?-  I didn't.
- Sorry to keep you waiting. -No.
You remember Dr. Evans, my personal physician?
I'm told you want to do more blood work today.
Yes, I just want to make sure his blood clotting factors are back to normal.
Well, let's get this over with.
The surgery isn't for another six days.
Why not wait? Test it closer to the date?
Relax, Hank. Congress shoots arrows at me all day.
I think I can handle a little needle in the arm.
In light of what happened, I'll be at the President's side until the surgery's completed.
Happy to have you. This won't take a minute.
Mr. Creasy.
Agent Hoffman's office called again. They want to schedule an interview.
- Did he say what it was about? - Something to do with Dr. Sanders.
Schedule for tomorrow.
Also, Colonel Blair is looking for you.
- I'll help you. - Thank you, sir.
I'll take these.
I was going to take them to our lab at MCH.
The President's blood is always analyzed at the Naval hospital.
- Of course. - We'll send you the results.
Thank you.
I'll need the trash as well.
All traces of the President's DNA are safeguarded.
For national security reasons.
- You going somewhere? - I was looking for you earlier.
Really? Did you call?
Text? How exactly were you looking for me?
- Well, uh... - So.
What happened with our problem?
- It's under control.
- Does that mean it's been eliminated?
Not yet. But it will be.
- So, it's not under control. - It will be.
Soon.
You have my word.
Good.
Then I guess we have nothing to worry about.
You're going to the reception tonight, right?
- Yes. - Good.
Afterwards, I want you to come back to my house,
- I'm having a few people over. - Sounds good.
Three times in one day. You are getting to be a regular, Ellen.
Last request, I promise. Can I get a workup on this blood sample?
Is there enough in there?
Hmm. I'll see what I can do.
Great, well I'm going to take off for the night.
- Would you mind emailing me the results? - Sure. I still have your email.
Actually, the old one got hacked, long story.
Could you just send it to this one?
- Will do. - Thank you.
- Everything okay with your family? - Oh, yeah, yeah.
My wife's phone was stolen and it was found at the scene of an accident.
- But she's fine. - Hmm.
Glad to hear that.
The informant we were supposed to meet in Southeast turned out to be full of crap.
Just an ex-girlfriend looking to settle a score.
So, I guess we're back to square one.
- I'll let you get that. - All right.
Yes?
Where do you want to meet?
I'm glad you came, Agent Hoffman.
I have quite a story for you.
Mr. Creasy.
Quite the surprise.
- Lift up your shirt. - Excuse me?
This is 100% off the record.
I don't want any wires or recording devices.
Pockets.
The President's going to be assassinated.
Everything is in place. The wheels are already in motion.
How do you know?
Because I'm involved.
I can get you all the details. But I want a deal.
You want a deal for committing treason?
I'm saving the President's life.
Without me, Paul Kincaid is a dead man.
I want full immunity from Federal and State prosecution.
And $5,000,000 cash.
Cash?
I'll need to disappear.
I think the witness protection program will be a more viable...
Not for me.
The people behind this are extremely powerful.
If I don't hear from you in five hours, I'll be on a plane.
And you and your colleagues will be running around like Chihuahuas
trying to figure out who just killed the President of the United States.
- Let me talk to a Federal prosecutor... - No.
Go straight to the Attorney General.
He's the only one who can make this deal. And he's the only one I trust.
- xxx great. - Good evening.
Good to see you, Quentin.
Colonel.
You missed the Dutch Ambassador's opening remarks.
Shame.
Well, why do you think I came late?
You shouldn't look so serious, Quentin.
Everything's going to be fine.
- Oh, I'm not worried. - Good.
Drink up. Enjoy.
See you later tonight.
So, you got this guy Kramer wrapped around your finger.
He's a good guy, relax.
You think it's really smart getting involved with him?
Right now?
Smart? No.
But since when is that the criteria?
Well, you're a big girl. You can do what you want.
- As long as I'm not on the wrong end of it. - What are you talking about?
In spite of what your boyfriend says, this limo driver thing...
- It isn't over. - Not your problem.
Sure it is. 'Cause if they go for him, or you,
that puts all of us at risk.
Just like the missing nurse.
Difference is, I know how to keep my mouth shut.
Are you saying you don't trust me?
When it comes to cutting a deal on a murder rap,
I don't trust my own mother.
And I love that lady to death.
No, thank you.
I always love these cocktail receptions, all the scintillating chit chat and the rumors.
You know me.
The more vapid the conversation, the more I enjoy it.
Don't go. Not yet.
There's something I want to say to you.
- Pardon me? - I've always liked you.
Despite our issues.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
You read the Bible, Quentin?
You know, Moses.
He led his people all the way to the promised land,
but he never set foot in it.
Sorry. I'm not a religious man.
We will succeed.
In the end.
Like I said, Quentin.
I'm sorry.
Is he okay? What happened?
Quentin, are you all right? He's not breathing!
Call a doctor.
There's been an accident.
The Chief of Staff has suffered a heart attack.
I'm sorry to hear that.
You wanted to see me?
Yeah. I need you to drive me to the Attorney General's office right away.
What's this all about? I need to deliver these files in person.
I also need somebody to watch my back.
- I'll explain more on the way. - Fair enough.
- Why are we stopping? - I think we have a flat tire.
You need a hand?
Requesting Physician: ELLEN SANDERS
BLOOD TYPE: AB-
HLA/HUMAN LEUKOCYTE ANTIGEN (799)
GENERAL MHC CLASS 1:A*01 B*1
MHC CLASS 2:              A*02 B*3
MARKERS: C (0023-LU84)
BETH ZION HOSPITAL
NINA CARLISLE BLOOD WORK UP
Requesting Physician: DR. HENRY KAGEN
Requisition: 17-28937002
BLOOD TYPE : AB-
HLA/HUMAN LEUKOCYTE ANTIGEN (799)
I ran a test on the President's blood.
He and your wife both share the same,
very rare,
blood type.
His bone marrow is the perfect match for her.
I'm aware of that.
She's the President's daughter, isn't she?
Yes.
Why don't you just ask him for the bone marrow,
- why do you have to kill him? - Because he doesn't know she's alive.
If he did...
he'd kill her.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入