-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
You are being watched.
The government has a secret system-
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror, but it sees everything...
Violent crimes involving ordinary people.
The government considers these people irrelevant.
We don't.
Hunted by the authorities, we work in secret.
You will never find us.
But victim or perpetrator,
if your number's up, we'll find you.
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
疑犯追踪 第三季第9集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
时间轴：二狗以后不要做HR[大哭]
We know about Quinn and what he did to Cal.
Then you know why he can't get away with it.
Where are we taking him? Fed building downtown.
The FBI may be the only ones we can trust.
The judge has been asking to see you.
Do we have a problem, Your Honor?
Do you consider a felony murder charge a problem?
Because if that bitch cop and her gun-wielding cohort
get Alonzo Quinn into federal custody, that's what we'll all be facing.
No one is gonna be charged.
We have checkpoints on all the roads. They'll never make it downtown.
Carter said she had evidence on HR, pictures, recordings.
She has me on tape working with you people. We have a team tossing her place.
No one is gonna kill her until we get that evidence.
We need to come up with a story.
Do you have a firearm in the house?
In that far drawer.
Fine, what's the story?
Robbers broke into your home, they looted the place,
and shot you.
Old man would've talked.
He's got state's evidence written all over him. Get rid of this.
Bring me Officer Carter and Alonzo Quinn alive.
And if Quinn gets so much as a hangnail,
I will come after you. Do you understand?
What about our pal in the suit?
I should've ended him a long time ago.
Tell our friends, shoot to kill.
- Shadow. - Victor.
- Bravo. - Time.
- November. - Whiskey.
- Flight. - Uniform.
- X-ray. - Close.
- Delta. - Foxtrot.
Know what happens if you try anything?
I believe I can fill in the blanks.
We're not stopping until we get you to the fed building downtown.
So don't die on us, you hear?
You keep forgetting, this is my city.
There's just two of you.
we won't be outmatched for long.
Finch is sending the cavalry.
Wouldn't kill you to clean up every once in a while.
Why? I got you as a maid.
Oh, yeah? Well, the maid's gotta go to work.
Mrs. Olson is gonna drop in and make sure you're okay.
Nice necklace, dad.
It's a key, smart guy.
Friend of mine's got some information on some very bad guys, and I'm keeping it safe.
Sure that's a good idea, trusting you with it?
Turns out your old man's a pretty tough guy.
The bad guys, they don't want no part of this.
So how 'bout you mind your own business and get some shut-eye?
Good night, buddy.
What kind of cop doesn't use a vertical dead bolt?
What the hell? Where'd you come from? It doesn't matter.
It's where we're going that's important. Grab your gun, Lionel.
Let me guess, Mr. Congeniality's in some kind of trouble.
You could say that. Reese and Carter nabbed the head of HR.
They need a little help escorting him into FBI custody.
You ready?
I don't care who you are, you break in my house again, you're gonna be sorry.
I'm already sorry, I'm gonna have to listen to your whiny ass all the way into Queens.
Me? You know the dog's the only one that likes you, right?
Attention, all passengers.
Please report any bags left unattended.
I'm sorry I got you into this.
You get us into Manhattan, I'll take Quinn to the fed building alone.
What is it about you, Joss,
makes you want to do everything on your own?
What is it about you, John, that makes you want to save everybody else's life but your own?
Mr. Reese? Excuse me.
I have some very bad news.
Guessing this is about a number. Several, actually.
It took me a while to realize that they were all prior aliases for one person.
You, Mr. Reese.
Something wrong? No more than usual.
Check your phone.
HR has put a bounty on your head, and they're distributing this picture.
My old chess partner called to inform me his men will sit this one out.
That's nice of Elias.
Yes, but unfortunately, they're the only ones.
It appears that every criminal in New York
is trying to kill you.
Don't suppose they're just trying to be friendly.
That's a nice suit. Maybe we'll bury you in it.
Too bad. I just had it cleaned.
Something funny?
Subway, thugs.
Kind of reminds me of the first time we met.
Gotta transfer to the R train.
It'll drop us a couple blocks from Federal Plaza.
May I have your attention, please?
Due to an incident at the Lexington Avenue station,
all train service has been suspended to Manhattan. Guessing that's not just bad luck.
Our friends in blue aren't making it easy for us.
- Keep moving. - Or what?
You'll shoot me? That's exactly what I'll do.
I'm giving you a warning. That's more than you gave Cal.
Finch, I need an exit strategy.
- Finch, you there? - Looking for this?
You two still believe you're the heroes of this story?
My men will have every subway, train, and road from Queens blocked.
This ends one way, and it's not with you riding into the sunset.
Let's go. Your men are looking for three people.
We just need better camouflage.
Mr. Reese?
Can you hear me?
Ms. Shaw, I'm afraid I've lost contact with Mr. Reese.
Well, at the risk of stating the obvious, Finch,
you could just ask the machine for his location.
I don't speak to the machine, and the machine doesn't speak to me, Ms. Shaw.
Well, it speaks to her.
I might not know where our friends are, but I certainly know where they're headed.
26 Federal Plaza, to be exact.
Based on their last location, there are two direct routes
into Manhattan- the Long Island railroad and the BQE to Brooklyn Bridge.
HR will be patrolling both spots heavily.
So are you saying Fusco and I need to split up?
Is that glasses? Tell him this is the last time I chauffeur your ass.
Divide and conquer, I assume that's all right with you.
I thought you'd never ask.
Something's wrong with your attack dog.
He appears to be the smart one.
Why are you still awake?
Not bad dreams, I hope.
I heard it said once that a pregnant woman may see the face of her unborn child in her dreams.
I saw every digit,
every line of code
as I created it.
But you've changed that, haven't you?
You found a way to alter the DNA to rewrite the code.
Is that how you get it to speak to you?
You have the relationship with her that you wanted.
She respects that.
My relationship is more...
intimate.
Sorry I asked.
Why are you asking? What's gotten you so upset?
Is the big lug in trouble?
Has his number finally come up?
I don't really care for the man myself,
but he means a great deal to you.
So if you can see it fit
to set me free from this cage,
I'll return him to you, unharmed.
How could I ever let you go
when I know with an almost absolute certainty that bad things will happen?
Bad things will happen regardless.
The question is, are you gonna let them happen to your friend?
Come on, Harry.
Let's not pretend that John is your first helper monkey.
Exactly how many guys did you go through before him?
Pleasant dreams.
Thanks for giving us a lift.
Don't get too comfortable, we'll be at the fed building soon.
Petersen, surprised you dragged your ass out of bed.
I was told there was a chance to shoot people.
Imagine my disappointment, suit's a no-show. Probably laying low.
Doubt he's gonna stick his head out again.
Our pal stormed a judge's house.
Subtle he ain't.
He's hiding, all right, but you can bet it's in plain sight.
Fusco?
I haven't spotted our friends, but I'm not the only one looking.
Yeah, HR's got a checkpoint at the Brooklyn Bridge too.
No sign of our people.
Hope they find their way out of dodge.
Get us through,
you can go about your night. Got a bus coming.
Come on.
Hey! Hey, stop that ambulance! I'll take it from here.
Any luck finding our friends?
If you mean by "Luck," helping them escape an HR checkpoint
and bully their way into Manhattan, then yes.
Lionel?
Detective Fusco, are you all right?
Game over, Lionel.
What do you want to do with him, boss?
I got a few ideas.
Reese and Carter broke through HR's roadblock into Manhattan.
They're on their way to the fed building. I heard. Thanks to Detective Fusco.
Unfortunately, he wasn't so lucky.
I can find him, but it might not matter. Might be dead by now.
Remind me to hire an optimist next time.
Even an optimist can't be two places at once.
So what'll it be, Finch?
Detective Fusco is currently without any aid.
Reese and Carter will have to make do on their own.
Locate the Detective.
The hell am I? Someplace no one will hear you scream,
since you'll be doing a lot of that.
Meet your new best friends.
Petersen, right? Always remember a pretty face.
How about this? Look familiar?
You emptied my pockets.
Think there's some lint in there too.
You're a funny guy, Fusco.
Must have had your ex-partner in stitches.
When's the last time you saw Carter?
I don't know. Let me check my day planner.
We know you met with Carter tonight.
She handed you something, looked an awful lot like this.
What does it open?
See, Carter has information on our organization, hidden it somewhere.
From the size and shape of this key,
I'd say it opens up a safe deposit box.
It's my locker at the Y.
You're welcome to my dirty jock.
Hey, Fusco, want to know your fortune?
"You will be unusually successful at your career. "
You know, I don't think that one's true.
"A thrilling time is in your future. "
We're getting close now.
Oh, here we go.
"Tell your friends what they want to know,
or they will break you apart limb by limb. "
That's more like it.
So what's it gonna be, Fusco?
Courtesy of the driver.
He's gonna have one hell of a headache when he wakes up.
I did say I was sorry.
Fed building's just four blocks up.
Looks like we're late to our own party. We'll have to go in on foot.
- Let's go. - Come on.
Hey, hold up.
Come on, come on, come on. Move!
'Sup?
We gotta get off the streets now. In here.
Finch, could use a little help here.
Mr. Reese, where are you?
Not my final stop, I hope. City Morgue, downtown.
Go ahead, make yourself at home.
HR has gangs patrolling the street. Can you send Lionel to pick us up?
I'm afraid Detective Fusco has been apprehended by HR.
Chances are, they're planning to use him for leverage, or worse.
I've asked Ms. Shaw to locate him.
They got Fusco, didn't they?
Don't worry, Shaw will find him.
And if she doesn't?
Nope, no sign of our boy.
Oh, damn it.
Ow! No!
You know that's not real meat, right?
The hell- who are you?
Concerned citizen. Our police force
should really be filling up on something more...
substantial.
Now...
I want you to call your pal Simmons
and find out where he's keeping Detective Fusco.
I- um, I don't know what you're talking about.
Do it now, or I lose the pin to this grenade...
permanently.
You don't understand.
You might kill me,
but I cross Simmons,
he'll hunt down my wife,
my sister.
He won't stop until everybody I love is dead.
Please.
Wait, I need that pin!
Federal Plaza.
Four blocks and only 15 rounds of ammo between us.
And who knows how many guys HR has hiding in the shadows?
So we wait until sunup.
Less likely they'll risk taking a shot at us in broad daylight.
Still haven't learned yet, have you?
There's no place you can hide, no place my men won't f-
What was that? A sedative... I think.
Any ideas where to put him?
Let the man rest in peace.
See, I told you we'd have you screaming. Where is the safe deposit box?
Just tell him, get it over with.
That the best you got?
No.
You know us, Lionel. It's gonna get so much worse.
What are you gonna do, read some more fortune cookies?
Bore me to death?
See, that's the problem with you, Fusco.
You never listen. It's like talking to a child.
You have a kid, don't you?
What's the little guy's name? Lee.
I feel sorry for that kid, I do.
He's got defective genes, just like you.
You touch him, and I'll send you to hell.
Is that a promise? Huh?
Because when I make a promise, I keep it.
Where's the safe deposit box? Which bank?
Or I kill you and your kid.
You know what?
Put the kid out of his misery before he turns out like his old man.
Okay, okay, okay!
Bank's in Hoboken, Jefferson and 9th,
but it won't be open this time of night.
Oh, they'll be open for me.
Sit on the kid while I get a warrant, make sure he's telling the truth.
Keep an eye on Detective Fusco.
What do you got? I got a line on the man in the suit.
Thought he gave us the slip. Then we saw this.
He's holed up with the stiffs in the City Morgue.
Good, saves us the trip. Rally the troops.
Care package for the road?
15 rounds, bone saw, scalpel, and some assorted tools.
You do realize we gotta kill HR before we can autopsy them.
Apply the right amount of force, this can do some damage.
Hezbollah surgeon. 2 more inches to the left,
would've cut right through my axillary artery.
Fallujah.
300-pound gorilla of a Marine escorting me.
One minute, we're walking on patrol, and the next, I hear a click.
Land mine?
Guy looked right into my eyes, then he was dust.
Never saw it coming.
When your time is up, it's up.
That was a close call. Yeah.
Was that your closest?
13 stitches. How'd the other guy fare?
Touch and go for a while.
It was a C-section. Taylor was breech.
Doctors weren't sure if he was gonna make it or not,
had to rush me into surgery.
It was the worst moment of my life,
followed by the best.
What about you, John? What was your closest?
That's got somebody's name on it?
Mine.
There was a time I thought about saying good-bye.
Lost someone.
Lost myself.
What happened? What stopped you?
I got in a fight with some punks on a subway.
Cop detained me.
He brought me to you.
You changed my mind, Joss.
You changed me.
Mr. Reese, I have some alarming news.
I've been monitoring the police scanners.
Someone has reported suspicious activity at the morgue.
I suggest you leave by the southwest emergency exit.
Doesn't look like we're gonna be leaving anytime soon.
We're surrounded.
Next, they'll lock down the building,
seal us off from witnesses, everyone.
HR's moving in for the kill.
Here we go.
You three, flush 'em out. Hey, what's going on?
We got some reports, some vandals have broken in the back, sir.
Reports? From who? It's just me.
Cuff him.
Hey, you can't do that.
Make sure the rent-a-cop keeps his mouth shut,
and watch the front.
Think that'll hold 'em?
It's gonna have to.
Spread out. They're here somewhere.
Breakfast.
It's 4:00 in the morning.
I may not be back in time.
I may not be back at all.
I can't imagine what it must be like for you.
After all this time, to have to let go of your creation.
The machine is still sending us numbers, Ms. Groves.
I wasn't talking about the machine.
John. It's not too late.
I can help you stop whatever's about to happen.
Please let me help you.
Good-bye, Ms. Groves.
I understand.
I hope someday you'll trust me.
I'm so sorry for your loss, Harold.
Checked out the bank. Good news and bad news.
Bad news is Fusco lied. Good news is you get to kill him.
Sounds fun. What about the evidence?
We still have the key.
Only a matter of time before we find the right bank.
And the kid?
Look, I'll tell him where it's at, I swear.
Look who finally wants to talk.
You tell Fusco I made him a promise, and I keep my word.
Waste 'em both.
They're tossing rooms.
Won't be long until they find us.
Check the supply closet.
Might be some chemicals that'll come in handy.
John?
John! John! Don't do this!
I'm sorry, Joss, but I can't lose you. They'll kill you.
They'll try, I'm counting on it. Listen, I'm gonna draw them out.
You make a run for it with Quinn.
Anything happens to you,
I swear, I'll hate you forever.
You're stuck with me, remember?
You make sure Quinn gets what he deserves.
See you on the other side.
Hey, you got the kid?
Yeah, I got him.
His piece-of-garbage dad lied.
You know what to do.
I don't care what you do to me, just let my kid go.
Tell you what, I'll let you say your good-byes.
Put the kid on the line.
Let Fusco listen in while you do it.
Last words, make 'em count.
Dad?
Lee?
Lee... it's gonna be okay.
I'm right here with you, okay? I'm right here with you.
Just close your eyes, all right?
I love you. It's gonna be okay.
Lionel.
It is gonna be okay.
Lee is fine, but the guy they sent to kill him isn't doing so good.
Figured these scumbags would come after your kid.
Thank you, thank you.
But, Lionel,
you understand this means I can't be there for you.
I had to choose.
Figured you'd want me to come here instead.
Yeah, you did good. You did good.
I'm sorry, Lionel.
Looks like your fortune's run out.
Never did have very good luck.
Turns out neither did Officer Miller.
My friend killed him. My boy is fine.
Doesn't change your fate. I got a full mag.
The only question is where to shoot first? Ever kill someone, Petersen?
Not recently.
Can't take down a group of bent cops without having casualties.
Someone was always gonna end up in a casket.
Truth is, guys like you and me, we're all gonna catch a bullet sooner or later.
Best you can hope for is someone to hold your hand while you bleed out.
Oh, that's sweet. You want me to hold your hand, Fusco?
Oh, I forgot, we broke your fingers.
Yeah, you did.
Which made it no big deal for me to break my thumb.
Can I help you?
Officer Simmons said you might be in need of my assistance. Yeah? Who are you?
I'm the guy that's gonna catch you when you fall.
Sorry, I'm not very good at this.
I know they're here. Find 'em!
There he is! Shoot him!
Son of a bitch.
Come on, come on. Follow me, damn it.
Finch, I'm out of bullets and out of time. Make sure Carter gets to safety.
Will do, Mr. Reese.
Detective Carter, the area is clear.
You are free now to exit the building.
Hey, wake up. We're checking out.
Come on.
Hold it right there!
Do you have a weapon, sir? Are you armed? Mr. Reese, are you okay?
Yes, I am.
Got a tip that a man matching your description was brandishing a weapon.
I somehow managed to locate two of NYPD's honest cops.
You have the right to remain silent. Anything you say can be held against you.
Do you understand? I assumed you'd prefer incarceration to death.
I do, and thanks.
You'll never get a conviction, not in my city.
This used to be your city. Not anymore.
Officer Carter. This is Alonzo Quinn.
New York City's Police Department has been rocked this morning
with the arrest of Alonzo Quinn.
Alonzo Quinn has been booked on suspicion of being the ringleader of HR.
Police are still searching for Officer Patrick Simmons,
who they believe is Quinn's second-in-command.
Congratulations, Detective.
It is Detective again, isn't it? Can't say I miss the uniform.
It seems John Doe is being held at the Third Precinct.
My lawyers are trying to extricate him.
Let's just hope John can stay out of trouble for a long while.
Or has your computer told you otherwise?
What did you say?
How else could you know when someone's about to be in trouble?
I just figured you built some sort of supercomputer
that can siphon information from government feeds.
I'm impressed.
I am a Detective.
Speaking of which, duty calls.
I'll drop by the Third, make sure our friend gets released.
I'd appreciate that, Joss.
Shouldn't you be at work? Nice to talk to you too.
I'll be in later. Keep my seat warm.
And, uh, nice to have you back, partner.
Glad to be back. I'll see you soon.
Chip off the old block, huh? Looks like he's doing okay.
You, on the other hand, look like crap.
Heard you took a bullet.
Yeah, stupid bastard shot me where I had plenty of padding.
Would've gone for the head shot myself.
Course, you got plenty of padding there too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank you, truly.
Shut up and drive, Lionel.
I'm Carter. You didn't give us a name.
Seems like the only time you need a name now is when you're in trouble.
So...
am I in trouble?
Got your man locked up, Carter. Must feel good.
Not all of them.
Still haven't been able to locate our pal Simmons.
Can't hide forever. We'll get him.
All right, where's my weapon? John Doe didn't have a permit.
Your gun's property of the NYPD now.
Time I got some new hardware. Looks like your ride is here.
Guess we were all worried about you.
If my number was up,
I'm just glad I was with you.
No one I'd rather be with at the end.
Your time's up. Told you I'd end you.
No, not today!
Joss, Joss, I'm here.
It's okay.
I need- I need to see my boy.
I need to tell him- And you will, and you will.
Just stay with me.
Promise me you'll look in on him.
I won't have to 'cause you're gonna make it, okay?
Promise me you'll tell him.
He knows, Joss.
He knows.
John...
don't let this-
Joss-
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入