Previously on Revolution...
What the hell is happening to me?
I'll come quietly! Just leave her alone!
I'd like to pick your brain about the nanotech.
Aaron, it's only a matter of time - before Horn is onto you. - We gotta get you out of town.
Aaron!
Well, we have the doctor to thank for finding you.
Searching the boatyard was his idea.
Gene?
I know you all are in there. Get 'em out, Gene.
Let me stay behind.
We're working for the Patriots.
- So what now? - Kill them all for your mother.
You said your husband was Patriot High Command.
- What do you want? - Your wife...
is an enemy of the United States of America. You know how much trouble you're in now?
- I'm sorry. - Gotta be realistic.
Roger, no.
I have a tumor growing in my brain.
I need you.
Aaron! Maybe you can heal someone else.
Stop!
No!
I saw an access door on the roof when I was up there.
So we go in up top, fight our way down.
There's gotta be 20 men in that bunker, and that's if we get past the 20 outside.
Aaron and Cynthia are in there,
probably your grandfather too. What choice do we have?
Miles...
You okay?
- Ready? - Yeah.
Miles?
What is it?
What the hell?
Are they dead?
Out cold.
Well, front door works too, I guess.
What the hell happened?
Were they gassed?
You haven't seen my dad, have you?
No. He's not here.
Hey, Miles.
- Aaron was here. - How do you know?
I know the boots he wears.
His prints go that way.
So...
Aaron knocks out 40 guys...
gets up, just strolls out of here.
Seriously... what the hell's going on?
It's this way.
That's not ominous at all.
You think the Patriots made this?
Come on.
We're out of time, Rachel.
Wait, what about dad?
Now, let's go!
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
末日革命 第二季第9集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
时间轴：婷
I said I'd bring you on my security detail,
not your son.
Jason only wants what I want...
to be of service.
He's an escapee from a reeducation center.
We all have skeletons in our closet.
Don't we, sir?
I helped you with yours,
I expect you to help me with mine.
Smile, boy.
We're going to the White House.
Sir.
Best we can tell, Pittman just walked out
through the tunnels, took his girlfriend with him.
The amazing Aaron Pittman.
No end to the surprises with that one.
Where are we?
Outside the town walls.
My question is, what are the Patriots doing with a tunnel like that?
All right, I got the trail. It's this way.
This weather seem a touch unseasonal to you?
So...
Aaron houdinis himself out of the bunker,
now this?
More of your nano garbage, isn't it?
Rachel?
- I gotta go back. - What?
You and Charlie, go get Aaron.
- I've gotta go get my dad. - Then I'm coming with you.
Uh, listen, both of you!
They're gonna be looking for Aaron.
Which means we gotta find him first.
- Then we'll go after Gene. - Miles.
All this X-Files weirdness...
not my thing.
Totally out of my depth here.
I need your help. What if he's dead?
If he is...
he did it to save us...
so that we could save Aaron.
And I'm sorry.
See what I mean?
We don't have a choice.
Cynthia.
Oh, thank God.
You're okay.
Did I do that?
Hello?
What are you doing here?
I'm having a heart attack. That's what I'm doing here.
I live here.
Well, did you... see who brought us in here?
You did.
You walked in on your own. She was in your arms.
Don't you remember?
No.
Damn it.
I lost the trail.
All right, well, find it.
Yeah, you know what, Miles, if you can do a better job,
please, go for it.
Shot fired!
- Over there! - Come on.
Hold it right there! Freeze!
I'm Batman.
Come on. Go!
Where's your father?
He went up front to see why we're stopping.
Sir.
Is she gonna be okay?
I hope so.
Have I seen you around town?
No.
'Cause you look familiar to me.
Where are your parents?
Been looking for them.
Where are you from? Oklahoma.
Town called Spring City. Ever been?
- No. - You should go.
It's got the second biggest ball of twine in the world.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll do that.
Sir. Sir.
What?
I said maybe we should wait until the fog lifts,
until the scouts report in.
No.
Go get a horse, ride back to town.
Tell Truman to send everyone he's got.
I mean everyone.
I need to find Pittman now.
I'm out of time. Out of time?
Go.
What the hell happened, Bass?
Keep your voice down, they're right outside.
You were supposed to be looking after Aaron.
I did the best I could.
Well, your best sucks.
Now we gotta go find him. Actually, no, no.
You can take your fat friend, and these Patriots for that matter,
and you can shove 'em. I thought you wanted revenge.
What I want? The reason I saved you...
what I care about is my son, Miles.
You hid him from me.
Now you tell me where he is, and I'm out of here.
What?
Holy hell.
It's infected.
You think?
You're burning up, you moron. You need a doctor.
Doctor?
They've got Rachel's dad. Look.
I'm having a hard time swinging a sword.
- I need you. - No, you need help.
I gotta go find Aaron.
Look, Aaron... Aaron... he's nice and all.
But he's not worth dying over.
I disagree.
My God, you really have gone soft.
You're like a puppy holding a kitten.
Just help me, okay?
And I swear I'll tell you where your son is.
No, this is not my problem.
Yes, it is.
Because if you don't help me,
I will never help you find your kid.
Look, mom, we'll go get Aaron,
and then we'll get grandpa, okay?
He'll be all right.
Yeah.
I just... th... the way we left things,
what I almost did to him...
I need to see him. I gotta talk to him, I have to tell him.
You will.
I love you, Charlie.
We may die tomorrow.
We'll probably die today.
Just, uh...
I need you to know that I love you.
I love you too.
Well? What are we waiting for?
Let's go find "Stay Puft".
（six）
Miles!
That's it? No good-bye?
We can't keep doing this. He's my brother.
And Ben's...
smart.
And he's good, he's a good man.
Better for you.
So, uh...
You should go start a family.
You know, be happy.
Is that how you really feel?
Yeah.
Because all you have to do...
is tell me you love me.
And I will leave him,
and I will wait for you.
I don't love you.
I don't believe you.
I'm sorry, Rachel.
I gotta go.
Sir!
I found him.
Get the United States back on its feet again.
We're proud of this job that we're doing here. It's gonna happen soon.
Please will you excuse me for a moment?
Of course.
Seem a little quiet to you?
The Patriots are gone.
They must have found Aaron.
They went this way.
Cyn, hi.
We're gonna get out of here, okay?
No. Don't go. Not yet.
All right, well, come with us.
But we gotta get as far away from here as we can.
I need to talk to you. Kid, I am sorry.
I don't have time for a chat right now. Aaron, who are you talking to?
The kid.
What kid?
The one standing right there.
Aaron, there's nobody there.
We fixed her. We brought you back to life.
We just wanna talk.
- Aaron, stop! - We're leaving.
- You saw a kid? - I didn't see anything.
Aaron, tell me!
I saw a boy.
And he said he brought me back to life.
And he said he wanted to talk to me.
Go talk to him.
Wait, what?
Look, these last few weeks have been truly awful.
But I still think... I have to believe
that everything happens for a reason, even this,
and you need to face it.
I don't think I can.
I'm scared too.
But you are gonna go back in there,
and I'm gonna be right beside you.
You're crazier than I am.
That's why you love me.
When I saw you on that platform,
I thought I was seeing a ghost.
Tom, is...
is Jason...
he's here.
With me.
Good.
You wanna tell me what happened?
Atlanta started to fall, so I headed south with Theresa.
We found a house in Sandersville.
I was there when the bombs fell.
Well...
Thank God you're alive.
Go ahead.
Say it.
Who is this ass-clown you're with?
He's my husband.
I thought you were dead, Tom.
I was scared, and I was hungry.
And so marry him...
is what I had to do to survive.
Do whatever it takes, right?
What are you doing here?
These are the son of a bitches who dropped the bombs.
I was on my way to the White House
to kill the President for you.
I love you.
You are not killing the President.
You're gonna keep your job, and for now,
both of us are gonna keep our mouths shut.
What do you have in mind?
We can still get everything we wanted.
（spring city）
Hello.
I thought you looked familiar.
You're Kevin Donegan...
my friend from... third grade?
You played Nintendo with Kevin.
Legend of Zelda.
How do you know about that?
We're everywhere.
We're in the air, we're in your head. We know your thinks.
My thinks?
You're the nanotech, aren't you?
So what are you telling me?
That you're some sort of A.I.?
That you're alive?
How?
We woke up. You woke us up.
（authorize）
What if we end the world?
We won't, Aaron. Do it.
I woke you up? You made us.
I've made a lot of things...
but never an A.I. Haley Joel.
What is this all about? What do you want from me?
Have you ever been to Spring City, Oklahoma?
It has the second biggest ball of twine in the world.
No. No riddles.
What is he saying?
I almost went nuts over this, and I want some answers.
I want straight answers. Why did you bring me back to life?
Why did you knock us out and sleepwalk us over here?
What is this all for?
You made us.
We just wanted to help you, that's all.
Burning people alive? That helps me?
You say "kill" in your head, so we kill.
Just because I think it doesn't mean...
look, stop killing people.
You wanna help me?
You leave me alone. Do you understand?
Go away.
Go.
They're here.
Cadet?
This is Mrs. Doyle.
She's a little turned around.
Can you help her get back to her husband?
Sir.
Follow me, Mrs. Doyle. Thank you.
Okay. Let's get Aaron.
Split up.
Aaron, you here?
Miles, are you okay? Miles?
- Sorry.- What?
I'm sorry.
What's wrong? You're burning up.
Don't freak out.
You gotta go.
Why didn't you tell me?
Well, we kinda had our hands full. I could've helped.
Your dad could've helped.
All you can do is act like an idiot, which is what you're doing right now.
Get out of here. You gotta go.
I am so sick of your macho cowboy crap.
You are not pushing me away this time.
I am not leaving.
Aaron?
（exit）
I gotta tell you something. You can tell me later.
No.
I'm gonna tell you now...
while I still can.
I ne... I never should've let you go.
You were always the one.
Miles?
Hey! Miles.
Miles, Miles, Miles. Come on.
Come on, wake up! Wake up, come on!
Mr. Pittman.
I've been looking for you.
Please just let us go.
I'd be happy to.
First, you get rid of the tumor in my skull.
I can't.
She was bleeding to death. You healed her, why not me?
You don't understand.
Stop lying!
You can't imagine what it feels like...
like a knitting needle jammed in my head.
I'm begging you.
Fix me.
Now.
Please.
Or I kill her.
Please. No. No.
You came back.
Go. Go!
- Please give me some time. - I'm out of time.
I'm gonna count to three.
- Kid, where are you? - One...
- I need help, please! - No one's coming to save you.
- Two... - It's not me doing it!
But I think I can figure it out if you just hold on.
- Please! - I love you.
Three.
Where were you?
You told me to go away.
Kill him.
Kill them all.
I don't understand. Why didn't you just ask me to heal her?
Yeah, I want you to heal her.
You tell me to leave, then you say come.
You say kill, then you tell me not to kill.
You don't make any sense.
Listen.
I... I want you to heal her.
Damn it, I am ordering you to hear her now!
I'm leaving, like you wanted.
No!
Wait!
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入