THEN
Take your brother outside
as fast as you can!
Now,Dean!Go!
What else do you remember?
Nothing.I was a kid,all right?
- And most important...
- Watch out for Sammy.
Watching out for you...
it's kinda who I am.
I got this brother,right?
And he's always telling me how
he's gonna watch out for me.
Now eat your dinner.
Don't forget your vegetables.
Don't you dare think that there is
anything that I would put in front of you!
Sammy's hurt.He's hurt real bad.
I heal Sam while healing myself.
Every time I use my power,it weakens me.
You went through the trials.
I just think it's better if you took it
easy,you know,and didn't act like you were...
Possessed by an angel.
NOW
Wait up!
Hurry!He's right behind us.
H*****
Come on,come on!
Hurry!
Go,go,go... it's open!
Come on,guys.
The barn is a no-fly zone
during hide-and-go-seek.
Boys?
Come on,you delinquents.
Time for bed!
All right!Game is over,boys!
Let's bring it in!
Lights out was 10 minutes ago!
You little bastards.
Okay,I'm gonna...
You got till the count of 10,and you'd
better come out or the belt's coming off!
1...
Come on!
Boys?
This isn't funny.
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly
Presents
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET-静静的生活
Supernatural
Season09Episode07
BAD****
Dean?
Kevin?
Hello?
- I'm sorry,there's no,uh... there's
no Dee-dawg,uh...- I got it.I got it.
Sonny,hey.So,what's up?
Okay.
All right.Yeah,just sit tight.I'll
be there as soon as I can.
Yeah.
So,what was that all about,Dee-dawg?
You remember when we were kids
that spring in upstate New York?
Dad was on a rugaru hunt.We,uh...
we crashed at the,uh...
the bungalow colony
with the ping-pong table.
Yeah.Uh,y-you disappeared.
Dad came back.You were gone.
He shipped me off to Bobby's for a
couple months and went and found you.
You were lost on a hunt or something.
That's what we told you.Right.
I'm sorry.That's what you told me?
Truth is,um...I lost the food money
that dad left for us in a card game.
I knew you'd get hungry,
so I tried taking the five-finger discount
at the local market and got busted.
I wasn't on a hunt.They
sent me to a boys' home.
- A boys' home,like a reform school?
- Yeah,more or less.
It was a farm,and the guy who ran it...
Sonny... he,uh... you know,he looked after me.
Wait.Does Sonny know what we do?
Yeah.He's good people.
I gave him the number to the bat phone,and
sounds like he's got something in our wheelhouse.
So...Hey,you gonna be cool to
do this,or are you too tired?
Uh,no.Yeah,I'm just,uh...I'll be fine.
And everybody's okay with
heading out to the Catskills?
I am everybody.
Yeah.Right.All right.Grab
your stuff,and we'll head out.
Hey,Dean...I mean,why didn't you
just tell me you went to a boys' home?
I don't know.Uh,it was dad's idea.
And then it just... you
know,the story became the story.
I was 16.
S*****
You were here for two months
and dad couldn't find you?
Oh,no.He found me.He found me quick.
But he left me here
'cause I lost our money.
You were 16.You made a mistake.
Yeah.I made the mistake.
Look,I know how you think.None
of this was dad's fault.
What can I do for you boys?
I'm Dean.This is my brother,Sam.
We're old buddies of Sonny's.
Prison buddies?
No.Uh,you mind telling
him that we're here?
I'll go get him.
I just mopped this floor,so you
take off those roach stompers.
Sonny's an ex-con,huh?
What,and we're such angels?Trust
me,he's more than made up for it.
Steven Hewlett caught him red-handed
...stealing up at his store.
So,what did he take?
Get this... peanut butter and bread.
Okay.And how about family?
Well,his old man called.
Once he found out what happened,he
said let him rot in jail.
Judge is off on a fishing trip.The
boy's too young to leave in county.
So we thought it best he
stay here till arraignment.
I don't see why not,man.
Appreciate it,Sonny.
Where'd you get the shiner?
You think that's funny?
I think you're slow.
- You sucker punched me!
- You wish!
Come on,now!Billy,I got this,buddy.
It's all right.
You shouldn't do that,kid.
Yeah?Why?Because he's a cop?
Because when you make him
mad,he leaves with the key.
Eh,don't sweat it.
Deputy do that?
What,your old man?
Well,then,how'd you get it?
Werewolf.
Okay.
So,how do you know I
won't just run away?
- Because you're hungry.
- No,I'm not.
Well,then,why'd you steal
bread and peanut butter?
So,what is this place,anyway?
It's for boys like you.
You work the land.
Teaches you some discipline
and responsibility.
Keeps you out of trouble.
That's lame.
Beats jail.
Come on.I'll fix you something to eat.
Dee-dawg!
- Sonny,good to see you.
- Hey,you,too,brother.
Oh,and this must be Sam.
- Good to meet you.
- Back at you,brother.
So,farm looks,uh,nice.
Oh,please,man.It's barely standing.
- Only got a handful of kids working around here now.
- Why's that?
Because these days,the system would
rather incarcerate a boy than redeem him.
Hey,Sonny,uh,y-you
mind if we talk alone?
Hey,Ruth,would you,uh,please
go check on the boys,
make sure their morning
chores are getting done?
All right.So,what's happening?
Well,you remember Jack,don't you?
Yeah.The,uh,tough,old leatherneck.
Well,somehow,that ancient,rusty,
broken-down tractor just roared to
life and ran him over the other night.
Maybe... maybe it just,uh,slipped
out of park or something.
Couldn't have.
You know,I never... I never believed any
of this mumbo-jumbo stuff you boys are into,
but...something ain't right.
What do you mean?
Well,just things started happening...
you know,lights flickering on and off,
strange scratching sounds coming from
inside the walls,windows and doors slamming.
All right.You think you can round up
the boys while we take a look around?
Well,that shouldn't be a problem.
Most are home on break... well,except
those with no home worth going to.
All right.Why don't you take the
house?I'll check out the barn.
Yeah.
k***
DA**
D***
I am so sorry.I-I-I thought
I...saw something in,uh...
Like a ghost?
Sonny told me you were old friends,but
I know why you're really here.
That's why I was praying for us.
Praying for what?
For the ghost that
haunts this farm to leave.
All right,Casper...
Where are you at?
Hello?
Anybody here?
Hey,kid,what are you
doing in here by yourself?
Fighting monsters.
What kind of monsters?
All sorts with Bruce
the monster smasher.
Is that a cape?
Little impractical for
smashing monsters,huh?
You know,you could choke.
I clobber evil!
I bet you do.
I'm Dean.
Timmy.
Let's try that again.
If you're gonna be a man,you got
to learn how to shake like one,okay?
So give me your best Kung Fu grip.
Good.Now look me straight in the
eye.Let me know that you mean business.
Shake as hard as you can.
That's it.
You shake like that,you'll be all right.
Hey,Timmy,did you know
Jack who worked here?
What can you tell me about him?
He yelled a lot.
He was yelling when he had his accident.
How do you know that?
'Cause me and the other boys were
playing here when it happened.
Did you see anything?
Is there anything else about that night
that you can remember,anything at all?
It suddenly got really cold.
Can I go?I have to finish my
chores before Ms.Ruth gets mad.
That Ruth... she runs a tight ship,huh?
Yeah,you better roll.
I grew up in this town.
I used to come up here as a little girl.
The Wasserlaufs,Howard and Doreen...
they used to own this farm back then.
My co-worker,Jack,may he rest in
peace,he worked here as a farmhand.
Howard was a nice man,but...
Well,he'd get into that corn liquor.
And one night he got it
into his thick skull that
Jack and his wife,Doreen,were
rolling around in the hay.
It wasn't true,but... but Howard's
paranoia got the better of him.
He tried to kill them both.
Jack got away,but Doreen...
He killed her?
With a meat cleaver.
Got life in jail...
which for Howard ended a year ago.
He always swore he'd get his
revenge on poor,old Jack,and...
looks like he finally got it.
Is Howard buried here in town?
So Dad didn't want you to tell me.
How come?
Was this place really so bad?
I don't really remember.
I mean,look,nobody bad touched me.
Nobody burned me with their smokes
or beat me with a metal hanger.
I call that a win.
All right.Let's barbecue old MacDonald
here,get the hell out of Dodge.
Help! Help!
Ruth,you okay?
What's wrong?
Open up!
Ruth!
Ave Maria Ave Maria That's okay.
Dean,you know I'm fine just grabbing
a burger to go somewhere,right?
What,and miss out on the best
banana pancakes you ever had?
Thanks.
No problem.I do this for all the boys
after they've been here for a month.
I meant for getting the
charges against me dropped.
Well,being hungry's not a crime.
It's the stealing that is.
But I feel if you only do that
once,you don't deserve a record.
And seeing as how we can't find your pops
anywhere,you can stay here as long as you want,Dean.
You're doing good in school.
You're making friends.You
made the wrestling team.
I'm proud of you.
Let me ask you something,and I
want you to be straight with me.
Are you into the whole
heavy-metal,devil-worshiping stuff?
What?No.
Hey,I'm not... I'm not judging.
It's just I found a few occult-looking
symbols carved into your bedpost.
It's...It's a very long story.
That story have anything to
do with why you put the salt
in front of your bunk door
every night before bed?
Well,it's a family thing,so
I can't really talk about it.
Same family that left you here?
What are you... what are
you,in the mob or something?
More like something.
I was part of this gang,right?
They were my family.
I lived,breathed,I would
have even died for them.
You know where it got me?
15 years in a correctional facility.
And for what?
Being loyal?
To who?
I should have been loyal to myself.
Because you get one shot at this
game,Dean,and when you look in the mirror,
you want the guy looking
back at you to be his own man.
Hey,guys.
-Hey,Robin.How are you?
- I'm good.How are you?
Good.Meet my new ranch
foreman here,Dean.
Welcome to Cus's.What can I get you two?
Bet you never thought
you'd see me here,huh?
Uh,look,I'm a little bit slammed right
now.Do you guys want to hear the specials?
Robin...Dean Winchester.
I used to live up at Sonny's.
Uh,look,sorry.There's just... there's
so many boys that pass through there,
it's... it's hard to remember
every... every name and face.
Yeah.Uh,no.Sorry,I just...
I remember you coming
up there with your mom.
She'd give guitar lessons.
It's,uh... it was a long time ago.
Yeah.Mom... she loved
helping out the boys.
I guess that's why I kept
giving lessons after she passed.
Hey,Robin?
Um,would you excuse
me?I'll be right back.
- Dude...
- Let's go.
- what was that?
- Nothing.
Nothing?Well,obviously it was something.
- Who was that waitress?
- Said it was nothing,all right?Drop it.
Sonny.
What?
I tried to get in to save her,but
the damn door wouldn't open.
Locked?
There's no locks on the farm.
That means our little field
trip to the cemetery was a bust.
Sonny,is there anything
else weird you can remember?
What,'cause we're not
chest-deep in weird already,boys?
I know,I know.I mean anything... really.
There was one thing.
Ruth always had her rosary beads with
her,but now I can't find them anywhere.
All right.Um,let's start with the
vics,okay?I mean,both lived in the house.
They both,uh,worked
closely with the boys.
All right,why don't I go have a
chat with the rug rats,see what's up?
Yeah.
Sonny,you got any employee
records on the victims?
In my office.
Let's do it.
Come on,whatcha gonna do
about it?You gonna cry?
Timmy,you're such a little weirdo.
- What are you doing?Come here.
- Nothing.
Timmy,what's going on?
All right,you two.
Where were you this morning
when Ruth had her accident?
Unless you're a cop,we don't
need to tell you anything.
Oh,okay.Well...how about that?
We weren't even here this morning.
Sonny sent us into town to get
some chicken feed... we swear.
What about Ruth?What can
you tell me about her?
Uh,we used to call her the warden.
She was a real
Bible-thumping hard-ass.
Obviously.What else?
Anything different or
weird you can think of?
You mean besides Timmy?
Either of you touch him ever again,I'm
gonna go all Guant??namo on you.
Understand me?Get the hell out of here.
Go on!Get.
- You and Bruce okay?
- Yeah.
Listen to me.
Guys like that... they're cowards,okay?
All you got to do is stand up to them
one time and they'll stop,I promise.
Okay.
Sonny,wait.
W-what is all this?
It's our hall of fame.
We had some pretty great athletes come
through here,including your brother.
He was Sullivan county
135-pound wrestling champion.
Hey,guys!
She could give me a lesson anytime.
Gross.She's like ancient.
What the hell?
What's this doing in here?
Kid's gonna need about 8,000
stitches,but he'll be fine.
That kid was bullying Timmy
before the accident,right?
Yeah.Why?
Check this out.
Timmy was found in an abandoned
building about a year ago all by himself.
No one was sure how
long he had been there.
And what about his parents?
Well,they posted a picture on the
Internet,but no one ever showed up.
Well,then,what's he doing
here?Shouldn't he be in an orphanage?
He kept running away
from Child Services.
So about three months ago,Sonny
offered to take him in.
All right,so hard-ass counselors,bullies
all bite the dust,but Timmy's still standing.
So,what are we talking?We got
ourselves a Damien on our hands?
No.EMF rules out a demon.So...
probably ghost possession.
Meaning what,we find Timmy and shove a fistful
of salt down his throat,forced ejection?
You're taking the barn this time.
- So,you've been a lot of places?
- Yeah.
My,uh...My dad likes
to move around a lot.
What's your dad do?
Boring stuff.
Do you like it?
No,not really.
But my dad expects me to
follow in his footsteps.
So I've kind of gotten used to it.
Yeah.I-I get it.
My pops wants me to take over the
diner,but that's not happening.
So,what do you really want to do?
I want to be a photographer and see the
world,go to strange lands,eat crazy food.
I want to be a rock star,but...
I also really like cars.
Being a mechanic seems rough.
What?No,no.Not at all.
Cars are freaking cool as hell.
Fixing them is like a puzzle,and
the best part is when you're done,
they leave,and you're not
responsible for them anymore.
Have you kissed many girls?
What?
Yeah.Of course.
- Lots.
- Really?
Well,I guess we'll just
have to keep practicing.
Uh,what happened to you at the diner?
I turned around to take your
order,and you were just gone.
Long story.
Um,have you seen Timmy?
No,not yet,but he should be here
any minute for his guitar lesson.
Yeah,we're gonna cancel that.
What?
We got to get out of here,okay?
I don't have time to
explain.You just got to trust me.
T-trust you?
And why would I do that again?
You do remember me.
How could I forget?
What's wrong?
I just hope this lasts.
I'm not going anywhere,Robin.
Yeah,says you.
Well,I can't.
Who else would take
you to the school dance?
Is this your way of asking me
to be your date,Dean Winchester?
Yeah.How am I doing so far?
There were... there were
reasons why I had to leave.
I don't have time to explain
them to you right now.
I got to get you out of here.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Sorry about what,Timmy?
I can't stop it.
Go,go,go!
Sam,go!
- Locked.
- Damn it!
Circle.
Dean,what... what
just happened in there?
Okay,listen to me.Whatever
happens,you stay inside this circle.
Understood?
All right.Dean...
I can't control her.
Can't control who?
Your mom,right?
Timmy,listen.
We need you to tell
us about the fire,okay?
It was late,and we were driving
home when we crashed in the woods.
Everything was on fire.
But she saved me,pushed me out...
Before the car blew up...
With her in it.
But that's not all,was it?
I ran through the woods.
I found an empty building,where I hid.
I was scared.It was dark and cold.
So I cried.I cried for my mom.
And then she came.
But she had changed,right?
I'll bet she gave you that
cool action figure,huh?
Yeah.When I turned 9.
Timmy...
I'm gonna need that action figure.
No!
I clobber evil!
I...clobber...evil!
It looks like it wasn't the action
figure that was anchoring her here,Dean.
Well,then,what is?
Him.
You know what?
I think maybe his mom can't let go and
she's still protecting him from the grave.
Protecting him from what?
What,from us?
Maybe she doesn't know what threats are real
and what's not,so she just attacks all of them.
Great.So,what,unless we waste
the kid,we're sitting ducks?
This is... this is crazy.
Robin.Robin!
Damn it.
Robin,wait!
Who are you?
Right now I'm the only thing
that's keeping you safe.
Timmy,we're gonna need your help,okay?
Listen to me.
I need you to focus,okay?
Look,we are not here to hurt you.
Sammy!
I can't stop her.
Timmy,you have to try!
She came to you when
you cried out for her.
Now you have to tell
her to stop and go away!
She's my mom.
She's a ghost.
Timmy,because she can't move
on,she's going crazy.Okay?
You got to let her go.
You'll be okay.
Listen to me.
Sometimes you got to do what's best for
you,even if it's gonna hurt the ones you love.
Mommy...Stop it.
Timmy,Kung Fu grip!
Mommy,stop it!Stop hurting people!
You have to go.
Never come back.
I'll be okay.I promise.
I love you,too.
So,then,this is the family business?
Told you it was boring.
Yeah,right.
Well,as you can see,I did not
run off to become a rock star.
I don't know about that.
You look pretty rockin'
to me,Dean Winchester.
And what about you?
I mean,I always thought that I would hate
being in the same little town my whole life,
and,you know,taking over the diner
like dad always wanted,but...I don't.
I just... I love it.
I guess we didn't know everything
we thought we did at 16,huh?
Not everything.
Just some things.
Sounds like Timmy's gonna
need some help adjusting.
Yeah,but he's got you.
I always hate to see you go,Dee-dawg.
Can't thank you enough for this one,man.
Sonny,we'll see you around.
You can bet on that,boys.
Take it easy,man.
Hey,h-how did you know Timmy asking
his mom to leave was gonna work?
I didn't.
Total hail Mary.Got lucky.
You just got lucky?
Kind of like you did with this place.
I mean,here I was thinking this
was the worst part of your life,
and it turns out it was the best.
Why'd you ever leave?
Never felt right.
Really?
It was two months,Sam,okay,and I
couldn't wait to get out of here.
I don't know what to tell you.
It wasn't me.
Oh,look at you.
- You clean up good!
- Thank you.
You know,uh...I've never actually been
to one of these school dances before.
Yeah.
Look,about that,Dean,your old man's
outside,and,man,he's really something.
I tried to tell him what a
big night it was for you,Dean,
and ask him if he could come back later,but
he just said to tell you he had a job,
said you'd know what that means.
You know,after I got out of jail,this
place gave me a second chance,
and it's done the same for you,too.
So if you want,I'll stick my neck out
for you,and I'll fight for you to stay.
Sonny...
thank you... for everything.
But I have to go.
Dean...
Thank you.
For what?
For always being
there,for having my back.
Look,I know it always hasn't been easy.
I don't know what the
hell you're talking about.
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Proudly
Presents
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET-静静的生活
Supernatural
Season09Episode07