previously onwhite collar...
the mosconi codex.
you're gonna steal it for me.
when does it end?
you left him bleeding on the sidewalk.
I didn't kill the dude.
I pulled that badge and gun
out of the trash,I swear.
summers told us where she hid the
$2 million,but it wasn't there.
a chiropractor's office?
it'll look the part.agent
gruetzner.we've been expecting you.
any reason he'd slip away to come here?
neal always has a reason.
if this book is a puzzle,maybe
these are the pieces.
this stained glass window could
be right here in manhattan.
this is where neal was standing.
for 20 minutes,after which he went
straight home,according to his anklet.
from this intersection,you could
scout a museum,two banks,and a gallery,
not to mention all the
residential targets.
peter,I made some calls.There was
no suspicious activity reported.
not unless you count
neal caffrey being here.
you think I'm overreacting?
no,I just think we might
consider the possibility
that caffrey was just
picking up some groceries.
long walk for a loaf of bread.
okay.
so what was he doing there?
first,there was the missing cash,then
the fbi pen at the chiropractor's office,
and now this street corner.
so what do you think it all adds up to?
that's the problem.
I can't see how it all connects.
I'm missing something.
- See if any cameras in the area picked up anything.
- will do.
listen,I also ran the card that
you found in siegel's badge.
talked to the real estate company.no
one knew what "cooper 3?" meant.
I looked through siegel's old case
files,friends and family back in chicago.
hell,I even looked on google.
no hits.sorry.
listen,I hate to ask you this,
but you don't think caffrey knows
anything that he's not telling us,do you?
- about siegel?
- yeah.
- I don't.
- all right.
- checked black market code
words,drop locations,c.i.Names.
mozzie even tried to tie
it to d.b. Cooper.nothing.
- maybe it's an fbi
agent grasping at straws.
we both know your
instincts are rarely wrong.
- well,for now,we've got a stolen
shipping crate that demands our attention.
grabbed from canadian customs this
morning by a fraudulent trucking company.
the driver ran.no sign of him yet.
- must be some exotic canadian
contraband to get you out of the office.
- oh,this is well worth
a stretch of my legs.
don't tell me.it's diamonds from the
diavik mine in the northwest territories.
maybe it's maple syrup.
- you joke,but the great canadian
maple syrup heist was worth 18 million.
you'd need a bigger crate though.
- and a lot of pancakes.
special agent burke.go ahead.
- It's like christmas morning.
- no,it's not a gift.
this is stolen property.I know
the line gets blurry for you.
- Based on the size of the
box and the country of origin,
my best guess is a sculpture from
emanuel hahn,canadian artist,circa 1918.
- oh,this is better than christmas.
this is a dinosaur egg.
Even now you kind of expect
it to crack open,don't you?
- I really don't.
- a fossilized egg doesn't
capture your imagination?
- well,the value of it does.
- hello?excuse me.I'm Dr.Khatri.
I'm one of the curators of
the natural history museum.
- agent peter burke.
- you're the one who found my egg.
- well,he can't take all the credit.
- and where's the mother?
- what do you mean?
- there was a second shipment
containing the mother.
- what kind of mother?
- a tyrannosaurus rex.
- you're saying there's a tyrannosaurus
rex lost somewhere in new york city?
<font
color=#238E68>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-ProudlyPresents
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET-静静的生活
<font
color=#238E68>white.collar.s05e08
- tyrannosaurus rex was being shipped
simultaneously on a different truck.
no sign of it anywhere.hunting a t-rex.
seven-year-old me
would be going crazy.
- adult you isn't exactly serene.
- I can't wait to see it in person
when it's reunited with its egg.
- mozzie used to create fake
fossils and bury them at dig sites.
- used to?
- it's been a couple months.
- the alternate history of
the earth according to mozzie.
that's terrifying.
- I'm just saying,the black market
is rife with fake fossils like this.
do we know the egg is real?
- khatri ran an acid
test and authenticated it.
- well,people with way too much money
and no subtlety do love to put them
in their office as a display of power.
- yeah,what bigger display than a t
-rex and its egg?
whoever the buyer is,it's
clear they want the entire set.
- valuable alone,invaluable together.
it's like having queen mary's diamond
riviere without the la peregrina pearl.
jones is working on a list
of suspects.I gotta get home.
what are your plans tonight?
- I'm just gonna relax at home.
do a little light reading.
- I'm really happy that you called.
I found something,and
I brought something.
- yeah,I should've mentioned...agent
gruetzner will be joing us.
- hello.
- a rare book expert and a wine connoisseur.
california zin.
well,there's no shame
in having one specialty.
- you said you found something?
- uh,yes.yes,I did.
so I was looking into the stained
glass window,and I stumbled across this.
mosconi's grave site.
- uh,yes.just look
down here at the bottom.
- it's a masonic compass.
so he was a mason.
- I should have noticed it sooner.
I mean,this is why he put
the chapter 13 into the codex.
- 13 is considered a sacred
number for the brotherhood.
- he was sending a message
to the other masons.
- the codex could lead us anywhere.
I mean,masons have their hands in
everything.finance,government,art.
- untimely death.
look at the date on the gravestone.
- april 17,1887.
that's the same month he finished the
window.that must have been his final work.
do you think that he was
killed because of all of this?
if that's so,the stained
glass could tell us why.
well,thanks for everything.we'll
take it from here.
okay,I'll leave you to it.
- Yes,thank you for coming over and for the wine.
- sure.
- dinner on wednesday
without the chaperone?
- of course,agent caffrey.
I look forward to working
with you more on all of this.
- what?
I got it under control.
well,I hate to report the obvious news,
but the last thing you are
right now is under control.
luckily,you have a guardian
angel looking over you.
- this is less angel and more stalker.
- I vetted her,a cursory
audit.financials,education,daily schedule.
she keeps a tight routine,speaks three
languages,studied two years in france.
here,just keep it.just in case.
- t
-rex and her egg were owned legally by a man in toronto for 50 years.
he kept it in his family room
until he died three months ago.
- that's a hell of a
pet to get your kids.
- big pooper scooper.
- he dictated that,upon his
death,it be donated to the museum.
- I'm guessing someone tried to
persuade the estate to sell it instead.
- lots of someones.
- who do we like?
- well,there's a number of people
who pursued it very aggressively.
- lots of escalating offers.
- and a lot of suspicious people making them.
- anyone only try once?
- yeah,there were two single bids.
I mean,one was a lowball
offer,but then there's this guy.
he made a single high-priced
offer,then nothing.
brett forsythe,corporate raider,made
millions from hostile takeovers.
- I've heard of him.
He led a takeover of a
company called aegis last year.
that's the kind of guy who knows
when someone's not gonna sell,
and his only option is
to take what he wants.
- I'm gonna pay him a visit.
- I'm sorry,Mr.Forsythe is
unavailable at the moment.
- of course he is.
well,if you could tell him
that agent burke of the fbi,
white collar division,would
like to speak with him.
I can wait here as long as it takes.
I'm sure these guys would
love to keep me company.
that's probably her boss telling
her that I can see him now.
when you took over aegis,the board
didn't know you'd stolen their company
until you walked through the
door and fired all of them.
- that was my legal right,agent burke.
- it was.
and then you sold off pieces of the
company one by one,made a great profit.
lost a lot of jobs.
- The feds questioned me about
the aegis takeover a month ago.
it was all aboveboard.
- I know.
- why are you here?
- is that a velociraptor skull?
- yeah.
I should sell it.
thanks tojurassic park,everyone
thinks they're an expert on them.
- except the movie
got everything wrong.
velociraptors were
most likely feathered,
based on the quill knobs
found by paleontologists.
and the film made them much larger,more
like the size of a deinonychus.
- that's true.
velociraptors were closer
to the size of a chicken.
- still,one mean
-looking chicken.
- and very dangerous.
are you a collector?
- oh,on a government salary?
I'd barely be able to
afford an ankle joint.
how'd you get it?
- there are many legal ways
to purchase fossils,agent.
- true.many illegal ways as well.
- that why you're here?
to question the legality
of my velociraptor?
- no,I'm hunting something bigger.
a t-rex.
- thought you said you
weren't a collector.
- it's not for me.
it was supposed to go to a
museum but didn't make it there.
- Agent burke,even if I stole a tyrannosaurus
rex,which I did not,what would I do with it?
it's not like I could
just put it on display.
- that's a good point.
but what a thing to have.
- you think he has an actual
skeleton in his closet?
- I don't know what
he's hiding in there,
but there was a large open space
right underneath the raptor skull.
- well,he stalled when you got
there.that gave him time to move it.
so chances are it's illegal.
- is that what takes you so long
to come to the door when I knock?
- you think I'm hiding
illicit goods under my bed?
- I think you're hiding something.
but I don't have enough for a
warrant to search forsythe's office.
- you should stake it
out,see what happens.
especially around 6:00 p.m.
- I'll keep an eye out
for anything suspicious.
- you said the empty space
was near the raptor skull?
- yeah,right underneath.
- it's not empty anymore.
now there's a mean-looking club there.
looks pre-columbian.
- forsythe must have
moved it back after I left.
- as long as I'm here,I should
see what else he's hiding.
- no,get the picture,and get out.
- the trick with sliding locks is they leave
a smudge that can tell you what the code is.
- this does not sound
like you getting out.
the key is guessing where
it starts and where it ends.
is he right-
or left-handed?
- right.why?
- right
-handed people instinctively draw counterclockwise.
- I told you to get out.
- forsythe has a whole lab back here.
microscopes,test tubes,all
kinds of forensic equipment.
- forsythe came back.
- almost done.
- did you set off an alarm?
- peter,that's hurtful.
- either way,he's headed your way.
- all right,leaving now.
- where are you?
where are you?
- it's called a
macuahuitl.- "macua-neenle."
- no,"macua-heetle."
- "macua-heednum."
- I said that.
- okay,either way,your hunch is right.
it was stolen from a pre-columbian
exhibit here in new york.
- I guess forsythe does some business
in the black market after all.
- yeah,but get this.It
was stolen eight years ago.
- statute of limitations is up.
- forsythe's a smart guy.he
knows we can't get him on it.
- sure,he didn't want to raise
a red flag in front of a bull.
- not when he's hiding
something bigger.
for a job as big as a t-rex,he'd wanna use
somebody he can trust,somebody he'd used before.
any suspects in the macuahuitl theft？
- there were no arrests,but
there were three suspects.
one's in jail.one recently
questioned in prague.
then there's this guy,michael holt.
suspected in four other
robberies along the east coast.
- he doesn't stay in
one place very long.
- no,but even a master thief needs time to unload a 40
-foot prehistoric skeleton.
- either way,we've got a narrow window
before he leaves town.track him down.
- before we do,you wanna know why caffrey
was standing on that street corner?
- yeah,I do.
what do you have?
- not what.it's who.
I got this off a security
camera from across the street.
- she looks familiar.
- her name's rebecca lowe.
- yeah,the woman we brought in
from the gershon heist a while back.
what's neal doing with her?
- you know,I was talking to el,she has
a friend she'd like to set you up with.
- does this friend know
that I come with a rap sheet?
interested?
- tell elizabeth thank you,but
I'm not looking right now.
- well,it's been a while since sara,and I
thought you might wanna get back out there.
not that it's difficult for you.
- you'd be surprised.
anyone I date,I have to lie to or
wonder why she's interested in a felon.
- no luck at all?
yeah,jones?
where to?
yeah.
okay,thanks.
holt's gone.
jones checked his credit cards.
he bought a plane ticket
out of the country.
- the only reason I'd buy a plane
ticket under my name with my credit card
is if I wanted someone to
think I'd left the country.
- the airline confirmed
that he got on the plane.
- the airline confirmed someone
with holt's ticket got on the plane.
you know that time you
thought I was in monaco?
- don't tell me that I had interpol
scouring the streets for nothing.
- bought a first
-class ticket under my name and checked in for my flight.
once I got to the gate,I looked for
someone traveling alone with a carry-on.
- if someone checks a bag and doesn't get
on the plane,the flight doesn't take off.
so I offer them my ticket,which
of course they're gonna take
because no sane person facing a 3,000-mile
trip is gonna say no to a seat in first class.
- and they don't suspect
an ulterior motive?
- Not everyone is as naturally
suspicious as you,peter.
- my nature has developed from years
of tracking your suspicious behavior.
so this unsuspecting stranger gets
your ticket,gets on the plane--
- and neal caffrey is
on his way to monaco,
while the real neal caffrey
slips out of the gate unnoticed.
I can't believe you never knew that.
- cameras caught michael holt
scoping out their security system.
- he's still after that egg.
- he thinks it's at the museum.
catching holt in the act is our best
shot at tracking down that stolen t-rex.
- I'll put surveillance teams
outside the museum around the clock.
- keep me posted.
- all right.
- well,I guess someone else enjoyed
that first-class ticket.- so...
holt had 1/2 million
good reasons to stay.
- how did you know what
forsythe was gonna pay holt?
- I found a briefcase full
of cash in his back room.
- and you opened it?
see,this is the reason I
have a suspicious nature.
I'm gonna count every penny of it.
- I don't blame you.you should.
it was a rough estimate
though.it's a round number.
- hey, hon.
- yeah?
- how'd you like to go
on a double date tonight?
- with trey and sheila?
- neal.
- does he know we're coming?
- he doesn't know we're coming.
- he's been sneaking around with this
woman,and I think he's up to something.
- or maybe he's having a
nice meal with a nice girl.
- there's no reason for
neal to keep this from me.
what do I care if he's
going on a date with a girl?
- clearly you care quite a bit.
- nah,there's more to it than this.
a lot of things neal has
been doing don't add up,
and my gut tells me
she's at the center of it.
now according to his
anklet,they're at the clifton.
- you know I've always
wanted to go to the clifton.
- really?
- you think this is a good idea?
- I do.
- Thought you might like this.
- the wine is lovely.
and it reminds me of this summer
that I spent in france studying.
I actually think I've
been to this vineyard.
- really?
- really.
did you have the fbi run
a background check on me?
- the fbi had nothing to do
with this dinner.I promise.
- hmm,you know,you never told
me why you became an fbi agent.
I assume it wasn't
only to pick up women.
how does an art lover
become an fbi agent?
- eh,it's a long story.
- I spend my life
studying ancient texts.
- I don't mind long stories.
- I want this dinner to be about you and me,okay?
we don't need to talk about work.
- all right.
I really do like this place and
the wine and the codex and the kiss.
- I liked that part too.
- you know,you-- you don't have to do
all this just to get my help on the case.
- do you really think I would do that?
- no.
- what kind of guy do you think I am?
- I don't know.you're an fbi agent.
- yeah.
- if it's too complicated,I'll understand.
- are you trying to give me a way out?
- apparently without much subtlety.
- no.
I don't want one.
do you?
- no.
- neal?
- peter,what are you doing here?
- elizabeth has been dying
to try this place out.
hi,I'm peter,neal's boss.
- we've met.I'm rebecca.you
almost arrested me.
- oh,right.sorry about that.
- no,it's-- Wait,I thought your boss was--
- and this is elizabeth,peter's lovely wife.
- it's so nice to meet you.I'm
really sorry for interrupting.
- oh,nonsense.no secrets between friends,right?
- course not.
- I didn't know that you two had
been in touch since the investigation.
- you guys met on a case?
- oh,yeah,you know how sometimes
your personal and professional lives
just crash into each
other without any notice.
- it's actually how peter and I met.
- yeah,agency resources were
involved from what I recall.
- it was completely aboveboard.
- actually,we were just talking
about how neal became an fbi agent.
- yeah,but it's a long story.
- I know I'd love to hear that story.
- um,I'm gonna go check and
see if we can get a table.
would you like to go with me?
maybe let the boys chat?
- of course.
- see you in a little bit.
what are you doing
here?did you follow me here?
- you have until they come back to
explain why she thinks you're an fbi agent,
or I'm telling her the truth.
- we met on a case.I told
her I work for the fbi.
- she assumed I was an agent.
- and you didn't correct her,did you?
- I didn't see any reason to.
- Because you're impersonating
a federal officer.
- I suppose technically-- -
no,not technically.you are.
the pen,the chiropractor's office.
this is all to convince
her of this story.
- you're... you like her,don't you?
lying is a funny way of showing it.
- she doesn't look at
me like a criminal,okay?
she looks at me the way el looks at you.
I don't want to ruin that.
- neal,you have lovely friends.
- oh,aren't they great?
we are gonna get out
of your hair right now.
we got a table.come on,let's go.
sure.you two have lots to talk about.
excuse me one minute.
- this is agent burke.
- it's Dr.Khatri.someone's here.
I don't recognize him.
- all right,remain calm,doctor.we
have agents in the museum.
- no,I'm not there.I took the
egg to my lab to run a cat scan.
- hang up and find someplace
safe.we'll be there soon.
neal,we have to
go.Dr.Khatri's in trouble.
- nypd is on the way,but we're closer.
- we're running out of time?you
better tell me where it is?
what,you think I'm playing games?
- I'll never give it to you.
- it's holt.
- I'm not gonna ask again.
- If we go in with guns
drawn,he might shoot her.
- khatri's not giving up that egg.
we gotta come up with something,or
she's gonna get herself killed.
- where the hell is the egg?
- where is the mother?what
have you done with her?
- it's just an egg.tell me where it is.
- it's so much more than that.
it is a child that needs
to be with its mother,
and I'll be damned if I'll
ever give it up to you.
- have it your way.
- doctor,do you have the isotopic
results-- - hold it right there.
I don't want any trouble,okay?
- where is the damn egg?
- I'll show you.
- no,you can't give it to him.
- I'm not taking a bullet
for a fossil,all right?
follow me.
right through here.
- get off of me?
- give me a hand.
- not every thief who
brings their own handcuffs.
- very thoughtful of you.
holt confirmed that forsythe
hired him for the fossil heist.
- so why are you not doing an "about
to get the dinosaur" happy dance?
- because he doesn't know
where the dinosaur is located.
- and if we arrest forsythe now,there's no guarantee we'll get the t
-rex back.
- and our evidence is largely
circumstantial.I want hard proof.
- you want the dinosaur.
- damn right I do.
- Dr.Khatri will be happy to hear that.
just got off with the hospital.
she's fine,just a little shaken up.
- there's only one chip
we can play right now.
the egg.
- we can plant a tracker on it.
- I bet he'll stash it with the t
-rex fossils.
- follow him,make a clean arrest.
- I don't wanna put the egg in play.
it's too valuable,too important.
lucky for us,we know someone
with a history of forging fossils.
- Dr.Khatri gave me fragments of real
calcite shell and sedimentary rock.
I'll sculpt the core from alabaster.
- adhesives?
- already mixed.we should get started.
- I assume you don't mean the royal we?
- a correct assumption.
the hydrochloric acid is reacting perfectly
with the calcium carbonate in the shell.
- we made a baby dinosaur,moz.
- ah,like father,like forged embryo.
each with his own anklet.
- at least peter won't be able
to follow this tracker to rebecca.
- oh,have you spoken to her since your ill
-fated dinner?
I warned you,neal.
you,business,and women.
- unholy trinity,I get it.
- well,you can be grateful that the suit
didn't expose your agent nom de guerre.
- well,I am.
what happens when peter digs deeper?
- could find out about the codex.
- yeah,or hagen.
- cause for concern.
keep in mind,to make an
end is to make a beginning.
- you think I should end it with her?
- that was t.s.Eliot.
but if rebecca is on big brother's
radar,the timing could be right.
- all right,do we have a
game plan for the church yet?
- I'm working on it.
but to steal the stained glass window
will be difficult with so many witnesses.
- well,that's a problem
that can wait a day.
- indeed.
today we revive the cretaceous period.
tomorrow we steal a window that could
be connected to a bedlamite's tome.
c'est la vie.
- c'est la vie.
- not bad.
- I was gonna give it to you after this,but
if you don't think it's very good...
"not bad" doesn't mean "not good."
- it doesn't mean "good."
- I'll give it to someone who can appreciate it.
- no,this is fbi property.
I can take it if I want.
- okay,the tracker's live.
when forsythe moves the
egg,we'll be right behind him.
- neal,tell us about your cover.
- john mcdowell.accomplice
to michael holt.
here to deliver the egg because the fbi
is looking into holt,and he's laying low.
- which was confirmed by holt when he
called forsythe to set up the meeting.
- we'll have ears on
you the whole time.
- with a forgery like
this,you should be out quickly.
- with 1/2 million in cash.
- the fbi is investigating
holt?should I worry?
- nah,it's just one agent shaking every
tree he can find to see what falls out.
he doesn't have anything.
but to be safe,I'm here instead of holt.
hey,if you don't want the egg anymore,I'm
sure I can unload it somewhere else.
- no,no,no,no.it's fine.
I wanna see it.
no,it's not yours
yet.not till you pay me.
- you're getting ahead of yourself.
I need to authenticate it first.
- let's get a move on.
ticktock.
- calcite levels and pebble texture appear appropriate.
- I assume that's good news.
- oh,it very much is.
- then I think this is
the part where you pay me.
- I will.after one last test.
can't tell you how many times two-bit hustlers
have tried to rip me off with fake artifacts.
which is where the cat
scan comes in handy.
- he won't see an embryo on a cat scan.
- but he will see the tracker.
- the scan will take about
ten minutes.so settle in.
- look,I didn't think this was gonna be an all
-day thing.okay?
- you worried the scan won't work?
- no,I just don't understand
what this thing is gonna show you
that all the other tests didn't.
- it'll show me what's inside.
or what isn't.
- we need to pull neal out of there.
- wait,Dr.Khatri should
have a cat scan of the egg.
- I'll call to see if
she can send one to us.
- you ever heard of a macuahuitl?
- It's the weapon you're
holding in your hands right now.
- what else can you tell
me about this weapon,john?
anything about this one in particular?
- I stole it for you eight years
ago with holt right here in new york.
you're holding it wrong.
you mind?
the early macuahuitl handle
is 2 inches wider at the top.
hold it like this.
better grip means a
faster swing.more control.
- you're right.
- you know,I've stolen a lot of things,but
I've rarely taken anything just to have it.
- you should try it sometime.
we should be at the
embryo any moment now.
yeah?
why is he here?
fine.
I'll be right there.
- who's here?
- that fbi agent.
still shaking his trees.
don't worry,I'll get rid of him.
- Mr.Forsythe,thanks for seeing
me.I won't take up much of your time.
michael holt,he's our prime suspect
in the fossil shipment theft.
- what's it got to do with me?
- I was wondering if maybe he
approached you on buying them.
- well,if he contacts
me,you'll be my first call.
- all I wanted to hear.
- then you'll be on your way.
- you know,even though their
name means "speedy thief,"
they say that the velociraptor
wasn't particularly fast.
- that's true.
- and that it was dumb.
Yeah,not much room for
a brain in there,I guess.
one slow,dumb chicken with big teeth.
- don't touch the skull.
- how do you keep them glued in there?
epoxy or tacky?
- agent burke,don't...
guess you should've used superglue.
- is that all?
sorry I broke your dinosaur.
- well,will you look at that?
money's in the briefcase.
- pleasure doing business with you.
- the things people do when
they think no one's watching.
- like following your friend
to a first date and crashing it?
- come on.
Let's show forsythe how the
fbi handles natural selection.
- you just think of that one?
- yeah,on the way over.
- what the hell are you doing here?
- I thought about what you said.
I figured out what I wanna take.
- how'd you follow me?
- that little guy
told me where you were.
- or at least a gps tracker
we put inside it did.
- let's go.
- open it up.
- okay,that definitely
captures my imagination.
- you know,it's not too late
for you to be a paleontologist.
- some things are better
enjoyed from a distance.
- oh,like grand larceny.
- are all of your hobbies illegal?
- I like chess.
- you hustled chess in union square.
- agent burke.
Mr.Caffrey,follow
me.you need to see this.
here she is.
- she's...
- majestic.
- this mother and child reunion was
only possible because of you two.
the museum is in your debt.
- I know someone who would love a year
-round pass.
- agent burke,you have vip status
here.our doors are always open.
- peter burke,vip.we should get you a badge.
- quiet.
thank you,doctor.
- thank you.
- come by the house for dinner tonight.
el's cooking branzino.
- branzino,look at you.
- I can be fancy.
- thanks for the invitation,but--
- it's not an invitation.
- so it's an order?
- 7:00 p.m.
don't be late,agent caffrey.
- bad news.
- another amazing meal.
- well,it should be.it's your recipe.
- should've thrown it on a barbecue.
- never let him be sous chef.
- he's actually very
good on the barbecue.
- so...rebecca.
- yeah,rebecca.
- what do you wanna know?
- have you told her everything?
- everything?
- why you're working for the fbi?
- Why you're wearing an anklet?
- has she seen it?
- okay,I was waiting
for the right time.
- There's no right time,neal.
- what do you think happens
if I tell her the truth?
- the more time passes,the
more the truth will hurt.
if you really want this
to work,tell her now.
pray she'll accept it.
- you agree?
- if you really care about rebecca,she
deserves to know the real you.
- okay,if peter had told you
something like this when you first met,
would you have accepted it?
- honestly,neal,I--
I don't know.
but I'd want the choice to decide.
and so will rebecca.
it's a risk you should take.
- I don't wanna ask
why you have that thing.
- mm,it was there for
the taking.thank you.
- you're welcome.
cheers.
- cheers.
byron always said the city spoke to him.
- I can relate to that.
- you're a lot like him.
- how did you feel when he
told you he was a criminal?
- it hurt.
but I loved him.
and it didn't matter what he was.
it only mattered who he was.
- I wish I could separate the two.
- well,you'll learn with time.
- just a second.
find something new?
- yeah.
- great.
- no.
I was gonna lie,pretend I found
something,but I just wanted to come see you.
whatever this is between us,I...
i don't want it to stop.
- I don't either.
- yeah?
- but there's something
you should know about me.
- okay.
- I'm not an fbi agent.
I'm a criminal informant.
I was convicted of bond forgery and served part
of a four-year sentence before I became a c.i.
- I'm--I don't
understand.
I've been to your office.I've been
working with your boss,agent gruetzner.
- yeah,he's not my boss.my real boss
is peter burke,who you met at dinner.
that office was just a setup
to get your help with the codex.
- you set up a fake office
all so you could lie to me?
- are you even researching the codex?
- I am.
just not for the fbi.
rebecca.
- why would you do this to me?
- I need your help,all right?
and I-- I didn't expect
this.I didn't expect us.
- is there anything else I should know?
- thank you.
I think I was
just-- - june?
- neal?
I was just chatting with
this wonderful man,mr...
- you can call me "curtis."
- curtis.it's a lovely name.
- thank you.
- well,I think...
I'll just be running along.
- you stay away from her,hagen.
- quite the life you've built.
hate to see things fall
apart over one little window.
that's right,I know that the
codex leads to the window.
Isn't it lucky you were already
planning to steal it for me?
That was what you were
planning,wasn't it?
- of course.
- good.
that would be best for everyone.
<font
color=#238E68>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-ProudlyPresents
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET-静静的生活
<font
color=#238E68>white.collar.s05e08