更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
Woo hoo! One day to guys trip.
Hey Boog! When are you gonna bring your fine self down here
to fix up our habitat huh?
Just as soon as I finish helping Riley with the dam.
There we go.
You all set for tomorrow? it's gonna be awesome!
Sorry Boog! I gotta build this dam. No guys trip for me.
What? No guys trip? No guys trip? Have you lost your mind?
I gotta finish this or O'Grady will tear my eye.
Yeah.  That's okay it's cool.
We'll think about you while we're making this and talking trash.
I'm not sure that you can fit in there jerky!
Hey I don't know maybe the whole batch?
Alright you troops! Let them fly!
Hey you need anything else just let me know.
We gotta get on the road bright and early tomorrow baby.
Uh about that Boog. I've got a wee problem.
With all the new kids I'm not done collecting my nuts.
Believe me lad. I'd rather be skittling with you.
Than getting my minds with these boffin goons.
Yeah right.
Ant! Guys' trip?
No can't do bugger! I got too many.  responsibilities.
No problem. Birdie?
- Sorry Boog.  - Great.
Surfs Danny? Let me guess.
Uh. _ we cannot go suddenly.
That's what I thought.
That's okay. At least I've got Elliot.
He won't let me down. It'll be like old times.
Me and he. The original partners.
- Sshh. _ Quiet.  - Koo! Koo-koo!
- Giselllal Gesalital I was just looking for your dad.  - Sshhh.
Rabbit fight huh?
Yeah count me in. Where's your little bro?
You'll never find me here.
Alright let's see. Where to hide?
Ahhh  _ X marks the spot!
- Got you! - Gotcha!
You're out!
You gotta work on the landing.
- reat game dad.  - Yeah great game you guys.
- That was awesome.  - Alright when your mother asks.
You'll say I lost for protecting you from a wild boar.
And a sidekick ferret.
- Mom's gonna kill you.  - I was attacked by a ferret.
- No you weren't.  - Dad. Stop telling Elvis to lie.
Mom says you're not supposed to do that.
That wasn't a lie? It was uh. It was a reverse!
A stretch of a non-actual. Boog. Buddy back me up here.
ust tell the truth. it's the only way to roll.
Exactly what I was saying.
And stay in school.And don't talk to strangers.And never run with scissors.
So Boogster you wanna take the kids fishing?
- Actually Elliot. I'm kinda getting ready for guys'.  -I see where you're going with this.
It's time to teach survival skills.
- I was hoping to  - Grab a baseball.
- Well I..  - Acupuncture? Origami?
- Elliot Elliot  -Yoga? Sumo wrestling?Pods. What happened to pods right?
I tell you what. Just take them. Do whatever you want.
- I'm trying to get ready for guys' trip!  - Oh yeah!
- So are you definitely going?  - How could I miss it?
-Yeah I knew I could count on you.  - Elliot!
Remember to tell Boog that you can't go on guys' trip.
I meant to say I have to babysit the kids.
'Cos Giselle's going to see her mother.
That's okay E. Don't sweat it.
You've got family obligations. And sometimes you've got to cancel.
Sometimes? Don't you mean always?
- How long have you known about this?  - Two weeks
Two weeks? Oh just forget it.
- I don't know why I even bother.  - Boog!
Oh he'll get over it. Just like he did when I canceled the fishing trip.
- I guess rabbit fight's over.  - Pretty much.
…
Mother! I was attacked by a ferret!
I guess me and Elliot. We weren't as tight as I thought we were.
Oh hey. You're not gonna cancel on me too are you?
'Cos bears gotta stick together.
You know what I like about you dinkleman?
You're always there when I need you.
And don't worry. We're gonna have a blast tomorrow.
This will be the best guys' trip ever. You'll see!
Elliot. Three meals a day. And everyone in bed by sunset.
I know.
And make sure to apologise to Boog when he gets back. Okay
For what?
For some things you said yesterday.
And for some things you forgot to say two weeks ago?
Kids. Keep an eye on your dad.
Bye mom!
We love you! Safe journey!
Have fun!
- Have fun with the old dadillacs.  What was that Elliot?
I love you. Say hi to your mother for me.
I will.
What are we gonna do first hm? father?
Don't worry kids.
I've got a tons of things planned.
Right. When does uncle Boog get back again?
it's gonna be fun!
Then he realised
that his best one horn friend in the world had abandoned him.
And worse than that? All that was left on his hand was.
A hook!
This is very fun.
Well I guess it could be worse.
Who am I kidding? This whole thing was a bad idea.
It's not a guys' trip with only one guy?
I mean. it's not like I changed? He's the one who changed.
He's the one who flakes all the time.  - But he has a family.
You have to be more understanding.
- Yeah.  - Understanding my butt!
You're better off without that under privileged broken horn plank cancel it.
- But you guys are partners.  - Partners?
Who cares baby? That deer ain't got nothing on us.
Yeah! You know you're right!
You know what would be great to eat just about now?
Another woo-hoo bar. And I know just the place to get it.
Beautiful.
Now all we need are the balloons and you'll be ready to go!
hehe
Don't worry baby.
I'll never let anything happen to you ever again.
Hello. ladies!
Don't you all love my finest evening?
Hooty-O's? Hoo- Hoo.
Coco Ding bats. My favourite!
Honey? Now that's more like it.
There you go buddy. Don't worry. Nobody's driving.
Hey rabbit!
You ain't leaving 'til you eat those Coco Dingbats.
This is the best guys' trip ever!
Me and Dinkleman agree with you a hundred percent!
Rabbit loves Dinkleman. Dinkleman loves rabbit.
Was what that Dink?
Can't go on guys' trip because I'm married?
No deer on guys' trip.
Bla bla bla guys' trip.
Dink? We gotta go somewhere where folks don't let us down.
Place where we fit in. A real home.
Wow. A place like that.
With other bears who totally get us.
If only we knew what that was.
Wait a minute.
A place where no one lets you down.
You stay here rabbit. Keep your eye on the stash.
Doug. Why do you always let me down?
Circus in two days.
You could at least pretend to care.
Oh was I supposed to catch you?
How classy.
Rehearsals over!
I'm telling you Alistair.
One of these days I'm gonna give that diva a piece of my mind.
- I'm sure you will.  I mean back where I came from.
- I know the zoo.  - No.. No.. No…
- For the last time.  - It's the Wild Animal Park.
There's a difference you know?
Anyway. When I was in the Wild Animal Park. No one treated me like that.
All the animals worshiped me.
There was one grizzly. One king of the jungle. Me.
Just as soon as we get out of here. We're gonna find a place just like that.
And I won't forget your help.
I'll be king. And you'll be.
Well we'll find something for you to be.
OK here's the plan. You lift the cart. And we'd both squeezed through.
- Go on. Give it a try.  - You want me to pull something?
Have I ever done you wrong before?
- You promise to take me with you?  - Of course I will.
- You're the Yin to my.  - Yang.
What? No! What kind of word is Yang?
I was thinking more like. You're the 'Yin' to help me get 'Yout'!
Now let's hurry up before someone sees us.
Come on. What are you waiting for?
A little help? Please?
Now you're supervising that's good.
You want something done? You gotta do it yourself.
Too heavy!
Ssshh. Someone will hear you.
Yeah I know. We need another set of arms.
Hey I'm upset too. You can't take this on personal?
We all have our limitations?
Oh hey!
That wheel's on your hoof. Doesn't that hurt?
Now where were we?
Oh yeah. We need another set of arms.
Question is. Where to find it?
Protect me!
What in the world?
Ho! Another grizzly in the flesh!
You don't know how long I've waited for this day.
Yo you got some kind of thing going out of your neck.
- I know. It's called Alistair.  - Hola! Comme es ta?
- What do you want bear?  - The name's Boog.
Man! Another grizzly? This will be so great!
We'll go fishing have rabbit fights. Be best friends!
- Wow. She's here too?  - Hold up. Are you talking about Ursa?
She's difficult to catch.
- She is like Bear-vana  - Bear-vana?
Listen Boog. We're busy here. Go back to where you came from okay?
Back where I came from?
- Back there. I'm the only bear.  - The only bear?
- Yeah. All the other animals? They.  - Worship you?
- What?  - Oh yeah that sounds fantastic.
Didn't you hear me? I said I'm the only bear.
You must be so lonely.
The only lonely bear.
That's very sad. I promise I wouldn't do this but.
- Right.   - Right.
Sounds terrible.
Give me just a second.
What are you doing? Don't you see this is our chance?
We get the bear to help us move the carts and we're out of here!
But the circus will miss us!
- They'll send a search party!  - You're right.
I'll go.
- But you. But you.  - Trust me. I got it all figured out.
Listen Boog. You and me? We're gonna do all those things you talked about.
- Fishing camping.  - Oh and rabbit fights?
Sure! Girls rabbits whatever you want.
So here's what I'm gonna do for you!
I'm gonna find a place where we can all be best friends together.
- Really? You'd do that for me?  - In a bear-minute.
We're grizzlies Gotta look out for each other.
So here's the thing.
We gotta swap places so the circus doesn't know I'm gone.
But I come back tomorrow night. And you me and Ursa. We go on a kind of..
Bears' trip?
Bears' trip. Bears' trip. Together.
- Alright! I'm in.  - Great.
Now hold still for just a second.
Keep it down and stop moving
Oh yeah. This is gonna work!
Now what about me?
Hey like you said. If they figure out you're missing
you're missing they'll send a search party.
Don't worry. I'll bring someone back tomorrow night to swap with you.
When I say three lift as hard as you can.
- Got it?  - Got it
One two three.
You'd better hide that doll so nobody gets suspicious.
- What doll?  - That one. In your hand.
You mean Dinkleman? He ain't no doll!
He's my bro! My boy! My Blouse
Right.
Hey so where's that all for only bear place you were talking about?
You know just so I make sure I stay away from it.
Over the mountain pass forest and down by the stream.
Cool! Thanks! See you tomorrow night!
So. [Speaking in Spanish]? Hm?
When can I meet Ursa?
Perhaps it's better to do that in the morning.
When you're a little more. Awake. no?
- I don't know why I'm so tired.  - Oh. . Si. . .
Could it be the chocolates?
So what are you? Some kind of lama?
I'm an Argentinian Carnelian.
What's an Argentinian Carnelian?
It's a kind of lama.
Nice digs.
I just want you to know. That I [Speaking in Spanish]
That you came all this way. Just to meet another grizzly.
Oh Mr. Weenie mommy's going to miss you so much.
I promised myself I wouldn't cry.
Now remember. Play nice with everybody.
Ready for your third dinner?
Mommy and Bob are going to look for Big Foot. Okay sugar plum?
Remember. mommy loves you!
- Wow! Is she always like this?  - Yeah but it's not so bad.
And my friends! it's so good to see you all!
Hey you too! You look great.
Weenie it's been ages.
Thank you for it.
Why?
- Who is our new friend?  - I'd like you to meet Nate. Nate meet Mr. Weenie.
- Hello  - He's a strong silent type.
You! Are trying my patience!
Come on! Work you! Work! Work! Work!
- Fussy.  -Yeah?
- Nine?  - Yeah? You know
some animals are much kinder once they've been
Fixed!
Oh.. Hi..Mr. Weenie. Come and sit with me.
We can watch the television together.
He's not still mad at me is he?
I think his angry days are behind him. If you know what I mean.
One night only! The great Maslova Family Circus!
Hey! That's Boog!
I don't remember Boog's fur being so light and spiky like that.
Listen I know Boog as 'Zat' guy Boog!
Wow if that is Boog he sure looks terrible.
Of course he looks terrible! They're trying to kill him! This is horrible!
Look out Boog! Poor Boog.
We have to do something!
Let's go save him! Oh I wanna go save him.
- Oh please please please please.  - We must hurry!
How? Have you noticed? We're in the air stream.
There's no way out of here. How are we gonna save him?
- Are you thinking what I'm thinking?  - No.
But if we climb out of that vent.
I could track us to the circus. To save Boog.
Yeah the coast is clear!
Keep it moving keep it moving! Keep it moving.
Relax Fifi.
Remember what the vet said about staying calm?
You stay calm! With 500 pounds of animal on your back!
- Nice stitches!  - ah
Marshmallows?
Slightly burned.
Mixed with enoki.
- Robust poop!  - What's with you always with the poop?
Ah-ha! The circus! This way!
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Come on. Who's up for a rabbit fight?
Can't we wait for uncle Boog to get back?
- He was supposed to be home last night.  - Yeah!
Do you think he's still mad at you for ditching him on guys' trip?
He can stay on guys' trip forever as far as I'm concerned.
What does he think?
That I can just you know.
Leave the kids alone while Giselle visits the mother in law of doom?
- Dad.  - Children needs constant attention.
- You ignore them for one second.   -Dad!
Come here Little E.
You're not going rogue son.
- Dad let's just play okay?  - Good idea.
We don't need uncle Boog.
Rabbit fights are way more fun without him anyway.
You're out.
Gotcha. New game?
Well that's enough fun for one day.
- Now can we wait for uncle Boog to come back?  - Boog Boog Boog.
From now on we will no longer mention his name.
Okay ….
So…What do you wanna play next?
Well how about a game of. Shrub.. jump?
Diving? Where we jump into the nearest shrub.
- And uh.. come on Elvis I'll show you.  - Dad!
No! It's poison ivy!
It's part of the game.
Whoever scratches first. Loses!
I win!
Ooh that has gotta hurt.
Okay who's hungry?
Dad. We need uncle B.
I mean. We need someone Taller. To reach a branch that high.
Not so.
Who knows more about getting honey than a deer huh?
Come here Little E.
Spine so frail.
- Dad?  - Quiet Gisella.
The slightest sound could wake the bees.
Bees!
At least getting stung will take his mind off the itching.
Yeah.
Hey! Keep it down!
Too much chocolate.
- Hey why did you do that?  - Just hold still.
Give a little poof over here. A tease over there.
- A pull a tug.  - A comb.Wow!
Speaking in Spanish
Get a camera because you are Perfecto!
The spitting image.
They will never know the difference. Now let us go dance.
Doug is here everybody!
Remember what they say about not talking.
If you don't have something nice to say?
Wow. She's beautiful.
I see what's going on here.
What are you talking about? Nothing's going on here.
Okay.
- I'm serious.  - Hm-hm?
Hey I'm just happy to meet another grizzly. That's all.
Whatever you say. Tiger. Show me your strength.
So uh…Hey Ursa.
I thought I'd introduce myself because you know.
Doug? Why is voice low?
Are you again.  to be sick?
- I'm not actually.  -You'd better not be.
No! I mean um.. hey!
Watch it with that stick little dude! Come on Doug. Arms up! Why must we go through this everyday?
A little bribe perhaps? It's chocolate! You love chocolate.
Come on arms up! Please.
Now we are ready. Let's begin.
- Right foot up!  - Left foot up!
- Slower  - Faster.
Jump! Squat leg!
Hey! Oh! Oh! Ahhh!
- Stop! Wildly bear!
Hit it!
- Wow. You can really move.  - You ready?
Hey I was born ready baby.
Wait I'm not. I'm not ready for.
Why can't you just once be there when I need you?
Oh wait! Ursa let me explain.
- I'm not.  - Doug! I don't want excuses.
- Maybe if you just Cut the lift.  - No wait! I could've caught you.
It's just that I'm not.
- Doug. Thanks a lot!  - Yeah thanks Doug okay?
He only thinks all about himself.
- Listen I'm not.  - Doug. That was worse than yesterday.
Oh wait! Ursa.
Uh.. give her some time to cool down maybe okay?
But I have to tell her who I really am.
There will gonna be plenty of time for that. When we are all living in Bear-vana.
Trust me.
If there is one thing I know. It is women.
And. Musical theater. But that is not important right now.
What is important.
Is that women. Do not like to be rushed.
Look Alistair buddy.
I wait in here until Doug is back at sunset
And everything is gonna be fine.
Alright Alistair. If you say so.
Alright ladies buckle up.
One two three four. - Look I'm flying!
This must be the place. Bear-vana.
Finally. I'm the only bear.
And all the animals are gonna worship me. Just like they did Boog.
Boog's back everybody!
Boog! - Boog! - Thank goodness he's back!
About time.
Yeah I know. It's good to finally be here.
You look terrible! And your voice seems worse!
- Yeah. Complete Gaga girl.  - What are you talking about?
My voice is as smooth as silk.
Must have been rough out there.
Rough? Yeah it was rough alright.
That's why I look terrible. My voice sounds like Ka-Ka.
Now why don't you all run along and fetch me some goodies?
Boog!
Here. Hold these for a second.
How dare you show your face around here? After what you've done?
Gotta go polish my
Uh…me too. Me three.
Yeah…
Dad. I thought you were going to apologise?
Apologise? If anyone should apologise it's him.
To me. For…
For…
This! And this! Then this!
Well? Uh ….
The silent treatment.
Well I too can play at that game. Only I'm not playing.
I was fine before I met you.
Oh sure I was tied to the hood of the car.
Sorry uncle Boog. Dad hasn't been the same since you've been gone.
Now look at me. A pathetic shell.
And all because of you!
it's too late now Boog. This deer Has sailed.
Sorry uncle Boog. I hope you guys can work things out.
Dad!
We're all glad you're back uncle Boog!
That is one seriously messed up deer.
Ooh. that's better. Good to be myself again.
Time to hit the road.
Doug?
- He's not coming back.  - Give him a chance.
It's still early. Besides he's a grizzly.
We're family.
It's all a lie. There is no Bear-vana.
- Come on Alistair. He'll be back.  - Grizzlies hate each other.
- It's in their genes.  - What are you talking about?
- Grizzlies don't hate each other.  - The mens do!
They are.[Speaking in Spanish]
Doug lied so you would help him escape.
And I…I was his partner in crime!
In crime!
Who have I become?
If Doug's not coming back.
Then Ursa won't talk to me. What am I doing here?
This one goes to my girlfriend.
Out on the Pampas.
I'm all alone.
My heart has crushed to nada.
What are you looking at?
Nothing. That was well you were. That was beautiful.
- You are making fun.  - No! No! Really!
Listen Ursa. I know you've got no reason to believe me.
But I gotta tell you the truth!
I'm not Doug. I'm Boog!
You are right. I have no reason to believe you.
Look. I never should've come here.
I know that now. This was all a big mistake.
- Why is fur dark?  - Like I told you.
I'm not Doug. I'm Boog.
I was just you know. Looking for a place where I belong.
So if you just give me a hand moving one of the carts. I'll be out of your hair.
Oh now I see truth.
You want me to help you escape. And ruin circus!
- No!  - You are pathetic Doug.
No Ursa seriously.
- You twanged?  - No.
Okay 'cos I thought I heard my name.
It doesn't matter.
I. _ just want you to know that I am sorry.
I really thought Doug was my best friend.
That's okay.
- I suck at picking best friends too.  - Are we good? You and me?
- Yeah! We're good.  - Excellente.
I promise I will never tell you I'm coming back when I'm not.
And I promise I'll make time for you..
Even when I got a bunch of important things going on.
- Amigos?  - Yeah! Amigos.
Oohh. _ this is nice. Talking like this.
We will do this every night. A kind of.  guys chat.
Guys chat? I like that.
Since you're stuck here.  A little advice okay?
The way to a woman's heart. Is through. Her. Art.
- The circus is coming!  - How can a circus be coming? A circus is a tent.
With posts stuck in the ground!
- This is a highway!  - Oh
Oh no! No!
Thank you.
We made it. Uh. _ that wasn't easy.
This still doesn't look like a circus.
Strange.
It sure smells like it.
No! I need those! I need those! I need them!
There you go baby.
Just like new.
Hi how's it going Stew?
So far so good. I got your balloon order.
- How could you have been so wrong?  - I don't know?
- Maybe it's allergy.  - Wait a minute. Look in the window!
The circus poster will tell us where to find Boog.
Quickly! Before we are seen!
There you go baby.
Wait 'til you see the super balloon bouquet I whipped up for ya.
Nice exploration of negative space.
Hurry up! I should be on top! I should be on the top!
A little closer!
Nine a little closer.
Ooohhh. Meat snack. Look they're colored.
It's perfect replacement. I need those.
- Hey! Stop that!  - We have been discovered!
You just.  Hey! Come back here!
- No!  - I'm gonna get you!
Get back here!
Gotcha!
Meat Snack!
- Meat Snack.  - Come back here!
You knew you were going to this guys' trip.
For two whole weeks before you told him.
- Maybe I should go talk to him.  - Hold it right there big fella.
So you forgot.
If he was a real friend. He'd understand.
You're absolutely right! Boog is a real friend.
Your life is a mess without him.
By mess you mean awesome!
- No I mean mess!  - Awesome!
- Stop that!  - Enough!
Dad?
Girls. I was just.
Not important. So is it breakfast time again?
Lunch? Dinner? Play time?
Is it a dope problem?
- What's a dope problem?  - Nothing what's up?
Mom always says that.
You should try and work things out.
You're upset with me?
You're right! I've been a complete failure.
How can you ever forgive me?
Uh.  We were talking about you and uncle Boog?
You should go talk to him.
Or maybe we should go and get uncle Boog.
Bring him.  here.
And you're not a complete failure.
You're a dad. We love you no matter what.
Father?
It's okay.
All for the taking.
Hey Boog! Can you help me with my digging?
Can you help me get my wife unstacked from the pine?
Can you help me with my nuts?
Thought we were gonna mark the perimeter?
- Hold on!  - What about our habitat?
- Yeah!  - Hey Boog can you help me with thing?
#￥%……
Do you think dad and uncle Boog will ever forgive each other?
What's going to happen if they don't?
Enough! Enough!
I'm not your servant!
I'm king of the jungle!
Well technically the lion is the king of the jungle.
And this is the forest.
A jungle tends to be denser and hotter.
- Deer!  - What? I travel.
Fine! Then I'm king of the forest!
Either way. Things are gonna change around here.
You! Go get me some nice ripped berries.
And you two. Find me a good waterfall where I can have a nice soak.
- And you Doily!  - Riley!
Whatever!
You and your guys go build me a nice comfortable bed. Up on that hill.
- Don't you mean in your cave?  - Oh yeah.
My cave.
- Move!  - Better do what he says.
He's gone bluhnicaccasl
He has really lost it.
- Yeah.  - Could be stress. Big mad bear disease.
- It could be stupid deer disease.  - Seriously? Is that going around?
Maybe we've all been taking him for granted a little too much.
Oh! Hello girls.
How long have you two been standing there?
We just uh. Got here?
What is that? Some kind of nervous tick?
Oh uh. Nervous? Who's nervous?
What do you girls want?
We just wanted to say.
How glad we are that you're back. Bye!
Hey. _ Perhaps Boog is uh.  changing huh?  - That's not it.
We change all the time huh?
Just yesterday. Deni he's in love with foei gras.
Then I tell him what it is and. He can't talk he can't sleep.
Can you just go and find our mom? Please?
- I'll be your best friend.  - Alright alright
You twist my wing. But only because the two of you are so good.
Thank you Serge!
You guys rock!
Deni follow my tail!
What do you think?
Your tie is a smart bow tie. Perfecto!
Aahh. _ I see you're sweating. Nervous anticipation.
What are you talking about?
- I'm not sweating?  - Yes you are.
I see a little drop of moisture on your upper brow.
Right there.
- Hello little sweat.  - Yeah sweat.
Nothing to worry! You're gonna knock her out with the real you!
She'd be like. _ Doug! Who is Doug? I'm all about Boog baby!
There is something different about Doug.
Looks like someone got a hair brush for birthday.
- Still think I'm Doug?  -Yes.
How about now?
- What are you trying to prove Doug?  - That I'm Boog!
- Let's try the ladder.  - Oh forget it.
-Well can you ride.   - Unicycle?
Check this out.
See? I'm Boog!
Look I'm sorry we got off on the wrong foot.
But once you get to know me. The real me.
-You might like me.  - Leave me alone!
Doug was afraid of heights.
If you're really Boog. Why don't you come up here and prove it?
Don't give up. Follow her. She wants you to.
That's.  pretty high.
You're probably right.
That impressed a pretty girl.
Hm.  -Just go!
One can't help but be moved no?
Wow. Now you believe me?
I believed you when you ride the unicycle.
Doug couldn't do that either.
You mean you made me climb all the way up here for nothing?
Not for nothing.
You need to be punished for juggling the dog.
Boog. What a nice name.
If you want to practice the dance.
Meet me outside.
You put a girl in grizzly!
Cats tonight you're gonna play your little whiskers off.
And a one and a two. Miaw miaw miaw miaw…
- You dance very well Boog.  - I practiced.
I figured you might trip me or something if I messed up.
Me? I would never do that.
Yeah but I might. So you'd better watch yourself.
Oh definitely looking good.
You are not like other bears.
- Why is this?  - I don't know.
Maybe it's because I grew up with humans.
- Really? Me too! I grew up in circus!  - Me too!
Well.  Kinda.
I mean I used to do this show back in Timber Line.
It wasn't a whole circus. But I juggled and stuff.
You and me we are not like other grizzlies.
We are not like. Anybody else in the world!
Ooh that was so inspiring.
So moving.
So.  so prof undo.
Let us retire to the caravan. For our end of the day talk.
- We should practice the lift.  - I'd like that.
Come. We will hook. Over to the trailer.
Time to share.
Like the amigos we are!I pulled something.
If just once I could perform the dance. The way it was meant to be.
I would never need to perform it again.
Boogie! What about the guys chat?
Huh? Yeah. Ursa and I need to practice.
Doily! Make sure you get that spot right by my third
Ooh! Yeah! That's it!
Sorry Boogster. Just a little cramp at my neck.
Seriously? Six pack take some pride in your work!
Any chance we can take a little break?
A break? You all just had a break. Like. _ six hours ago.
- What is going on here?  - Giselle! Thank goodness! You're back!
Now you can vent him.
Excellent! Re-enforcements. You two! Go get me some more berries.
And you! How about you start massaging my paws?
All this clapping is making me sore.
Now!
- Who are you?  - What are you talking about?
Boog would never yell like that. Especially at fawns.
- So who are you?  - Who am I?
- If you haven't noticed I'm.  -Boog!
I'm so sorry I let you down.
- Can you ever forgive me?  - Does that answer your question?
Giselle! Oh thank goodness you're back.
See? Even the crazy broken deer knows I'm Boog.
- Do you even know his name?  - Of course I do.
- It's…Uh…  - Starts with an E.
E …. Emily?
- Edward?  - What about 2 L's?
Eleanor? Oh whatever. It doesn't matter what his name is.
All that matters. Is that I'm a grizzly. And I'm king of the jungle.
- First of all this is a forest.  - I tried to tell him.
- And second of all. What have you done with Boog?  - Yeah!
Where is Boog? What have you done?
What difference does it make?
You would all do what I say.
- I'm your Boog now!  - Boog!
Boog now that we're best friends again. What do you say we go on guys trip? Just the two of us?
He's not Boog!
Oops. You're not Boog! That's not Boog!
Oh thank goodness. I thought you were mad at me.
But now I know that you weren't. Because you're not even you!
- What a relief.  - Elliot?
- Yes dear?  - Elliot!
Oh right. What have you done with Boog?
He's locked away somewhere. You'll never find him!
Especially after tonight when they take him back to Russia.
- Russia? Who's Russia?  - it's not a 'who'! It's a 'where'.
And believe me. You could walk for the rest of your life and never get there.
You won't get away with this!
No? Who's gonna stop me?
[Panting]
- Okay! Okay! Okay I'm ready to talk.  - I'm listening.
He's at the circus. Just follow the search lights and you'll find it.
That's a good one. What search lights?
Now let's go save Boog! 'Cos I owe him a big apology.
And because we miss him and we want him to come home before they ship him off to Russia!
Yeah!
- Impostor!  - Sorry.
That Boog sure is one lucky guy.
I Wish I had a friend like that.
Wait. I do have a friend like that.
Thank goodness that nice man at the Punimart called us.
You poor dear's. Must have been hungry
to go all that way to find food.
But don't worry. Mommy won't make that mistake again.
That's enough isn't it Bob? Maybe we should stay.
No no you're right.
My snugly woddly and I need this time apart.
Kick me out Bob before I change my mind.
Well we might as well dig in since all hope is lost.
Wait for it wait for it!
Oh Meat Snack!
Excuse me for a moment.
I hate cats.
- So do I.  - Fi! Look! The circus!
I've seen of these lights before.
Wait! You mean the circus is just behind those trees?
Yes! My new old friend!
Boog is closer than we ever imagined.
Alistair? What's wrong?
And once again.
- I have been tossed away.  - Hey hey Alistair. Come on buddy.
Don't bother me!
I sat in my trailer all night.
Waiting for the sweet sound of paws. Knocking on my [Speaking in Spanish]
But no. All I hear…Is the sounds…Of loneliness.
- What are you talking about?  - Have you forgotten? Already?
Do I mean so little to you?
It's time for guys chat Just us on guys chat.
You blew off guys chat!
- You blew it!  - Oh man! I totally forgot!
See I was with Ursa and
Well you know how it is when you're all caught up and.
Look Alistair. Sometimes it's hard to find time for everything.
And everyone that's important to you.
- Alistair.  - En
Alistair. You're right.
I've been a bad friend.
You might not believe this but
I know exactly how you feel right now.
And I'm sorry.
It's okay. I forgive you.
- Seriously?  - That's what friends do!
Amigos!
Don't worry! We're gonna have plenty of time for guys chat
Once we get back to Russia.
Huh? Russia?
Oh sure! Oh you're gonna love it there.
All the snow and the ice.
You're gonna love the way it pierces your skin.
And makes your. Oh I get excited just to think about it.
Plus it's only 5 000 miles away.
So you can visit home every year or two.
Or three. Maybe four.
You're gonna be a polar bear. That's what you're gonna be.
Let's go troops! Look alive!
Uncle Boog never took us on a rescue mission.
Yeah I know. This is way cool!
You should go out of town more often mother.
Elvis I don't think so.
Release the emergency break.
We are moving!
- Hang on to your little horses.  - Steady…Steady…
Alright everyone steady.
I can't see a thing!
Why?
Out of the way! Out of the way!
Steady…Steady…
Oh no! Oh no! They're gone! They're gone!
- What's gone?
- Turn left right?  - Right!
No! Nine! I said left!
No! No!
No! [Yelling]
I'm calling it a day.
It's worse than I thought.
They strap him to wheels and light him on fire. Then point and laugh!
It's torture at its worst!
We have to rescue Boog before. They make him wind into tiny whiny rope of death!
Let's go!
Wait! Their fortress is in-penetrable.
Unbreakable
it's hard to break into. So here's what we're gonna do.
McSquizzy and Buddy you work on the left flank.
Kids you run the charging maneuver on the right.
Ian Giselle you find a chisel a toothbrush. And as many maracas as you can carry.
Or.  what about this instead?
Serge and Danny you find the exits.
Mom and Ian you stay and look out here and here.
While the rest of us sneak in here and rescue Boog.
- Yeah!  - That's ridiculous!
The tent's too big.
We need at least 6 more of us to pull that off.
Mr. Weenie? What are you guys doing here?
- We are here to safe Boog!  - Kick some pals!
- So are we!  - It's destiny.
Ladies and gentlemen! I'd like to welcome you
To the great Moslova Family Circus!
- Everyone clear about what to do?  - Yes! No problem.
Uh what was the middle part again?
Everyone spread out and try to find Boog. When you see him.
- Go get him.  - Alright let's move it out.
Be careful girls.
Okay mom.
- So. Come here often?  - Don't even think about it.
Stop acting like such a troop.
I really missed you guys.
- Yeah me too.  - A full house! This is fantastic!
Are Ursa and Doug ready to go?  - They're ready.
Boog. Where did the rest go?
You! You must be the new recruits!
Yeah yeah. That's what we are.
Come on let's go.
- Any sign of Boog?  - No I can't see him from here.
We need to get to higher ground. Like that.
Man I can't wait to get back and see Alistair. Back to my own cart.
Home cooking. Three meals a day.
I don't know Bob. This expo is a bust.
When we head back to the air stream.
Did you hear that? He's close by. I can smell him.
Let me try the bathing call.
Big Foot!
Ladies and gentlemen. The miraculous balancing [Russian language]
Stanley! Do you see him?
- I'm not seeing him.  - Please. Welcome The juggling pugs.
Fifi! Do you see him?
Great!
Boog!
Come on. Let's find a different spot.
You'd think we can't miss a 1 200 pound fat bear!
Ursa! Wait!
Come on Boog! Let's show them what you got.
I can't see a thing from back here. Any sign of Boog?
- Ursa!  - You're doing great Boog.
Oh you see him? Good! Let's get him!
- Mika! You have returned! Time to go back into space.  - It's dark in here! Let me out!
I'm coming Buddy!
Mr. Weenie!
Look Bob proof aliens do exist!
- Keep up handsome.  - Ursa!
Where are you uncle Boog?
Hi Fifi!
I hate dogs.
Uncle Boog!
Tell dad he's right there!
- Ursa! Ursa!  - Boog! What are you doing?
You need to get to your place.
I need to talk to you about Russia.
- It's so far away and…I'm not sure if I..  - Boog we need to focus here.
It's almost time for the big lift!
Come on Doug!
Dad! Dad! Dad!
Gesalital
Uncle Boog is right there!
- What are you saying? Right? Left?  - Left? Rig ht? Left?
- Boog!  - Elliot!
- Wait what are you doing here?  - Thank goodness I found you!
- We're here to rescue you.  -rescue me?
- Elliot I can't go!  - Doug! Pay attention!
Ready? Go Doug go!
Boog! It's worse than I thought. He's been brain washed.
And now Ursa. The great bear in disguise.
Featuring the flying nano plates.
Boog. Are you sure you can do this?
I don't know. Russia's a big step and.
No I mean the lift.
I've never been able to do it before and
If you are not 100 percent sure you can do it.
I'll be ready.
Plan B. Smash and grab. Smash everything and grab Boog.
Don't bother with me. Just another circus dancer.
You ready?
Come on Ursa! Go for it! I got you!
Boog! Okay guys smash and grab!
Please hold me.
He did it!
Oh she finally did it.
You got me.
Boog! You're safe! We're here to save you!
- Rescue accomplished!  - Yes!
What are you all doing here?
Come on let's get moving before your captors return.
Wow hold up Elliot! I appreciate you all trying to rescue me but
I need to talk to Ursa.
- Ursa? Who's Ursa?  - I am.
So.  what? She like your new best friend or something?
No I am.
What?
You have 2 new best friends?
I canceled one guys trip and the next thing I know I've been replaced.
- Twice.  - Elliot buddy. I'm sorry.
You haven't been replaced. You'll always be my BFF.
Are you apologizing?
Yeah. I forgive you. But only because you forgave me first.
Now let's ditch the goat and the babe and hit the road!
I am not a goat! I am a Iama.
Really? 'Cos you look more like an Argentinian Carnelian.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The musical scaling of Alistair!
Come on Boog.
We gotta get out of here.
Elliot Alistair. Hold on come on you guys.
- I'm not letting go  - Do it!
Guys..Come on. Stop!
Everybody just hold up!
Ursa. My beautiful Russian bear.
I came here looking for a place where I belong.
But what I found was so much more.
What I found Was you.
Oh Boog.
Come with me.
Come to the forest make me the happiest bear on earth.
Oh Boog. I really want to.
But I can't.
A Russian circus without a bear is like no circus at all.
I could never do that to them.
You should go.
I can see that they are more than just your friends.
They are your family.
And family should always stick together.
Come.
I will help you move the carts.
Boog. You should stay. I learn something too!
That friends want each other to be happy.
So if she makes you happy. Then you should be with her.
Elliot. That was really nice.
- You're awesome dad.  - Yeah!
I know.
These are tears of joy!
So beautiful!
Alistair!
You came back for me?
- Oh buddy! I'm glad to see you!  - Oh it's good to see you too!
- I'd like to breathe.  - Sorry I tricked you Boog.
Sometimes you don't know what you have until you've lost it.
I know exactly what you mean.
- Ursa.  - Doug.
Come on! We're late for our show!
Ladies and gentlemen. The duet you've been waiting for.
Looks like the circus has a bear.
Looks like you do too.
What are we waiting for? Let's go!
- Let them go.  - But the circus!
The circus Will be fine.
Or try to work to Rome.
A place that we call home.
- You sure you're cool with this?  - Absolutely!
It's important to make time for your friends.
Even when you have a babe around.
Oh yeah!
Dinklemanl I didn't know you were a girl!
Have fun Elliot!
And don't forget to keep an eye on Elvis.
Let's get move on! Guys trip waits for no deer!
That's right son.
You're old enough to take part in the sacred tradition that is.
Guys trip.
# On the road again #
#Just can't wait to get on the road again #
# I've always loved making music
with my friends #
#And I can't wait to get on the road again #
- He's not coming?  - He's gonna join us later.
Maybe we'll get some answers Bob.
Like if Mr. Weenie was probed or not.
# On the road again #
# Going places that I've never been #
# Seeing things that I may never see again #
#I can't wait to get on the road again #
Hey Alistair. Aren't you glad to be going back to Russia?
Oh truth said it amigo.
I hope I get to see my girlfriend.
Carmen I'm coming for you!
# On the road again #
# Like a band of gypsies we go down the highway #
# With the best friends #
# it's now the world keeps turning our way #
#In Norway#
Ooh. _ what is it?
It's just a little something something we set up for you.
This is so sweet.
Thank you for making me feel welcome.
Alright ladies.  Look alive!
Oh brother.
Oh arrest me officer.
Got it.
Shake it shake it. To the right two three four.
Who's up for the rabbit fight!
Look out baby.
Guys trip!
It doesn't getting any better than this.
Just me and my best friend in the world having a good time.
You got it Boog. BFF till the end.
￥%@……%&*
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：274796078