KUNG FU PANDA
更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
Legend tells of a legendary warrior...
...whose kung fu skills\nwere the stuff of legend.
He traveled the land\nin search of worthy foes.
I see you like to chew.\nMaybe you should chew on my fist!
The warrior said nothing,\nfor his mouth was full.
Then he swallowed. And then he spoke.
Enough talk. Let's fight!
Shashabooey!
He was so deadly in fact,
that his enemies would go blind from\noverexposure to pure awesomeness.
- My eyes!\n- He's too awesome!
- And attractive.\n- How can we repay you?
There is no charge for awesomeness.
Or attractiveness.
Kablooey!
It mattered not how many foes he faced.
They were no match for his bodacity!
Never before had a panda\nbeen so feared! And so loved.
Even the most heroic heroes in China,
the Furious Five,
bowed in respect\nto this great master.
We should hang out.
Agreed.
But hanging out would have to wait.
Because when you're facing\nthe 10,000 demons of Demon Mountain,
there's only one thing\nthat matters and that's...
Po! Get up!
You'll be later for work!
What?
Po! Get up!
Po. What are you doing up there?
Nothing.
Monkey! Mantis! Crane! Viper! Tigress!
Po! Let's go! You're late for work.
Coming!
Sorry, Dad.
Sorry doesn't make the noodles.
What were you doing up there?\nAll that noise.
Nothing. I just had a crazy dream.
About what?
What were you dreaming about?
What was I?
I was dreaming about...
...noodles.
Noodles? You were really\ndreaming about noodles?
Yeah. What else\nwould I be dreaming about?
Careful! That soup is sharp.
Oh, happy day!
My son, finally having the noodle dream!
You don't know how long I've been\nwaiting for this moment.
This is a sign, Po.
A sign of what?
You are almost ready to be entrusted\nwith the secret ingredient
of my Secret Ingredient Soup.
Then you will fulfill your destiny\nand take over the restaurant!
As I took it over from my father,\nwho took it over from his father...
...who won it from a friend in mahjong.
Dad, Dad, Dad, it was just a dream.
No, it was the dream.
We are noodle folk.\nBroth runs through our veins.
But, Dad, didn't you ever want\nto do something else?
Something besides noodles?
Actually, when I was young and crazy,
I thought about running away\nand learning how to make tofu.
Why didn't you?
Because it was a stupid dream.
Can you imagine me making tofu?
Tofu.
No! We all have our place in this world.
Mine is here, and yours is...
I know, is here.
No, it's at tables 2, 5, 7, and 12
Service with a smile.
Well done, students...\nif you were trying to disappoint me.
Tigress, you need more ferocity!\nMonkey, greater speed.
Crane, height. Viper, subtlety.\nMantis...
- Master Shifu.\n- What?!
It's Master Oogway. He wants to see you.
Master Oogway, you summoned me?\nIs something wrong?
Why must something be wrong\nfor me to want to see my old friend?
So, nothing's wrong?
Well, I didn't say that.
You were saying?
I have had a vision.
Tai Lung will return.
That is impossible! He is in prison.
Nothing is impossible.
Zeng!
Fly to Chorh-Gom prison and tell them
to double the guards, double\ntheir weapons, double everything!
Tai Lung does not leave that prison!
Yes, Master Shifu!
One often meets his destiny\non the road he takes to avoid it.
We must do something! We can't let him\nmarch on the valley, take his revenge!
He'll...
Your mind is like this water,\nmy friend.
When it is agitated,\nit becomes difficult to see.
But if you allow it to settle...
...the answer becomes clear.
The Dragon Scroll.
It is time.
But who? Who is worthy to be trusted\nwith the secret to limitless power?
To become the Dragon Warrior?
I don't know.
Excuse me. Pardon me. Sorry.
Watch it!
Sorry. Suck it up!
Sorry. A thousand pardons.
What?
(The Notice)
Master Oogway's choosing\nthe Dragon Warrior! Today!
Everyone! Get to the Jade Palace! One of\nthe Five is gonna get the Dragon Scroll!
We've waited 1,000 years for this!\nTake the bowl!
This is the greatest day\nin kung fu history! Just go!
Po! Where are you going?
To the Jade Palace.
You're forgetting your noodle cart.
The whole valley will be there,\nand you'll sell noodles to all of them.
Selling noodles?
But, Dad, I was thinking, maybe I...
- Yeah?\n- I was thinking maybe I...
...could also sell the bean buns.\nThey're about to go bad.
That's my boy!
I told you that dream was a sign.
Yeah. Glad I had it.
- I'm a kung fu warrior!\n- Me, too!
- There's spots at the top.\n- Let's go.
Come on. Come on!
Almost there.
What?
No! Oh, no!
- Sorry, Po.\n- We'll bring you back a souvenir.
No. I'll bring me back a souvenir.
It is an historic day.
Isn't it, Master Oogway?
Yes, and one I feared\nI would not live to see.
Are your students ready?
Yes, Master Oogway.
Know this, old friend.
Whomever I choose will not only bring\npeace to the valley...
...but also to you.
Let the tournament begin!
No, no, wait!
I'm coming! Wait, wait!
Yes!
Hey! Open the door!
Let me in!
Citizens of the Valley of Peace,
it is my great honor\nto present to you... Tigress!
Viper! Crane! Monkey! Mantis!
The Furious Five!
Yeah, the Furious Five!
Warriors, prepare!
Wait. No. Oh, peeky-hole.
- Ready for battle!\n- Yeah.
The Thousand Tongues of Fire.
Look at that.
Hey! Get out of the way!
And finally Master Tigress!
And believe me, citizens,\nyou have not seen anything yet.
I know!
Master Tigress! Face Iron Ox\nand his Blades of Death.
I sense the Dragon Warrior is among us.
Citizens of the Valley of Peace,
Master Oogway will now choose\nthe Dragon Warrior!
Oh, no! No, no, wait!
Yeah.
Po!
What are you doing?!
What does it look like I'm doing?! Stop!
I'm going to see the Dragon Warrior!
But I don't understand.\nYou finally had the noodle dream!
I lied. I don't dream\nabout noodles, Dad.
I love kung fu!
Come on, son. Let's get back to work.
OK.
Come back!
What's going on?
Where?
What are you pointing?
OK. Sorry.
I just wanted to see\nwho the Dragon Warrior was.
How interesting.
Master, are you pointing at me?
- Him.\n- Who?
- You.\n- Me?
The universe has brought us\nthe Dragon Warrior!
- What?\n- What?!
- What?!\n- What?!
Stop, wait! Who told you to?
Master Oogway, wait.
That flabby panda can't possibly be\nthe answer to our problem.
You were about to point at Tigress\nand that thing fell in front of her!
That was just an accident!
There are no accidents.
Forgive us, Master. We have failed you.
No. If the panda\nhas not quit by morning
then I will have failed you.
Wait! Wait, wait, wait!\nI bring a message...
...from Master Shifu.
What?!
"Double the guard?!"
"Extra precautions?!"
"Your prison may not be adequate?!"
You doubt my prison security?!
Absolutely not.
Shifu does. I'm just the messenger.
I'll give you a message\nfor your Master Shifu.
Escape from Chorh-Gom prison\nis impossible!
Impressive, isn't it?
It's very impressive.
One way in, one way out.
One thousand guards and one prisoner.
Yes, except that prisoner...
...is Tai Lung.
Take us down.
What are you doing?
Oh, my.
Behold Tai Lung.
I'm just gonna wait right here.
It's nothing to worry about.\nIt's perfectly safe.
Crossbows! At the ready!
Crossbows?
Hey, tough guy, did you hear?
Oogway's giving someone the Dragon\nScroll, and it's not gonna be you.
Don't get him mad.
What's he gonna do about it?\nI've got him completely immobilized.
Did I step on the wittle kitty's tail?
I'm good. I've seen enough.
I'll tell Shifu he\nhas nothing to worry about.
No, he doesn't.
I'll tell him that.
Can we please go now?
Dragon Warrior! Dragon Warrior!
Wait a second!
I think there's been a slight mistake.\nEveryone seems to think that I'm...
The Sacred Hall of Warriors! No way!
Look at this place.
Master Flying Rhino's armor,\nwith authentic battle damage!
The Sword of Heroes!
Said to be so sharp you can cut yourself\njust by looking.
The Invisible Trident of Destiny!
I've only seen paintings\nof that painting.
No!
The legendary Urn\nof Whispering Warriors.
Said to contain the souls\nof the entire Tenshu Army.
Hello.
Have you finished sight-seeing?
Sorry, I should have come to you first.
My patience is wearing thin.
Well, I mean, it's not like you\nwere going anywhere.
- Would you turn around?\n- Sure.
How's it going?
How do you get 5,000...\nMaster Shifu!
Someone... broke that.
But I'll fix it. Do you have some...
...glue?
A splinter.
So you're the legendary Dragon Warrior?
- I guess so.\n- Wrong!
You are not the Dragon Warrior. You will\nnever be the Dragon Warrior until...
...you have learned the secret\nof the Dragon Scroll.
So, how does this work?
Do you have a ladder,\nor a trampoline, or?
You think it's that easy?\nThat I'll just hand you the secret
- to limitless power?\n- No, I...
One must first master\nthe highest level of kung fu.
And that is impossible\nif that one is someone like you.
Someone like me?
Yes, look at you!\nThis fat butt! Flabby arms!
Those are sensitive in the flabby parts.
And this ridiculous belly.
And utter disregard\nfor personal hygiene.
Now, wait a minute.\nThat's uncalled for.
Don't stand that close.\nI can smell your breath.
Listen, Oogway said I was...
The Wuxi Finger Hold.\nNot the Wuxi Finger Hold!
Oh, you know this hold?
Developed by Master Wuxi\nin the Third Dynasty.
Then you know what happens\nwhen I flex my pinky.
- No, no!\n- You know the hardest part of this?
The hardest part is cleaning up\nafterwards.
OK, OK, take it easy.
Now listen closely, panda.
Oogway may have picked you,\nbut when I'm through with you,
I promise you, you're going to wish\nhe hadn't! Are we clear?
Yeah, we're clear. We're so clear.
Good.
I can't wait to get started.
- Let's begin.\n- Wait, wait, wait.
What?
- Now?\n- Yes, now.
Unless the great Oogway was wrong\nand you are not the Dragon Warrior.
Oh, OK, well...
I don't know\nif I can do all of those moves.
Well, if we don't try,\nwe'll never know, will we?
Yeah, it's just, maybe we can find\nsomething more suited to my level.
What level is that?
Well, I'm not a master, but...
...let's just start at zero. Level zero.
No. There is no such thing\nas level zero.
- Maybe I can start with that.\n- That?
We use that for training children and\npropping the door open when it's hot.
But if you insist...
The Furious Five!
You're bigger than your action figures.\nExcept, you, Mantis. You're the same.
Go ahead, panda.\nShow us what you can do.
Are they gonna watch, or should I wait\ntill they get back to work?
Hit it.
OK, yeah. I mean, I just ate.\nSo I'm still digesting.
So my kung fu might not be\nas good as... later on.
Just hit it.
All right.
What you got? You got nothing,\n'cause I got it right here.
You picking on my friends?\nGet ready to feel thunder.
I'm coming at you with crazy feet.
Come on. I'm a blur.\nYou've never seen bear style.
You've only seen praying mantis.
Or monkey style.
Or I could come at you snickety-snake.
Would you hit it!
All right. All right.
Why don't you try again?\nA little harder.
How's that?
(tooth)
That hurts.
This will be easier than I thought.
I'm feeling a little nauseous!
Those are hard!
My tenders.
How did I do?
There is now a level zero.
- There's no words.\n- No denying that.
What was Master Oogway thinking?
The poor guy's gonna get himself killed.
He is so mighty!
The Dragon Warrior fell out of the sky\non a ball of fire!
When he walks, the very ground shakes!
One would think Master Oogway would\nchoose someone who knew kung fu.
Yeah, or could at least touch his toes.
Or even see his toes.
OK.
Great.
Hi. You're up.
I am now.
I was just...
Some day, huh?
That kung fu stuff is hard work, right?\nAre your biceps sore?
I've had a long\nand rather disappointing day, so...
Yeah, I should probably\nget to sleep now.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Of course.\n- OK, thanks.
It's just...\nMan, I'm such a big fan!
You guys were amazing\nat the Battle of Weeping River.
Outnumbered a thousand to one,\nbut you didn't stop. You just...
Sorry about that.
Look, you don't belong here.
I know. I know. You're right.
I don't have... I just...
My whole life I dreamed of...
No, I meant you don't belong here.\nI mean, in this room. This is my room.
Property of Crane.
OK. Right, right.
So, you want to get to sleep.
- Yeah.\n- I'm keeping you up.
We got big things tomorrow.
All right. You're awesome.\nLast thing I'm gonna say. Bye-bye.
What was that?
I didn't say anything.
OK. All right. Good night.
Sleep well.
That seemed a little awkward.
Master Tigress!\nI didn't mean to wake you.
- You don't belong here.\n- Yeah, of course.
This is your room.
I mean, you don't belong\nin the Jade Palace.
You're a disgrace to kung fu,\nand if you have
any respect for who we are\nand what we do,
you will be gone by morning.
Big fan!
I see you have found the Sacred\nPeach Tree of Heavenly Wisdom.
Is that what this is? Sorry. I thought\nit was just a regular peach tree.
I understand.\nYou eat when you are upset.
Upset? I'm not upset.\nWhat makes you think I'm upset.
So why are you so upset?
I probably sucked more today\nthan anyone in the history of kung fu.
In the history of China.\nIn the history of sucking!
Probably.
And the Five! Man, you should've\nseen them! They totally hate me.
Totally.
How is Shifu ever going to turn me\ninto the Dragon Warrior?
I mean, I'm not like the Five.
I've got no claws, no wings, no venom.
Even Mantis has those... thingies.
Maybe I should just quit\nand go back to making noodles.
Quit, don't quit.
Noodles, don't noodles.
You are too concerned\nwith what was and what will be.
There's a saying:
Yesterday is history,
tomorrow is a mystery,
but today is a gift.
That is why it is called the present.
- Oh, no!\n- What's happening?!
To your battle stations! Go! Go! Go!
Fire crossbows!
Fire!
Tai Lung is free! I must warn Shifu.
- Not going anywhere! Neither is he!\n- Let go of me!
Bring it up!
Wait! Bring it back!
- He's coming this way!\n- He won't get far. Archers!
We're dead. So very, very dead.
Not yet we're not. Now!
- Can we run now?\n- Yes.
(Commander is killed)
I'm glad Shifu sent you.
I was beginning to think\nI'd been forgotten.
Fly back there and tell them...
...the real Dragon Warrior\nis coming home.
Good morning, Master!
Panda!
Wake up!
He's quit.
What do we do now, with the panda gone?\nWho will be the Dragon Warrior?
All we can do is resume our training\nand trust that in time,
the true Dragon Warrior\nwill be revealed.
What are you doing here?!
Hi! Good morning, Master!
I thought I'd warm up a little.
You're stuck.
Stuck? Nah. What? Stuck?
Nah. This is one of my...\nYeah, I'm stuck.
- Help him.\n- Oh, dear.
Maybe on three. One, two...
...three.
- Thank you.\n- Don't mention it.
- No, really, I appreciate...\n- Ever.
You actually thought you could learn\nto do a full split in one night?
It takes years to develop\none's flexibility!
And years longer to apply it in combat!
Put that down!
The only souvenirs we collect here are\nbloody knuckles and broken bones.
Yeah! Excellent.
Let's get started.
- Are you ready?\n- I was born re...
I'm sorry, brother.\nI thought you said you were ready.
That was awesome! Let's go again!
I've been taking it easy on you, panda.\nBut no more.
Your next opponent will be me.
All right! Yeah, let's go!
Step forth.
The true path to victory is to find\nyour opponent's weakness...
...and make him suffer for it.
Oh, yeah!
To take his strength\nand use it against him...
...until he finally falls...
...or quits.
A real warrior never quits.
Don't worry, Master. I will never quit!
If he's smart,\nhe won't come back up those steps.
But he will.
He's not going to quit, is he?
He's not going to quit bouncing,\nI'll tell you that.
I thought you said acupuncture\nwould make me feel better.
Trust me, it will.
It's just not easy finding the right\nnerve points under all this...
- Fat?\n- Fur. I was going to say fur.
Sure you were.
Who am I to judge a warrior\nbased on his size? Look at me.
I'm over here.
Maybe you should look at this again.
Oh, OK.
Stop it. Stop!
I know Master Shifu is trying\nto inspire me and all...
...but if I didn't know better,\nI'd say he was trying to get rid of me.
I know he can seem kind of heartless...
...but he wasn't always like that.
According to legend,
there was once a time when\nMaster Shifu actually used to smile.
- No!\n- Yes.
But that was before.
Before what?
Before Tai Lung.
We're not really supposed\nto talk about him.
Well, if he's going to stay here,\nhe should know.
Guys, guys, I know about Tai Lung.
He was a student. The first ever to\nmaster the thousand scrolls of kung fu.
And then he turned bad,\nand now he's in jail.
He wasn'tjust a student.
Shifu found him as a cub...
...and he raised him as his son.
And when the boy showed\ntalent in kung fu...
...Shifu trained him.
He believed in him. He told him\nhe was destined for greatness.
It was never enough for Tai Lung.
He wanted the Dragon Scroll.
But Oogway saw darkness\nin his heart and refused.
Outraged, Tai Lung\nlaid waste to the valley.
He tried to take the scroll by force.
And Shifu had to destroy\nwhat he had created.
But how could he?
Shifu loved Tai Lung\nlike he had never loved anyone before.
Or since.
And now he has a chance\nto make things right.
To train the true Dragon Warrior.
And he's stuck with you.
A big fat panda\nwho treats it like a joke.
That is it!
Wait! My fault!\nI accidentally tweaked his facial nerve.
And may have also stopped his heart.
Inner peace.
Inner...
Would whoever is making\nthat flapping sound quiet down?!
Oh, Zeng.
Excellent.
I could use some good news right now.
Master! Master!
I have... It's...\nIt's very bad news.
Shifu.
There is just news.\nThere is no good or bad.
Master, your vision.\nYour vision was right.
Tai Lung has broken out of prison.\nHe's on his way.
That is bad news...
...if you do not believe\nthat the Dragon Warrior can stop him.
The panda? Master,\nthat panda is not the Dragon Warrior.
He wasn't meant to be here!\nIt was an accident.
There are no accidents.
Yes, I know. You've said that already.
- Twice.\n- Well, that was no accident, either.
Thrice.
My old friend,
the panda will never fulfill\nhis destiny, nor you yours,
until you let go\nof the illusion of control.
Illusion?
Yes. Look at this tree, Shifu.
I cannot make it blossom\nwhen it suits me,
nor make it bear fruit\nbefore its time.
But there are things we can control.
I can control when the fruit will fall.
And I can control...
...where to plant the seed.
That is no illusion, Master.
Yes.
But no matter what you do
that seed will grow to be a peach tree.
You may wish for an apple or an orange,\nbut you will get a peach.
But a peach cannot defeat Tai Lung!
Maybe it can.
If you are willing to guide it.
To nurture it.
To believe in it.
But how? How?
I need your help, Master.
No, you just need to believe.
Promise me, Shifu.
Promise me you will believe.
I will try.
Good.
My time has come.
You must continue\nyour journey without me.
What are you? Wait!
Master!
You can't leave me!
You must believe.
Master!
Yeah, so I'm like,\n"Fine, you may be a wolf,
you may be the scariest bandit\nin Haijin Province...
...but you're a lousy tipper."
Really? So how did you\nget out of there alive?
I mean, I didn't actually say that...
...but I thought it...
...in my mind.
If he could read my mind,\nhe'd be, like, "What?"
Order up! Hope you like it.
- This is really good!\n- No, come on.
Try my dad's Secret Ingredient Soup.\nHe actually knows the secret ingredient.
What do you mean? This is amazing!
- You're a really good cook.\n- I wish my mouth was bigger.
Tigress, you've got to try this.
It is said that the Dragon Warrior\ncan survive for months
on nothing but the dew of ginkgo leaf\nand the energy of the universe.
I guess my body doesn't know\nit's the Dragon Warrior yet.
I'm gonna need a lot more\nthan dew and universe juice.
- What?\n- Nothing... Master Shifu.
Never be the Dragon Warrior unless you\nlose 500 pounds and brush your teeth!
What is that noise you're making?\nLaughter? I never heard of it!
Work hard, panda, and maybe someday...
...you will have ears like mine.
That's good.
Ears. It's not working for you?\nI thought they were pretty good.
It's Shifu!
Of course it's Shifu.\nWhat do you think I'm doing?
Master Shifu!
You think this is funny?
Tai Lung has escaped\nand you're acting like children!
- What?\n- He is coming for the Dragon Scroll,
and you are the only one\nwho can stop him.
And I was saying\nyou got no sense of humor.
I'm gonna... stop Tai Lung.
What? You're serious? And I have to?
Master Oogway will stop him,\nlike he did before.
Oogway cannot!
Not anymore.
Our only hope is the Dragon Warrior.
- The panda?\n- Yes, the panda!
Master, let us stop Tai Lung.\nThis is what you've trained us for.
No! It is not your destiny\nto defeat Tai Lung.
It is his!
Where'd he go?
You cannot leave!\nA real warrior never quits.
Watch me.
Come on.
How am I supposed to beat Tai Lung?\nI can't even beat you to the stairs.
You will beat him\nbecause you are the Dragon Warrior.
You don't believe that.\nYou never believed that.
From the beginning,\nyou've tried to get rid of me.
Yes! I was.
But now I ask you to trust in your\nmaster as I have come to trust in mine.
You're not my master.\nAnd I'm not the Dragon Warrior.
Then why didn't you quit?! You knew\nI wanted you gone, yet you stayed.
Yeah, I stayed.
I stayed because every time\nyou threw a brick at my head
or said I smelled, it hurt,\nbut it could never hurt more
than it did every day\nof my life just being me.
I stayed because I thought,\nif anyone could change me...
...could make me... not me...
...it was you.
The greatest kung fu teacher\nin all of China!
But I can change you!
I can turn you into the Dragon Warrior!\nAnd I will!
Come on. Tai Lung is\non his way here right now.
Even if it takes him a hundred years\nto get here, how are you...
...gonna change this\ninto the Dragon Warrior?
How?
- How?!\n- I don't know!
I don't know.
That's what I thought.
This is what you trained me for.
Tigress!
Don't try and stop me.
We're not trying to stop you.
What?
We're coming with you!
What? I eat when I'm upset, OK?
No need to explain.
I thought you might be Monkey. He hides\nhis almond cookies on the top shelf.
Don't tell Monkey.
- Look at you.\n- Yeah, I know, I disgust you.
No, I mean, how did you get up there?
I don't know. I guess that...
I don't know. I was getting a cookie.
Yet you are ten feet off the ground.
And you have done a perfect spilt.
No, this? This is just...
...an accident.
There are no accidents.
Come with me.
I know you're trying to be\nall mystical and kung fuey...
...but could you at least\ntell me where we're going?
You dragged me...
...all the way out here...
...for a bath?
Panda...
...we do not wash our pits\nin the Pool of Sacred Tears.
The Pool of...
This is where Oogway\nunraveled the mysteries...
...of harmony and focus.
This is the birthplace...
...of kung fu.
Do you want to learn kung fu?
Yeah!
Then I am your master!
OK!
Don't cry.
OK.
(personal hygiene)
When you focus on kung fu,
when you concentrate...
...you stink.
Perhaps that is my fault.
I cannot train you the way\nI have trained the Five.
I now see that the way\nto get through to you...
...is with this.
Oh, great, 'cause I am hungry.
Good.
When you have been trained, you may eat.
Let us begin.
After you, panda.
Just like that?
No sit-ups? No ten-mile hike?
I vowed to train you, and you\nhave been trained. You are free to eat.
Enjoy.
Hey!
I said you are free to eat.\nHave a dumpling.
You are free to eat.
- Am I?!\n- Are you?!
I'm not hungry.
Master.
Cut it!
Where's the Dragon Warrior?
How do you know\nyou're not looking at her?
You think I'm a fool?
I know you're not the Dragon Warrior.\nNone of you!
I heard how he fell out\nof the sky in a ball of fire.
That he's a warrior unlike\nanything the world has ever seen.
- Po?\n- So that is his name. Po.
Finally, a worthy opponent.
Our battle will be legendary!
We've got this. Help her.
Monkey!
Go!
What was I thinking?!
Mantis!
Now!
Shifu taught you well.
But he didn't teach you everything.
You have done well, panda.
Done well? Done well?
I've done awesome!
The mark of a true hero is humility.
But, yes, you have done...
...awesome
Guys? Guys?! They're dead!
No, they're breathing. They're asleep?\nBut their eyes are open.
We were no match for his nerve attach.
He's gotten stronger.
Who? Tai Lung? Stronger?
He's too fast!
Sorry, Po.
I thought we could stop him.
He could have killed you.
Why didn't he?
So you could come back and strike fear\ninto our hearts. But it won't work.
It might. I mean, a little.
I'm pretty scared.
You can defeat him, panda!
Are you kidding? If they can't?!
They're five masters. I'm just one me.
But you will have\nthe one thing that no one else does.
You really believe I'm ready?
You are...
...Po.
Behold the Dragon Scroll.
It is yours.
Wait. What happens when I read it?
Legend says you will be able\nto hear a butterfly's wing beat.
Really? That's cool.
Yes. And see light in the deepest cave.
You will feel the universe\nin motion around you.
Can I punch through walls?
- Do a quadruple back flip?\n- Focus.
- Will I?\n- Focus.
- Focus.\n- Oh, yeah, yeah.
Read it, Po, and fulfill your destiny.
Read it and become...
...the Dragon Warrior.
It's impossible to open.
OK. Come on, baby. Come on now.
Thank you.
I probably loosened it up\nfor you though.
OK, here goes.
- It's blank.\n- What?!
- Here, look.\n- No, I am forbidden to look upon...
Blank. I don't...
I don't understand.
OK. So, like...
...Oogway was\njust a crazy old turtle after all.
No. Oogway was wiser than us all.
Oh, come on! Face it,\nhe picked me by accident.
Of course I'm not the Dragon Warrior.\nWho am I kidding?
But who will stop Tai Lung?
He'll destroy everything and everyone.
No.
Evacuate the valley. You must protect\nthe villagers from Tai Lung's rage.
- What about you, Master?\n- I will fight him.
- What?\n- I can hold him off long enough
for everyone to escape.
But, Shifu, he'll kill you.
Then I will finally have paid\nfor my mistake.
Listen to me, all of you.
It is time for you to continue\nyourjourney without me.
I am very proud\nto have been your master.
We've got to get them out safely.
Come, little one. Let's find your mama.
Viper, gather the southern farmers.\nMantis, the north.
Crane, light the way.
Look, it's the Dragon Warrior.
Hey, Dad.
Po!
Good to have you back, son.
Good to be back.
Let's go, Po.
So for our next shop,\nit's time to face it...
...the future of noodles\nis dice-cut vegetables...
...no longer slices.
Also, I was thinking, maybe this time
we'll have a kitchen\nyou can actually stand up in.
You like that?
Po, I'm sorry if things didn't work out.
It just wasn't meant to be.
Po, forget everything else.
Your destiny still awaits.
We are noodle folk.\nBroth runs deep through our veins.
I don't know, Dad.
Honestly, sometimes\nI can't believe I'm actually your son.
Po...
...I think it's time I told you\nsomething I should have told you...
...a long time ago.
OK.
The secret ingredient\nof my Secret Ingredient Soup.
Come here. The secret ingredient is...
...nothing.
You heard me. Nothing!
There is no secret ingredient!
Wait, wait.\nIt's just plain old noodle soup?
You don't add some kind of special\nsauce or something?
Don't have to. To make something\nspecial, you just believe it's special.
There is no secret ingredient.
I have come home, Master.
This is no longer your home.\nAnd I am no longer your master.
Oh, yes. You have a new favorite.
So where is this Po?
Did I scare him off?
This battle is between you and me.
So, that is how it's going to be.
That is how it must be.
I rotted in jail for 20 years\nbecause of your weakness!
Obeying your master is not weakness!
You knew I was the Dragon Warrior.
You always knew.
But when Oogway said otherwise,\nwhat did you do?
What did you do?!
Nothing!
You were not meant to be the Dragon\nWarrior! That was not my fault!
Not your fault?!
Who filled my head with dreams?!
Who drove me to train\nuntil my bones cracked?!
Who denied me my destiny?!
It was never my decision to make!
It is now.
Give me the scroll!
I would rather die.
All I ever did, I did to make you proud!
Tell me how proud you are, Shifu!
Tell me!
I have...\nI have always been proud of you.
From the first moment, I've been...
...proud of you.
And it was my pride...
...that blinded me.
I loved you too much\nto see what you were becoming...
...what I...
...was turning you into.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
I don't want your apology.
I want my scroll!
What?!
Where is it?!
Dragon Warrior has taken the scroll\nhalfway across China by now.
You will never see\nthat scroll, Tai Lung.
Never.
Stairs.
Who are you?
Buddy, I am the Dragon Warrior.
You?
Him? He's a panda.
You're a panda. What are\nyou gonna do, big guy? Sit on me?
Don't tempt me.
No. I'm gonna use this.
You want it? Come and get it.
Finally!
That scroll is mine!
Lightning!
The scroll has given him power!
No!
Finally! Oh, yes.
The power of the Dragon Scroll is mine!
It's nothing!
It's OK. I didn't get it\nthe first time, either.
What?
There is no secret ingredient.
It's just you.
Stop it!
I'm gonna pee.
Don't.
Don't! Don't!
You...
...can't defeat me.
...you're just a big...
...fat...
...panda!
I'm not a big fat panda.
I'm the big fat panda.
The Wuxi Finger Hold!
Oh, you know this hold?
You're bluffing. You're bluffing.\nShifu didn't teach you that.
Nope.
I figured it out. Skadoosh.
Look!
The Dragon Warrior.
That's my boy! That big lovely\nkung fu warrior is my son!
Yes!
Thanks, Dad.
Hey, guys.
Master.
Master?
Master Shifu!
Master!
Shifu, are you OK?!
Po.
You're alive.
Or we're both dead.
No, Master, I didn't die.\nI defeated Tai Lung.
You did?
It is as Oogway foretold.
You are the Dragon Warrior.
You have brought peace...
...to this valley...
...and...
...and to me.
Thank you.
Thank you, Po.
Thank you. Thank you.
No! Master! No, no, no,\ndon't die, Shifu, please!
I'm not dying, you idiot!
Dragon Warrior...
...I am simply at peace. Finally.
So, I should stop talking?
If you can.
Want to get something to eat?
Yeah.
(fun stuff coming ahead)
Everybody is kung fu fighting
Your mind becomes fast as lightning
Although the future\nis a little bit frightening
It's the book of your life\nthat you're writing
Everybody is kung fu fighting
Your mind becomes fast as lightning
Although the future\nis a little bit frightening
It's the book of your life\nthat you're writing
You are a natural
Why is that so hard to see?
Maybe it's just because\nYou keep on looking at me
The journey's a lonely one\nSo much more than we know
But sometimes you've got to go\nAnd be your own hero
Everybody is kung fu fighting
Your mind becomes fast as lightning
Although the future\nis a little bit frightening
It's the book of your life\nthat you're writing
You're a diamond in the rough\nA brilliant ball of clay
You could be a work of art\nIf you just go all the way
Now what would it take to break?\nI believe that you can bend
Not only do you have to fight\nBut you have got to win
'Cause everybody is kung fu fighting
Your mind becomes fast as lightning
Although the future\nis a little bit frightening
It's the book of your life\nthat you're writing
You're a diamond in the rough\nA brilliant ball of clay
You could be a work of art\nIf you just go all the way
Now what would it take to break?\nI believe that you can bend
Not only do you have to fight\nBut you have got to win
'Cause everybody is kung fu fighting
Your mind becomes fast as lightning
Although the future\nis a little bit frightening
It's the book of your life\nthat you're writing
(about panda)
(about the restaurant)
(Shifu plays poorly on Chinese Chess )
(about Mantis)
(about crane)
(about monkey)
(Demon Mountain continued)
(reveal the scroll to the young citizens)
(about viper)
(where are the peaches?)
(about Oogway)
(laughter?never heard before?)
(poor Zeng fixing up the Urn)
(about shifu)
(about tailong)
(the owner and the action figure himself)
(about the movie)
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：1610169789
(growing seed)
THE END