更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
South Park: Bigger Longer & Uncut
There's a bunch of birds
In the sky
And some deers
Just went running by
Oh, the snow's pure and white
On the earth rich and brown
Just another Sunday morning
In my quiet
Mountain town
The sun is shining and the grass is green
Under the three feet of snow, I mean
This is a day when it's hard to wear a frown
All the happy people stop to say hello
Get out of my way!
Even though the temperature's low
It's a perfect Sunday morning
In my quiet little mountain town
Well, good morning, Stan
Mom, can I have eight dollars to see a movie?
A movie?
Yeah It's gonna be the best movie ever
It's a foreign film from Canada
All right, But be back for supper
Thanks, Mom.
Oh, what a picture-perfect child!
Just like Jesus he's tender and mild
He'd wear a smile while he wore a thorny crown
What an angel with a heart so sweet and sure
And a mind so open and pure
Thank God we live in this quiet
redneck mountain town
Dude! Dude, wake up!
Kenny, come on!
Coming!
The Terrance and Phillip movie is out
You wanna come?
Sure Let's go!
Where do you think you're goin'?
You can't You have to go to church
Well, fine
Go ahead and miss church
Then when you die and go to hell
you can answer to Satan!
Okay!
You can see your breath hanging in the air
You see homeless people but you just don't care
It's a sea of smiles in
which we'd be glad to drown
That's right! It's Sunday morning
In our quiet, little
White-bread redneck mountain town
Ready, Ike? Kick the baby!
Don't kick the baby
- Kick the baby!
Ike! You broke another window!
That's a bad baby! Bad baby!
Kyle,we're going to the Terrance and Phillip movie
Oh, my God, dude!
Kyle! Where are you going?
Uh, ice skating
Well, take your little brother with you
He's not even my real brother He's adopted
Do as I say, Kyle!
Okay, okay, I'm sorry
Look at those frail and fragile boys
It really gets me down
The world is such a rotten place
And city life's a complete disgrace
That's why I moved to this redneck, meshugeneh
Quiet mountain
Town
Ike! Bad baby!
This program is brought
to you by Snacky Smores
the creamy fun of Smores
in a delightful cookie crunch
Mom! Somebody's at the door!
- Coming, hon - Aah! I can't see the TV!
It's been six weeks since Saddam Hussein
was killed by a pack of wild boars
and the world is still glad to be rid of him
Oh, look, Eric It's your little friends
- Cartman! - What are you guys doing here?
Oh, sweet, dude! Yes! Yes!
Off to the movies we shall go
Where we learn everything that we know
Cause the movies teach us
What our parents don't have time to say
And this movie's gonna make our lives complete
Cause Terrance and Phillip
- Are sweet! - Super sweet!
Thank God we live in the quiet
Little, redneck podunk, white-trash
- Whoo -whoo!
U S
A
Can I have five tickets to
Terrance and Phillip's Asses of Fire, please?
No!
What do you mean, "no"?
Asses of Fire has been rated "R"
by the Motion Picture Association of America
You have to be accompanied by a parent or guardian
But why?
Because this movie has naughty language!
Next, please
This can't be happening
We have to see this movie, dude
Ah, screw it
It probably isn't all that good anyway
Cartman, you love Terrance and Phillip!
Yeah, but the animation's all crappy
Wait, I've got an idea
Uh, hi, I want six tickets to Asses of Fire
This movie might not be appropriate
for your little ones
He says this movie isn't appropriate for you
Look, Mr Homeless Guy
if you don't want to buy us tickets
and not get your ten bucks and
not buy yourself a bottle of vodka
then be my guest
Six tickets, please
Let me have some candy, Cartman
Oh, let's see
Uh, nope, I don't have any Jewish candy
Like you really need all that chocolate, fat boy!
Shh! The movie's starting
- Hooray! - Say, Terrance
What did the Spanish priest say to
the Iranian gynecologist?
I don't know, Phillip What?
Where do they come up with this stuff?
You're such a pig fucker, Phillip!
What did he say?
Why would you call me a pig fucker?
Well, let's see First of all, you fuck pigs
Oh, yeah
Well, fuck my ass and call me a bitch!
Oh, you shit-faced cockmaster!
Wow! - Shit-faced cockmaster
Listen, you donkey-raping shit-eater
- Donkey-raping shit-eater - Shit-eater
- You'd fuck your uncle! - You'd fuck your uncle!
Shut your fucking face uncle fucker
You're a cock-sucking ass-licking uncle fucker
You're an uncle fucker Yes, it's true
Nobody fucks uncles quite like you
Shut your fucking face uncle fucker
You're the one that fucked your uncle uncle fucker
You don't eat or sleep or mow the lawn
You just fuck your uncle all day long
What's going on here?
What garbage!
Well, what do you expect? They're Canadian
Uncle fucker
Uncle fucker, uncle fucker Uncle fucker
Shut your fucking face uncle fucker
Uncle fucker
You're a boner-biting bastard uncle fucker
You're a uncle fucker I must say
Well, you fucked your uncle yesterday
Uncle fucker That's U
N- C-L-E Fuck you!
Uncle fucker
Suck my balls
Dude, that movie was fucking sweet!
You bet your fucking ass it was
Fuck, dude, I wanna be just
like Terrance and Phillip
- Wait a minute Where's your guardian? - Huh?
I knew it! You paid a homeless guy
to get you in, didn't you?
Fuck off, you donkey-raping shit-eater!
Shut your fucking face uncle fucker
You're an ass-licking ball-sucking uncle fucker
Hey, hey, hey!
- Where have you guys been? - Oh, nowhere
We just went to see the Terrance and Phillip movie
- How'd you get in?
Hey, stop crowding us, you shit-faced cockmasters!
Wow!
You're all a bunch of ass-ramming uncle fuckers!
We've got to see this movie
Terrance and Phillip are Canadian, just like my brother
There's the girl that I like
Hey, Stan, tell about when Terrance called Phillip
a testicle-shitting rectal wart
Now more than ever she gives me butterflies
It makes my stomach queasy
Every time she walks by
Asshole, I'm talking to you!
I know I can be cool if I try
Hi, Stan
Gross!
Come, Wendy Let us try to jump the hilly brush
- Who are you, kid? - My name is Gregory
I just transferred from Yardale
where I had a 4 0 grade point average
Wanna skate with us?
We've been skating and laughing
and talking of memories past
We saw the Terrance and Phillip movie
Try and catch me, Wendy
Bye, Stan
Yes, yes, I saw the Terrance and Phillip movie
Who wants to touch me?
I said, who wants to fuckin' touch me?
Come on, gang
We gotta see the Terrance and Phillip movie too
I hate you, Kenny
Shut your fucking face uncle fucker
You're a boner-biting bastard uncle fucker
- You're a - Shh! Shh!
Okay, children, let's take our seats
We have a lot to learn today
We sure do, Mr Hat
Okay, children, let's start the day
with a few new math problems
What is 5 times 2?
Don't be shy Just give it your best shot
- Yes, Clyde - Twelve?
Okay, now let's try to get an answer
from someone who's not a complete retard
Anyone? Come on Don't be shy
I think I know the answer, Mr Garrison
Shut up, fat boy!
Hey, don't call me fat, you fucking Jew!
- Did you just say the "F" word?
- "Jew"? - He's talking about "fuck "
You can't say "fuck" in school
you fucking fat-ass - Kyle!
- Why the fuck not? - Eric!
- Dude, you said "fuck" again - Stanley!
- Fuck - Kenny! - What's the big deal?
It doesn't hurt anybody
Fuck, fuckity, fuck-fuck-fuck!
How would you like to go see the school counselor?
How would you like to suck my balls?
What did you say?
U- Uh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Actually, what I said was:
How would you like to suck my balls, Mr Garrison?
Holy shit, dude
I'm very disappointed in you boys
m'kay? You should be ashamed of yourselves
I've already called in your mothers
You called my mom?
- That's right - Oh, no, dude!
Mr.Mackey, can I ask a question?
m'kay, what?
What's the big fuckin' deal, bitch?
Aaah! Now, I want to know
where you heard these horrific obscenities! m'kay?
Nowhere
We heard them from Mr.Garrison a few times before
Boys, I seriously doubt
that Mr Garrison ever said, uh
"Eat penguin shit, you ass spelunker "
Sweet!
Thank you all for coming on such short notice
This isn't like you, Stanley
What did my son say, Mr Mackey?
Did he say the "S" word?
- No, it was worse than that - The "F" word?
Here's a short list of things they've been saying m'kay?
- Oh, dear God - What the heck is a rim job?
Why, that's when you put your legs behind your head
and have someone lick your ass
Young man, tell Mr Mackey this instant
where you heard all these horrible phrases!
- I, I - We can't tell you
We swore ourselves to secrecy
It was the Terrance and Phillip movie
- Dude! - Fuck you guys. I wanna get out of here
Terrance and Phillip? Those Canadians?
What the heck is Terrance and Phillip?
Terrance and Phillip
are two very untalented actors from Canada
Nothing but foul language and toilet humor
I'll send a warning letter to parents
before more children see Terrance and Phillip
- Everybody's fuckin' seein' it - Eric!
I'm sorry! I can't help myself
That movie has warped my fragile little mind
My mom gave me egg again
There's the girl that I like
Over there laughing with that smart new
Hey! You're holding up the goddamn lunch line!
Hello there, children!
- Hey, Chef - How's it goin'?
- Bad - Why bad?
We got busted for swearing
We can't ever see the
Terrance and Phillip movie again
Oh, that's too bad
You should've seen Kyle when his mom showed up
He was scared out of his mind Shut up
I'd be scared too. Your mom's a fucking bitch
Don't call my mom a bitch, you fat fuck!
Don't call me fat, you butt-fucking son of a bitch!
Whoa, children!
Where did you learn to talk like that?
Pretty fuckin' sweet, huh?
Chef, how do you make a woman
like you more than any other guy?
Oh, that's easy
You just gotta find the clitoris
What does that mean, "find the clitoris"?
Forget I said anything
Move along. You're holding up the line
You guys, do you know where I can find the clitoris?
- The what? - Is that like finding Jesus?
Attention, students
We are now enforcing a new dress code
at South Park Elementary
Terrance and Phillip T-shirts are
no longer allowed in school
Anyone wearing a Terrance and Phillip shirt
is to be sent home immediately
The R-rated Canadian film "Asses of Fire"
is number one at the box office
But is the film destroying American youth?
Here with a special report is a midget in a bikini
It appears the effects of the Canadian comedy
are far-reaching indeed
All over America children seem to be influenced
like at this spelling bee in Washington
This is for the silver medal
Spell "forensics "
fuck that Why should I fucking
have to spell "forensics"?
- Yeah! - Here you go
"S-U-C-K M-Y A-S-S " "Forensics"
Tom, the devastating impact of the
Canadian duo can also be seen
with their new hit song
"Shut Your Fucking Face, Uncle Fucker "
Shut your fucking face uncle fucker
You're a boner-biting bastard uncle fucker
I told you that we won't stop
Thought I told you that we won't stop
Back to you, Tom
Thanks, Midget, Shocking report
The controversy began in the small
mountain town of South Park
where the local P T A
is trying to ban the movie
With us tonight is the head of the P T A
Sheila Broflovski - Hello
And the Canadian minister of movies
Thanks for having me, buddy
Minister, parents are concerned about
your country's entertainment
Your thoughts?
Well, the film is R-rated
It's not intended for children
But of course children are gonna see it
Can I finish?
We Canadians are quite surprised by your outrage
You just don't care!
Can I finish? Hello?
The United States has graphic violence
on television all the time
We can't believe that a movie with some
foul language would piss you off so much
Because it's evil!
Can I finish? Please! Can I finish?
Okay, I'm finished
But it isn't like this film is
the first troublesome thing to come out of Canada
Let us not forget Bryan Adams
The Canadian government has apologized
for Bryan Adams on several occasions
You Canadians are all the same
with your beady eyes and flapping heads
You're trash!
I resent that! I find that racist!
Our children are now addicted to your trash
You are a racist, ma'am!
It is going to take us weeks to erase
the damage this film has done to our children!
Um, kids, I wanna welcome you to rehabilitation m'kay?
Your mothers insisted that you be
taken from your normal schoolwork
and placed into rehab to learn not to swear
I don't belong with these rogues
I attended Yardale and had a 40 grade point average
You're a fuckin' faggot, dude
m'kay, children, this is what I'm talking about
We have to get you off of foul language
- How are we gonna do that? - Well, listen here
There are times when you get suckered in
by drugs and alcohol and sex with women m'kay!
But it's when you do these things too much
That you've become an addict
and must get back in touch
You can do it It's all up to you, m'kay
With a little plan you can change your life today
You don't have to spend your life addicted to smack
Homeless on the streets Giving hand jobs for crack
Follow my plan and very soon you will say
It's easy, m'kay
Step one Instead of "ass," say "buns"
Like "kiss my buns" or "you're a buns-hole"
Step two Instead of "shit," say "poo"
As in "bull-poo," "poo-head"
and "this poo is cold"
Step three With "bitch," drop the "T"
'Cause bich is Latin for "generosity"
Step four Don't say "fuck" anymore
Cause "fuck" is the worst word that you can say
So just use the word "m'kay"
We can do it. It's all up to us
- m'kay - m'kay
With a little plan we can change our lives today
You can change it today
You don't have to spend your life
shooting up in the trash
Homeless on the streets Giving hand jobs for cash
Follow this plan and very soon you will say
It's easy, m'kay
- Step one - Instead of "ass," say "buns "
Like "kiss my buns "
Or "you're a buns-hole "
- Step two - Instead of "shit," say "poo "
- As in "bull-poo " - "Poo-head "
And "this poo is cold "
- Step three - With "bitch," drop the "T "
Cause bich is Latin for "generosity "
- Step four! - Don't say "fuck" anymore
Cause "fuck" is the worst word that you can say
"Fuck" is the worst word that you can say
We shouldn't say "fuck"
No, we shouldn't say "fuck"
- Fuck no - You're cured! You can go!
You don't have to spend your life
shooting up in the trash
Homeless on the streets Giving hand jobs for cash
Follow this plan and very soon you will say
- It's easy, m'kay - It's easy, m'kay
- It's easy, m'kay - It's easy, m It's easy, m
It's easy, m'kay
m'kay! m'kay!
m'kay!
Now you're cured
You can take the rest of the afternoon off
for personal reflection m'kay?
Find your own constructive way
to better yourself, m'kay?
Well, Phillip, I hope you've learned something
through this whole experience
I did. I learned that you are a boner-biting
dick-fart-fuck-face
Want to see the Northern Lights?
You burnt yourself to death by lighting your fart!
I sure did, Phillip!
Uncle Fucker
Good night!
That movie rules!
Man, that movie gets better every time I see it
Yeah, but that part about lighting farts is bullshit
- You can't do that - Yeah, you can
- No way! - Yes, you can!
Okay, Kenny, I'll bet you $100
you can't light a fart on fire
Holy shit, dude!
Oh, my God!
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
Help! Somebody do something!
This stick is on fire!
- Oh, my God! You killed Kenny! - You bastard!
I guess you can light a fart on fire
Over here, Doctor!
Load that I V with 70 ccs of sodium pentothol
We just called the parents
Now our moms are gonna find out
we went to the Terrance and Phillip movie again
Vacuum! Try to untangle his trachea and esophagus!
- Dude! - No, that doesn't go there!
- Gross, Stan! - That's sick!
- Watch his liver! - I'll get it!
We have precious little time
We're gonna lose him soon!
Doctor, his heart's stopped!
Let's get it out of there!
We need to zap this, quick!
Who's making a potato?
My bad, sir I missed lunch
Damn it, I'm not gonna lose this kid!
Close him up We've done all we can
The rest is up to God
Kenny? Kenny, can you hear me?
Holy shit, dude
How are you feeling, son?
Great Son, I have some bad news
We accidentally replaced your heart
with a baked potato. You have three seconds to live
- What? - Fucking weak, dude!
Oh, my God They killed Kenny!
You bastards!
Damn it! It never gets any easier!
I bet him he couldn't do it I bet him $100
Cartman, it's not your fault
No, I know I'm just fuckin' stoked
I don't have to pay him
Oh, that's real nice
He was your friend, you fat fuck!
So, boys, you saw that movie again?
- Yes - Well, Kyle, I have had it!
You are grounded for the next two weeks!
Grounded?
And you, Stan Come on
And you're grounded for three weeks, Eric
Why am I grounded more? That's fuckin' bullshit!
What was that word, young man?
word, young man? word, young man?
Little boy at peace
What is this place? Beyond the stars
Open up your eyes
What are these things you're moving toward
Head so full of wonder
Worries in the past
Could it be that you are free at last
No!
Little boy you're going to Hell
You said bad words Threw rocks at the birds
And now this is your hotel
You ain't goin' back
This ain't Disneyland It's Hell
Little boy it's time for you to pay
For hurtin' that bird and
not goin to church
and starin' at boobs every day
Thought you were in bed Instead, you're in Hell
Hell isn't good Hell isn't good, Hell
Oh, Hell isn't good Hell isn't good, Hell
Hey, fuck-face, have you seen Gracie?
There is orderliness in the universe
Hell isn't good Hell isn't good
Hell
Parents, our children are out of control
This is what happens when toilet humor is
allowed to run rampant!
That's right Kenny set himself on fire
because he saw Terrance and Phillip do it
in that dirty movie!
We must stop dirty language
from getting to our children's ears!
We must go fight the source of it!
- But what is the source? - Oh, that's easy
Times have changed Our kids are getting worse
They won't obey their parents
They just want to fart and curse
Should we blame the government
Or blame society
Or should we blame the images on TV
- No! Blame Canada - Blame Canada
Before their beady little eyes
Have packed their heads so full of lies
Blame Canada Blame Canada
We need to form a full assault
It's Canada's fault
Don't blame me for my son Stan
He saw the darn cartoon
and now he's off to join the Klan
And my boy Eric once had
my picture on his shelf
But now when I see him
he tells me to fuck myself
Well? Blame Canada
Blame Canada
It seems that everything's
gone wrong since Canada came along
Blame Canada
They're not even a real country anyway
My son could've been a doctor
or a lawyer rich and true
Instead he burned up like a piggy on a barbecue
Should we blame the matches
Should we blame the fire
Or the doctors who allowed him to expire
Heck, no! Blame Canada
Blame Canada
With all their hockey hullabaloo
And that bitch Anne Murray too
Blame Canada Shame on Canada
For the smut we must stop
The trash we must smash
The laughter and fun must all be undone
We must blame them and cause a fuss
Before somebody thinks of blaming us
All right, you turds, listen up!
Your moms are away at a meeting
They put me in charge of you
But you're still grounded
so you're not allowed to have any fun
- Any questions? - Shelley, where's the clitoris?
Now you all just sit there
and keep your mouths shut
while I go listen to my Britney Spears records
Okay, it's clear
Our next guests have the number
one movie in the world right now
Please welcome Terrance and Phillip
- Hello, Conan - Hello, Brooke Shields
Guys, some people claim that your Canadian humor
is nothing but immature fart jokes
That's not true Take this classic
Canadian joke, for instance
- Excuse me, Terrance - Yes, Phillip?
Gosh-darn it!
- Good one, Phillip Cheers! - Cheers, fuck-face
Guys, you can't say that on TV
Now Terrance smells like my ass!
I farted once on the set of Blue Lagoon!
So, guys
does it make you nervous to be in America?
A lot of organizations here want
you arrested for destroying children
They'd have to find us first
You're right Now!
Terrance and Phillip
Mothers Against Canada
is placing you under citizen's arrest!
- Mom? - Dude, what the hell's going on?
We have a court order for your arrest!
Phillip, we've been ambushed!
Here you go, Conan
This little scrotum-sucker deceived us
- You are a bad man! - Don't listen to them, Conan
You loved our movie, Conan, We watched it together
Remember? You laughed!
What have I done?
Holy crap! Did you see that?
They arrested Terrance and Phillip!
As the Canadian ambassador
I condemn the actions taken
by America in apprehending Terrance and Phillip
As you can see
the entire economy of Canada
relies on Terrance and Phillip
Without them, we are doomed to recession
What say you, Mr American Ambassador?
- Fuck Canada! - Hey, fuck you, buddy!
Terrance and Phillip will not be released
They are going to be put on trial
for corrupting America's youth
We don't know what all the fuss is about
The fuss is "aboot" taking our citizens!
It's "aboot" not censoring our art It's "aboot"
It's "aboot" What's so goddamn funny?
N- Nothing Nothing
Could you tell us again
what your argument is all about?
This is not "aboot" diplomacy;
this is "aboot" dignity
This is "aboot" respect
This is "aboot" realizing that humor is
You guys are dicks!
Release Terrance and Phillip
or we'll give you something to cry "aboot"!
Stop! Stop!
Pilot to bombardier!
Pilot to bombardier! Were nearing the target!
Bombs ready, buddy!
Baldwin residence
No, this is Billy Baldwin!
If you want Daniel Baldwin
call his extension, stupid!
Alec, do you know what sucks about being a Baldwin?
No, What?
- Nothing! - Yeah!
Ha-ha! You missed me!
Children, your mothers are all making me
throw away my lesson plan and teach theirs
How come our moms arrested Terrance and Phillip?
- Yeah! - That's gay
Well, your moms are just upset
They're probably all on their periods or something
Not cool
Mr Garrison
Wendy and I think that was a sexist statement
I'm sorry, Wendy, but I just don't trust anything
that bleeds for five days and doesn't die
Anyway, children
let's start off with some vocabulary
- Attention, students! - Oh, what now?
Come to the gymnasium immediately
for a special announcement m'kay?
What's goin' on, Chef?
Something big, children
Chef, I can't find the clitoris
You have to help me
Stan, the clitoris is
Take your seats, everyone
They're about to announce it
- m'kay? - This is a state of emergency
We go now to the White House for an announcement
from the President of the United States
My fellow Americans
at 5:00 a.m today, a day which will live in infamy
the Canadians have bombed the Baldwins
In response to this
the U S has declared war on Canada
- Oh, no! - War?
No, Gregory, no!
This is bad, Wendy Hold on to me
All the Baldwins are dead?
Now it is time for us to send a message to Canadians
In two days' time
the war criminals Terrance and Phillip
will be executed
They're gonna kill them?
And now I'd like to bring out my
newly appointed secretary of offense
Ms Sheila Broflovski
- Holy shit, dude! - My fellow Americans
our neighbor to the north
has abused us for the last time
I have a plan as commander-in-chief
Canadians want to fight us
because we won't tolerate their potty mouths
Well, if it is war they want
then war they shall have!
Dude, this is fucking weak
How could things be any worse?
Fallen one, I am Satan
I am your god now
There is no escape!
Now feel the delightful pain
Hey, Satan! Did you hear the news?
A war just broke out up on Earth
Meet Saddam Hussein, my new partner in evil!
Huh? - Move over, Satan
You're hoggin' all the fun
Yeah! Yeah! Man, this is gettin' me so hot!
Saddam, would you let me do my job, please?
Come on, rub my nipples
while I torture this little piggy
- Could I talk to you a second?
I don't see why you have to
belittle me in front of people like that
Hey, relax, guy!
Well, sometimes I think
you don't have any respect for me
Hey, come here, guy
- Who's my cream puff? - I am
- That's right, baby - Huh?
Dude, I don't wanna be at war
You don't think they're really gonna
kill Terrance and Phillip, do you?
Kyle, you need to stand up to your mother
Smack her in the face and say,
"That's enough of your shit, you fuckin' bitch!"
Don't call my mom a bitch, Cartman!
You guys, stop it
This isn't helping We've got to think here
Let's see What would Brian Boitano do?
Yeah, what would Brian Boitano do?
Hey, what's goin' on?
America thinks it has the right to police the world
Your government is going to kill two Canadian citizens,
an action condemned by the U N
Home of the free, indeed
- Let's play tetherball - Yeah!
This is about freedom of speech, about censorship!
Can't you guys be more political like Gregory?
There's the girl that I like
Now it appears that she likes another guy
It must be because he's political and stuff
I bet I could be political too
What do you think, Sta
- Oh, God! - Damn it!
You guys, this is all Kyle's mom's fault
Shut up, Cartman!
Kyle's mom started that damn club
and all because she's a big, fat, stupid b
Don't say it, Cartman
Well
Don't do it, Cartman!
- I'm warning you! - Okay, okay
I'm gettin' pretty sick of him calling my mom
Well, Kyle's mom's a bitch She's a big, fat bitch
She's the biggest bitch in the whole wide world
She's a stupid bitch if there ever was a bitch
She's a bitch to all the boys and girls
Shut your fucking mouth, Cartman!
On Monday she's a bitch On Tuesday she's a bitch
On Wednesdays and Saturdays she's a bitch
Then on Sunday just to be different
She's a super King Kamehameha "bee-utch"
Come on! You all know the words!
Have you ever met my friend Kyle's mom
She's the biggest bitch in the whole wide world
She's a mean old bitch and she has stupid hair
She's a big, big, big, big Big, big bitch
Bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch Bitch
bitch, bitch, bitch She's a stupid bitch
Kyle's mom's a bitch
- And she's such a dirty bitch - Bitch!
Talk to kids around the world
it might go a little bit something like this:
Have you ever met my friend Kyle's mom
She's the biggest bitch in the whole wide world
She's a mean old bitch and she has stupid hair
She's a bitch, bitch, bitch bitch
bitch, bitch, bitch
Bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch
- She's a stupid bitch - Uh, Cartman
Kyle's mom's a bitch
and she's such a dirty bitch
I really mean it
Kyle's mom
She's a big, fat
Fuckin' bitch
Big old fat fuckin' bitch Kyle's mom
Yeah!
What?
Oh, fuck
Okay, everyone, settle down!
As we continue to send troops into Canada
M A C is also fighting the war
against potty mouths here at home
Here to present the V-chip is Dr Vosknocker
The machinery of the V-chip is very simple
It is placed under the child's skin
where it emits a small shock of electricity
whenever an obscenity is uttered
Now, uh, wait a minute
This chip somehow knows if the child is swearing?
It's just like a lie detector Things
happen to you when you swear just like when you lie
The chip picks up on this
and gives the subject a little prick
Patient B-5, would you step out here, please
Patient B-5 here has been
fitted with the new V-chip
- Ow, my head hurts - Don't worry about that
Now, I want you to say "doggy "
- "Doggy " - Notice that nothing happens
Now say "Montana "
- Montana - Good!
- Now "pillow " - Pillow
All right, now I want you to say "horse fucker "
Go ahead, Eric It's all right
Horsefu Aaah! Yiii!
That hurt, godda Aiii! Oww! Fuck Aaah!
Now I'd like you to say "big floppy donkey dick "
No! Success!
The child doesn't want to swear!
This isn't fair, you sons of bitches Yaaaah!
We will start putting V-chips in
all our children next week
Snacky Smores presents:Course of the war
Let's hear it for our boys in blue
President Clinton has called them
to action to fight the evil Canadian scourge
A full-scale attack has been launched on Toronto
after the Canadians' last bombing
which took a horrible toll on the Arquette family
For security measures
our great American government
is rounding up all citizens that have any Canadian
blood and putting them into camps
All Canadian-American citizens are
to report to one of these death camps right away
Did I say "death camps"?
I meant happy camps
where you will eat the finest meals
have access to fabulous doctors
and be able to exercise regularly
Meanwhile, the war criminals Terrance
and Phillip are prepped for their execution
Their execution will take place
during a fabulous U S O show
with special guest celebrities including:
Of course, the only way to see the U S O
show is to sign up for the Army
So join the Army and kill some Canadian scum
as we continue:
We must rid ourselves of anything Canadian!
- Down with Canada! - Bomb them!
Dude, don't you like Terrance and Phillip anymore?
Of course not My mommy says I hate Canadians now
cause they made me have a dirty mouth
Burn it all!
- Hey, dudes - What's the matter, Cartman?
It's this V-chip I hate it
I can't say any dirty words - Really?
- So you can't say "fuck"? - No
- And you can't say "shit"? - Nope
So you can't say, "I'm Cartman
the fattest fucking piece of shit in the world?"
- Fuck you Aaaaah! - Dude! Sweet!
This has gone far enough
It's time we talked to our moms
We're supposed to be grounded
Come on, Kyle It's time for us to get political
Canada will no longer corrupt our children!
Mom, can I talk to you?
Kyle, what are you doing here? You are grounded!
Now get back to the house and stay there!
You too, Stanley
Mom, we think you're going too far
You can't kill Terrance and Phillip
We must fight for our children's futures!
You're starting a war You have to stop it
- To make them safe again! - Hello?
- Our children are precious! - Hello!
We must make a stand now!
Stop at nothing!
I told you my mom wouldn't listen
Then we're gonna have to save Terrance
and Phillip ourselves - What? What?
What would Brian Boitano do?
He'd figure out a way to rescue Terrance
and Phillip before they're executed
We can't do anything
Our moms' organization is too strong
Then we'll round up all the grounded kids
in town and start our own organization
to help save Terrance and Phillip
Hey, yeah! Our own secret club!
- I guess that could work - We have to try
What would Brian Boitano do
If he was here right now
He'd make a plan and he'd follow through
That's what Brian Boitano'd do
When Brian Boitano was in the Olympics
Skating for the gold
He did two salchows and a triple lutz
While wearing a blindfold
When Brian Boitano was in the Alps
Fighting grizzly bears
He used his magical fire breath
And saved the maidens fair
So what would Brian Boitano do
If he were here today
I'm sure he'd kick an ass or two
That's what Brian Boitano'd do
I want this V-chip out of me
It has stunted my vocabulary
And I just want my mom to stop fighting everyone
For Wendy I'll be an activist too
Cause that what Brian Boitano would do
And what would Brian Boitano do
He'd call all the kids in town
And tell them to unite for truth
That's what Brian Boitano'd do
- Did someone say my name? - Who are you?
- I'm Brian Dennehy - What?
No, not fuckin' Brian Dennehy!
Get the fuck outta here
Oh, Bye
When Brian Boitano traveled
through time to the year 3010
He fought the evil robot king
And saved the human race again
And when Brian Boitano built the pyramids
he beat up Kublai Khan
'Cause Brian Boitano doesn't take shit
From anybody
So let's call all the kids together
And unite to stop our moms
And we'll save Terrance and Phillip too
'Cause that's what Brian Boitano'd do
Hey, relax, guy!
Oh, there's nothing on
You just get cranky when you're tired, that's all
I'm not cranky!
What started as a spat between the U S
and Canada is quickly turning into World War Three
- World War Three? - Shh!
Terrance and Phillip are going to be put
to death for crimes against humanity
The time of execution has
It has come to be.
The Four Horsemen are drawing nigh
The time of prophecy is upon us!
I love when you get all biblical
Satan You know exactly how to turn my crank!
No, I'm being serious
- It is the seventh sign - What?
Behold, the first signs of my reign have all come true
The fall of an empire, the coming of a comet
and now, when the blood of
these Canadians touches American soil
it will be our time to rise!
Man, I'm gettin' so hot! Let's fuck!
Do you always think about sex?
I'm talking about very important stuff here!
I'm just excited about taking over the world! Come on!
Is sex the only thing that matters to you?
I love you
I want to believe that
So what do you say you shut off
that light and get close, huh?
Yeah, you like that, don't you, bitch?
Okay, we can use my dad's computer
to call all the kids together
Before we put a message out
do a search on "clitoris "
Oh, okay
- "Found: Eight million pages with the word 'clitoris '" - Wow!
I'll just try the first one
"You must be 18 to enter this web site "
Okay "Welcome to German Sick Fetish Video
If you are under 18, do not ''
Well, okay
Dude, it's a lady getting pooed on!
Whoa! Is it Cartman's mom?
- Oh, very funny - Hey, it is Cartman's mom!
- Essen mein Scheisse! - All righty, then
Aw, son of a bit Aaaaah!
Get out of here, Ike! You're too young for this
- Bullshit - What's he doing now?
Click it off, dude!
What the fuck is wrong with German people?
All right, let's just do what we came here to do
and put a message out to kids
I've gotta put out an all-access e-mail
Goddamn, your mom sucks
- Just get to the message board - I'm trying
I can't find a Canadian server
I've got to break into the mainframe
Damn it, they've got an access code
I'll try to reroute the encryptions
Okay, here we go "Want to help Terrance and Phillip?"
- Tell 'em we'll have punch and pie - We're not!
More people will come if they think
we have punch and pie!
"This is top secret The password is "
La Resistance
And so the draft will begin tomorrow
as more and more troops are needed to
invade the Canadian border
The Canadian government pleads for a peaceful resolution
but naturally, we're not listening
Good night, hon
Mom, when is the war gonna be over?
I don't know, hon Soon, we hope
You want it to end quickly, huh?
- Mom? - Yes, hon?
If you were in a German Scheisse video
you'd tell me, right?
Sure, hon Good night!
Poltergeist!
Kenny, is that you?
Satan? Satan is coming here?
Saddam Hussein? That doesn't make sense, Kenny!
Eric! Eric, what is it?
- I saw him! I saw Kenny! - Oh, you poor dear
You've been through so much
I bet him he couldn't light a fart on fire
and now he's all pissed off
Aaaah! I can't say "pissed off"? Aaaah!
The execution of Terrance and Phillip is imminent
Soon Saddam and l will rule the world
Hey, Satan! I got some new luggage
for our trip up to Earth!
Let's fuck to celebrate!
What's it like up on Earth, Saddam?
Tell me about it again
Let's not talk Let's get busy!
When you first got here we used to
talk all night long until the sun came up
We would just lie in bed and talk
Well, yeah, 'cause I was still waitin'
to get you in bed, dummy!
How come you always want to
make love to me from behind?
Is it because you want to pretend I'm somebody else?
Satan Your ass is gigantic and red
Who am I gonna pretend you are? Liza Minnelli?
Aww, don't get all pissy!
Sometimes I think
When I look up real high
That there's such a big world up there
I'd like to give it a try
But then I sink
'Cause it's here I'm supposed to stay
But I get so lonely down here
Tell me, why does it have to be that way
Up there there is so much room
Where babies burp and flowers bloom
Everyone dreams I could dream too
Up there
Up where the skies are ocean blue
I could be safe and live without a care
Up there
They say I don't belong
I must stay below alone
Because of my beliefs
I'm supposed to stay where evil is sown
But what is evil anyway
Is there reason to the rhyme
Without evil there could be no good
So it must be good to be evil sometimes
Up there there is so much room
Where babies burp and flowers bloom
Everyone dreams I can dream too
Up there
Up where the skies are ocean blue
I could be safe and live without a care
Without a care
- Live without a care - If I could
If only I could live
Up there
I wanna live I wanna live up
I want to live
Up there
You're late, Cartman!
I had to ride my bike here My behind is killing me
Your "behind"? - I had to say "behind"
because I'll get shocked if I say ass
Did you bring the punch and pie?
No You guys, something happened
I don't think Kenny's dead
- What? - I saw him in my room
I know, Cartman I see Kenny every day
- You do? - Sure, dude On the face of every child
On the smile of every baby
I'm telling you this was Kenny!
He said that if Terrance and Phillip die
Saddam Hussein and Satan are gonna
come up and rule the world
Saddam Hussein?
- Who is it? - I'm here for La Resistance
- What's the password? - Uh, I don't know
- Guess - Uh, bacon
Okay
Viva La Resistance
- Oh, no! It's that kid! - This is the place
- Wendy? - Stan? You started La Resistance?
You're more political than we thought
Let us get this meeting underway
There are others coming
Wow A lot of people showed up
Okay, uh, Terrance and Phillip
are supposed to be killed
and we thinks that sucks ass!
Yes? - Uh, we were to understand
there'd be pie and punch
- There isn't any - Oh
Uh, Terrance and Phillip are supposed to be killed
so we think we should prank-call a bunch of policemen
and have pizzas sent to them
that they didn't order
Viva La Resistance!
- May I? - What?
Terrance and Phillip are being held
at a Canadian internment camp
two kilometers outside of town
They are to be executed tomorrow
during a star-studded U S O show for the troops
- Tomorrow? - Once the show begins
we have one hour to get Terrance and Phillip
out of their cell and into this clearing
There we will all rendezvous and
take Terrance and Phillip safely back to Canada
Wow, dude, Wendy's new guy is smart
you must all meet me at the rendezvous point at
precisely 10:00 p m.
Sneaking in and breaking out Terrance
and Philip will be the most dangerous part
so I'll go myself
No. We're going
We'll get Terrance and Phillip
and meet you at the rendezvous point
This will be very dangerous
- Are you quite sure? - Fuck that Aaaah!
Cartman, do you want that
V- chip in you forever? We're going!
Now let's run through the plan
Now, uh, when you shoot somebody
go for someone wide open
Oh, boy! Military action, Ned!
Let's kill us some goddamn Australians!
I think we're fighting Canadians
Canadians, Australians What's the difference?
This uniform makes me feel
like a tough, brute man, Mr Hat
It sure does, Mr Garrison
I can't wait for our first shore leave
so I can get me some fuckin' poontang
Pay attention! Tomorrow night
is the U S O show for all you troops
There will be celebrities
followed by the execution of Terrance and Phillip
After the show, we will finally be sending
ground troops into Canada
so let's strategize
Map!
Our sources have told us
that the Canadians are preparing for our invasion
so we must use caution
Each battalion has a specific code name and mission
Battalion Five, raise your hands
You will be the all-important first attack wave
which we will call Operation Human Shield
Hey, wait a minute!
Operation Human Shield will suffer heavy losses
Battalion 14?
Right You are Operation Get Behind The Darkies
You will follow Battalion Five here
and try not to get killed
Are there any questions, men?
Yes, soldier?
Have you ever heard of the Emancipation Proclamation?
I don't listen to hip-hop
After that we will march into
the heart of Canada, and we will
Comin' to get ya!
What's wrong with this thing?
Fuckin' Windows 98!
Get Bill Gates in here!
You told us Windows 98 would be faster
and more efficient
with better access to the Internet!
It is faster Over five million
All right, men, get lots of rest
and prepare to go into Canada!
After you have Terrance and Phillip
make your way to this ridge
We'll be there, but we cannot wait long
If you're not there at 10:00, we will have to leave
- Gotcha - You are indeed brave,
but you will need help
Here is the address of the Mole
The Mole? - An expert in covert operations
A mercenary for hire
Your first task will be obtaining him
Get lots of sleep Tomorrow we will
all be risking our lives for freedom
God has smiled upon you this day
The fate of a nation
In your hands
And blessed be the children
Who fight with all our bravery
Till only the righteous stand
You see the distant flames
They bellow in the night
You fight in all our names
for what we know is right
And when you all get shot and cannot carry on
Though you die La Resistance lives on
You may get stabbed in the head
with a dagger or a sword
You may be burned to death or skinned alive or worse
But when they torture you
you will not feel the need to run
For though you die La Resistance lives on
Blame Canada Blame Canada
Because the country's gone awry
Tomorrow night these freaks will fry
Tomorrow night
Our lives will change
We'll be entertained
An execution
What a sight Tomorrow night
Up there there is so much room
Where babies burp and flowers bloom
Tomorrow night up there is doomed
And so I will be going soon
Shut your fucking face uncle fucker
You're a boner-biting bastard uncle fucker
Looks like we may be out of luck
Tomorrow night we're pretty fucked
Why did our mothers start this war
What the fuck are they fighting for
When did this song become a marathon
- I want to be - When Canada is dead and gone
- Up there - There'll be no more Celine Dion
- They might cut your dick in half -Tomorrow night
- And serve it to a pig - Our lives will change
- And though it hurts you'll laugh - Tomorrow night
And dance a dickless jig
We'll be entertained
But that's the way it goes
In war you're shat upon
I want to be
Though you die La Resistance lives on
Blame Canada Blame Canada
- Blame Canada - omorrow night - On
Oh, boy! I'm so excited!
Just one more day until we can take over the world!
I don't know if I can sleep, if you know what I mean
This book is really interesting
It talks about how people communicate differently
Like, I communicate by wanting you to ask me questions
and you communicate
Hey, that is interesting Let's fuck!
Saddam, I'm trying to have
a nice conversation with you
Hey, Satan
Now, that is just not appropriate!
Aw, come on I'm just fuckin' with you It's not real
Oh Well, that's still not appropriate
Hey, Satan
Ha-ha! It's not real either! Come on, guy!
- What's wrong? - Oh!
Soon the world will belong to me
No, what's wrong, dude?
It's Saddam He doesn't nurture my emotions
He just wants sex and can't learn to communicate
You're right
I should leave him
I'm just gonna tell him: "Saddam,
I'm going to Earth to rule alone "
I'm strong, and I don't need him!
Good for you!
Today's the day for the U S O show
We're so happy we get to go
I don't know but I been told
Canadian pussy is mighty cold
Ike, you have to stay in the attic
If they find you,
they'll put you in a Canadian concentration camp
Don't worry We're gonna put an end to this
Then I'll make Mom come home
and we'll all be a family again
Home
Allo?
Hi We need to speak with the Mole
I'm sorry The Mole is grounded
He can't come out and play
- What? - He's a kid?
He said very naughty things about God
Well, can we just talk to him
for five seconds, please?
Well, all right Cristoph!
Hi We're gonna rescue Terrance
and Phillip from the U S O show and we
Shh! Who are you? Who sent you?
That Gregory kid
You intend to break into the U S O show
filled with thousands of soldiers
and break out Terrance and Phillip?
I thought it was a stupid idea too
We're La Resistance
We want to save Terrance and Phillip
and stop the war and stuff
I can't help you I'm grounded
So are we Our parents think we're home right now
Why are you grounded?
Why? Because God hates me, that's why
He has made my life miserable
so I call him a cock-sucking asshole,
and I get grounded
- So, will you help us? - Very well
Meet me in the backyard in five minutes
Viva La Resistance
We'll show God we're not gonna
fucking take anymore of His - What?
- Cristoph, get in here! - Coming, Mother
I must be strong I must be strong
Saddam, I need to talk to you
Hey, you'd better get packin', bitch!
We have to go! We're running out of time!
Saddam, sometimes you can love a person very much
but still know they aren't right for you
What the fuck are you talking about?
You treat me like shit!
I'm leaving you
I'm going up to Earth to rule alone
No! No, you can't do that!
I'm sorry, but I have to be strong
Satan, please, give me another chance!
I have to go to Earth!
You don't even have any respect for me
Ah, sure I do, guy
Please, just hear me out
Some people say that I'm a bad guy
They may be right
But it's not as if I don't try
I just fuck up
Try as I might
But I can change I can change
I can learn to keep my promises I swear it
I'll open up my heart and I will share it
Any minute now I will be born again
Yes, I can change I can change
I know I've been a dirty little bastard
I like to kill I like to maim
Yes, I'm insane, but it's okay 'cause I can change
It's not my fault that I'm so evil
It's society
Society
You see, my parents were sometimes abusive
And it made a prick of me
But I can change I can change
What if you remain a sandy little butthole
Hey, Satan!
Don't be such a twit
Mother Teresa won't have shit on me
Just watch, just watch me change
Here I go! I'm changing!
Hey!
You see? I've really matured
- Oh, all right - All right!
- Come on We have to hurry - I love ya
Ladies and gentlemen of the American army
welcome to the U S O show!
Get ready for loads of
entertainment and fabulous celebrities
followed immediately by the
nasty execution of Terrance and Phillip!
This is the U S O show
where those military bitches
intend to kill Terrance and Phillip
Oh, my God!
God? He is the biggest bitch of them all
We have to hurry
We rendezvous with the other kids at 10:00
You realize that by doing this
we could be grounded for two,
perhaps even three weeks
- We're willing to take that risk - Then let's go
And now, here are your hosts for the evening
Sheila Broflovski and Big Gay Al!
Al, tonight is a very special night
Do you know why?
Ooh! They're having a sale at Merv's?
No Because we're going to abolish Canadian smut
That's right, Sheila! Bring out the condemned!
Today is a great day for democracy!
Oh, Phillip, this is worse than
that night I fell asleep
and you put your dick in my mouth
and took a picture
I know, Terrance I know
Well, Sheila, while you're getting set up over there
let's bring out our first act
Yippie, the back-flipping dog!
Be careful not to touch this wire
Aaah! Motherfu
Aaah! Fuck
Shit The U S O show has started
We are running out of time
Do you see Terrance and Phillip?
Yes, but they are heavily guarded
We have to dig from here
so as not to be seen Come on, bitches
Hey, Mole, you know where the clitoris is?
The what?
I have to find the clitoris
so I can get this Wendy girl to like me again
You need to stop thinking with your dick!
You have to be on your toes!
Because I am not going to be grounded again!
Not for you, not for anybody!
Men, when you're out there in the battlefield
and you're looking into the beady eyes of a Canadian
as he charges you with his hockey stick
or whatever he has
and people are dying all around you
just remember what the M P A A says:
Horrific, deplorable violence is okay,
as long as people don't say any naughty words!
That is what this war is all about!
What?
Shit
Move Move
Okay, we will split up here
Let's synchronize watches
We don't have watches
You don't have watches?
Dude, you didn't say anything about watches
What do you think this is, TV kiddie hour
where we all sit around
and lick Barney the Dinosaur's pussy?
This is real life with consequences
you take to the grave!
Dude, we don't have watches!
Shit, Did you bring the mirror?
- Got it Check - And the rope?
- And the "butt for"? - What's a "butt for"?
For pooping, silly
Listen carefully I will dig under the stage
With that bedrock, I will need more time
Stan and Kyle, stall the show any way you can
Keep that show going until I get the prisoners
- Okay - Cartman, over there is the electrical box
You must shut it off before
I return with Terrance and Phillip
or the alarms will sound
and I will be attacked by guard dogs
- Got it? - Okay
You must shut off the alarms
I fucking hate guard dogs
I heard you the first time,
you British piece of shit Aaaah!
If anything goes wrong,
make a sound like a dying giraffe
What's a dying giraffe sound like?
- 'Kay - Let's go
- Be careful, dude - "Careful"?
Was my mother careful when she stabbed me
in the heart with a clothes hanger
while I was still in the womb?
Damn, dude, that kid is fucked up
How are those chairs coming, Sheila?
Al, we're minutes away
Super! In the meantime, here's pint-sized pixie
and darling of the indie movie scene
Winona Ryder!
Hi, guys!
I'm super-psyched to be here today
What you're doing for our country is so cool
I mean, war, man Wow War
You know? Wow
Okay! And now for your enjoyment,
here's my famous Ping-Pong ball trick!
Oh, my!
"Shut off the power, Cartman
This is very important, Cartman "
Dude, did you hear what Winona Ryder's doing?
Oh, we can't miss this!
There, I didn't miss one
That's my Ping-Pong ball trick!
Eh-heh
Well, that's all the acts we have for you tonight
so let's just get on with the execution!
Oh, no We have to stall him
- More! More! - Yeah, more!
Oh, you big sillies! You want to see more of me?
Yeah! Big Gay Al! Big Gay Al!
Big Gay Al! Big Gay Al!
Well, I do have a little song I wrote about the war
Oh, but we haven't rehearsed
- Sing it! - Yeah, sing it!
- Oh, I can't - Sing the fucking song!
Well, all right If you insist, I'll sing my song
I believe it goes a little bit like this
Bombs are flying People are dying
Children are crying Politicians are lying too
Cancer is killing Texaco's spilling
The whole world's gone to hell But how are you
I'm super Thanks for asking
All things considered
I couldn't be better I must say
I'm feeling super No, nothing bugs me
Everything is super when you're
Don't you think I look cute in this hat
I'm so sorry Mr Cripple
But I just can't feel too bad for you right now
Because I'm feeling so insanely super
That even the fact that you can't walk
can't bring me down
He's super Thanks for asking
All things considered
he couldn't be better he must say
I'm super No, nothing bugs me
Everything is super when you're
Don't you think I look cute in this hat
These little pants
This matching tie that I got at Merv's
I'm super
He's in the barracks and the trenches as well
- Stick 'em up! - Big Gay Al says Do ask, do tell
Diddles!
Yes, he's super and he's proud to be fey
- Okay? - Everything is super when you're
Gay
When you're gay
Again! Again!
Who's there? l
Son of a gun! Heck!
They're coming?
But our moms won't listen to us!
Okay, everybody
Just want to take a minute to thank
our wonderful sponsors
He's almost got 'em
Shh! We are here to rescue you
After I release you, follow me through the tunnel
Hey, guys, seriously
- What, Cartman? - Kenny I saw Kenny again
Did you shut the alarm off, Cartman?
Cartman? - Whoops
Oh, shit!
Hey, did you hear that?
Sounds like a giraffe is dying over there
Aah! Shit!
- A spy! - Get him!
Shit! Shit!
Oh, no
- Come on, Mole Come on - Shit! Shit!
Fucking guard dogs! Shit!
The alarms, they went off
Yeah, that was my bad Sorry
Hold me It's so very cold
There is no hope now, You must get out of here
We can't leave without you
It's okay I'm done for
No, we can't leave without you
We don't know where we are!
Where is your God when you need him?
Huh? Where is your beautiful, merciful faggot now?
Here I come, God Here I come, you fucking rat
Now the light, she fades
And darkness settles in
- But I will find strength - No, Mole, Hang on
- I will find pride within - We'll get you home
- Because although I die - I can't face my mother
- Our freedom will be won - Not alone
Though I die
La Resistance lives
On
Shit!
Okay, folks, here it is, the moment we've all been
waiting for: the execution!
- The day is ours! - Super!
Oh, no, dude, it's happening
We have to tell them about Saddam Hussein and Satan
No way, dude My mom can't see me here
Kyle, you have to stand up to your mother Come on
Gentlemen, do you have any last words?
Last words? Let's see How's aboot,
"Get me the fuck out of this chair"?
- How's that for last words? - All right, Anonymous
Ready the switch!
- Wait! - Stanley!
- Eric! - Kyle!
- Go on, dude, tell her - l I can't
You can't kill Terrance and Phillip
If they die, Satan and Saddam Hussein
are gonna come take over the world
Throw the switch, Mr Garrison
Hey, I'm supposed to be anonymous
Good-bye, bastards!
No!
The Canadians are attacking! Run for your lives!
Come on! We have to shut off the power!
Ow! Fuck! Aiiiee!
Hey! Some little fat kid saved us!
Hey, you guys! Shut it down!
Shit!
Terrance and Phillip, wait!
We have to get you to the rendezvous point!
Ned, behind you!
Be not afraid
- Oh, my God! - Behold my glory
- What are you? - I am the Clitoris
The Clitoris? I did it! I found the Clitoris!
Stan, you must not let Terrance
and Phillip's blood be spilled on the ground
Wait You're supposed to tell me
how to get Wendy to like me
There are more important matters right now
No way, dude I looked all over for you,
and now you have to tell me
how to get Wendy to like me
Dude, you just have to have confidence in yourself
Believe in yourself and others will believe in you
Chicks love confidence
Now go Hurry The Clitoris has spoken
Stan! Stan, are you okay?
I see you've failed in your mission
I should not have sent a boy to do a man's job
Come on, everyone We've got precious little time
Die, Canadian, m'kay?
Did you hear that, Terrance? I farted
You did? Just now?
Terrance and Phillip!
We have to get you to the rendezvous point!
Hey, it's Mr Garrison
Children, take M-Mr Hat
please Get him out of here
Holy shit! Yaagh! Hey,
this V-chip is getting all screwy!
Take cover in the trench!
Human Shield up front
then Operation Get Behind The Darkies
Remember, Human Shield
protect our tanks and planes too
Holy Mother of Jehoshaphat!
Fire on my command!
All right, squad Just like I told you
One, two
- Is some people gonna die? - Fire!
- three! - What in the
Great plan, Chef
Operation Human Shield, my ass!
My God This is terrible
This is what we wanted
We wanted our children to be brought up
in a smut-free environment
But we didn't want this!
Where are you going?
We're going to find our boys
For God's sake, Sheila, we're going to get them killed!
Kyle, all those times I said
you were a big, dumb Jew
I didn't mean it
You're not a Jew
Yes, I am! I am a Jew, Cartman!
No, no, Kyle Don't be so hard on yourself
What the hell am I still holding this for?
- Mr Hat! No-o-o! - Fuck this, dude!
I'm getting out of here before
I get in really big trouble! - I heard that!
- Stan! - Dude, I found the Clitoris
Now I think I can get Wendy to like me again
Oh, that's swell, Stan
Yeah, I guess all's well that ends well, huh?
We can go home now You dipshit!
What's wrong with this thing?
Come on, We can't let Terrance and Phillip die
or else the whole world's gonna end!
- Terrance, look! - There they are!
Oh, Phillip! We're done for!
All right, men fire!
Oh, Phillip! We're done for
All right, men,fire!
Good-bye, Terrance
- What is this? - Don't shoot
I'll take care of this Kids
get out of the way now!
- Kyle! - I'm not gonna let you kill them, Mom
- What, what, what? - I'm not moving
- Yeah, Uh-huh - Me too
Stand down, children
You can still see fart jokes on Nickelodeon
No! This is about more than fart jokes
This is about freedom of speech,about censorship
and stuff
What about Ike? Huh, Mom?
Did you forget that your own adopted son is Canadian?
I'm l-l-I'm doing very important things
But, Mom, you never took the time to talk to me
Whenever I get in trouble
you go off and blame everybody else
But I'm the one to blame Deal with me
You keep going off and fighting all these causes
but I don't want a fighter
I want my Mom
Poor little fella!
No-o-o!
Terrance!
Holy shit, dude!
Young man, you watch your mouth!
My time has come!
You are really fucked now!
It's Saddam Hussein! Shoot him!
What a dumb-ass!
You have spilled the blood of the innocent
Now begins two million years of darkness
Oh, good job, Mrs Broflovski Thanks a lot
I was just trying to make the world
a better place for children
Yeah! And you brought enough intolerance
to the world to allow my coming
Now, everyone, bow down to me!
Yeah! Bend over!
Oh, what have we done?
Saddam, I'm the dark ruler, not you
Relax, bitch You're better seen
not heard
- Satan, you gotta do something! - I can't
Let's start by building a big statue of me
right over there where that fat kid is standing
Hey! Don't call me fat, butt-fucker!
Yeah, Cartman Do it!
Damn! Shit! Respect my fuckin' authorit-ay!
Hey! You need to watch your mouth, brat!
Dogshit taco!
Quick, Satan! Do something!
Try this on for size
Blood-drenched frozen tampon Popsicle!
Hey, buddy, I know I was mean before
But don't worry I can change
- Oh! - Okay
Not!
Fuck, shit, cock, ass
titties, boner, bitch, muff, pussy
cock, butthole, Barbra Streisand!
What are you waiting for, bitch? Destroy him!
Come on, you weak, stupid cum bucket! Save me!
That's it! I have had enough of you!
Hey, guy! Relax!
He spent so much time convincing me
I was weak and stupid
that I believed it myself
I have you to thank, little one
You showed me that I had to get away from him
Just make any wish you want and I shall grant it
- Are you sure, Kenny? - What did he say?
He said that his wish
is for everything to go back the way
it was before this horrible war
Kenny, you realize that means you'd go back too
I know
Well, very well, then
I will pull all my minions back
I'm guess I'm destined to live in hell alone
Hello What's this?
Hi there, little guy
Would you like to go to Hell with me?
Sure, I bet we could be best friends, Mr Satan
Feel free to come back and visit us
anytime you want, Satan
I just might do that
- Thank you, Kenny - Yeah, thanks for going
back to Hell for us You're a real pal
Good-bye, you guys
l I'm alive Where's Mr Hat?
Wow We were all dying,
and now we're fine That's super!
What the fuck's going on?
You see, Mom? After all that
it was Cartman's filthy
fucking mouth that saved us all
I'm sorry I didn't pay attention to you, Kyle
But, Wendy, what about Gregory?
- Oh, Stan, I never really cared for Gregory
- You didn't? - No, dude Fuck Gregory!
Fuck him right in the ear!
Yea! Thank you, Clitoris
Everything worked out What a happy end
Americans and Canadians are friends again
So let's all join hands and knock oppression down
Good Lordy, I'm found
Don't you know Our little lives are now complete
Cause Terrance and Phillip are sweet
Super sweet
Thank God we live in this quiet, little
Pissant, redneck podunk, jerkwater
Greenhorn, one-horse mudhole, peckerwood
Right-wing, whistle-stop hobnail, truck-driving
Old-fashioned, hayseed inbred, unkempt
Out-of-date, out-of-touch white-trash, kick-ass
Mountain
Town
Look!
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：274796078
Brian, skate
What would Brian Boitano do
if he was here right now
He'd make a plan and he'd follow through
That's what Brian Boitano'd do
Brian, skate
Brian, fight
When Brian Boitano was in the Olympics
skating for the gold
He did two salchows
and a triple lutz wearing a blindfold
When Brian Boitano was in the Alps
fighting grizzly bears
He used his magical fire breath
and saved the maidens fair
Brian, skate
Brian, yeah
So what would Brian Boitano do if he was here today
I'm sure he'd kick an arse or two
That's what Brian Boitano'd do
Brian, skate
Brian, hey
When Brian Boitano traveled
through time to the year 3010
He fought the evil robot king
and saved us all again
And when Brian Boitano built the pyramids
he beat up Kublai Khan
'Cause Brian Boitano doesn't take shit from anybody
No, Brian! Those chicken wings are really spicy!
Don't eat those!
I never seen a man eat so many chicken wings
Brian, skate, Brian
'Cause that's what Brian Boitano'd do
The eyes of a child
So innocent and pure
A child's heart is full of song
Take their tiny hand
And lead them to the light
As adults we see pain in the world
And it sometimes don't seem right
But through the eyes of a child
The world seems magical
There's a sparkle in their eyes
They've yet to realize
The darkness in their soul
The beauty of their smile
Adventurous and wild
Life is kind of gay but it doesn't seem that way
Through the eyes of a child
So don't give up
Even when the road seems long
Just find that child inside of you
Yeah, you've got to find you
Spread your wings and fly
To the brightest star
If you want I can even get my friend Steve
To detail your car for, like, 20 bucks
But through the eyes of a child
The world seems magical
There's a sparkle in their eyes
They've yet to realize
The darkness in their soul
The beauty of their smile
Adventurous and wild
Sure, life is kind of gay
but it doesn't seem that way
Through the eyes of a child
The world seems magical
There's a sparkle in their eyes
They've yet to realize
The bastards they really are
The beauty of their smile
Adventurous and wild
Sure, life is kind of gay
but it doesn't seem that way
Through the eyes of a child
Guys out there is hurted