更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
Our father,who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread,
and forgive us our trespasses,
as we forgive those who trespass against us.
Lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
For the kingdom,the power,and the glory are yours,
now and forever.
Amen.
Looking at mostly cloudy skies
and with lows in the upper 20s.
There will likely be some refreeze on some of the roads.
So,slick spots are possible tonight in isolated lo...
You know the most important thing
your granddad ever taught me?
Be ready.
Hurricane,flood,whatever it ends up being.
No more food gets delivered to the grocery store,
gas stations dry up.
People just turn on each other,and,uh...
All of a sudden,
all that stands between you and being dead is you.
I'm proud of you,son.
It was a nice shot.
Put your hand in the hand of the man who stilled the water
put your hand in the hand of the man who calmed the sea
take a look at yourself
and you can look at others differently
By putting your hand in the hand
of the man from galilee
every time I look at the holy book,I want to tremble
and then I read about the part
where a carpenter cleared the temple...
Hey,come on,hon.
Wait,wait,wait. I forgot something.
Hold on a second,Anna!
Ralph,you have the venison?
Yup.
I forgot the pie.
Are we taking the truck?
We're going up the street,you dope.
Come on.
Hey,wait for your mother,please.
Give me a ride.
Here.
Oh,you're gettin' heavy.
Um,Danny's dad said he'd sell me their old car.
I got half of what I need saved from the summer.
-I thought maybe you'd...-forget it.
I can barely get enough carpentry work
to keep up with the mortgage.
Well,why don't you rent out grandpa's old apartment house?
Like I keep telling your mother,it's an old building,
and it'll cost a fortune to fix it up.
Okay,okay.
They're here!
Hello.
Happy Thanksgiving. Happy Thanksgiving.
Anna,wait until we're invited.
Oh,for God's sake,Keller.Get the hell in here.
Aah!
Keller,you got the deer you shot?
This one's Ralph's.
Well,you killed it,you take it into the kitchen.
All right. Thank you.
Happy Thanksgiving.
-Happy Thanksgiving. -There he is.
Thank you. Happy t-day.
All right.Joy. Joy,three times.
Joy,get your dolls off the table.Y'all missing the game.
-Anna! Anna! -Hi. How are you?
Hey. Happy Thanksgiving.
Anna,come here.
We wait until we're invited.You understand?
You're in charge of this.
Us veterinarians make lousy butchers.
No problem.
Can I go outside with joy?
Uh,convince your brother to go with you,and you can.
All right.
And wear a hat,please.
You're just getting over a cold.
Joy,you wear a hat,too.
Did you feel bad for that deer
when you shot it?
Do you feel bad for cows when you go into McDonald's?
That's... that's what my dad says.
And the deer,if they have too many babies,
then the babies starve anyway.
You gotta keep the population down.
Right. Your dad say that,too?
Pull harder.
Hey,hey! Get away from that thing!
Let me see that.
Come on,let's go.
No.
I said let's go!
Stop. You can't just take somebody's stuff like that.
No! Let's go!
Come on. Come on,come on,come on.
Wait. Shh.You hear that?
Somebody's in there.
All right,I don't feel like getting yelled at.
Let's go. Not on Thanksgiving,okay?
Now the school board's telling me
there's no money for new marching-band uniforms.
These kids are wearin' the same uniforms
they had when we went there,and they were old then.
I mean,marchin' right out of 1979.
Why isn't he speaking to me?
He doesn't speak.
Cutie pie.
Mm-hmm.
Oh,my gosh!
He's fast,too.
He's so quick.\nIs that a slide?
Thank you,all. Thank you,all. Got a surprise.
And I am taking requests.
Yes! No.
You gotta listen out for it,'cause this is not easy.
Mom. Mommy,can I take joy to our house?
Why?
My red whistle.She's gonna help me look for it.
Oh,my sweetheart,I think that red whistle is long gone.
What whistle?
The emergency whistle daddy gave me.
I lost it...
133 days ago.
Well,if you want to find a whistle,
you have to whistle for it.
So we'll do "jingle bells" to find it.
Jingle bells,Batman smells,Robin laid an egg
the Batmobile lost its wheels,and joker got away... hey!
Yay! Okay! Okay! You can go,all right?
Just make sure Eliza and Ralph go with you,please.
-No looking in the basement. -I won't.
Y'all eardrums are just startin' to grow.
I don't want to damage them yet.
But I am taking requests from you,Keller.
From me?
Your day,your request.
Oh. Uh,the piano.
No.
No,no,no. So all set?
Wait,listen,he used to love...
he used to dresslike Springsteen.
-Really? -I still love Springsteen.
"The River," "Jersey Girl."
Well,I ain't white,and I like him too much
And I'm too drunk to cover the Boss.
Thank you.
Honey? What else?
Nothing comes to mind. Nothing.
Oh,I know. What?
He actually loves "the star-spangled banner."
I know. Sings it in the shower.
I do not.
-Yes,you do! -I got you.
Where are your sisters?
I can't find them.
You,uh,you go to the house with them?
No. What are you talking about?
Earlier? No.
What? They were supposed to come down earlier and get you.
They didn't come get you?
No. We haven't seen them since we ate.
It's all right. All right.
They're probably at our house.
Anna? Joy?
Anna?
Girls?
Girls?!
Who put these dishes in here?
Get outta here.They weren't outside.
It's starting to rain.
Did you check over by Maria's swing?
Yeah.
Well,they're gettin' whupped when they get here.
Sorry,Grace.I whup kids.
So they weren't there either?
They must be at home.
Are they here?
No. They're not here.They weren't there?
No,they're not at our house.
No,they're not there.
I checked the entire house.They're not here.
The... the...the RV.
What RV?
Dad,there was this RV,and they were playing on it.
We thought there was someone inside.
Where? Where was it? Show me.
You wait here.
I'm gonna gonna over the house again.
Relax. Relax.
Go that way. I'll meet you on the other side.
Anna?!
Joy!
Roger,you seen my daughter walk by here?
No. Is there a problem?
Anna?
Here!
Dad,it was parked right here.
Anna? Anna?
Hello,hello!
Did you see 'em? No!
Hello!
I couldn't find 'em!
Were you messing around in this house? -No.
I told you not to come here. We weren't.
They were just on the RV,and we got them off of it.
Tell me everything you remember about that rv.
Everything. A-a ladder on the back.
Police,police.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Thanks.
Hey,you have any of those,um,fortune-cookie things?
My boss told me cops don't like fortune cookies.
What year were you born?
Are you a dragon or a snake or a horse?
I'm a monkey.
Oh,you're a monkey.
You're very intelligent.
You have an ability to influence people.
Think maybe you could influence your boss
to lower the check a little bit?
No. I cannot.
My boss is a rooster.
Silly,selfish,and eccentric.
That's...
All units,all units,
an RV was reported matching the description.
The vehicle is parked at a rest stop off of route 46,
northbound,past exit 17.
Any available units?
This is 12-12 responding.
10-80 responding.
This is 13-40.I'm five minutes out.
I'll meet the responding units.
12-12 standing by.
10-80 standing by.
13-40. I'm on scene.
Be advised,we're moving in.
Whoa! Hey,don't move! Hey!
Whoa,whoa,watch out!
Hey,don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
All right,Sloan,take the right!
Clear!
Wait,wait,wait,wait,wait! I got this.
Gimme that.
Hey.
Hey. I see you in there.
Show me both your hands right now.
Hey,I see you in there!
Show me your hands!
Both hands right now!
That's it.Slow. Slow. Slow!
Slow. Slowly. Both hands.
Both fuckin' hands!
Walk! Walk!
Hey!
Walk!
Get up! Get up!
Get up!
Show me those girls!
Show me where you put those girls,huh?
Where are those girls?
Where are those girls?!
Hey,give me the flashlight.Sir.
Show me where those girls...they in the woods?
You put them in the woods?
Where did you put those girls?
You hear me?!
What the fuck is this guy on?
He's high on something.
Put this fucking guy in the car.
Get him in the car. Put him in the fucking car!
Walk! Let's go.
Hey,call PSP,tell 'em to send their scent dogs.
And seal off the whole area.
The entrance,all of it.
Right.
You,come with me.
No,they weren't playing on your RV?
No.
Okay,take a look at 'em again.
Don't recognize these girls?
I didn't see them.May I sit down?
What do you do in the RV? Answer my question.
Sleep there.
You sleep in there?
You were sleeping out there?
In the day?
Why was the RV parked outside the house?
Hmm.
I went for a drive?
You went for a drive? You weren't driving.
I know for a fact those girls were playing outside your rv.
You weren't driving.It was parked.
Was it a special day?
Were you planning on taking two little girls?
No.
Have you done that before?
-Did you ask them to come inside? -No.
You ask them to come inside the RV and then you take them away?
No.
Did you put those girls somewhere?
May I sit down? Come on.
-Did you put those girls somewhere? -Please don't touch me.
I know you put those girls somewhere.
You hide 'em? No.
How did you hide 'em? Do you tie 'em up?
Do you tie 'em up?
Huh? Hey. Hey. Hey.
Look,I know you're a good guy,all right?
I know you're a decent guy.
I'm not tryin' to tell you you're doing anything bad.
I'm just tryin' to get the right answers out of you,okay?
The real ones. That's all I want.
Where do you usually park your rv,Alex?
My aunt's house. Your aunt's house?
She lets me park it in the backyard.
The grass don't grow back there anyway.
It was my husband's.
For sale,if you want it.
No,thanks.
Well,would you tell me
what you're doin' on my property then?
I'm just glad to know where he is.
He's always home before dark,and...
I just don't understand.
That boy has never been in trouble,
not a day in his life.
Uh,in the summertime,
he sleeps out in the camper some,but...
This time of year,he sleeps in here on the sofa bed.
That's my husband.
We had a fight,jeez,five years ago.
Walked out,didn't come back.
Alex loved him like a father.
Where are Alex's real parents?
My husband's brother and his girlfriend,
they died in a car accident when Alex was about 6.
Sorry to hear that.
He doesn't have much.
What have you got?
Well,this thing's clean.
I mean,it's filthy as shit,but we didn't find anything.
We didn't find any,uh,wool fibers,anything like that?
The girls could be wearing some wool gloves or wool hat.
No cotton fibers?
Well,if he was just usin' this thing to transport 'em,
I might buy that.
But if there had been a struggle,
I would have found something.
I'd start lookin' in the woods by the rest stop.
Yeah.
Half the uniformed cops in the state
are doin' that right now.
When you're done with this thing,
can you send a crew over to the aunt's house?
Anna!
Anna?!
Thanks for comin'. Franklin birch.
My wife's in here.
Honey?
Her name's Nancy.
Detective Loki is...honey?
These photos are better than the ones my husband gave you.
You can see her eyes more clearly.
So,did we pass?
I'm sorry,what did you say?
The poly thing.
The lie detector we took this morning.
Did we pass?
Oh,yeah,yeah. Sorry.
Yes,we appreciate your cooperation.
It's embarrassing,all the...all this fuss.
Everyone's gonna think we're crazy
when those two come out of hiding,wherever they are.
Do you have some reason to believe they ran away?
No.
They're happy.
They must have run away.
I think they must have run away.
Right?
Um,your police captain told me
that you've solved every case that you've ever been assigned.
Is that right?
Sorry.
I am so sorry.
Do you... do you have children,detective?
I'm gonna find your daughter.
We believe that they came back here
after they left you at the birches' yesterday.
They were looking for Anna's red whistle.
Right.
I read your statement.
I'm detective Loki.
I'm heading up the investigation
into your daughter's disappearance.
Please sit down.
Uh,uh,m-my son already told you
that the guy was inside the RV just watchin' 'em,right?
We haven't found any physical evidence inside the RV.
Or his aunt's house where he lives.
Nothing?
Alex Jones unfortunately has the I.Q. Of a 10-year-old.
There is no way that someone with the I.Q. Of a 10-year-old
could abduct two girls in broad daylight and then...
Somehow make them disappear.
Uh,well,how can he drive an rv?
If he can't answer a question...
Well,he has a legal Pennsylvania license.
And he ran,right? They said he tried to run away.
Why... why... Why would he run?
I've just spent 10 hours questioning this boy. Okay?
I hear what you're saying.
Uh... Did... did you give him a lie detector?
You gave us a lie detector. Did you give him one?
Sir,I understand what you're asking me. Yes,we did.
We gave him a lie detector,and there is no way of...
A lie detector doesn't work
if you don't understand the questions.
Well,maybe he wasn't on his own.
How could he drive an rv
if he has an I.Q. of a 10-year-old?
Hey,we're considering all possibilities.
I don't think you are considering all possibilities.
I-I hear what you're saying. Sir... sir...you listen to me.
Just shut the fuck up for a fucking second!
This is what I'm gonna need you to do for me.
I need you to calm down.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Please listen to me for a second.
Mr. Dover,I understand this is an incredibly hard time.
But I have every uniformed police officer in this state
looking for Anna.
I don't understand what any of this means.
They said he ran.
They said he tried to get away.
I don't understand why he would try to run away.
We're considering all possibilities,Mr. Dover.
I hear what you're saying.
I'm not crossing anybody off my list.
Just... Let me do my job.
Hey!
Detective!
-Oh,shit. -Hey!
He stays in custody until my daughter's found,right?
Right?
We have a 48-hour hold on him
that ends tomorrow unless we bring charges.
Well,charge him with something. Charge him.
Mr. Dover,I understand what you're...
detective,detective,two little girls
have got to be worth whatever little rule
you've got to break to keep that asshole in custody.
Now,I know you can't promise me anything.
I understand that.
But I'm asking you to be 100% sure.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
So you're positive he's innocent,
but you want to keep holding him?
Anna Dover's father was on my ass this morning.
I-I get it. I understand. But it's not gonna happen.
I was asking for one more day. Fuck you.
No,no.
You find his daughter,he'll forgive you.
You don't,he's gonna hate you anyway.
So what's next?
I'm knockin' on doors all night.
Yeah,well,you're comin' up on 24 hours missing,
and you have exactly shit.
No,I've got nine level-three sex offenders
living within a 10-mile radius of Fairmont circle.
So if you don't mind...
Then go. Yeah.
Go.
It's right here.
Look,I-I'm staying straight,okay?
Well,hey,look.Look,I know you're...
you like yourself some German porn,huh?
Look,I was...
Father! Open up! It's the police!
Father!
Father.
You mind if I take a look around?
Fuckin'drunk.
What the fuck?
Whoa.
Aye. Fuck.
Oh! Please,God! God!
What's the name of your buddy down there,huh?
What's the name,huh? I don't know his name.
You don't know his name?
I don't know his name.
Hey,you know what?
I spent six years in Huntington Boys' Home,father.
You know the Huntington Boys' Home,right? Huh?
Hurting a fuck like you'd be a real treat for me.
Why don't you tell me his fuckin' name?
He didn't tell me his name.
He came to me for confession.
He said he'd killed 16 children.He bragged about it.
I convinced him to come back here.
He said he'd kill more.
16 children,huh?
Let's go,you fucking chicken-hawk!
Hey.
They're letting him go.
What? The man.
The police said they're letting him go today.
O-okay.I'll take care of it.
Dad? Keep searching.
Where are you goin'?!
He wants you to write your whole name.
That's good.
Mm-hmm. Good job.
Now you give it to the man.
All right. Come on.
I don't want you minding these people out here.
Don't talk to them. You've got nothing to say to them. Come on.
Come on,Alex. You took those kids,didn't you?
Sir...I just want to talk.
He's a free man,I'm a free man!
Hey! Tell me what you did with them!
Tell me!
They didn't cry until I left them.
What did you say? What did you say?!
Whoa,no,no!
Fuckin' get off!
God! Get up!
Get him down! Get him down!
Move back!
Please,just let us go.
We're fine. Thank you.
Now,I know your dad was a guard at Graterford.
And I've got a daughter of my own,
so we're gonna pretend this never happened.
And as for Alex Jones,
he has orders not to leave the commonwealth.
What?
Sir,I need you to go home. All right?
I need you to go home to your family.
Why aren't you sending someone out to go arrest this guy?
Tell detective Loki what you just told me,
and he'll definitely look into it.
Go ahead.
That asshole you promised me you'd keep in custody,right?
And you didn't.
And right now when I grabbed him in the parking lot,
he said right to my fucking face,
"they didn't cry until I left them."
Right to my fucking face.
He... he said that to you in the parking lot just now?
Right now,yeah. What did I just say?
In the parking lot.
Before you grabbed me off him.
Did anyone else hear it besides you?
I don't know. It was quiet.
He... he said it to me. He wanted me to know.
Are you sure he said that? What?
Are you sure that's what he said?
Jesus Christ,you think I'm makin' this up?
No. Why would I make this up?
Hey,hey,hey,whoa,whoa. No,think about it.
Why would I make this up? I'm not saying that to you.
I'm just asking you a couple questions.
I will talk to him.
No,don't talk to him! Mr. Dover...
arrest him!
What did I fuckin' tell you?
What'd I tell you? One more day.
You sure you didn't say anything to Mr. Dover
in the parking lot today?
Anything he could have misinterpreted or...?
I was right there.
They didn't say anything to each other.
Man just attacked the boy.
Nothing like "get away from me" or "help" or...
Anything like that?
No.
Can I speak to Alex alone for a minute?
It's all right,sweetie.
I'll be right in the next room.
You love your aunt,don't you,Alex?
Yes.
You know if you know something you're not telling us
that she could go to jail for a very long time.
Do you want that for her?
After everything she's done for you?
No.
Mr. Dover,this is detective Loki.
Have you arrested him?
Yeah,look,I just came from Alex Jones,
and he said he didn't say anything to you
in the parking lot.
I pushed him pretty hard,and he didn't budge.
So,look,we can't waste any more time on this guy.
All right? You're gonna have to trust me.
I'll let you know if I have anything new,all right,
for the...
Fuckin' A
The zipper on her coat was broken,
and I told her it didn't matter
'cause we were just gonna go right down the street.
No,no.
Why hasn't she come home?
It's been three days.
Why can't you make her come home?
I don't understand.
I don't understand. It's been too long.
Please make her come home.
Please make her...
How many of these? How many of these?
How many of these? I don't know!
It's okay. It's all right.
Just take one.
Here.
No.
I just want to sleep.
I just want to go to sleep.
You...
You made me feel so safe.
Oh,God...
I'm gonna go out and help the police.
Just keep an eye on your mother.
Your sister needs us to be brave for her.
Be brave for her.Be a grown-up for me,okay?
Can you do that?
I know you're scared. Look at me. Come here.
I know you're scared.
It's gonna be okay.
The former is a reason why we should be very patient.
The latter why we should be very penitent
when we are afflicted.
He reminds him that trouble and affliction
are what we have all reason to expect in this world.
Man is brought into trouble,not as man,
but as sinful man,who was in transgression.
Man born in sin and therefore born to trouble.
Come on.
Come on,Tucker.
Jingle bells,Batman smells
Robin laid an egg
the Batmobile lost its wheels
joker got away,hey
jingle bells,Batman smells,Robin laid an egg
Jingle bells,Batman smells
Robin laid an egg
the Batmobile... -Alex.
Lost its wheel...
That song.
Where did you hear those words?
Hmm?
Did you bring a change of clothes like I told you?
Yeah.You gonna tell me why?
It's better if I just show you.
Show me what?
Didn't you used to live here?
Close the door.Lock it.
Oh,my God.What... what did you do?
Keller,what the hell...?
I heard him singing the same song
they were singing on Thanksgiving.
Swear to God,Franklin. The same fucking song.
And I told you what he said in the parking lot.
Then we take him to the police...
no,no,no.The police won't do shit.
He'll just clam up and act crazy like he did last time.
Someone has to make him talk.
Someone.
Shit,man.This... this ain't right.
I mean,what if you're wrong?
I'm not wrong. But what if you are?
What if you only heard what you wanted to hear?
What if...
Man,I want my daughter back as much as you do,
but it ain't right. Franklin! Franklin!
We hurt him until he talks,or they're gonna die.
This ain't...
No! No!
We hurt him until he talks or they're gonna die.
That's the choice.
That's the choice you have to make.
I've made my choice.
I know what I heard.
He's not a person anymore.
No,he stopped being a person when he took our daughters.
I need your help.
This is your last chance.I know you're scared.
And I know you wanna go home.
And I don't...I don't want to hurt you.
I don't.
I'm gonna take the tape off,
and I want you to tell me where they are.
Hey. Come on.
Did you see my glasses?
What?
I can't see.
If you're not gonna talk,Alex,I'm gonna have to hurt you.
Tell me where they are.
Where are they?
Tell me where they are!
Yeah,I'm out here at a house on Fairmont circle,
the house the rv was parked in front of.
It's only been on the market a couple of months.
I'm gonna track the owners down,see if they know anything.
You got any new info on that corpse
we found in the priest's basement?
No DNA,dental,or fingerprint matches.
Nothing.
Priest is sticking to the story,too.
All right.
Same person who took him took those girls.
I'm sure of it.
Wearing out the tape,I guess.
I watch it every day after breakfast.
It's the only video I have of him.
It was before your time.
26 years ago,August 19th.
I took a nap in the afternoon,
and when I woke up,Barry was gone.
No one could ever tell me what happened to him.
He was playing in the front yard,
just a few feet from where they say that rv was parked.
What do you think that means?
I'm more interested in what you think that means.
I don't think we'll ever know.
It's just like Barry.
No one took them.
Nothing happened.
They're just gone.
How you doin',father?
I'm... I'm...gettin' better.
So detective Chemelinski tells me
that you have some specifics
about the crime you claim that guy committed.
The abductor.
He was...
Waging a war against God.
Great.That's great.
I thought you said he had something specific.
Tell him how he took the kids.
He said...
he took them in daylight.
Sometimes...
More than one child at a time.
He said that?
Yeah.
Did he say he was with anybody?
He did it alone?
He...
He said he had a family.
That's it?
All right.
Informative.
You said they cried when you left them.
Look at me.
You said they cried when you left them!
Now tell me!
Where is she? Hmm? Hmm?
Tell me where they are!
Just tell me.Just tell me and I'll stop.
I'll stop as soon as you tell me.
Just...
Just tell me where they are.
Why won't you tell me?
Huh?
Why won't you just fuckin' tell us?
He knows.
I can see it in his eyes.He fucking knows.
I know you know!
Why aren't you fucking telling me?!
Why?!
Fine.
Get him up.Get him up. Get up.
Get up. Get up.Get up!
You gonna make me use this?
You gonna tell us?
If you don't,I'm gonna use this.
Fine.
You're doing this to yourself.
Just tell us.Tell me.
Tell me!
Tell me! Tell me!
Where's my daughter?!
Where's... My...Daughter?!
Four days have passed
since Anna Dover and Joy Birch
were last seen by their families.
The two girls,aged 6 and 7,
are believed to have been playing on this street
when they disappeared without a trace.
As you can see,despite the cold,
a lot of people have turned out tonight to show their support.
Police are asking that anyone
with any information on the girls' whereabouts...
Where have you been?
I was searching for her in the woods.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
Franklin.
Franklin,what is it?
I just need a minute.
What the fuck?
Hey! Get offa me!
Hey! Hey!
And this is who police are saying
is a person of interest
in the investigation of the two missing girls.
Now,this unidentified man,
who was last seen at last night's candlelight vigil,
fled on foot when the investigating detective
attempted to question him.
Police caution the public not to approach this man,
but to call police immediately if they do see him.
Thanks,John,for that update.
And now for the weather.
We should expect heavy rain into the weekend and...
Look,Keller,I mean,just think about it.
Why would the police be lookin' for this man
if they didn't think that he did it in the first place?
They did it together.They know each other.
Listen,I fuckin' told you,all right?
Jones looked me in the eye and he said,
"they only cried when I left them."
He left 'em with someone,and he knows where this guy is.
Holly Jones' dog got hit on southward street.
Apparently Alex Jones took the dog for a walk
the night before last...they never came home.
And his aunt didn't want to tell us about the dog
when we called her about it this morning.
She said that she thought
it would get him into trouble or some shit.
I thought you said you would keep him under surveillance.
Yeah,and I thought you said the guy was innocent.
And I thought the guy from last night you said was our guy.
Look,I don't have money in the budget
for watching innocent people.
You said to me that you'd put him under surveillance.
What do you want me to say? You gonna keep your word?
You could have just given me a call,because I would have
been there all night. I would have stayed up all night.
I would know where he was now.
I need to know where everybody is.
All right,point made. All right? Point made.
If you can be clear with me,then I'll be clear with you.
I need to know where everybody is.
If you're gonna do something different,please tell me.
Tell me about your RV.
What do you do in your RV?
It's where I go...
To be alone.
What music do you listen to in your RV when you're alone?
Radio,tape...
The RV was parked over on Fairmont circle?
No.
Is my aunt coming?
Have you seen these girls?
No.
Take a look at 'em.You seen these girls?
Did you participate in any way
in the abduction of those girls?
No.
Loki! You got a call.
All right.
I called as soon as I saw the sketch on TV.
He comes in here every week almost
and buys kids' clothes,
but he's always buying stuff in different sizes.
Caught him messing around with the mannequins once.
What did he pay with?
Cash.
All right,you give me a call if you hear anything.
Okay.
It's been five days.
Maybe five days since they had a drink of water.
This could be the last night that matters.
Look,I'll call you after Nancy goes to sleep,all right?
I promise.
Where have you been all this time?
What the hell were you thinking?
You tell anyone?
Did you?
I wanna see him.
Please help me.
Could you help me find my little girl?
Got a picture.
See?
This my baby.
You see her?
Her name is joy.
And,um...
This is...
A stuffed animal we got her when she was 2
because she's afraid to sleep by herself.
Please... Tell me where my little girl is.
Please tell me where my little girl...
I know you're gonna tell me.
I know.
Help me.
Franklin,did you close the door to the...
Nancy!
What the fuck you doin'?
God damn it!Damn!
Let it go!
You untied him? Huh?
That was close.
What is it? What happened?
Get Franklin.I need to show you something.
Did he say anything new?
He will soon.You'll see.
No light gets in.
There's barely enough room to sit down inside.
Shower still works,
but we control it from out here.
And I rigged the water heater
so it either comes out scalding or freezing.
And,uh,you talk to him through this.
It's to remind us...
In case we start feeling sorry for him.
My God.
I can't hurt him any more without killing him,
so this is the only way.
Have you lost your mind,Keller?
Do you have a better idea,Franklin?
Do you?
Go ahead.Let him out,if you want.
I'm not gonna stop you.
If that's what you really want,you go ahead.
You think someone's lookin' out for our girls
the way you're lookin' out for him?
I hope.
It's been five days now,man.We're runnin' out of time.
You don't even know it's him.
Yeah,I do. No,you don't.
I do. I know you. You don't.
Look,I want my baby back...
As much as you miss Anna.
And despite what you think about me,
I would die for my daughter.
But this ain't right.
This has to stop.
Well,then,you better get to work.
You can start with that wall there.
Franklin.
Stop.
Franklin...
Think of joy.
I need to get out of this place,Ralph.
Everything in this house just makes me want to throw up.
Your dad's building?
There is no way I'm staying in that crackhouse.
It's disgusting.
Yeah,okay.
We're not gonna help Keller,but we won't stop him,either.
Let him do what he needs to.
We don't know about it anymore.
Eliza?
Excuse me.Eliza?
Eliza,open the door!
Eliza?
Is she in there?
Honey?
Get out of the way!Get out of the way!
Yeah,fuck you both!
Next time you plan on leaving me here alone,
maybe you could try at least telling me where you're going!
Ralph?
Anna?
Mom?
Anna.Anna was here.
Mom,it's freezing in here.
Mom! Hey,mom,mom,mom,please sit down.
Stop. Calm down.I'm gonna close the window.
And she wasn't here.
And then I heard a sound from my room,
and I... I came in and the window was open.
And... and it wasn't open before.
And then... and then Ralph,he... he came in...
And he looked and... and,um...
And then...
Then I don't know.
Aren't you gonna write this down?
The basement.
I didn't check the basement. We need to check the basement.
I-I'll show you. I'll show you.
The kids know they're not allowed down here.
They're not supposed to come down here,
but I-I don't know.
My husband likes to be prepared for emergencies.
Where is your husband,Mrs. Dover?
I was gonna ask you.
He's been out searching with the police for Anna.
Which you should be doing right now.
Does he always stay out this late?
Yes,he stays out this late
when he's looking for my daughter,
since my daughter has been gone... yes!
Shit.
Hey,go aro...
go around.
Fuck.
Come on,Mr. Dover.
Shit.
Why are you following me?
Get in the car.
Where did you go just now?
I parked at a liquor store.
I have a bottle of liquor.
You're the shit-hot detective.Work it out.
I actually meant before that.
You were walking in the opposite direction
across the parking lot.
Towards campello street.
Yeah,well... I haven't had a drink
in nine-and-a-half years.
I figured if I walked around the parking lot for a while,
by the time they opened,I'd stop wanting it that bad.
And then... then I saw you.
Sorta helped me make up my mind.
There's a bag of lye in your basement that's half-empty.
Your wife thinks you've been helpin' us...
But we both know that's not true.
I used the lye to bury our dog last year.
And "helping the cops" sounds better
than "I've been driving aimlessly in my truck
'cause I don't know what the fuck else to do."
Is that what you were doing last Saturday night?
Probably.Am I a suspect?
No,I'm only asking
I'm only asking 'cause you assaulted a man who's now missing.
I heard about that.What happened to him?
Thought you had him under surveillance.
I'm gonna assume you're asking me because you have no idea.
Well,I didn't think it was something I could get away with.
It's not.
Yeah,well,it couldn't be that he skipped town
'cause the asshole is guilty. Couldn't be that,right?
'Cause that would mean it would be your fault,right?
Mr. Dover?
Mr. Dover? What?
You need to take care of yourself and your wife.
That's the best thing you can do right now.
That little girl is gonna need you when she comes home.
Kids gone for more than a week
have half as good a chance of being found,
and after a month,almost none are.
Not alive. All right?
So forgive me for doing everything I can...
You know what?It hasn't been a fucking week.
You're right. It's day fucking six!
Day six!
And every day she's wondering why
I'm not there to fucking rescue her!
All right. Do you understand that?!
Me! Not you! Not you! But me!
Every day!
So forgive me for not going home to have a good night's rest!
Now,why don't you look
for my fucking daughter rather than fighting...
hey,hey,hey,hey,hey,hey.
Don't follow me.
Mr. Dover. Mr. Dover.
You don't think I'm gonna let you get behind the wheel
after you've been drinkin',do you?
I'm gonna walk.\nYou look for my daughter.
Daddy.
Look,daddy,we found it.
Anna... Where was it?
I'm not Alex.
What... what are you saying? What? What?
I'm... Not... Alex.
Wait a minute. You're not Alex? What?
I'm not Alex.
Just a second. I don't understand.
Just... just talk to me.
I waited,and he never came.
Come on. No more riddles.
Just fuckin' tell me.
I'll let you go home to your aunt
if you tell me where they are.
I just wanted to play.
Don't make me do this again.
And he never came. Don't make me do it.
He never came.
I just wanted to...
why are you making me do this?
Help me,God.
Relying on your almighty power
and infinite mercies and promises,
I hope to obtain pardon for my sins.
Fuck me.
No... no noise.You shut up.
You make any noise,I'm gonna turn on that tap.
Hey,rise and shine.
I'm not gonna find two girls here,am I?
Fuck you.
What about Alex Jones?
What about him?
I came here to drink.
I don't want to drink in front of my wife.
Look... My father left me this building,all right?
You mind giving me a tour?
Why didn't you tell me about this place?
I didn't think it mattered.
Everything matters.
It's all pretty much like this.
I'm gonna renovate soon.
Yeah.
Not as organized as your basement,huh?
What's up with all the survivor gear in there?
Pray for the best,prepare for the worst.
Guess we agree there,yeah?
Come on,hurry up.
Shit.
Hello?
The guy that you were looking for was just here.
He saw me watching him and ran.
You get a plate?
Yeah.
Go home,Mr. Dover.
Hi.
Mornin'.
Why'd you run away from me the other night,man?
I've never seen you before.
You sure you have the right house?
You doin' some shopping at the value mall lately?
Yeah.
Why? Is it a crime to shop there?
I can't afford to buy suits from Brooks Brothers.
Yeah,I know.
You bought children's clothes.
Did I?
Must've been in a hurry.
Do... do you have children?
No.
I don't...Have...
Have anything...
Come on! Christ!
Give me your fucking hand.
Hey.
If you move,I'll put a bullet through your fuckin' head.
This is 13-40.
I need additional unit for search.
437 Carrol street.
Possible kidnapping victims on the premises.
Anna?
Anna? Joy?
Fuck.
Aye! Fuck.
Ah.
Ah. Fuck.
So we've taken photographs of some of the clothing
we found in the suspect's house.
Mr. Dover.
Mr. Dover,is your wife here?
She's not coming.
Well,if you can't make a positive I.D.
On any of these photographs
I'm gonna need her to come in and take a look at them.
Have a seat.
So he confessed? He said he killed them?
We were hoping he was lying,but...
We haven't even found any bodies,Mr. Dover,but...
the birches positively identified
two pieces of clothing.
I'm gonna need you...
I'm gonna need you to tell me if you recognize anything.
No.
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
No.
That... That's her...
That's her sock.
You...
You wasted time.
You wasted time following me.
You let this happen.
Don't talk to them.
Eliza told me they're dead.
Is it true?
No.
She said they found their bloody clothes
don't you tell your mother that.
Don't you dare tell your mother that.
You understand me?
Now,I need you to listen to me.
I need you to stay around the house for a couple of days,
and you make sure she does not watch the news,
and when the paper comes,
you just throw itthe fuck away... listen to me!
We do not give up on your sister!
We do not!
I'm gonna find her.I'm gonna bring her home.
We do not give up.
You're gonna bring her home? She's dead.
You can't do anything.
You've been leavin' me and mom here while you...
you've been goin' out and getting fuckin' drunk!
You think I can't smell it on you?!
Shut up!
How long has this Bob Taylor been workin' on this map?
Three-and-a-half hours.
And you think this is gonna lead you to the bodies?
'Cause I sure as shit don't.
Do me a favor,captain.Go fuck yourself.
We weren't getting anywhere questioning him.
That looks more like a maze than a map.
He's got a thing for mazes.
I'm goin' home.Call me if somethin' happens.
Give me that card,Johnny.The key card.
All right,it's done now.
Tell me what you're drawing.
You said you were drawing a map.
That looks like a fucking puzzle.
You tell me what you're drawing.
Tell me what you're drawing.
I can't!
Yes,you can!Yes,you can!Oh,shit!
Shit!
Yes,you can!Yes,you can!
Take him! Come on! Yes,you can!
Yes,he can!
Oh,shit!
Gun! Gun! Gun!
Bob,don't! Put the gun down!
Bob. Bob. Put the gun down!
Bob,Bob,Bob,Bob,Bob,no! No,no,no!
No,no,no!
Fuck.
Go call a fuckin' R.A.!
Our father who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done,
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day\nour daily bread,
and forgive us our trespasses...
As we...
As we for...
He explain this before he ate the bullet?
I'm sorry.
Fuck you're sorry.
Save it for the girls' parents.
I don't know what to do,Alex.
I don't know what to do anymore.
And what's completely fucked up about all this
is I know you know where they are.
I think we're done.
They're in the maze.
That's where you'll find them.
What?
What did you say?
In the maze.
What... what... maze?
Where is it?Where is the maze?
Where do I find it?
Alex?
Alex,Alex,listen to me.
I'm gonna get you out of here,okay?
Just tell me where the maze is.
That's it.Just tell me,man.
Where is the maze?
Come on,tell me.
Just tell me where the maze is,okay?
Come on,don't fuck with me.
Don't fuck with me now.
Tell me,God damn it!
Tell me where they are!
Tell me! Tell me! Tell me!
Something's gonna get to you,man.
Something's gonna get to you!
Just a minute!
Can I help you?
Morning,ma'am.
Um... I'm Keller Dover.
Uh,my little girl was abducted with a friend.
What do you want?
Uh...
I-I guess I haven't thought this through too good,huh?
I...
I've been thinkin' a lot about what happened to your nephew.
And I know I scared him
the other day at the police station,and... and...
What I'm tryin' to say is
I kind of feel responsible for him running away.
You wanna come on in?
Yeah.
My husband and I were...
Very devout at one time.
Spent our summers driving around
in that camper with our son...
Handin' out pamphlets...
Spreadin' the good word.
After our son died of cancer...
We started seein' things differently.
Adopting Alex helped...
But we never got over it.
I'm sorry.
You look very tired.
Yeah,I don't sleep much.
I,uh...
I keep dreaming about being lost in a maze.
I'm sorry.
Alex never talks very much,so...
When people come over here,I hardly know what to say.
He doesn't talk much?
Well,he talks,you know.
"Good morning," "good night"...that sort of thing.
Hard to get too much more than that out of him.
He had an accident when he was little.
After that,he started
choosing his words a little too carefully.
What,uh,what kind of accident did he...
Oh.
My husband kept snakes.
It wasn't that bad what happened,
but Alex had a fear of them and...
That's not my favorite memory.
I'm sorry. It's none...none of my business.
Oh,it's...
Can I get you a cup of tea,Mr. Dover?
Oh.
Oh,I'm so sorry.
I thought you had known about that already.
I say it's better this way.
You know,that awful man,
he would have spent years on death row
just watchin' TV and gettin' fat.
Well,least I don't have to worry about losing you to PSP.
When forensics is finished with the guy's place,
we're gonna deploy the cadaver dogs.
Look,kid,we can't always save the day.
All right? We're just cops,janitors.
So you lost this one,all right?
Look,you want fulfillment,you need to find a girl,
you know,start a family,have some kids.
Let it go.
Yeah?
Hey,it's Rich.We found somethin'.
Guys,let us have a look.
Two kid-sized department store mannequins,
with their heads caved in.
I just talked to our lab guys,
and they told me that all the blood that we sampled
from the plastic containers pig's blood.
All right,you guys,let's get this covered up.
It's supposed to snow soon.Hurry up,okay?
It's like he's play-acting.
I mean,case in point.
Except for the few items I.D.'d by the Dovers and the Birches,
all the kids' clothes that we found
still had the tags on them.
And that maze book that we found,he made it.
Photocopies,pictures from this book
that we found in the attic.
Ex-F.B.I. Agent wrote that.
"Finding the Invisible Man."
Yeah,it's about a theoretical suspect that he believed
was responsible for a bunch of child abductions.
It's totally discredited,I guess,
but I read some of it.
Taylor... Taylor was abducted when he was a kid.
He ran away after three weeks.
And the captor drugged him
on some sort of LSD/Ketamine cocktail.
He never remembered. They never caught the guy.
Okay,so...
He read the book
and decided he was taken by the invisible man.
Now he's doing his best imitation,right?
Yeah,he was doing his best imitation.
He killed himself last night.
How did he do that? I thought he was in custody.
Hey.
Taylor drew this.
It's a map to the bodies.
And we found the same design on a pendant
that we pulled off that corpse the other day.
There's a connection. Okay?
The connection is that it's the last maze in the book.
I did it. It's unsolvable.There's no way out.
Your corpse is another wannabe who read the book.
What are you saying to me,Rich?
What are you saying to me? What are you saying?
That... that...that this guy is a fake?
You're saying that the girls...
the girls are still out there somewhere?
How did Bob Taylor get those clothes?
How did... how did the parents...
Positively I.D.Those clothes?!
That I can't reconcile.
You can't reconcile that?
Just keep knockin' on doors,look in the windows.
Hey,why is that there? Bag that.
Will do,sir. Right away.
Yes?
Um,yeah. This is she.
What?
Oh,my God!
Uh,wait. Is she...?
Ralph! Keller!
Keller! We need to go to the hospital!
They found joy,but not Anna! What?
They didn't find Anna!
Maybe she'll know where Anna is! Please,we have to go!
Keller!
Eliza's not picking up.
You should text her.
Yeah.
Nobody gets beyond this point.
Don't touch me.
Miss! Wait a minute...
It's okay.
Nancy.
Grace.
They'll find Anna. I know they will.
I know they will.
I know.How is she?
Is she awake?
Joy,were you far from our street?
How far from the street were you,Joy?
Joy?
You can't be doing this now.
How long did it take you to get there?
Just let me ask a question! Please. Keller!
The detective will be back in just a minute.
You need to wait.
She's been drugged.
Joy.
Sweetheart...
Just let us know she's alive,okay?
Can you just nod your head,baby?
Just nod your head? Baby?
Can you give us a nod?
Can you nod your head for us,please? Joy?
Joy?
You were there.
What? I was... I was where?
It put tape on our mouths.
Shhh.
It's okay.It's okay,baby.
It's okay. It's okay.
Mommy and daddy are here now,okay?
You're all right.
Excuse me. You're all right now.
I said nobody's allowed in that room but her family.
Hey! Where you goin'?
Keller?
Hey! Where's he goin'?
I don't know. Hey!
Call downstairs. Don't let him go.
Hey! Hey! Block off the exits.
Hey!
Stop that car! Get his truck!
Stop it! Hey! Hey!
I've got you,you fucker.
I know where you're goin'.
Hello again.
Hey. I was hoping you'd,uh,you'd let me do some penance.
For what?
For scaring you the other day at the,uh,the police station.
You already apologized for that.
I know. I was... you know,I thought maybe you,uh...
You could use some,uh,help around the...
you know,I noticed your door here needs fixing,
so I brought my tools and,uh...
Oh.
I see.
I burned myself.Feel a little icky today.
But I'm glad you want to talk some more.
No need to make excuses.
You come on in and make me a cup of tea.
Come on in.
I don't want to have to hurt you.
I know they were here.
Put your hands on your head and turn around.
Do it.
I'm just gonna go.
Don't touch that bag.
Put your hands on your head.
Come over here to this counter.
Come on!
Top drawer.
Open it.
Put them on.
You don't know me,Mr. Dover.
But believe me when I tell you,I won't let you go.
You don't have to drink all of it.
About a third should do for a man your size.
Something to make you more manageable.
Forget it.
Drink it,Mr. Dover,
or I'll kill you right here in my kitchen
and bring your daughter in here
and have her scrub your brains off the floor...
Where is she?
Drink.
Just let me see her.
You want to see her? Yes!
That's your ticket to your daughter right there.
A little more,Mr. Dover.
Little more.
Good,isn't it?
That's my darlin' husband's recipe.
Now go on out back.
Let me see her.
Take it out of your pocket.
Put it in the sink.
Put it in the disposal.
Put your car keys on the table.
That's right.
Over to the trans am over there.
The car over there.
Come on,move it. Get over there.
The look on your face.
My husband used to have the very same look...
Till we took Alex.
He was the first kid we ever took.
His name was Jimmy.
Or Barry.
Can't remember. Doubt he can,either.
So many names.
Forgot all about Bobby Taylor
till I read about him in the paper.
Get in the driver's seat.
Open the door and get in the car.
Making children disappear is the war we wage with God.
Makes people lose their faith.
Turns them into demons like you.
Had to slow down since my husband disappeared.
But I do what I can.
Start the car.
Keep tryin'.
Back up. Slowly.
Come on. Back up.
Come on.
Stop.
Turn it off.
Turn it off!
Get out.
Think you should know.
Alex never laid a hand on those girls.
Just wanted to take 'em for a ride in the camper.
I was the one who decided they should stay.
Take a look.
Maybe your daughter's under there.
You never know.
Anna.
Anna!
Anna?
Anna. Anna!
Anna!
Anna?!
I had the girls down there
when the police came pokin' around.
Should have left 'em down there.
I was so lonely without Alex.
Now get in there.
What?
Get in.
You want me to get in there,you're gonna have to shoot me.
I'm not gonna get in there just 'cause you asked.
Go on. Get in there.
That's right. That's right.
Make yourself a tourniquet.
Just might last 24 hours.
I'd love for you to still be alive
when I dump your daughter's body down there.
Wait! No,wait,wait,wait!
Wait!
No.
Hey.
I need you to go over to Holly Jones.
She needs to be notified.
No. I need to find Dover.
Come on. You're done with Dover,okay? Please?
You want me to go to Holly Jones?
I want you to go to holly Jones' and notify her,please.
Oh,God.
Almighty God...
Protect my girl.
Mrs. Jones?
Show me your hands right now.
Don't move and show me your fuckin' hands right now.
Stop! Right now!
Show me your fuckin' hands.
Do not move and show me your hands.
Make sure they cremate me.
I sure as hell don't want to be buried in some box.
Both hands! Right now!
Right now!
Fuck!
Anna.
Oh,my God.
Oh,God.
Anna.
Oh,shit.
Come on. Come on. Anna. Anna. Come on.
Stay with me,Anna.Anna,stay with me,huh?
Stay with me,Anna!
Stay with me,Anna! It's all right!
It's all right! Come on!
Go,move,move,move,move!
Don't die,don't die.
It's okay,it's okay.
Honey. You're okay.
Hey.
Hey! Help!
Help! Help!
Help!
Uh,detective Loki?
I hope we're not intruding.
No.
She's doing real good.
She's gonna be up and around in a few days,
aren't you,buddy?
She just wanted to come and say thank you and hi to her hero.
Hello.
Uh,would you mind giving me a minute?
Yeah. Thank you.
Say Goodbye,joy. Bye.
I'll be out in a minute.All right?
Say goodbye,Anna.
She found her whistle?
Uh,no.
She keeps insisting that Joy helped her find it
on Thanksgiving before they were taken.
But I think she's just confused.
I got her a new one.
He hasn't contacted me.
I know you don't...
I know you probably don't believe that,but he hasn't.
I-I believe you.
Do you think you're gonna find him?
Yeah.
And he'll go to jail.
Probably.
Anyway...
Thank you for everything.
Oh,God.
I miss him.
He... He did what he had to do to find Anna,
and I thank God for that.
He's a good man.
Bye.
That's it.Let's pack it up.
You all done for the night?
Yeah,the ground's frozen solid.
It's gonna take weeks to excavate the entire property.
Just found some dead snakes and shit.
Pray for the best,prepare for the worst,yeah?
Night.
Shut her down.
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：1610169789