更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
If the great Christmas icicle continues to melt at this rate,
Christmas magic stored in the ice crystal will vanish.
These days, children and their pups just don't believe like they used to.
Their focus is on themselves, instead of on giving to others less fortunate.
If they don't understand the true meaning of Christmas,
the icicle has no chance.
I'm afraid that's something we just can't teach.
Soon it will be Puppy Paws' responsibility
to show the next generation the importance of Christmas spirit.
Now, Dasher! Now, Dancer! Now, Prancer and Vixen!
On, Comet! On, Cupid! On, Donner and Blitzen!
That was fun. Let's do it again.
I'm afraid we're all too tired now, Puppy Paws.
Comet, please?
Look, we have a lot of work to do today.
- Like what? - Well, for one thing,
we have to get ready for Christmas Eve.
You know, the most important night of the year?
Fine. I'll go find some fun on my own.
That pup sure has a lot to learn
before he takes the reins and is responsible for Christmas.
Perfect.
Three trucks done!
- Here comes some more toys. - I got another load.
It's all packed and ready to go!
All right! This'll be good.
- It's going fast. - Grab those...
Stop this! Stop...
- Oh, no. - What's going on? It's chaos!
Come on.
Grab that...
This is getting out of control.
Look out!
- I checked it a couple minutes ago. - What do you mean?
Puppy Paws!
Son, I am very disappointed in you.
You disrupted the workshop and wasted a whole day of work.
The elves are very upset. They're now another day behind schedule.
You know how hard they work getting ready.
I didn't realize it would cause such havoc.
I just wanted to have some fun.
Maybe you should be thinking about how important Christmas is
to children and puppies all around the world.
It's our responsibility to deliver good puppies the gift
they've wished for the entire year.
You mean it's your responsibility.
I just want to be an ordinary puppy.
You're grounded until further notice.
That means no playing fetch with the elves
and no flying with the reindeer.
I wish Christmas would just go away.
Puppy Paws! What a horrible thing to say!
Do you think I was too strict with him?
Maybe just a smidgen, but...
...I'm sure he'll get over it.
Puppy Paws has to understand,
he's the future of Christmas.
You pups want to sing along?
Yo, I don't sing. I rap.
Why do we even have to come here?
It's a Christmas tradition.
I've been watching the lighting of the tree since I was a pup like you Buddies.
You're quiet this evening, Budderball.
I hadn't even heard your stomach grumble.
Anything the matter?
I'm still in the doghouse for eating the Thanksgiving turkey.
Are you worried you might be on Santa Paws' naughty list?
Santa Paws is just Dad dressed up in a red and white suit.
That's all, dawg. They just use it so we behave all year.
Is that right, B-Dawg?
Let's look at the evidence, Deputy Sniffer.
If the jolly dude came down the chimney, wouldn't there be a lot of soot?
I'm not really buying the whole ''Santa Paws'' thing, either,
but I sure do love all the presents.
Your material desires are those of the wanting mind.
Enough is never enough.
Buddha's right, Buddies.
Getting material things isn't what Christmas is all about.
Christmas spirit is about the unselfish spreading of love and kindness.
There are plenty of lonely puppies
without families or children to love them.
Hello, everybody. Thank you for coming down to the annual lighting
of the Fernfield Christmas tree.
Not quite the turnout we expected.
Three...
...two... one!
Buddies, it's Mr. Cruge, the dog catcher.
It's probably just a faulty bulb.
Oh, my!
Thank you, Lord, for this blessing. Amen.
Thought you could run wild in the streets?
Not on my watch you don't.
I don't wanna be responsible for Christmas.
I just wanna be an ordinary puppy.
I wish Christmas would just disappear.
The naughty book gets thicker every year.
We're just on the pups.
If Puppy Paws doesn't understand the true meaning of Christmas,
how can we expect other puppies to?
''Bubba. Offense: destruction of property.
Chewing shoes, 1 7 cases.''
Oh, my. That is naughty, all right.
''Budderball. Offense: gluttony.
Eating the Thanksgiving turkey.''
Budderball!
Big appetite for a pup.
I have the feeling little Budderball's tummy always leads to naughtiness.
Santa Paws, Claus, we got the mail truck ready for a systems check.
Great, Eli. We could use a break from this.
I haven't even checked the list twice and we're already tired.
Budderball. One of the five Air Buddies.
He has three brothers,
Mudbud, B-Dawg, Buddha, and a little sis, Rosebud.
They live in Fernfield, Washington.
Each with their own families.
Regular, ordinary, fun-loving pups.
They sound perfect!
The sooner you get going, the better. We've got a lot of pickups scheduled.
Over 1 ,000 cities and towns.
Eli, sir, she's all yours.
Confirming. The route is programmed.
OK, let's run the diagnostic tests. New Delhi.
I am liking this very, very much.
Florence.
All seems in the working order, Santy Claus.
Give me the clearance, I'm ready to roll.
That's an all-clear from the North Pole.
Well, here I go.
Time to hitch a ride to Fernfield.
Good work, team. We're right on schedule.
Jingle all the way, Eli.
Holding up all right? Good, good...
Good work.
Oh, no!
I don't like the look of this one bit.
It's happening fast.
The magic of Christmas is fading away, right before our eyes.
''Fernfield: Where everything is possible.''
My kind of place.
Holy Christmas spirit.
We're almost out of power.
It looks to me like we've tapped into all the additional power we've got.
Oh, my. Another leak.
I hate to even say it, but I think the North Pole is starting to melt.
Any thoughts, Eddy?
Well, sir, spirit is down,
but there seems to be something else going on.
The icicle is melting faster than we ever thought possible.
Has anyone seen Puppy Paws?
He seems to be missing.
My guess would be the stables.
You know how he loves to play tricks on Donner and Blitzen.
Come on, you're next.
What do you want?
I was hoping you could deliver this note to the real Santa for me?
The real Santa?
I know that the real Santa
is busy at the North Pole making gifts and you're just one of his helpers.
If you could deliver this note to him, I would really appreciate it.
Yeah, I'll see what I can do.
OK. Time's up.
There's other boys and girls that need to see Hank.
I mean, Santa.
Merry Christmas, sir. Thank you. And God bless.
Merry Christmas to you, too.
What do you want?
They couldn't have found me already.
I did it! Holy...
Say ''cheese,'' pipsqueak.
Man, this is itchy.
An imposter.
What are you doing?!
What'll it be?
- What in the heck are you doing? - I'm trying to catch that dog!
Comet, what's wrong?
Santa Claus, Santa Paws, I wouldn't come in here if I were you.
All of us reindeer, we've been hit with some sort of flu bug.
Could be contagious.
Are you gonna be OK?
I don't know, Santa.
Cupid isn't feeling the love and Dancer isn't doing much dancing.
We all feel really weak.
It's a lack of energy from the icicle.
It's affecting us all.
Is there anything we can help with?
We're looking for Puppy Paws.
- Have you seen him? - Come to think of it, no.
He hasn't been asking us for rides...
Everything OK?
People sure aren't very jolly in Fernfield.
I think it's time to call it a night.
- Thanks again, Mrs. Davis. - Take care.
I guess I'll have to find Budderball in the morning.
Merry Christmas!
Hey, look, everybody, Eli's back.
Hey, what happened? You're back early.
For a minute there I thought I might have to push.
- What's wrong with the truck? - Almost ran out of power.
Where's all the mail, sir?
That's all there was.
Sweet mama! Gingerbread cookies!
Budderball? Is it really you?
I've been looking for you all over town.
That polar bear cub sure looks realistic.
His mouth even moves.
Come on, big fella!
Budderball! Wait!
Good boy.
Oh, my!
All right. I've just got...
OK... Just a little knot here.
What in tarnation?
Excuse me?
Excuse me!
Oh, hello there, young'un.
Deputy Sniffer at your service.
I'm looking for a pup I just saw.
But then he disappeared. His name is Budderball.
Oh, I've known that pup his whole life.
So you know where he lives?
Budderball lives at Livingston Manor.
Now to get there you want to go left down Main Street,
then take a right at the candy store and keep going.
It's on the outskirts of town. You can't miss it.
Thanks, Deputy.
OK, heads up, I'm sending it down.
Thanks, Budderball.
Got it.
This must be it.
I think we got some in the van.
Yeah, there's a box right there. I'll grab 'em.
Here you go!
I'll send them up.
- A bit heavy. - OK, I got it.
OK. You sure?
Well, I think we
are just about done.
I think we should lower the candy canes a little.
They're kinda hard to... see.
Oh, that's heavy.
Off we go.
Come on, Budderball.
Oh, sweet mama.
I'm not sure how Dad does this,
but here goes nothing.
Hey! Do you mind getting off me?
It's you, right? Budderball?
I finally found you!
Who do you think you are rolling out of my chimney and busting my candy cane?
I'm Puppy Paws. Pleased to meet you.
- Where do you come from? - The North Pole.
Oh, yeah. I bet you belong to Santa Claus.
Well, technically, yes.
But Santa Paws is my pa.
Yeah, right. You expect me to believe that your dad is Santa Paws?
Why wouldn't you?
Who put you up to this?
No one. I was checking the naughty list and you looked like fun.
What'd you say? I'm on the naughty list?!
It was just a little turkey!
Don't worry, you can get off the naughty list and onto the nice list
by doing good deeds for others.
- Like? - Well...
Like teaching me how to be an ordinary pup.
OK, well, I'll show you what I like to do.
This is the most magical room in the house.
What kind of toys do you make here?
They don't make toys, they make food.
The most delicious food around.
Like roast beef sandwiches, chicken wings, chili dogs...
Is he one of your elves?
You're a real joker, aren't you? That's the chef.
- What's he doing? - Making cookies.
But we can't eat them, they're for Christmas.
Hey, how'd you get up there?
Bad idea.
- Wow! - What?
Those cookies. They just changed. How did you do that?
It's no biggie. Christmas magic is stored in here.
So I can do stuff like my dad.
But I can't quite control it.
Hey, you want a cookie?
Don't you remember? I'm trying to get back on the nice list.
Well, suit yourself.
Be good, Budderball, be good. Don't eat the cookies!
Oh, no!
My compliments to the chef.
I believe it's time for lunch, Budder...
...ball.
Oh, yeah, laugh it up.
Now I'm going to be late meeting my brothers and sis in the park!
How about you introduce me to them?
Once I get done with my timeout, I'd be happy to get you out of my fur!
Thanks! You're the best!
Is Budderball fashionably late again?
I hope the dude's not in trouble.
I'll meditate and send him some positive energy.
Who's the white, fluffy dude Budderball's with?
Puppy Paws, these are the Buddies.
The mucky pup is Mudbud.
The blinged-out one is B-Dawg.
Buddha looks like he's sleeping,
but he calls it meditation.
And Rosebud is our little sis.
But don't let the pink bow fool you.
She's feistier than she looks.
And this is Puppy Paws.
He claims to be Santa Paws' son from the North Pole.
Yo, you straight up trippin'?
We ain't fallin' for that, dawg.
I'm sorry about my brother.
We've just grown a little skeptical about Christmas.
You're not alone. No one believes in Christmas spirit anymore.
That's why I'm here. To learn how to be an ordinary pup.
Well, you found the right dog to school you.
Come on, I'll show you my crib.
All right, dawg, I'm gonna show you how to kick it like me.
- I like kickin' it. - Yeah, you know, bust some moves.
Yeah, bust some moves.
Watch and learn, cuz.
I call this the four paw pop,
into the boogaloo jaw drop,
to the tail rotation
for the B-Dawg Nation.
Yeah. Way to break those moves.
Yeah, I know. I'm the best.
Let's see you give it a shot, playa.
OK, I'll give it a whirl, playa.
I call this the Prancer hop 'n bop,
to the spinning toy top,
to the elf hustle 'n bustle,
to the shiny toy train.
Did I bust some moves?
You busted something, all right.
- Hey, dudes. - Yo, dawg,
it is your turn to hang with Santa Junior.
- No problemo, dude. - We'll see about that, dawg.
Why is he in such a huff?
I don't know, dawg. He be trippin', for shizzle.
Wowzers, dude. You don't have to talk like B-Dawg.
Isn't that how ordinary puppies talk?
Dude, only B-Dawg talks like that.
Oh. So, what are you doing... dude?
Just chillaxing with a mud bath, dude.
Dude, can I give it a roll?
Now what are we gonna do, dude?
Let me show you my sweet pad, dude.
This is the cleanest room in the house.
Strictly off limits.
Dude! Is it normal for mud to feel itchy?
No, dude! Don't do it!
How'd you do that, dude?
I don't know. It just happens, dude.
Dude...
Dudette, where are you?
What's up? Alice is about to give me a new Christmas outfit.
Oh, no. What happened to you?
Someone played a dirty trick on me.
You've gotta hang with Puppy Paws now.
I have to wear this clean coat as punishment.
Later, dudenator.
So, what sweet stuff are we going to do, dudette?
Oh, brother.
Awesome, and I'll call you ''sis.''
I've never had a sis before.
Or a brother. This is gonna be epic!
Rosebud! Where are you?
Like, wait here. I'll be back with a whole new Christmas look.
Wow! Like, that should be fun.
Hey, Rosebud.
You're gonna love this, Rosebud.
So, what do you think?
You're right. What was I thinking?
Accessories! Hang on. I'll be right back.
What's taking so long?
You startled me.
- That's your new Christmas look? - You don't like it?
I think it's totally fetch.
I like it, but it's not very Christmassy.
What could be more Christmassy than this?
Excuse me!
Rosebud sent me.
She was, like, totally freaking out about her Christmas makeover.
Well, it's time for meditation.
This Buddha statue came from the Ming Dynasty,
over 600 years old.
Very sacred.
So, like, how do we do this ''meditate'' stuff?
We simply sit and breathe.
A clear mind is developed through meditation.
My Buddha statue!
It's a snowman, very Zen in the North Pole.
Hello?
Anyone here?
Yes?
Hi.
My son would like a puppy for Christmas.
Well, then, you've come to the right place.
Quiet!
- Where are the puppies? - They're hiding.
They'll come out if they know what's good for them.
This is the one.
She's perfect. I'll take her.
That's $300.
I thought the puppies were free for adoption. We'll give her a loving home.
- Take good care of her. - You're wasting your breath.
That doesn't matter to me. I want the $300.
It's for my son for Christmas. He's sick.
A puppy might be just what he needs to brighten his spirits.
I have $50.
No money, no mutt.
If you can find it in your heart...
Dudes, where's Buddha?
Buddha's always on time,
whereas I'm only on time at dinnertime.
I sent Puppy Paws over to Buddha's.
I thought he might be the only one with the patience to handle him.
That ''being one with the universe'' stuff...
So powerful.
And being present, not just giving presents, is so Zen.
- So, how'd it go? - I lost it.
What's the ''it,'' Zen Master?
My temper! That's the ''it'' I lost, OK?
Hey, I know something that ordinary puppies always do.
- Play Hide-and-Go-Seek. - Hide-and-Go-Seek? What's that?
You close your eyes and count down from 1 2 while we hide.
When you finish counting, you yell really loud,
''Ready or not, here I come!''
And you start looking for us, got it?
Yo, BFFing dudes,
that sounds like mad, gnarly fun for shizzle! Namaste.
Oh, brother.
Twelve drummers drumming, eleven pipers piping...
Everyone go in separate directions and meet behind the stump.
Eight maids a-milking, seven swans a-swimming.
Six geese a-laying, five golden rings.
Two turtle doves,
and a partridge in a pear tree.
That's twelve!
Here I come!
I called you to this stump meeting to discuss Puppy Paws
and what we are going to do with him.
This game isn't so hard.
Puppy Paws actually thinks that I'm buying that his pop is Santa.
I'm not even shopping, yo.
That dude got me in some serious doo-doo.
I had the humiliation of wearing a clean coat for the entire day.
If he's Santa Paws' son,
why'd he get me in more trouble, rather than help me get off the naughty list?
And you should have seen what he did to me. It was a fashion disaster.
But I was just trying to be like them.
Wait a second, Buddies. We all have our own karma.
Puppy Paws is not responsible for me losing my center.
To find faults in him,
we're really just finding faults in ourselves.
The Zen dude is correctamundo.
He was only trying to fit in.
I was only jealous 'cause the dawg schooled me in the hip-hop battle.
I guess I ate myself onto the naughty list.
It's my responsibility to get myself off, not Puppy Paws'.
We should be ashamed of ourselves.
Poor Puppy Paws doesn't have any brothers or sisters.
I couldn't imagine not having you guys.
Let's embrace Puppy Paws with compassion.
Where did the dude go?
The Christmas icicle is almost gone.
I wouldn't believe it if I didn't see it with my own eyes.
When Puppy Paws left, the icicle started melting even faster.
If we don't find Puppy Paws, Christmas as we know it will be lost forever.
All right. Come on. Come on.
Sniff, sniff. All right, let's go.
Quiet!
All right.
You won't be needing this anymore.
In you go.
''Property of the North Pole''?
Very, very funny.
What is this place?
The pound is where they put us dogs that no one cares about.
No one cares about you?
- What's your name? - They call me Tiny,
because I'm the smallest of all the puppies.
I'm Puppy Paws. What's with that guy?
Did he get coal in his stocking or something?
He lost his Christmas spirit.
No one cares about Christmas anymore.
We do.
The hope for a Christmas miracle is all we have.
Good job. Now make a wish and turn it on.
I wish that Santa would get my letter.
Here we go.
I had no idea.
Thank you, Tiny. Thank you.
- Magicometer. - Magicometer.
Well, did you find any way of boosting the power?
The boys have modified the E.L.F. compressor with magicometers
and got a little more power with the spiriters.
We have great news!
I think we know where Puppy Paws is.
Fernfield, Washington.
In search of a pup named Budderball.
You know how he was saying he wanted to be an ordinary pup?
Santa Claus? Santa Paws? You OK?
Please, bring back Puppy Paws as fast as you can.
Without him I'm afraid Christmas may be gone forever.
Yes, sir! We'll be back quicker than you can say ''Candy Cane Lane.''
Well, at least we made it.
I have no idea how we're going to get back. The tank is out of magic.
All right. I'll try and find Puppy Paws.
And I'll see what I can do about the truck so we can get home.
- Where's Budderball? - That dawg ain't ever on time.
Being fashionably late is one thing,
but this is way out of style.
Dude, am I hallucinating or is Budderball running with an elf?
It's an elf, all right.
Where does he find these dawgs? The looney bin?
Hi, guys. Sorry I'm late.
I had another surprise visitor from way up north.
This is Eddy. He claims to be Santa Paws' head elf.
We need your help. Christmas is in great danger.
And we need to get Puppy Paws back to the North Pole.
Well, I for one totally love your shoes,
and will do anything to help.
Your presence indicates that our disbelief may have been unfounded.
But, regardless, there is one obstacle.
Puppy Paws has disappeared.
Quick, hide! It's Cruge!
Come on, let's go!
- Coming through! - Hurry up.
Oh, no! Do you think Puppy Paws might be in the pound?
This way, dawgs!
All right...
No magic in the tank, no way to get home.
It's officially the end of Christmas spirit.
- Next. - Have a nice day.
- Hello. - That's great.
There it is. There you go.
- Look at that. Keep moving. - Thank you.
If I had enough magic, even just a little...
Hey!
Bub, I'm all for slacking off,
but I've been busting my hump over here and you've been standing over here...
- ...hiding out, so... - I'm not hiding out.
I'm trying to see if I can make this sleigh fly
so we can get Puppy Paws back to the North Pole and save Christmas.
Puppy Paws! Of course! Yes!
I have an idea!
Let's sprinkle a little fairy dust over the reindeer
to come alive and they can fly you back to Santy Claus.
Do you have some?
No. No...
If you don't get back to work right now, I'm gonna tell the big boss.
This is killing me.
- You want your uniform revoked? - Of course not.
All right, follow me.
I don't think anyone's home.
Maybe we should come back another time, dawgs?
Dudes, look!
There's a hole in the back!
Yo, dawgs, hold up!
OK, you know the plan. Budderball, you're on lookout.
Bark twice if Mr. Cruge returns.
Mudbud and B-Dawg, you find the key.
Buddha, Eddy and I will find Puppy Paws.
- Got it? - Go! Quickly!
- Come on, let's go! - Hurry.
- Puppy Paws? - Puppy Paws!
Eddy! Is that you?
Over here, last cage.
Eddy, I'm so happy to see you.
I'm so sorry I messed everything up.
From now on, I promise to be good for goodness sake.
We're gonna need you to be great for greatness sake.
The Christmas icicle has all but melted now.
Santa Claus and Santa Paws need you back.
Your dad has grown very weak.
Your dad is Santa Paws?
There isn't going to be a Christmas?
I won't let that happen, Tiny.
You pups taught me the true meaning of Christmas spirit.
It's not just about presents.
In fact, it's not about presents at all.
It's about things you can't wrap in a box or tie with a bow.
First, find my collar so we can get out of here.
I'll retrieve it.
- The key is not in here. - It's not over here, dawg.
We've gotta find Puppy Paws' collar.
There's too many, dawg. Which one is it?
I remember! It looks like a candy cane.
There it is!
It's about time.
Hurry!
Wow! I can't thank you guys enough.
That's what friends do, help each other out of a jam.
Budderball, if you're here, then who's on the lookout?
They're coming to me now!
You guys go. I'll take care of him.
And we will help.
You would be willing to do that for Christmas?
It's us or saving Christmas, right?
This job just gets easier and easier.
Get back in your cage.
Get out of here! Quickly! Eli's waiting for you in front of town hall.
You guys can do it. I know you can.
You're our Christmas miracle.
We won't let you down, Tiny.
Come on, let's go!
Follow me.
Watch out! Coming through!
Move over, guys!
Go away! Go away!
Go away. Go away!
I'm ticklish!
Eli, wake up!
Puppy Paws!
We've got to get back to the North Pole right away!
- How'd you get here? - The mail truck.
But it doesn't have enough power to get us back.
I've been trying to figure out how to get this sleigh to work, but...
Puppy Paws, your collar!
It might have enough magic to make this thing fly.
It's lighter than the truck and it needs a lot less power.
But we still need reindeer.
There are no reindeer in Fernfield other than those plastic ones there.
Wait a sec! We know how to pull a sleigh.
Let me get this straight, Elf Dude.
All we have to do is pull the sleigh
and Puppy Paws' magic collar will make it fly?
That is correct.
- Will you guys do it? - B-Dawg is all about the heroics.
Yo, P-Squared, you need help saving Christmas,
we're your Buddies.
Let's do it!
For that little stunt, there'll be no dinner.
I'll bet you haven't laughed like that in a long time.
Who said that?
We know all about you at the North Pole.
You didn't get a puppy when you were a boy,
and it made you hate Christmas.
But Santa knew that your mother was very allergic to dogs,
that it wasn't right for your family.
I know a lot of things about you, Stan Cruge.
Are you talking to me?
I'm from the North Pole where we can communicate with all creatures.
It's part of the Christmas magic.
And you know the best way to heal your broken heart
is to give to those in need.
What has gotten into me?
Christmas, sir. Christmas has gotten into you.
It's time to let Christmas back into your heart.
Well, I would love to stay for eggnog, but I have to get back to the North Pole
and help save Christmas.
Dawgs, it just struck me that we ain't playin' no more.
This Santa stuff is for real, yo.
OK, you're all set.
We only have one shot at this,
so it's important you believe you can fly without a shadow of a doubt.
- Ready, Buddies? - That's ''reindogs'' to you, bro.
Next stop, the North Pole.
Did you see that?!
They're flying.
I most certainly did.
And, yes, they are flying.
- This is so fly! I'm flying! - But I'm afraid of heights!
Budderball, don't look down.
Yo, dawgs, there's the dog pound.
Let's do a flyby.
Guys, wait. Does anyone actually know how to get to the North Pole?
Just follow the North Star.
The best way to heal your broken heart
is to give to those in need.
Did you feel that?
Somewhere, somehow,
somebody just decided they believed in Christmas after all.
It only takes one person to change the lives of many.
Santa Claus, I do believe the Christmas spirit has begun its turnaround.
You see, the magic is stored all year round in the great Christmas icicle
and is released at Christmas.
If people don't believe in Christmas,
then there isn't enough magic for us to make the toys or fly the sleigh.
So, if there isn't enough Christmas spirit,
then the icicle that stores the magic will melt and...
...Christmas will be gone forever?
Precisely.
Children will never get to experience the joy of Santa,
or learn about the spirit of Christmas.
To children, you are Santa's elf.
That's why your job as an elf representative is so important.
You don't actually work for us directly,
but you do work to spread Christmas spirit.
And if you don't believe, neither will the children.
Wow.
Thanks, Eli.
See, I had no idea my job was so darn important.
Here comes my boss.
That little dog is your boss?
Eddy, this is Clark.
- He's an official elf representative. - Hey.
Eli, we'd better get back to the North Pole, lickety-split.
Santa's gonna need all the help he can get.
He can talk?
We don't have enough magic to power the truck.
We will soon. Eli, things are turning around.
What happened at the pound?
Christmas. That's what happened.
- Remember your promise, Clark. - I will.
Merry Christmas.
There it is, Buddies. The North Pole.
We can land right by Santa's house.
Yo, don't worry, P-Squared.
You are in good paws with the B-Dawg.
I guess I overshot the landing a little.
You could say that again.
Dad!
Son!
I'm so sorry for not believing.
I just didn't understand how important Christmas was.
And I'm sorry I was so hard on you.
I should have trusted you would come to that realization yourself.
Well, it took the help of a few friends.
Buddies! Nice to see you again.
How've you been behaving, Budderball?
Any more turkey infractions?
No, Mr. Paws. I haven't even sneaked a cookie.
Well, big fella, we'll have to see about getting you off Santa's naughty list
and back onto the nice list.
That would make my Christmas special, sir.
I can vouch for all the good karma Budderball has created
since the infraction in question.
Your wisdom is appreciated, Buddha. Namaste.
We are totally stoked to help, Santa Dude.
Bro, that would be super rad.
I'll make sure we all do everything we can to make Christmas happen.
Rosebud, your leadership skills are exemplary.
If memory serves, you're near the very top of Santa's nice list.
Thank you all for coming. We're very behind here at Santa's workshop,
and it's going to take all the help we can get to make Christmas happen.
Yo, I gotta give props to those elves.
They know how to get it done.
We are back in business!
Is that Santa Claus?
Yes, that's Santa himself!
Puppy Paws! It's so great to see you!
What a glorious day!
And you're right on time!
The great Christmas icicle is back!
Santa, my friends the Buddies have come to help!
Welcome, Buddies!
As you can see, there's still lots of toys to be made for children and puppies
all over the world.
We're gonna need all hands and paws on deck!
We're back.
That's quite a haul you've got there.
From the looks of this load, I'd say Christmas spirit is on the rise.
All right, peopIe, let's get these letters opened on the double.
Christmas Eve's a-comin'.
Hey, Budderball, nice haul.
Hey!
B-Dawg...
- Thanks, Mr. Cruge. - Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas!
Here it comes... Yeah! There it is!
We did it!
All right, Santa, we're ready for a test flight.
OK, everyone, let's give this our best effort.
Let's cross all our fingers and paws...
Comet, Donner, Blitzen! Are you OK?
Sorry, Santa Claus.
We still don't seem to have enough strength to even fly the empty sleigh.
The Christmas icicle is growing, but not fast enough.
The Buddies and I flew the small sleigh to the North Pole
with the little magic left in my crystal.
Maybe we can fly Santa's sleigh?
- What's happening? - That's what happens to the leader.
It's to light the way for the rest of us.
I think we're going to call you Ru-Dawg.
Now that's tight. My nose shines just like my bling.
Prepare for departure.
Good luck, son. Stay focused.
Tonight is the most important night of the year.
All good children and puppies are counting on you.
No matter what happens tonight, I want to thank you, Buddies.
You're the best friends I've ever had.
We should thank you. We had stopped believing in Christmas until we met you.
Enough of this Kumbaya stuff.
I'm in it to win it!
All right, Buddies, it's up to us to save Christmas!
- Bye! - Goodbye!
Merry Christmas.
Santa, I know it's late to be making Christmas wishes...
And I know I've been playing like I don't believe in Santa Claus...
I don't need any presents.
The only thing I want for Christmas...
...is for the Buddies to be safe at home. Amen.
''Dear Santa,
I know this is a lot to ask,
but this year if you could find a puppy
that really needs a home for Christmas,
it would change our lives.
I would take really good care of him.
And he would take good care of us.
I know we would be the best of friends
and I think my parents will worry less about me
if they knew I had someone to watch out for me.
We live in a small brown house at the end of Griffith Road.
Merry Christmas.
Love, Mikey.''
I think you're gonna make that boy very happy.
I'll get it.
Mom, Dad, look what Santa brought me!
First stop: London, England.
OK, Dad said the magic will make my paws stick to the side of the chimney.
Wish me luck!
Paris, France.
Love your hat. Merry Christmas.
Sydney, Australia, mate.
Yo, nice bling, dawg.
Tokyo, Japan.
This place has great feng shui.
Very Zen.
The island of Jamaica.
Hey, dude, gnarly dreads.
- Mexico City. - Mexico.
Oh, sweet mama. Bean burritos!
Fernfield, Washington.
Come on, Buddies! I need all your help on this one.
Puppy Paws? Buddies? Is that you?
- Tiny? - Yeah, it's us, Tiny.
What are you doing here?
My Christmas wish came true.
Mr. Cruge brought me to Mikey, my boy.
I'm so happy for you, Tiny.
This is the greatest Christmas ever.
Well, there's no reason why we can't make it more special.
Wow! Thank you, Puppy Paws.
No, Tiny, thank you.
You taught us all how important it is to believe in the Christmas spirit.
None of this would have been possible if it wasn't for you.
Hi, Tiny.
The icicle is back to full strength.
They've done it, Paws. They've saved Christmas!
Let's round up the reindeer and go get Puppy Paws.
That's it, Buddies. That was our last delivery.
We did it!
Dude? How are you gonna get home with no one to fly your sleigh?
I think I've got a ride.
Whoa, Cupid! Whoa, Donner!
Whoa, Blitzen!
Great work, pups! The North Pole is back in business!
You did it, son. You saved Christmas.
I couldn't have done it without the Buddies.
Indeed. Your teamwork tonight was most certainly top of the nice list material.
Which is why, Buddies,
we at the North Pole have decided to present to you
your very own,
genuine Santa hats.
Merry Christmas, Buddies.
And there's one more thing.
You earned this, son.
You're one of us now, young pup.
And with you on our team, I think it's pretty safe to say
that Christmas is going to be in very good hands for a long time to come.
I'm proud of you.
Now say your goodbyes, Puppy Paws.
We've got to keep the spirit of Christmas alive all year long.
Only 364 days 'til next Christmas!
I'm really gonna miss you guys.
Puppy Paws, you know how you wanted to be an ordinary pup?
- Yeah? - That's impossible.
You're too extraordinary to be ordinary.
I feel the same way about you, Buddies.
Thank you for making us true believers.
And for taking us on a way cool adventure.
Best time ever! All you can eat cookies and milk?
Sign me up!
Yo, Puppy Paws, you are now officially part of the B-Dawg Nation.
You now have four bros and one sis.
Maybe you Buddies can lend a paw next year
as official Santa's Helpers.
What do you say?
- Yeah! - Yeah!
Fo' shizzle!
Now, Buddies, you'd better get home to your kids.
You still have some Christmas wishes to fulfill,
and we've got to get back to the North Pole.
Let's go, Paws!
- Merry Christmas, everybody. - Merry Christmas!
On, Comet! On, Cupid!
On, Donner! On, Blitzen!
Now, Dasher! Now, Dancer! Now, Prancer and Vixen!
Merry Christmas!
Budderball!
I've missed you so much!
Hello?
Sorry to disturb you, but we were wondering if you'd join us for dinner.
I wouldn't want to impose.
Besides, I've got a lot of work to do here.
But it's Christmas, sir.
I'll go grab my coat.
I'm starving.
Stan, thank you. It's great to have you here.
Thank you for spending Christmas with us.
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：1610169789