更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
Christian just got back from vegas.
Yeah. It was just for the weekend. Private thing.
He knows everyone.
"knows."who "knows" anyone these days?
More like you hang out when you're in vegas.
So where did you guys stay in vegas?
I like the four seasons,the mandalay.
I like the end of the strip
So I can watch the planes fly into mccarran.
Well, it's good to finally meet you, man.
It's good to finally, you know,meet the man in person.
Yeah.
No problem.
And hey, I, um,
I really want to thank you for giving me that role.
I didn't give you that role.
Your girlfriend and the director did.
Yeah, but I heard I wasn't exactly gerald's first choice.
Ryan, come on.Don't say that.
No, he's right.You weren't.
But I went to him and told him that I'm paying for this movie,
So if he doesn't put my assistant's boyfriend in it,
Then I'm pullin' out, and that's when the panic sets in.
Panic. Panic set in?
I mean, it's just a low-budget slasher movie, christian.
I don't think people were panicked by you.
I think, you know, they could have found the money somehow,
But you made it easier, right?
Well, I have to admit, actually I was a little bit panicked.
Fact of the matter is I'm paying for this thing.
I heard from both of you that he was right for the part.
Yeah, indirectly I had something to do with you getting the role,
But if it wasn't for you helping out with the casting
And convincing me that this guy was,
You know, the best one for the role,
Then yeah, you probably wouldn't have the part.
And we thank you for the favor.
I think we all made the right decision.
You know, in the year that she worked for me,
She never mentioned having a boyfriend.
That is not true! I did, too!
You just weren't paying attention.
Really?
You guys look happy though.
Yeah, we are.Really happy.
Yeah, really are.
And you guys?
How long have you two been seeing each other?
I told you, baby, a year.Just like us.
Yeah.
I like to keep things loose,though.
I mean, I love her.
God, she's gorgeous.
But it's more fun to keep it a little complicated.
Complicated?
Christian, what are you doing?Where are you going with this?
Just being transparent, baby.
Being transparent about what?
You know that phone app, amore?
It's kinda like a girlfriend finder.
Yeah-- I mean no.
Wh-what does it do?
It makes... Things simple.
Certain... Assignations.
Just really easy.
You know, you get live video,make sure that people look
Exactly the way they do in their profiles.
Assignations for...
What is that?
It means meetings, dude.
Oh! Okay.Meetings for...
Hookups.
You know, girls, coupleswhatever, man.
Couples. Really?
Yes. Couples. Really.
I guess it's just, well,I don't know, I'm...
I'm just a more conventional guy.
Which is why you're with gina,and I'm with tara.
And you don't get jealous?
Jealous?
Yeah. If there are other people involved, like guys.
Well, it's mostly girls.And no, I do not get jealous
Watching my girl hook up with another chick.
Is this guy--is this guy for real?
Are you for real?Is he serious?
No, no, man.I mean, I--
Look, you're the man. I'm--
I-I was just trying to keep up with you.
Look, man, it's all about trust,all right?
I trust her,she trusts me.
Maybe if that trust wasn't there, I couldn't handle it.
But since it is,we have a good time.
Christian,I'm sitting right here.
What do you mean,you couldn't handle it?
Couldn't handle what?
The fact that I know you love me makes me trust you.
That makes everything we do more intense.
I'm sorry. Christian likes to shock people.
I get it.
Or at least he tries to.
This has nothing to do with shocking people.
I'm just sick of the old school shit about fucking propriety,
Etiquette and all that crap.
You've been around me for a year.
It's just fuckin' annoying.
It's like when you're at your family dinner on Sunday,
And everyone's just lying--christian, I want to go.
Can you get the fucking check?- I've ordered the check.
It's comin'. It's on its way.
Really?How long does it take?
Mm. It's coming though.Don't worry about it.
Oh, christian,before I forget,
I'm finalizing all the rooms for next month.
Are you definitely sure that you're not gonna come?
Yeah, there's no way I'm going to new mexico
And watch a bunch of kids get tortured and killed
By some pissed-off ghost in a warehouse.
Besides, I'll be busy making my own little movies.
What do you mean,you make your own movies?
Why in the hell did we have to go to that damn dinner?
Gina insisted.
Plus I was kinda interested to see who her new dude is.
What a fuckin' moron.Gina's a smart girl.
You'd think she could get with someone better
Than some loser actor.
What do you know about him?
Nothing.
I never even thought this movie would get made.
Well, gina worked very hard to make sure it happened.
I never even read the script.
I told gina if the mexicans or whoever came up with the cash
That I would just match it.
Why aren't you involved anymore, baby?
Why were you ever involved?
My father was on my ass about doing something with my life.
When I told him I was doing a movie, he got off my back.
Why are you wearing a robe?Guy's almost over here.
What's with all the dudes lately?
I don't know.It's a phase.
I like the idea of someone looking at something
They can't have.
Guy thing.Power and control.
But sometimes they do have me.
Just those two times.You didn't seem to mind.
I can't believe you at dinner tonight.
All that shit that you were telling them.
Is that why you're being so distant and bitchy, huh?
Why do you even fucking care?
It's just my assistant and some dumb actor.
I don't know. I guess I'd like to keep
Some parts of my life private.
Some aspects of my fucking life private.
Nobody has a private life anymore, tara.
Okay. What do you talk to your shrink about?
What do you talk about when you see dr. Campbell?
I don't tell dr. Campbell anything
That I wouldn't tell you.
That's a lie. That's not true.You just lied to me.
What would you like to know?
I want to know what you talk to dr. Campbell about.
I talk about my family.
I talk about my father trying to control my fucking life.
What the fuck do you think I talk to him about?
I don't know.Other girls.
I'm more serious about you than I have been with any other girl.
Hope you feel the same way about me.
Christian, there's a fucking guy coming over.
Really?
He's here.On his way down the driveway.
And I said I hope you feel the same way about me.
What was with you tonight, hmm?At dinner.
You were so tense. Hmm?
You let him in.
Hi. Reed, right?
Come on in.
I'm tara.
This is reed.
What's up, man?I'm christian.
Hey, man.
I see you've met tara.
Yeah.
You want something to drink?Shot of tequila.
Sure.
She's hot, right?
Way hotter than the pics you sent me.
Have a drink.
Relax.
Be comfy, man.
You wanna see something better than that.
How does he have all that money again?
Uh, trust fund.
His grandparents own like half of thousand oaks.
She's beautiful, tara, don't you think?
She's okay.
Don't go there, babe.I'm not doing that with you.
Doing what?
That whole "is that girl prettier than me?" thing you do.
I mean, why are you asking me that?
Look, you never even mentioned her.
You never told me about her for a year.
You didn't even mention her by name.
It was just"christian's girlfriend."
And you really didn't tell me what a douchebag that guy is.
Christ!
The reason I never mentioned her is that we never really hung out
Until she started helping me with the movie.
Why was she even helping you out?
She was bored.
She needed something to do besides shopping and fucking.
I mean, jon and I did most of the work,
But she helped out a little,I guess.
She did push you for the part.
I know it was probably a favor to me and christian,
But without her, I don't know what would've happened.
And then after casting,she just disappeared.
She just stopped coming by the production office.
I haven't seen her in like a month.
Hey.
Thanks.
I told you not to text me.
Why can't I text you?
Because he looks at my phone.
Why can't we meet at my place?
That's not gonna happen anymore.
So that's who you're with.Jesus.
Who'd you think you were--
So this is the guy that gave you the mercedes
And has a private jet and takes you to maui
And lives in the fucking mansion in malibu.
Ryan, please.
Last night killed me.
Why?
Because I finally saw you with him.
I know you better than he does.
You're not happy, tara.
Who said anything about happy?
He takes care of me,and he's in love with me.
It's serious.
Fuck it, ryan. Who's happy? Who's really happy?
Tell me.Gina.
Oh, of course.Gina is. Gina's happy.
Right, another reason why I couldn't stand being around her.
And-- you really do all that shit?
Couples? Random guys fucking you?
Jesus, tara.Ryan, stop.
This isn't going anywhere, okay?
So there's no point in having this discussion.
This has to end.We can't do this anymore.
Why are you asking me all this now?
Because I hadn't met him before,and I do care.
I think about you all the time.I can't help it.
And it makes me sick.
Can't get the things he makes you do out of my mind.
Ryan-- how do you think I felt
Watching him flashing pictures on his fucking phone
In front of me?
Last night made me sick.It made me fuckin' sick.
We can't do this anymore. This has gotta end.
What's gotta end, hmm?What?
Fucking me for the last four weeks?
You wanna end that?
Stop, ryan.
You ever tell him about me?Did you ever tell him
That you fell in love with me three years ago?
That you dumped me when you realized
I was the guy who might not make it,
That you essentially abandoned me
For a bunch of rich douchebags?
And now that asshole?- Ryan!
Who are you, ryan?You're still bartending.
You're still working for randall as a part-time assistant
At a fucking hotel.
This dumb little movie's not going to do anything for you.
Then why push me for it?- Oh, I don't know.
Because I care about you and knew how much you wanted it?
See, that's what\ I'm saying, baby.
I loved you so much, baby.We had so much fun together.
I never got over it when you left.
It killed me, and I tried so hard to let it go.
I tried so hard to let go of it.
And just when I think I'm gonna make it without you,
Gina suddenly started talking about her boss's girlfriend
But this girl she described didn't sound anything like you.
And then when I saw you at that audition...
I'm still so in love with you.
I don't fuckin' want to be,but I am.
I'm with him now.I'm with him.
What are you thinking?
You think you're gonna nail this guy, move in with him?
You think that creep's gonna marry you?
Ryan, don't go there.
It's hard for me, too, okay?It's hard for me, too.
That's why I tried helping you with the movie 'cause I care.
But you don't have to go and say things that are gonna hurt me.
Leave him. Get out of there.- And do what?
I don't know. Come back to me. We'll get a job.
We'll move in together.Get a job and do what, ryan?
Do you not remember how hard we were busting our asses?
Do you remember those days?
No, wait. Probably not because you're still living them.
I'm not going back to that, ryan.
I'm not going back to going on auditions
For jobs I'm never gonna get.
For bartending for 8 bucks a fucking hour.
I'm not gonna do it.
Do you remember how hard it was for us?
We were always fucking broke.We were busting our asses.
We couldn't even pay the fucking rent, ryan.
We couldn't pay the fucking rent.
That wasn't fun for me.I'm not going back to that.
And I need someone to take care of me.
And I needed someone to take care of me.
Hey.Hey.
Want me to get you something to drink?
Yes. Water.
Oh. How was your day?
It was fine.
Why don't you tell me about your day instead?
Okay. I got up, and I taught two yoga sessions this morning,
And then, oh, I went to that audition,
You know, the one that I told you about last time.
It was awful.
I definitely didn't get the job,but whatever.
Oh, my god, and then sheely called me,
And she started telling me all about this guy.
Goddamn it!What?
What's wrong?
Why the fuck did you do that? Why?
I just get into it with you, okay?
I'm sorry.I can't help it.
Look...
This... Is just this.
What does that mean?
I think you're hot.
I have fun.
But it's not changing my situation.
Okay, what's really going on here?
I think tara's seeing somebody.
Oh, jesus.
Christian, what does that even mean, okay?
Considering what you guys do.
I mean, do you even care?
Yes, I care.I care a lot.
What, you think she's cheating on you?
She was acting really, really strange at dinner last night.
I couldn't figure out why.
And then today she met some guy in the morning for coffee.
It's just, she-okay.
I mean, how do you know that she met someone?
What, did she tell you?No.
Okay, did--what, did the guy tell you?
No.
I've got some stuff I have to do today.
I think you better leave.
And I don't think you should come back here.
And why's that?
I can't handle this anymore.
Need some cash?
No. Christian,I don't need any cash.
Just-- just get out.
Come on, cynthia.
Get the fuck out.
Get the fuck out of here!
I'm really sorry that I didn't congratulate you
On starting your own pr company.
I mean, that must be really exciting.
Don't congratulate me just yet.It hasn't really taken off.
But you know,if it wasn't for christian
I'd never have been able to start it.
Yeah. Christian can be very helpful that way.
So dinner was fun last night.
I'm sorry if I, you know,seemed out of it and such.
I was just really preoccupied with things.
I know how christian gets.
And I have to say that ryan was a little shocked by him.
But he really liked him.He thought he was a great guy.
Oh, really? He did?
Yeah.Thought he was really cool.
You know, good guys are really hard to come by these days,
So you're a very lucky girl.\n- Tell me about it.
I can't believe I actually found someone so genuine.
He's a great guy.
Look, this was nice.
I just, um--
I'm sorry. I just wanted to know something.
What?
Why are you off the movie?
I mean, you're not coming to new mexico, right?
Oh, no. Yeah, I can't.No, I can't do that.
I'm just curious because I'm finalizing everything,
And, I don't know, you just seemed so into it a month ago.
Yeah, I mean...
Okay, tell me something.
Do you really like movies?
Yeah!
Really, really like movies?Of course!
When's the last time you went to see a movie in the theater?
A movie that you really thought meant something to you?
We went to the premiere last week--
Not premieres.Premieres don't really count.
I don't know, you know.
I guess maybe it's just not my thing anymore.
And plus I don't wanna be away from christian
For that long, I guess.
I get it.I totally get it.
I wouldn't want to be away from ryan for that long either.
No, it's just, at the time I was bored,
And I needed something to do.
And so that's why I got involved, and...
You know, now I'm looking for something else to do, so...
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm just--
I just have a lot of stuff going.
I'm so preoccupied and...
Look, I really have to go.
Wait! Stop.It's on me.
I can bill it to the production.
Seriously.Tara, it's okay.
Thank you.
Good seeing you, gina.Um, we'll talk soon.
Bye.
Bye, tara.
So I just had lunch with her
Nothing.
She said really nice things about you.
I mean, she seemed a little tense, but nothing.
She's not coming to new mexico because she said she'd miss you.
Really?
What did you think she was gonna say to me?
Nothing, babe.I just want the chance
For the two of you to reconnect.
I gotta go.I'll talk to you later.
Uh, okay.I'll be at the office.
All right, babe.See you there.
Oh, very good. Sexy.
Yeah. Keep it.Ha ha.
Pick up your chin.
Yes, very good. Smile.
Muscle up. Come on.Give me some attitude.
That's good. Profile.
Lower the chin.Very good.
He's pretty cute.
Ryan, on your mark.
Hey, ryan.That's your name, right?
Right. Get on the mark.
Good. Keep it right there.
Okay.
Yeah, a month. Yeah.
But zander said he would find someone to take my place
Just until I got back.
No, jeff, zander said it was cool if he gave me his shifts.
Jeff!
Jeff, come on, man.I just really need the cash.
If you're gonna make me beg,then fuck it.
I'll see you later. Bye.
I'm gonna head on up.All right.
Thanks, man.
We're also handling the leo event,
Listen, I gotta go.Ryan's here.
I know it isn't.
Yeah, I think we're all about to find out why.
Later.
Ah! Even on his day off,
It is always a pleasure to see my favorite assistant.
Thanks, randall, for the first and only compliment
I'm going to receive today.
Oh, I'm sorry.What's wrong?
I-I was just, uh--
I was just trying to get extra shifts at the bar,
But jeff's being a prick.
Well, what can I do to help?
Well, I was wondering if there was anything else
I could do around here.
You know, when I offered you this job, it was full-time.
I know, I know.
But I let you make it part-time because you wanted it that way.
Randall, I'm going to new mexico for a month.
They're barely paying me anything to do this movie.
I really need the cash.
Can I ask you something?
Have you ever considered--I don't know.
Making plans for a sustainable future?
Hmm?
What am I gonna do with you?
You've been really cool,randall.
I really, you know--
You know how much I appreciate what you've done for me.
You know you'll have this job waiting for you
When you get back.
You know that, right?
You'll have this, at least.
I'm so strapped.
What is it?
Oh, man, I totally forgot I have this appointment.
Yeah, of course you did.
Well, I will see you tomorrow, ryan.
And I'll see what I can find for you.
Thanks, randall
Shh. Don't worry, baby.
Gonna be all right.
Gonna be okay.
He in?Hey. Yeah.
Let me just tell him-keep an eye on that for me.
Oh--
Hey, christian.
No girls allowed.
What's that?
Going over effects the budget will allow.
Even though my boyfriend is the effects supervisor,
He's not doing this for free,so we have to pick and choose.
That little bitch
I wanna talk to you about something.
Yep?
What is it?
Ryan.
Another topic my boyfriend loves to hate.
Really? Why's that?
Every movie I've produced,
He thinks I'm trying to bang the leading man,
And, uh, half the time,he's been wrong.
I want you to call ryan in tomorrow.
Tell him he's been replaced.
What? Why?
What happened? What's gerald's problem?
This has nothing to do with gerald,
And ryan's not actually being replaced.
I don't get it.
Just call ryan in and tell him
That gerald's thinking of taking him out of the movie.
And you, jon, can convince him otherwise
If ryan's willing to do something for you.
Like what?
Tell him he gets to keep the part if he sleeps with you.
Why the hell would I do that?
Favor to me.
You're not joking, huh?
No, I am not.
Christian,I'm friends with gina.
Ryan is totally straight.
Really?
You think he's totally straight?
That's what I believe, yeah.
So how did he get the job at the hotel, huh?
'cause he's so straight or 'cause he's so, um, smart?
Christian, I'm best friends with gina,
And I can't do this to her.
Jon, jon, jon.
Relax.
It's just a prank.
Test ryan, see what his reaction is.
Afterwards, you can tell him it's a joke.
And if he has the balls to go to gina
And tell her about your little prank,
Then just say,"christian put me up to it."
Blame it on me.I'll take full responsibility.
Chris, I don't think I can do this.
Jon, there are a lot of people in this town
Who call themselves producers.
You're just one.
Okay.
But I still don't get it.
You don't need to.
Besides, you might get lucky.
Hey, tara!
Baby!
Hi.
What'd you do today?
I went to the gym.Which gym?
Equinox.The gym that I'm a member of.
The one on westwood or the one on sunset?
The one in west hollywood.
Why'd you go to the one in west hollywood?
Because it was closer to where I was meeting gina for lunch.
What time did you go to the gym?
Tell me something,do you find gina attractive?
No. I'd never hire an assistant I find attractive.
Why not? She's a pretty girl.
Do you find ryan attractive?
Okay, here we go.
No, I don't.
Well, I figured you have to find him attractive on some level.
You cast him as the lead in the movie.
No, no, that's not true.
I did not cast him in the movie.
All right, you made me cast him as the lead in the movie.
No, we've been over this. I didn't make you do anything.
You hired him as a favor to gina,
And that's why he's in the movie, isn't it?
Would you fuck him?
What did you just fucking ask me?
I said would... You... Fuck... Him?
No... I... Wouldn't.
Did actors in the past, and I have two words for them:
Never again.
I just thought maybe you two knew each other.
Maybe you met before.
When? When would we have met before?
Please, enlighten me.
Maybe your modeling days when you first got to la.
Oh, god, no, I hadn't, christian.
But you know, who knows?
I was pretty wasted during those days.
So anything's possible, right?
Come on.
Christian, why are you asking me these things?
No reason. You're the one getting all defensive.
I'm chill, baby.
Why are you asking me about ryan?
I just thought maybe the two of you had met before.
No. Nope.We had not.
We had not met before.
I'm gonna get another.You want one?
Yeah.
After that interrogation,give me a fucking double.
How was your day?
Did you go to the gym today?
Hey, babe!
Hey, babe.How'd it go?
Uh, I don't think I got it.Too many other guys.
I'm sorry, babe.
What are you doing?
Christian does yoga with cynthia gray?
What?
I'm just looking at his schedule.
Do you know her?
Yeah. Actually, I was in an acting class with her
A few years ago.
Weird to see her name again.
So she's teaching yoga now.Typical.
Right, that's exactly what christian's doing
When he's over with cynthia. It's yoga. Sure.
So I had lunch with tara today.
You did?Yeah.
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I just--
I don't know. I guess I'm a little surprised
After what you told me about her last night.
Yeah, I know, but christian asked me to go, so--
Why?I don't know.
It was like he wanted me to find out something.
Like what? I really don't know.
Afterwards, it just confirmed everything he already knew,
Which is that she doesn't wanna have anything more
To do with the movie.
What else did she say?
Well, I don't think she believed me
When I told her you thought christian was cool.
Why would you tell her that?Huh?
That-- why would you say that I thought christian was cool?
What does it matter? You don't care that I said that, right?
Ryan?
You can tell her whatever you want, babe.
I mean,I don't even know her.
She also seemed--
I don't know,she seemed scared.
Really anxious.
She kinda reminded me of like one of those girls
In those movies that's being followed by somebody.
I-- I don't know.It was just very weird.
Hey!Hey. Is everything okay?
I mean, you said we couldn't talk about this on the phone.
I asked gina what this was about.
She had no idea.Ryan, it's okay.
Close the door.
But why?
Uh, there's no one here.
Close the door, ryan.
Can we make this fast?
I'd rather just stand,if that's okay.
What's going on?
Why are you calling me to the office
At 11:00 at night, jon?
Look, I'll be upfront.
Gerald is still having problems with you for the lead.
I know you've known this,
And even though you've been officially cast for this,
He's reconsidering.
You're fucking kidding me.
No. I'm not fucking kidding you.
What does this mean?
What does "reconsidering" mean?
We're shooting in a month, jon.I put my whole life on hold.
Sit down.
I'm the one with the direct line to chris and gerald.
Has gina been told about this?
No, gina hasn't been told about this.
If gina hasn't been told about this, then why am I here?
I'm calling her.
No, don't. Put the phone away.
Ryan, put the phone down!
I can make sure you keep the role.
Yeah?
How's that?
Well, I'm going out to, uh,
Palm springs this weekend,and, uh...
Well, why don't you come?
Aren't you going with billy?
No.
You mean me and gina?
No. Just, um...
Just me and you.
Sure. Why not? But...
Why wait?
Exactly.
Let's do it now.
Yeah?Yeah.
Suck me off right now.
Right here. Now.In the office.
Yeah?Yeah.
Come on. Get to work.Fuckin' put it in your mouth.
Seriously?
Seriously. Come on.
I need to get off.Make it hard.
Is this what you want?
Suck me off right now.You know you want it.
Hey, cynthia?
Hey, uh, this is ryan from suzie walter's acting class.
Yeah, yeah, I know. It's-it's been a long time.
Listen, I wanted to ask you something.
Who is this?
I'm going out.Amber texted me.
We're gonna have a drink or see a movie or something.
Cool.
Really? That's it?
You're not gonna ask me where I'm going or when I'll be home?
Nothing?
No. I trust you, baby.
Okay.
I'm gonna take a shower first.
Okay. I'm going out. I'll be back in a bit.
Okay.
What are you gonna do?
Go online.
Look for somebody to be here when you get back.
Oh, okay.Really? Tonight?
Yeah. Really.
Okay.
You smell nice.
Thank you.
Hey, it's me.
I need you to come over now.
So, you remember me?No, I don't.
Yeah, I used to date christian, you know, before I met you.
Great.You don't seem surprised.
Honestly, I don't really care who christian dated.
And why would I be surprised?
Christian went out with a lot of girls before me,
And I don't care.
Well, I would.I would care.
cynthia...
Really don't have a clue,do you?
You don't know anything about me and christian, do you?
All right, you know what?
Lay it out, babe. What kind of trouble am I in?
Tara, you know,I have enough of a clue
To get into contact with you.
Okay, because I think, you need to get out of this relationship.
I think you need to get away from him.
Really?
Why?
Because he's sick.He's a sick little boy.
Go on.
I mean, even though he was,you know, fucking other girls,
There were, of course, the hookups that we did together.
I never wanted to.I mean, he...
Always pressured me into them.
Really? You didn't want to?
I'm assuming he does the same thing with you.
Just finish your fucking story,cynthia.
I need to get the hell outta here.
Not really a story. No.
Just that moment when everything became clarified for me.
You know, one night when things got out of hand.
How?
I found myself in the emergency room at ucla.
Hmm. How did that happen?
Christian decided to invite a bunch of guys over to the house.
And you let him.
No.
Actually, I didn't.I was passed out.
And who's fault was that, cynthia, hmm?
Your precious christian decided to crush up
A bunch of rufelin in a drink that he gave me.
I never called him "precious,"first of all.
I believe that was your name.
Secondly, it's "rohypnol."
Third of all--you know what I meant.
I don't believe you.
Really.
You don't.
So what are you saying, cynthia? What are you saying?
You saying that you didn't let yourself get gang banged,
That you had no control--he filmed the entire thing,
And then he threatened to put it up on different sites
If I said anything to anybody.
Obviously you weren't in control of christian. I am.
I'm telling you this because I think he's gonna hurt you
In the same way.
No, you're telling me this because you're jealous
And a little drunk.
God, it's such a girl-thing to do.
Look, christian's not gonna hurt me.
If anything, I'm the one that's gonna hurt him.
She's on her way back.
We got 20 minutes.
We are now hacking into ryan's facebook page
Because you have to be friends with him to look at it.
And privacy block is on,photos locked.
Is she friends with him?
No.
Are you sure?
Dude, I've been your tech guy for like three years.
What is up with the paranoia?I've never seen you like this.
Stop.
Christian, uh, you wanted me to check the phone?
Think I found those deleted texts you wanted me to see.
Um, not a lot of them, but, uh,
I don't know what this means,but it was sent to...
It was sent to ryan's phone.
How quickly can you hack into his bank account?
Who was that?
Who?
The guy that just walked out of the house.
Who in the fuck do you think I'm talking about?
Oh, he brought me some weed.
You're such a liar.
How does that make me a liar?
It's not just that.
How was amber?
I wouldn't know.I didn't see amber.
You didn't? Nope.
Where'd you go?
Who's cynthia?
I don't know who you're talking about.
Stop fucking lying, christian.
I know lots of cynthias.What I meant was
I don't know which cynthia you're referring to.
Fine. Okay.
Someone texted me because they wanted to talk to me about you.
Turns out that it's some girl you dated on the east side,
And not only did you put her in the hospital,
But you invited a bunch of fucking guys over
And then pulled a fucking train on her, christian.
I know the whole thing.Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That didn't fucking happen!Christian, what the fuck?
Oh, right, I'm sure.No, look.
I dated a girl named cynthia before you...
Now you remember.
But none of that other shit happened.
All right?
You're such a fucking liar.
I swear to god!
If it happened,I would tell you.
It didn't fucking happen.
I don't know why she would say that.
I have no fucking clue. Me either!
I don't know why she would say that either.
She's fucking on drugs,and she's obsessed with me.
I don't know what the fuck is wrong with-- I-I don't know.
What kind of drugs was she on? Roofies?
I have no idea. She's crazy. I don't fucking know.
She probably is jealous that I'm with you instead of her.
But it did not happen.She's on drugs.
Yes.
If it happened,I would tell you.
I swear to god.
But it did not.Oh. Thanks.
It didn't though.I swear.
Okay
Who's that?
Nobody. It's... Whoever.Nobody.
Christian, who is that?
It's just somebody I invited over,
But we can do it another night.
It's fine.We can cancel.
No. Tell 'em to come over.
Are you sure? I mean, they're close, but...
No. Don't cancel.
Where you going?
Tell 'em to meet me upstairs.
Yeah?
They wanna use the pool first.Great. Whatever.
They're here.
Let 'em in.
It's a little less than that.
It's always nice to cool off.
Ooh, it's cold out there.
It's warmer upstairs.
Let's go upstairs.
This is tara.
Come on in.
Come here.
Hello.
Let me see my girls together, come on.
Yeah, that's right.That's what I wanna see.
I wanna see the two of you together.
Just lie down.
Kiss him. Fucking kiss him.
Fucking kiss him.Come on, baby.
Now this is what I wanna to see.
Kiss him. Kiss him more.
Go down on him.
No, no, no.Not you. Him.
Go, jerry.
You listen to me, okay?
Thank you.
Strange how things work out.How do you mean?
Well, I remember liking you,and then you ended up with tara.
Then I remember liking christian,
And he ended up with tara.
I don't know if I'm gonna find a guy,
Maybe I just need to get out of la.
Yeah, it's a pretty fucked-up town, isn't it?
Sure you don't wanna stay, maybe grab some lunch?
I just wanted to come by and hear what happened
And to thank you in person.
It sounded like a weird request, but I appreciate it.
You took it a lot further than I thought. Thanks.
First acting gig I've had in years.
You really love tara?
Yeah. I mean, I'm with someone, but yeah.
I'm sorry.
Ryan, I let that go a long time ago.
You realize that you have to let it go, too, at a certain point?
I know.
Hey, hey, hey!Why are you following me?
What the fuck are you doing? What do you want, huh?
I don't know you!
I know who sent you! Come on, admit it!
Fucking christian!
You want my picture, huh?You want my picture?
Where's your phone?Give it!
Nobody wants your picture, okay?
I know, okay?
Tell christian I know what the fuck he's doing.
Tell that piece of shit I know!
What the fuck?
This can't be my phone.
Fuck.
What are you doing?
I was just looking for my phone.
Did you find it?
Christian, why is my phone in your drawer?
Yeah, christian-did you find it?
Christian, why was my phone--I know about you and ryan!
You fucking lying bitch!
Are you gonna fucking admit it? Are you?
Oh, shit! Are you gonna admit it
After I beat the fucking shit out of you?
You fucking lied to me!
I trusted you, and you lied to me!
Christian...You lied!
Please! I really don't know what you're talking about!
Jesus!
Oh, my god, I can't believe how late I slept.
How was your run?
Babe, why are you drinking tequila at noon?
Ryan.
I'm glad your boss is seeing a shrink.
I've been looking at christian's schedule.
Dr. Campbell, 3:00.
How do you know that dr. Campbell's a shrink?
Stop it. I googled him.
What are you doing, protecting this psycho?
Why do you even care?
Because he's a sick fuck.
Ryan, I told you, you don't have to like him. Wha--
The movie's not gonna happen, gina.
I really don't know what you're talking about right now.
The movie's not--the movie's happening.
The movie's not gonna happen.
Ryan, what did--okay, stop. What did jon--
It's not jon. It's not gerald.
It's not you. It's him. It's christian.
He's not gonna let the movie happen.
You need to calm down. He's gonna pull out.
He's gonna fuckin' pull out.What are you talking about?
I don't understand. What? I don't understand!
It's not gonna happen because I've been fucking his girlfriend
For the last month.
It's not gonna happen because..I'm in love with her.
That's why tara stopped working on the movie.
I never told you this, but we lived together for a year.
Me and tara.
She dumped me when she started hooking up with christian.
I hadn't seen her in three years
Until that day I walked into the audition room,
And then it started again.
And christian found out.
He's had me followed,
He's fucked with my bank account,
He's insane, and he knows about me and tara.
That's why the movie's not gonna happen, okay? Got it?
I love you, baby.
You believed in me.
You helped me so much,but I-- I can't control it,
How I feel about her.
But she'll never be with you.
She's not going back to that.
We can talk about this as much as you want.
I'll spend all day talking about this,
And then I want you out of here.
I want you to take all your things,
And I want you out of here.
And then I'm going to beg christian
To keep the movie going.
I don't care how much I have to degrade myself.
I will beg him to keep the movie going.
And I will make sure that you are not
Within a hundred miles of that set
For the duration of the shoot.
Usually I'm the one in control.
Last night I wasn't.
None of it seemed real.
Not when that guy was sucking my dick
Or when tara tried to get him to fuck me.
Which didn't happen, fyi.
There were certain things
That tara and the other girl wanted us to do,
And I don't even know why I care.
Just some dumb kids on the internet I'll never see again.
Just...
Didn't feel like I wasn't in control.
I felt objectified.
The way the two of them just watched
And told us what to do.
Doesn't usually go down like that.
Usually I'm the one directing the scene.
It made me feel like an actor.
It's kinda like how I feel when I'm here.
You feel like an actor when you are here?
We're all actors, aren't we? I mean...
We all act differently,
Depending on the situation we're in or we're around.
I don't act the same way with you as I do when I'm with tara.
Just last night and here...
Were pronounced,
That... Disconnect.
So do you worry about being an actor when you're here?
It doesn't worry me. I just don't like it.
I don't like to feel like I'm not in control.
Have you processed that coming here is non-negotiable?
That it's mandatory?
Have you been able to accept that?
You mean have I processed it?
I processed it. I've accepted it.
I just don't like it.
Every day I think what'll happen
If I don't go back to dr. Campbell's next week.
This thought is always on my mind.
And the answer is?
If I miss a session,you will call the asshole.
The asshole being...My father.
And if I told your father you're missing sessions?
Then the asshole will pull my trust fund if I miss a session.
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking have I been here long enough yet?
And the answer is?
Yeah, it's me.
You there? I got your little message.
Ryan, ryan, ryan.
Poor, poor ryan.
It all seemed so exciting
When you were 18, and that photographer found you,
Class trip from michigan, all the way out to los angeles.
Yeah, hollywood.
And you were suddenly so far away
From that shithole town you grew up in,
So you did\nsome modeling shoots.
Everyone was so encouraging.
You even did a commercial or two.
I saw one on youtube for pringles.
Looked like a fucking moron.
Then what, huh?
Nothing.
Nada.
So now you're bartending with the occasional hotel gig
To supplement your income.
That's just 'cause randall wants to fuck you up the ass.
Who knows?\nYou'd probably let him.
He probably has.
What happened last October at the post ranch inn, huh?
You tell gina about that?
I doubt you told gina about that romantic drive
All the way up the coast to the post ranch inn.
And then bam!
You reconnect with tara last July.
She convinces everyone to cast you in a movie
You're not even capable of acting in.
And then bam!
You're fucking my girlfriend.
And bam!
You convince cynthia to tell everyone some bullshit story.
So what, huh?
You get tara to dump me?
So you guys can, what, run away together?
Get married?
So you can, what,
Coexist in some dump of a house somewhere?
Think tara's going back to that kind of life?
You think she's going to that lifestyle again?
You want my advice, ryan?
Go back to michigan and get over it,
You clueless little motherfucker.
What are you doing here?
I just wanted to talk to you.
Why?
Ryan.
I had no idea that you two knew each other.
Interesting how small this town really is.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Come on, babe. Your little story?
What story? The ucla hospital.
Bunch of guys running a train on you.
There's no way that kid's smart enough
To come up with that on his own.
But I know somebody who is.
What was I supposed to do?
It worked, babe.
You wanted my attention, and you got it. Here I am.
Come here, smarty pants.
I'm not mad. I thought it was cute.
I'm sorry.  It's okay.
Did you really think I would need to slip a girl a roofie?
No.
What I am interested in...
Is how you guys know each other.
Oh, it doesn't matter.
Yeah, but I am curious. How'd you meet?
Do you like him?
Have you fucked him? Has he got a big dick?
Okay, yes, I... I met him\nbefore he knew tara.
We had the same acting class together.
And yes, we had a thing, and then he met her,
And then it was over.
Very interesting.
Interesting?
Really?
Why?
And why does it even matter to you anymore?
What did you think she was doing?
I mean, I don't know, she dated him for like a year or so,
And then she dumped him.
We didn't know each other very well back then.
I mean, we went to like a few of the same parties,
And I think we dated a few of the same guys,
But we weren't really friends or anything.
And then she met you.
Christian?
Christian, what are you doing?
Hello?
Christian?
Christian, what the fuck?
Christian! No! No!
Pick up, pick up, pick up.
Why don't you fucking answer?
Pick up the fucking phone!
Can't believe what you did to her, dude.
You are one sick fuck.
Cynthia?
Hi.
Where were you?
Dr. Campbell's.
What's that?
Um...
I'm gonna leave, okay?
I'm gonna go stay with my sister in santa barbara for a bit.
I'm sorry about this morning.About...
About everything.
Yeah, I know. I know. I'm sorry, too.
But I'm gonna leave anyway.
I just-- I need to hear that you're okay with it.
I wanna know that you're okay with me going.
Please.
Will you please just let me go?
I loved you.
I really... Loved you.
In my own way, but I loved you.
I know, I know.
I loved you, too.
But I-- I just need to think about things.
And I need to hear you say that it's okay if I go.
It's okay.
I'll be fine.
Thank you.
I need something from you.
Yes, anything. Tell me.
What do you need?
An alibi.
Wha... What?
For what?
This afternoon.
I-I don't understand. What happened this afternoon?
You went to...
You just said you went to dr. Campbell's.
What did you-what else happened?
Something happened to cynthia.
Christian...
Christian, what happened?
It's not important.
Uh, I don't--what happened?
I don't get--I don't understand.
What do you mean,something happened?
I left dr. Campbell's at 3:55.
Got here at 4:20.
You've been with me ever since.
Do you understand?
Nod for me, baby.
Nod for me.
One more thing.
If you ever see him again,
If he ever contacts you,
If he calls you,
If you're even in the same room together...
I will kill him.
Look at me.
I will kill him, and I will get away with it.
You understand?
Yes.
Nod for me, baby.
Nod for me.
Okay, okay.
That's a good girl.
Good girl.
So, you guys just got back from dubai.
Yeah, we stayed at the burj al arab.
I thought you had a bad experience at the burj?
Thought you were only staying at the atlantis now?
Yeah, but tara had never been to dubai,
So I thought it'd be fun for her.
It didn't matter to me. I was in meetings all day.
So how was dubai? What'd you do there?
You know, just shopped, laid out.
Weren't you working on a movie?
Yeah, uh, kind of.
Yeah. How'd you know?
We have a friend in common. Who?
Christian.
Didn't you used to go out with him?
Yeah.
He's producing another movie a friend of mine is in,
And jaden told me that you and christian used to live together
And when I met you tonight, I just put it all together.
Yeah, christian and I went out for about a year.
And then when we broke up,
I decided to take myself off the film.
Oh, I'm sorry.Was the breakup that bad?
No. No, not at all.
No, it's just, there were a lot of things going on and--
Wait, wasn't that--
Was that around the time when that girl was killed?
Christian's yoga instructor or something?
Yeah, actually...
Yeah, it was right around that time that we broke up, yeah.
They never found out who did that, did they?
No. I mean, they had some suspects,
But aside from that, no.
At the end, nothing.
Didn't they find like a knife in the car of someone's assistant?
Yeah, but... I mean, I heard that it was basically
Whoever killed the person, her,
Must have thrown it in his car.
I mean, I was with him that night, so it wasn't him, but--
Yeah, after that...
So they never arrested anybody?
No. Actually, no, they didn't.
That's so scary.
Yeah.
How is christian doing, by the way?
Christian, he's, um, he's good.
We don't really talk that much,
Aside from texts and facebook and stuff.
But the last time I heard from him was pretty recent,
And he's doing great,actually.
Gonna go to the ladies' room. I'll be right back.
Good, good. I'm glad you guys had a good time.
She's cute, man.Yeah, she's cute.
Hey! It's me.
Yeah, I'm here with her right now.
Yeah, we went to david's place first for drinks.
So... What do you want me to do?
Anything you want me to ask her
Besides what you already told me to?
She seems happy, even though she's like totally faking it.
Hello?
Hello, ryan.
Hello, ryan, are you there?
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：274796078