更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
Dreams are like stars.
You can't touch them but if you follow them
they will lead you to your destiny.
I used to dream of being the first dogmonaut to walk on the Moon.
And now I dream of going home to my boy Sasha.
It's incredible.
You two astronauts need to get some sleep.
- You've got a big day tomorrow Sam.
It's gonna be the coolest.
I've never seen a real spaceship before.
I wish you could come too.
But I've already asked school like 12 times.
No pets.
Look a shooting star Buddha.
Make a wish.
I wish to one day touch the Moon.
Sam honey come to bed.
Goodnight Buddha.
Launch.
I wish that all your dreams come true.
Sorry you can't come Buddha.
Namaste.
Not to worry. I have a plan of my own.
Catch!
Bye Rosebud!
Rosebud where are you?
Come on sis. I've got a plan for a rainy day field trip.
Gross! No way I'm going out in that rain. It'll wreck my furdo.
Come on let's go!
OK Budderball see you after school big fella.
Oh sweet mama.
Psst Budderball.
We're on a journey of ginormous proportions.
I'm about to eat some ginormous proportions myself.
I'll see you guys later.
Budderball there's no time for breakfast.
Breakfast is the most important meal of the day!
Come on!
Oh bother.
A little moonwalk.
Hit it B.
See ya. I've gotta bounce. I've got a field trip today.
B-Dawg!
Sorry I didn't mean to scare you.
Pshaw. You didn't scare me. I was just busting a new move.
What's the hip-hop happening home dogs?
We're not really sure but Buddha sure is excited about it.
All I can say is it's gonna be a blast.
Who put the Red Bull in Buddha's doggy bowl?
Let's go!
Not again!
You've gotta have a B-A-T-H before Mum and Dad see you.
B-A-T-H...
You just spelled the B word!
Mudbud come back!
Dude step away from the couch.
Oh!
Looks like he got a time out.
When it rains Mudbud gets grounded.
He's a repeat offender.
Remember the time I sampled the Thanksgiving turkey?
I got a serious time out for that too.
Sample schmample. You ate the whole Butterball turkey dawg.
Kind of embarrassing to be named after a turkey.
Guys what about Mudbud?
Am I ever glad to see you dudes.
Shh. I've gotta jimmy the lock.
Come on you guys we've gotta hurry. We might miss it.
- Watch it dude! - Move over guys!
Hurry! There's not a minute to spare!
Oh yeah!
Come on Mudbud we've gotta go!
Come along people!
The launch won't wait on us if we're tardy now will it?
The window of opportunity is upon us. Let's seize it.
We are the one lucky Fernfield class
who is going to see a real live
- spaceship launch. - Yeah!
So that's where you're taking us Buddha?
Surprise!
Vision Enterprises is going to make space travel available to anyone.
I'm in bagged lunch heaven. Oh Mama!
Budderball quiet!
Oh my goodness!
My allergy to dander is really acting up. I...
Come on.
Ready Gravity?
Let's go do this old buddy.
On behalf of everyone at Vision Enterprises
we would like to thank you for your continued support
on the Vision One project.
And gentlemen we give you the Vision One spacecraft.
She's... she's beautiful isn't she?
Uh... The... The Vision One
The... The design is an amalgamation of an air travel vehicle
and space design rocket.
The vehicle will comfortably carry two pilots
and four passengers into space.
The Vision One will land on the Moon
permitting our customers the opportunity
to walk on the surface.
Hi Finkel.
- Dr. Finkel nice of you to join us. - Of course.
Dr. Finkel. Dr. Finkel.
It is my pleasure Mr. Wolfson
until you fail and I take over of course.
Gravity behave.
I don't know what's more unsettling
that you accessorize with that brainless rodent
or that you converse with it too.
I like ferrets.
I've never been terribly fond of rats or weasels.
Nothing personal.
Well out with the old in with the new as they say.
Let's get on with it. Karl why is a cappuccino not touching my lips?
- Uh... - Don't speak.
Uh let me introduce you to some members of our team.
Fueling in progress.
Uh Slats Bentley is our Flight Dynamics Officer.
He will give you some details on today's mission.
Executing override sequence.
...approximately four days to get to the Moon and back.
Once we land on the surface we'll stay for 30 minutes
then re-launch back into space and head back home.
Good. Uh over here.
Uh this is Astro Spaulding.
Uh she is our pilot for the mission.
The pilot will be flying the spacecraft using a vectra system
vision-enabled control technology response array.
Um the uh systems will be controlled with the blink of an eye
It just scans your retina. It's all hands-free.
I thought there were no life forms on this mission not even a pilot.
Astro will remotely pilot Vision One from Mission Control.
Ultimately when we begin commercial travel uh... uh...
...the remote system will serve as a backup
in the event of a malfunction or a pilot illness or...
Sir there's been a break in the weather.
Ah well excuse us gentlemen.
Uh this is our big moment.
Dr. Finkel could you check and see if the tour group has arrived
and then greet them and help the kids if they have any questions.
Certainly Mr. Wolfson.
Sir!
OK people off the bus. Don't forget your lunch...
OK stop right here kids.
Welcome to Vision Enterprises. Everyone in. Don't touch anything.
We don't want to miss the launch. This way!
My! Oh dog germs!
Again please refrain from touching anything with your hands
you slimy little germ-infested creatures.
OK.
Our goal here at Vision Enterprises for some reason
is to make space travel accessible for everyone
including the family pet.
Let's hide over there dudes.
Quiet. They'll hear us.
Scanning.
- Wow. -  Human boy.
This is awesome.
As you can see we have some specifically designed space suits.
...and then do whatever you'd like...
- Excuse me. - Huh?
Please step away from the circle.
That device scans a life form and determines the right size suit.
It is highly sophisticated. So please step away.
Can I get a picture with the suit?
No you cannot have a picture with the suit.
Please just take it off immediately.
Uh all right you know what? It's fine it's fine.
You can keep the suit on. You probably already contaminated it.
- Just come back to the group. - Yeah.
Children this portion of the tour is over. Please follow me.
Thank you. Excuse me. Thank you.
Check out the fly gear.
Oh my gosh!
These outfits are so to die for.
Rosebud where are you going?
Device on.
Scanning.
- Wow. - Canine puppy.
Whoa dudes.
Will one of you boys zip me up?
I've gotta try this.
Scanning.
So how do I look?
Uh like our sister in a space suit.
I know I look tight.
Mine's a little too tight. Someone give me a paw.
Don't pull his paw!
Check it. It's the Goodyear blimp.
Let's go see the spacecraft up close.
Golly gosh maybe we could stop at the lunch pad for a snack
if it's on the way.
Budderball that says "launch pad".
Oxidize and loading is complete.
And voila
the spacecraft.
T-minus three minutes to launch.
Wow. I wish Buddha was here to see this.
Let's just take a quick look inside
then we'll come back and watch the launch.
Uh...
Do you think it's safe?
You never know how deep a puddle is until you jump in.
Huh?
Uh... I'll be right back.
Seriously dawg what does a puddle have to do with the spaceship?
Whoo-hoo! Oh yeah!
Come on let's go.
T- minus two minutes to launch.
Whoa. It's amazing.
I would've blinged it out a little more.
I call shotgun.
Wish us luck.
Hmm Lunch-O-Matic.
OK guys we've seen the ship. We better go.
Check out these retro shades.
Dude you shouldn't be touching those.
I could fly this thing no problem.
Piece of cake.
Yeah there's cake.
Ooh donut!
But I think I'll start with the chili cheese dog then steak
and finish with a bean burrito.
No beans!
Hey this does not look like a chili cheese dog.
All systems diagnostics check. I want a go or no go for launch.
Uh guys someone just closed the door.
Airlock door closed.
-  Airlock door secured. - Copy that.
Launch platform activated.
Are we moving?
Dudes this is not good.
B-Dawg what did you press?
I didn't press anything.
- Boosters. - Go flight.
Budderball my instincts tell me you should take a seat fast!
- But I was just getting to dessert. - Hurry.
- Flight out. - It's a go.
Guidance uh navigation.
- Go. - Propulsion and trajectory.
Everything's a go sir. That bird is ready to fly.
-  Vision One in launch position. - We are a "go" for launch.
- We're "go" for auto sequence. - Start sir.
T-minus 30 seconds and counting.
Guys I hear a low rumbling sound.
Hey don't look at me.
Guys I think we might be going on a road trip.
Restraints activated.
T-minus ten nine
8  7
eight seven
six five...
... four three
...two one and...
...ignition.
We're moving!
Gravity we have lift-off.
Yeah!
It feels like my stomach is in my throat!
This is like a ride on Space Mountain!
Dad always said I should be more down to Earth.
Why didn't I listen?
Leaving Earth's atmosphere.
That was a radical ride.
I don't recommend lift-off on a full stomach.
That was heavenly.
Zero gravity.
Huh?
Restraints released.
I'm floating like a balloon.
Wha... What's happening?
Zero gravity.
This is out of this world literally.
This is incredible.
You can say that again. Even I'm lighter than a feather.
This is off the chain dawgs. I could slam dunk in space.
Graviton reverser activate.
That doesn't sound good.
Whoa!
Gravity normal.
Hey hey I thought we were always supposed to land on our feet.
Who turned off that zero grav stuff?
Warning fuel low.
Sir I don't like what I see.
Somehow we are short a quarter of our fuel supply.
Fuel low.
Well first things first. Identify the source of the problem.
I know what the problem is.
Tank three was never completely filled.
The registries were blank. It doesn't make any sense.
She'll never make it to the Moon and back with that kind of shortage.
Hmm it pains me to say this
but I don't think we have any other option here but to abort the mission.
Astro how much time before we have to abort?
Approximately ten hours sir.
Good. Stay on course. Um...
OK... We have some time to solve this people. I need solutions.
Buddha I'm home.
- Buddha?
- Yo B-Dawg
I'm back in the crib. Let's bust some moves.
Rosebud come on let's go get a mani pedi
and a blow dry.
Rosebud?
Budderball I have your favorite dinner.
Budderball?
I knew we shouldn't have made him take a bath.
I think we're getting further and further away from home.
And further and further away from dinner.
I take full responsibility.
Sir I think we may have finally figured out a solution.
Great. I... I... knew you would.
Nice work. Let's hear it.
OK we think that we can refuel at the old Russian research space station.
But that space station disintegrated
into the Earth's atmosphere like years ago.
Well yeah but you said to check everything so I checked everything
including the conspiracy websites which said the station still in space.
The reason that no one has been able to find the space station
is because it's not in it's original position.
Somehow it has gotten out of geostationary orbit.
And one of the Russian cosmonauts he survived
and he's still living onboard alone.
-  Incoming communication. - Hold on.
Yuri this is Slats from Vision Enterprises
Do you read me?
American blue jeans! How are you?!
Um look I'm just confirming that you do have fuel
and are able to assist our spacecraft.
Of course I help you my comrades.
Yuri this is Pi.
Uh I am the spacecraft's designer
and mission flight director.
In exchange for the 3000 pounds of fuel uh I would like to offer...
No comrade in return for the fuel forget everything.
My location forget it.
Consider this information gone kaput okee-dokee pumpkin pie?
You have our word.
So we are going to have visitors. Good.
Oh don't worry old pal.
They promised not to tell anyone about us.
So we are free to live peacefully in space
forever and ever and ever!
Dudes what is this place?
Whatever it is it's getting closer.
I hope it's not an alien's house.
Not that I'd be scared or anything.
I hope it's a Denny's.
I could sure go for a Moons Over My Hammy right about now.
OK Yuri are you ready to receive the spacecraft. Over.
I've never been so ready in all of my life.
Come and get it rhinestone cowboy.
Oh right uh...
Let's switch from autopilot to remote pilot.
Switching now sir.
Astro she's all yours.
Docking maneuver initiated.
Remote pilot engaged sir.
Docking in progress
Docking in progress.
Docking successful.
OK Yuri we're locked in.
Uh we can begin fueling.
OK.
- What? - Huh?
We should explore and broaden our horizons.
Broaden our horizons?
We're lost in space dawg.
I think our horizons are broad enough.
I ain't going nowhere.
Good call bro if there's an alien intruder
we'll need someone to defend the spaceship.
Did... Did you say aliens?
Uh guys uh come on uh...
OK.
Come on follow me.
Dudes where are we going?
Yo dawgs hold up!
OK the gas is pumping like an American discotheque.
All right well when we get our 3000 pounds of fuel...
...we are going to the Moon.
Dawgs?
Come on aliens I... I ain't scared of nothing
because I float like a butterfly and... and sting like a bee dawg.
What is this place?
Huh?
It's an alien!
It's B-Dawg! He's in trouble!
Y... You don't wanna eat me! I'm all scrawny and boney.
Eat him! He has plenty of meat on them bones!
Uh...
I am no alien.
Though I suppose if I stay in space any longer I may qualify.
The name is Spudnick.
We're the Buddies. The pup in the chicken suit is B-Dawg
the dirty dude is Mudbud the Zen pup is Buddha
and Rosebud is our little sis.
Oh and uh me I'm Budderball. And I'm starving.
Nice to meet you. I'm a Russian dogmonaut.
We kind of got on the ship by accident.
And now we have no idea where we are.
You're aboard the RRSS
the old Russian Research Space Station.
You want me to show you around?
Follow me.
In this module we have our garden
where we grow all our food in space.
The added benefit is the plants filter out CO2 gas and produce oxygen.
And we also use them to create fuel for the station.
Now this joint is off the chain insane cuz.
Yes we've been off the orbital grid
for quite some time if that's what you mean.
Over here we have our solar panels which produce all our energy.
So you can keep the stereo pumpin' 24l7. That's wicked.
Right over here is the kitchen.
My favorite room in the house.
Huh?
Hmm. Where's the beef?
- Dude what is that? - Space juice.
Pee-yoo! It stinks. Who'd wanna drink that?
Well Yuri seems to like it. And we use it for fuel.
Who's Yuri?
He's the Russian cosmonaut I live with up here.
How long have you been up here dude?
Not really sure. It's all one long night in space.
I was only supposed to be on this station for a six month mission
but I'm sure it's been years and years.
Spudnick?
Spudnick? Where has my little puppy puppy gone?
Spudnick...
Yaaa-hoo!
Can you believe it Spudnick?
Our American comrades have given us a surprise gift!
Five fluffy puppies to keep us company here in space.
Thank you! Thank you!
He doesn't understand Spudnick.
We're not staying long.
Where that spaceship goes we go.
All right come on Spudnick.
Good.
We will finish refueling and then... we will celebrate.
Dude you have to help us.
Puppy puppies!
Dudes we've been hoodwinked.
You're telling me! OK this food is all vegetables.
Now what?
Uh we'll be ready to leave in less than 30 minutes.
The sooner we can get refueled
and get away from this bucket of bolts the happier I will be.
To life in space for eternity and forever.
And to you Spudnick.
A spaceman's best friend.
And to the new puppy puppies.
We will live together as a happy family till the end.
Ah. Whoo!
You want to get the dancing started?
That's a good idea Spudnick.
Let's get jiggle with it.
Yeah I'm not sure he's flying with a full jetpack.
He's crazy.
Oh ho!
Another you party animal?
I am sorry old pal. I am pooped.
All right one more one more.
OK let's do it.
Well...
Dudes I saw the Jamaican bobsled team do this.
Three two one push!
Wait guys! I changed my mind!
I told you guys this was a bad idea.
The dog's down for the count.
What a shame 'cause these space nachos are gnarly.
Huh space nachos?!
He's OK.
These are gonna be the longest 11 minutes in my life.
Ah!
Oooh.
Oo-y kapoo-y!
Yuri is knicker knackered.
Spudnick you know Yuri.
Too much dancing Yuri gets too much sleepy.
Oh that's nice. Hold me closer tiny dancer.
Oh that's nice.
Little Yuri. That's very nice.
Oh Spudnick.
My blanky.
Maybe Yuri take 40 blinks.
Just until the refueling is done.
Hmm.
Huh?
Quick! It's Yuri!
Hide!
Buddies where are you?
Spudnick.
Sir I'm showing that the tanks are full but the pressure is building.
- What happened to the crazy cosmonaut? - He's asleep.
Yuri this is uh
Vision Enterprises do you hear me?
This is my last chance to go home to my boy Sasha.
The station is falling apart anyhow.
And Yuri's plan is to go down with the ship.
Can you hear me? Wake up.
Da. Da. Yuri is just having a little kitty nap.
- Can I hitch a ride home with you guys? - For shizzle dawg.
I hope I never need it but better safe than sorry.
Refueling is complete. Can we disconnect the ship?
What?
The puppies are loose!
- You American dognappers! - What?
Oh no! The station is going into lockdown! Yuri's on to us.
Dudes I say we make like a bread truck and haul buns!
No! No come back! Puppy! No!
You guys where's Budderball?
Huh?
We can't leave without him.
You know our motto dudes: No pup left behind.
Budderball come on!
Not without my broccoli.
No! Please! Don't take away my puppy puppy pups!
Wait a second? Is he talking about puppies?
He's got more screws loose than the space station.
Come back! You cannot leave!
You cannot take my gift away from me!
I think he might be trying to shanghai the Vision One.
Enact emergency evacuation measures.
Let's detach from the station now.
Copy that.
That's not good.
Whoa!
Dude it's coming apart!
Wow! That's the Cosmopod escape vessel. He made it!
Signal lost.
Termination detected. RRSS destruction confirmed.
You guys find anything?
Nope haven't seen hide nor fur of them.
Don't worry. We'll find them.
Where there's a will there's a way.
- Mm-hm. - Yeah.
Are you ready to go home Spudnick?
Buddies we are not heading to Earth.
The coordinates show we are going to the Moon.
The Moon?
The ship is being controlled from Earth.
Yes it seems as though it is taking us to the Moon.
I'm sure Buddha and the other Buddies
are out there on some wonderful adventure.
I feel like he's a million miles away.
I know sweetie.
We'll find him.
Let's get some sleep now.
Come home soon.
Spudnick are you awake?
Yeah.
What are you thinking about?
I was thinking about my boy Sasha.
I hope he's still waiting for me.
We are nearing lunar orbit sir.
Let's get ready to initiate landing procedure.
Switch from autopilot to remote Astro please.
I am now in control of the ship and am prepared to land.
Surface of the Moon here we come.
huh?!
Wha...
Wha... What was that?
Night shade deactivated.
The Death Star!
B-Dawg it's the Moon.
It looks a lot bigger up here than when we used to howl at it from home.
Aw goodness! All the blue cheese a fella can eat!
We are heading for it and fast. Buckle up guys.
Restraint activated.
Onboard vectra activated
Whoa! Weird!
Wait this is unbelievable.
- I've lost control of the ship. - Talk to me.
I don't know. Somehow the onboard vectra system
has overridden the remote pilot.
B-Dawg what are you doing?
Stop the spinning!
A thousand feet and gaining speed sir.
If we don't get control soon and adjust our course the Vision One's a goner.
Who turned on the spin cycle?!
- Slats time? - 57 seconds till impact.
We're going in circles!
Someone do something!
This is a highly advanced piloting system.
- There we go. - Yeah I could've done that.
Just need a little practice that's all.
That was furry.
Good job Spudnick.
Thanks Rosebud but I'm turning it over to the experts.
Remote pilot engaged.
Whoa! Whoa! Yes I have control back.
- How? - I have no idea sir.
I'm just going with it.
Something very strange is happening up there.
OK initiate lunar landing procedure.
Initiating.
OK we're at 400 feet.
200.
Lunar landing...
Astro easy. 100 and counting.
50 feet.
And...
Touchdown.
- We're on the Moon. - Yes!
Ahh!
Yes!
Good job.
Wow the Moon.
Buddies are you ready to go for the walk of your lives?
Good idea 'cause I've gotta take a whiz something fierce.
Well let's suit up.
Wait a second. The system shows the airlock door is opening.
Spudnick you go first.
One small step for dog one giant leap for dogkind.
Sir you've gotta take a look at this.
What?
It's a... Well I think it's a... um...
I have no idea sir.
There's some sort of four-legged creatures surrounding the ship.
Sir I think we've discovered alien life forms.
OK uh Chuck zoom in on that would ya?
Roger.
I don't think it's cheese but I don't even care.
This is the first time in my life I haven't been hungry.
Thank you buddies for making dreams come true.
If they are extraterrestrial beings
why are they wearing Vision Enterprises spacesuits?
Open up the communication line on their helmets.
It appears we have canine stowaways?
Ah so maybe Yuri wasn't so crazy after all.
Those look like puppy puppies.
And they're walking on the Moon.
We're walking on the Moon!
Whoa! Amazing!
Check it. I'm doing the moonwalk.
Totally awesome.
Whoa! This is so cool.
How does something like this happen?
And more importantly how on earth are we going to bring them home?
Yeah leaving five puppies on the Moon it's not real good for PR.
No it is certainly not.
We could run an ad campaign.
- Oh. - Let me see.
Fly with us
we launched six poor innocent puppies into space
and then bid them farewell for eternity.
The bottom line is we can't leave them there.
How do you plan on coaxing a bunch of moronic animals
into a spacecraft from 228536 miles away?
Where's Buddha?
Om.
A view that will change your perspective forever.
This is totally unreal.
This one's for my boy Sasha.
Yo dogs I hate to crash the party but
how we gonna get home this time?
Galactic Canines do you read me?
- Does anyone else hear that? - Dogs I think I hear an alien.
Dude there's no aliens.
It must be Mission Control. They know we're here.
I'm Gravity Mission Commander's assistant.
Who are you doglings and how in the universe
did you get on board the Vision One?
I'm dogmonaut Spudnick Russian Space Agency.
And these are the buddies.
I got on at the Russian Space Station.
These pups uh they saved my life.
We got on at Vision Headquarters.
A field trip gone awry.
Dogs listen I can help you get back to Earth.
Dude are we over-stoked to hear a voice from home.
The Vision One will be departing for Earth in 15 minutes and 32 seconds.
So head back to the spaceship before your oxygen is depleted
and get ready for lunar lift off.
Until we get the puppies home safely
we keep this quiet. OK?
I mean I need full confidentiality on this. If this story were to leak
it would spread like wildfire and that would cause irreparable damage
to Vision Enterprises.
Uh guys guys! The uh d-dogs are going back on board.
Let's launch before they decide to go exploring again.
All right people we know the drill.
Boosters are a go V-1 is a go for lunar launch.
Robot arm activated.
Time to bring home a souvenir.
Preparing to launch.
Ready to launch sir.
We will be out of communication with you
for approximately 12 minutes
while you circle the backside of the Moon.
All right we're back in business.
Now let's get these puppies safely home.
We're live at Vision Enterprises where quite a tale is unfolding.
It seems that five golden retriever puppies
have been accidentally launched into space.
Mom!
Along with a bull terrier they are going
- where no dog has gone before. - What?
It is believed the pups rendezvoused
with the Russian dogmonaut
at the long-thought destroyed Russian Research Space Station.
- Wow! - They made history
by being the first animals to walk on the Moon.
Spudnick!
You know I have no idea how these guys could have gotten a hold of this.
Hackers these days.
Probably got into the system and jacked our video feed.
It's very off-putting.
- Come on guys. - Live for KTLA
- I'm Doug... - Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa.
Where do you think you're going?
We're here to talk about our pups that you guys shot into space.
Absolutely no one gets through.
Then we'll go talk to the newsman instead.
- Satellite is up in 8 seconds. - Hang on a second.
- We have a live wire. - Dr. Finkel?
I have a bunch of kids here
that claim the alleged puppies in space are their dogs.
I thought you'd like to know.
-  Send them in. - Yes sir.
Dr. Finkel would like to have a word with you.
Follow me.
Next is Steve with sports.
Excuse me Pi.
I'd like to introduce you to the children whose lives you've ruined
by launching their puppies up into space.
As you can imagine they're quite traumatized.
Pi wow it's an honor to meet you sir.
Buddha and I are your hugest fans.
I'm sure he's thrilled to be on your ship.
Thank you.
This is Gravity.
My assistant.
Kids uh be assured that um we're doing everything
in our power to bring your puppies home safely.
Um hey guys...
I'm Slats. I'm the flight dynamics officer.
That's uh FIDO for short.
Oh and over there that's Astro.
She actually is the pilot of the Vision One. How cool is that huh?
I'm Sam. My pup is Buddha.
That's Pete. His bro is Mudbud.
Bartelby's fella is Butterball.
Billy's homepup is B-Dawg
- and Alice's BFF is Rosebud. - Mm-hmm.
Slats why don't you get them up to speed on the current plan.
Um yeah. Oh yeah guys come on over here. Check this out. Very cool.
OK well all the vital stats are on the big board as we call it.
The ETA is tomorrow morning at 1100 hours.
That's 11:00am.
Well this ought to ensure this is a one way trip.
Critical course error.
You see that right up there?
Current telemetry unsafe. Confirm change.
- Dr. Fecal? - Yes?
Uh I mean it's Finkel. Dr. Finkel. Yes what is it?
What are you doing?
- I'm not doing anything. -  Telemetry changed.
You shouldn't concern yourself. You're just a child. Excuse me. Karl.
- Yeah me too. - If I come back.
No no. We'd bring you back for sure.
What's that?
- Ah it's just a meteor. - Just a meteor?
- Collision alert! Collision alert! - What?
Collison alert!
Oh! I thought our course was set to avoid the meteor shower.
I don't know sir. Somehow the telemetry has been modified.
Well looks like we're going to test our auto-avoidance system.
Engaging auto-avoidance system.
Auto-avoidance system activated.
Buddies you're right in the middle of a meteor shower.
Hang on!
Whoa!
Oh no!
Ah!
OK looks like we made it people.
Buddies looks like you're in the clear.
That was close.
Collision alert! Collision alert!
What was that?
Data communications terminated.
Go to back up.
The back up is down as well sir.
Reporting a total failure in signal strength.
Buddies the Vision One has been struck by a meteor.
All our system tests confirm
that the data communication antenna is damaged.
All we have left is audio communication
and that doesn't help us at all.
And the only way to fix it
is for an astronaut to do it externally.
We're gonna need one of you to do a spacewalk to fix the damage.
Without the data communication antenna
we can't control the ship from Earth.
Roger that Mission Control.
I should go. I've been in space the longest and know this stuff well.
Dude if something happens to you we're all doomed.
I'll do it! The sooner we get home the sooner I'll get some food.
I was just gonna raise my paw.
But you beat me to it dawg.
As far as we can tell all the functions of the Vision One
are normal and the hull is intact but its telemetry
has been diverted and it's way off course
and our re-entry angle is dangerously shallow.
The Vision One could skip off into the atmosphere
and tumble out into space.
Oh.
Well for the sake of those five kids...
...we cannot give up.
We can't.
The puppies along with their Russian comrade
are in great peril.
An unprecedented disaster has occurred aboard the Vision One.
The spacecraft has been struck by a meteor
and we are awaiting word if the damage is repairable.
Oh my goodness.
To control your movement you have four small jets.
Move your right hind leg you go back.
Move your left hind leg you go forward.
Wiggle your right front paw you go left.
Your left front paw you go right.
Look you'll be tethered to the ship
so you don't float off into outer space. Got it?
Uh which one is my left paw again?
We're doomed.
What? It's not my fault I'm dyslexic!
Just remember your right back leg you lift to take a wizzo.
Left back you use to scratch your tummy.
Left front paw you use to beg for food.
And the right front paw is for snackin'.
OK scratch forward. Wizzo equals backwards.
Begging go right and snacking go left.
See I got it.
The target is a data communications antenna.
Place it back into position
and we should be able to control the ship again.
Budderball did you eat all the bean burritos?
What can I say? I'm a nervous eater.
And walking in space makes me especially nervous.
Oh sweet mama. This is beautiful.
Budderball can you read us?
Roger Rosebud.
OK now gently move forward.
Uh how do I do that again?
Scratch leg dude. Scratch leg.
Oh right!
All this talk about scratching and now I've got an itch.
Budderball don't scratch.
But it's so itchy.
If you scratch you'll spin out of control.
I can't help myself.
Don't do it dawg.
Must scratch.
Budderball no!
Oh mama. Ah!
Ah!
Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa. Whoaah! Ah!
Whoa!
Ah! Ow!
In life sometimes you're the bug sometimes you're the windshield.
Did somebody catch the license plate on that UFO?
Quit messing around dude.
Go to the antenna.
Guys we have a problem.
It's not working.
You've got to be kidding dawg.
I swear. Cross my stomach and hope to starve.
The scratching episode used up all your fuel.
Now what are we gonna do?
I got it! Budderball just ate a dozen bean burritos right?
Dude this is no time to be cryptic.
We're gonna have to pull his paw.
Dawg he'll be asphyxiated.
Trust me I know what I'm doing.
Huh?
Robot arm engaged.
Easy.
- Whoa dudes. - Budderball are you with us?
I don't know what you guys are complaining about.
It's really not that bad.
OK now the methane gas you just produced
should give you enough fuel to fire up your jet pack.
Budderball that little bit of fuel won't last.
You have to fix the antenna.
I see the problem.
OK what does it look like?
It kind of does a dog leg to the wizzo side.
He means it's crooked to the right.
See if you can move it back into position.
Roger that.
Great news everybody.
Data communications has been restored to the ship.
Budderball you should be proud.
Data communication restored.
- Unbelievable. - She's back online.
Yeah!
Let's not uh celebrate too much here.
We still have a ship to get back on course. Slats?
Telemetry correction uplink underway sir.
Firing thrusters course correction to 152.2 over 5.
Vision One course correction confirmed sir.
OK Slats?
Find out how we could have gotten so off course.
I don't know sir.
Doesn't make any sense.
We were on course to avoid the meteor shower.
The last print-out showed us right on track. Look!
Wait a minute. The log shows an adjustment...
...made from the main terminal yesterday at 19:49.
Main terminal?
It was him!
Hm? Excuse me.
Please you can't be serious.
You don't think I would ever do such a thing?
Are you sure Sam?
I saw him at the computer earlier.
I knew he was up to something.
Oh is that right?
Pi you can't believe him over me.
He's an ignorant child.
OK then what's this?
Uh I'm not...
I don't know what is. I've never seen that before.
- It's your USB key sir. - Please Karl don't speak.
Sorry sir.
Ah! Hm. Security?
Can you give me playback of yesterday 19:49 hours of the main terminal?
Put it up in the Mission Control large screen.
Oh and security you might want to join us.
That won't be necessary.
Uh it's up on the big board now sir.
Good. Fast forward this.
Freeze frame!
Good now zoom in on that.
I...
Darn! Karl!
- Oh! - Security!
Take Dr. Finkel away.
Bye-bye Dr. Stinkel.
It's Finkel.
Finkel!
Faster than you can say "Fetch" it brings me great delight
to let you that this mission is back on track.
I have never been so hungry.
I think I might have to actually eat that broccoli to stay alive.
Budderball?
This is good.
Aw dude I can't believe you ate the whole thing.
Well I always said I'd eat broccoli when puppies fly.
What?
- Excuse me Mr. Slats sir? - Yeah.
What's that approaching to Vision One?
-  Warning! Warning!
- Aw snap it just doesn't stop!
Unidentified object approaching Vision One.
Whatever it is it's on a collision course with our spaceship.
- Take evasive action! Stat!
- Whoa whoa whoa whoa. OK.
It's the Cosmopod Yuri.
He's gonna crash into us.
- American comrades this is Yuri. - Is that Yuri?
He must have had an escape pod.
My Cosmopod is not irresponsible.
- Slats any ideas. - Negative sir.
The Russian pod is out of control.
It's entering the atmosphere
at a dangerous entry level at high speed.
It's pretty much an impossible rescue sir.
Yuri will burn up if you don't change his trajectory.
- I'm taking over. - Whoa I've lost control.
I'm going to have to dodge the Cosmopod to change it's course.
Let's do it dude. I mean comrade.
Hang on!
All right we've made contact.
It's crucial you level off the Cosmopod at 30 degrees.
Give me a countdown on re-entry. I'll pull up at the last second.
6  5  4
In six five four
three two one...
...activate thrusters.
Course corrected.
How did they know to level off
the Russian escape pod to those exact coordinates.
Eyes on scopes people.
Whoa!
You guys ready to go home?
Yo dawg I was born ready.
All right my friends I'm relinquishing controls.
Remote activated.
- Hey I got control back. -  Remote pilot engaged.
Well let's bring this puppy home. Uh puppies that is.
The re-entry sequence in three two one.
We've lost them in the blackout zone.
We won't have a visual for T-minus four minutes.
It's out of our hands.
Now uh we can't do anything but hope for the best.
The spacecraft has re-entered the atmosphere
and is now hurdling mercilessly towards Earth.
Communication is now in the blackout zone.
All of us here at Channel Four Fernfield
along with the world collectively hold our breath
as we watch anxiously awaiting a sign from the sky
that the puppies our space heroes
have survived the fiery re-entry into the Earth's atmosphere.
All we can do is pray.
Please protect Spudnick and his friends.
Stand by for reference.
- Re-entry successful. - OK we have visual people.
Buddies we did it!
Whoo!
Yeah!
See space travel ain't nothing.
Whoa!
What was that?
That was a sonic boom.
We just broke the sound barrier.
I knew that. I was just joshing you dawg.
Engaging landing sequence.
Good job Astro.
Touchdown whoo!
- Yes! - Yes!
- We're home! - Congratulations dogs.
You did it.
They made it! They made it!
Yes! They made it!
- They've done it! - Jolly good! Bravo! Bravo!
- Touchdown! - Way to go guys.
I have a feeling you and your furry friends had more to do
with this mission's success than we will ever know.
Come on come on.
Come on kids let's go greet the new heroes.
- Let's go. - Come on!
Yeah!
Here you go Gravity greet your new friends.
Welcome home Buddies. Spudnick that was some fancy
seat-of-the-pants aviation you demonstrated.
Whoa you're a ferret?
Yo dawg you mean to tell me
we had a rodent as our flight director?
Hey I'm not a rodent.
I'm related to the mustela family of mammals
which includes minks and skunks.
Hey I'm told I'm related to skunks too.
We couldn't have made it home without your help Gravity.
Thank you comrade.
Budderball.
Rosebud! Mudbud!
- B-Dawg! B-Dawg! - Namaste Buddha!
Hey! Oh I'm so happy you're home.
- Yeah. - B-Dawg! B-Dawg!
- Oh. - Yeah.
Oh and one last thing...
It seems a boy named Sasha is trying to contact you.
Really?
He's been waiting for you.
Oh hey hey. Oh.
Where am I? What?
Mother Russia.
How are you? Nice to see you. I come from space.
How are you?
This is more like it. I feel much prettier in pink.
Aw!
Uh thank you. Thank you for being here.
I would like to present wings
the symbol of true heroism in space...
...to our dogmonauts.
Here they are. The Space Buddies.
- Yeah! - Yeah!
Yeah
Yeah!
Ah! Rosebud.
Congratulations.
And B-Dawg.
Budderball.
Ah Mudbud.
I'm gonna miss Spudnick.
Spudnick is now officially part of my entourage.
I'll never forget he taught me to eat my vegetables.
He was a rad comrade.
He'll have a space in our hearts forever.
Spudnick!
I always dreamt I'd hold you in my arms again.
Aw.
Whoa.
This rock.
Is from the Moon?
I got to touch the Moon too.
I guess dreams really do come true.
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：1610169789
I fulfilled my dream of being the first dogmonaut to walk on the Moon.
But in returning home I realized it is the journey
and the new friendships I made that matter the most.