更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
Darkness.
That's the first thing I remember.
It was dark, and it was cold.
And I was scared.
But then,
then I saw the moon.
It was so big and it was so bright.
It seemed to chase the darkness away.
And when it did,
I wasn't scared anymore.
Why I was there and what I was meant to do,
that I've never known.
And a part of me wonders if I ever will.
Hello. Hello.
Good evening, ma'am. Ma'am?
Excuse me. Can you tell me where I am?
Hello?
My name is Jack Frost.
How do I know that?
The moon told me so.
But that was all he ever told me.
And that was a long, long time ago.
Still waiting for cookies!
Yes!
Finally!
How many times have I told you to knock?
What?
The Globe?
Shoo with your pointy heads.
Why are you always under boot?
What is this?
Have you checked the axis? Is rotation balanced?
Can it be?
Dingle!
Make preparations.
We are going to have company.
Eighteen central incisors.
Moscow, sector 9.
22 incisors, 18 premolars.
Heavy rain advisory.
Des Moines, we've got a cuspid at 23 Maple.
Head out!
Wait! It's her first tooth.
Have you ever seen a more adorable
lateral incisor in all of your life?
Look how she flossed.
My fellow Guardians,
it is ourjob to watch over the children of the world
and keep them safe.
To bring wonder, hope, and dreams.
And so I have called us all here
for one reason, and one reason only.
The children are in danger.
An enemy we have kept at bay for centuries
has finally decided to strike back.
We alone can stop him.
It's freezing!
I can't feel my feet! I can't feel my feet!
Cookies? Eggnog? Anyone?
This better be good, North.
Sandy, thank you for coming.
I know, I know.
But I obviously wouldn't have called you all here
unless it was serious.
The Boogeyman was here! At the Pole!
Pitch?
Pitch Black? Here?
Yes.
There was black sand covering the Globe.
What do you mean, black sand?
And then a shadow!
Hold on, hold on. I thought you said you saw Pitch.
Well, not exactly.
"Not exactly"? Can you believe this guy?
Yeah. You said it, Sandy.
Look, he's up to something very bad.
I feel it
in my belly.
Hang on, hang on.
You mean to say you summoned me here three days before Easter
because of your belly?
Mate,
if I did this to you three days before Christmas...
Please, Bunny.
Easter is not Christmas.
Here we go.
North, I don't have time for this!
I've still got two million eggs to finish up!
No matter how much you paint, is still egg.
Look, mate, I'm dealing with perishables.
Right? You've got all year to prepare!
Why are rabbits always so nervous?
And why are you always such a blowhard?
Tooth! Can't you see we're trying to argue?
Sorry.
Not all of us
get to work one night a year.
Am I right, Sandy?
San Diego, sector 2.
Come on, mate.
Pitch went out with the Dark Ages.
We made sure of it.
I know it was him. We have serious situation.
Well, I've got a serious situation with some eggs.
Man in Moon!
Sandy, why didn't you say something?
It's been a long time, old friend.
What is big news?
It is Pitch.
Manny, what must we do?
Guys, you know what this means?
He's choosing a new Guardian.
What? Why?
Must be big deal.
Manny thinks we need help.
Since when do we need help?
I wonder who it's gonna be!
Maybe the Leprechaun?
Please not the Groundhog, please not the Groundhog.
Jack Frost.
I take it back. The Groundhog's fine.
As long as he helps to protect the children.
Right?
Jack Frost? He doesn't care about children!
All right? All he does is freeze water pipes
and mess with my egg hunts!
All right? He's an irresponsible, selfish...
Guardian.
Jack Frost is many things,
but he is not a Guardian.
Now that, that was fun.
Wind!
Take me home.
Snow day!
It's freezing!
That looks interesting. Good book?
-All right! -Yeah!
-Snow day! -Snow day! Yeah.
You're welcome.
Guys, wait up!
Are you guys coming to the egg hunt Sunday?
Yeah! Free candy.
I hope we can find the eggs with all this snow!
It says here that
they found Bigfoot hair samples
and DNA in Michigan!
That's like super-close!
Here we go again.
You saw the video too, Claude.
He's out there.
That's what you said about aliens.
And the Easter Bunny!
The Easter Bunny is real.
He's real all right.
Real annoying,
real grumpy and really full of himself.
Come on! You guys will believe anything.
Easter Bunny, hop, hop, hop!
Mom, Sophie fell again!
You okay, Soph?
Jamie, hat.
We don't want Jack Frost nipping at your nose.
Who's Jack Frost?
No one, honey. It's just an expression.
"Who's Jack Frost?"
Okay, who threw that?
Well, it wasn't Bigfoot, kiddo.
Jamie Bennett, no fair!
You struck first!
Free-for-all!
All right, who needs ammo?
Look at that!
Crud! I hit Cupcake!
-She hit Cupcake. -You hit Cupcake?
-Did you throw that? -No.
It wasn't me!
A little slippery!
Jamie, watch out!
-That's the street! -Stop! There's traffic!
Don't worry, Jamie. I got you. Hold on!
It's gonna be all right!
Keep up with me, kid! Take a left!
Slow down!
Hold up. No, no, no, no.
Is that Jamie Bennett?
-There you go. -No, no!
-My gosh! -Yeah!
That looks serious.
Jamie, are you all right?
Did you guys see that? It was amazing!
I did a jump
and I slid under a...
Cool! A tooth!
-Dude, that means cash! -Tooth fairy cash!
-Oh, no! -You lucky bum!
I got to put this under my pillow!
Wait a minute. Come on. Hold on, hold on.
What about all the fun we just had?
That wasn't the Tooth Fairy, that was me!
My ears are freezing!
What's a guy got to do to get a little attention around here?
There was a patch of ice.
I don't understand how it got here.
I mean, Easter is around the corner!
...It was awesome!
So then I was flying down this hill
and it was like... through these cars
and then the sled hit this thing
and it was like way up in the air!
And then, bam, the sofa hit me...
...And see, my tooth came out!
All right, you. Tooth under your pillow?
Yeah, I'm ready.
Now don't stay up trying to see her, Jamie,
or she won't come.
But I can do it this time! You want to help me, Soph?
We can hide and see the Tooth Fairy!
Hide, hide, hide, hide.
Straight to bed now, mister.
Mom.
If there's something I'm doing wrong,
can you just tell me what it is?
Because I've tried everything
and no one ever sees me.
You put me here.
The least you can do is tell me...
Tell me why.
Right on time, Sandman.
I thought I heard the clippity-clop of a unicorn.
What an adorable dream!
And look at her.
Precious child.
So sweet.
So full of hope and wonder.
Why, there's only one thing missing.
A touch of fear.
That never gets old.
Feel your fear. Come on. Come on, that's right.
Yes, what a pretty little Nightmare!
Now,
I want you to go tell the others the wait is over.
Don't look at me like that, old friend.
You must have known this day would come.
My Nightmares are finally ready.
Are your Guardians?
Hello, mate.
Been a long time.
Blizzard of '68 I believe.
Easter Sunday, wasn't it?
Bunny! You're not still mad about that, are you?
Yes.
But this is about something else.
Fellas?
Put me down! What the...
Me?
Not on your nelly. See you back at the Pole.
He's here.
Quiet.
There he is!
Jack Frost!
You got to be kidding me.
-Put me down. -I hope the yetis treated you well.
I love being shoved in a sack and tossed through a magic portal.
Oh, good. That was my idea!
You know Bunny, obviously.
-Obviously. -And the Tooth Fairy.
Hello, Jack. I've heard a lot about you.
And your teeth!
My what?
Open up! Are they really as white as they say?
Yes!
They really do sparkle like freshly fallen snow!
Girls, pull yourselves together!
Let's not disgrace the uniform.
And Sandman.
Sandy?
Sandy? Wake up!
Anyone want to tell me why I'm here?
That's not really helping,
but thanks, little man.
I must've done something really bad
to get you four together.
Am I on the naughty list?
On naughty list?
You hold the record.
But, no matter. We overlook.
Now we are wiping clean the slate.
How come?
Good question.
How come? I tell you how come!
Because now
you are Guardian!
What are you doing? Get off of me!
This is the best part!
What makes you think I want to be a Guardian?
Of course you do.
Music!
No music!
This is all very flattering, but,
you don't want me.
You're all hard work and deadlines,
and I'm snowballs and fun times.
I'm not a Guardian.
Yeah. That's exactly what I said.
Jack, I don't think you understand what it is we do.
Each of those lights is a child.
A child who believes.
And good or bad, naughty or nice,
we protect them.
Tooth! Fingers out of mouth.
Sorry. They're beautiful.
Okay. No more wishy-washy.
Pitch is out there doing who knows what!
You mean the Boogeyman?
Yes! When Pitch threatens us,
he threatens them as well.
All the more reason to pick someone more qualified.
Pick? You think we pick?
No, you were chosen! Like we were all chosen.
By Man in Moon.
What?
Last night, Jack, he chose you.
Maybe.
Man in the Moon... He talks to you?
You see, you cannot say no.
It is destiny.
But why wouldn't he tell me that himself?
After 300 years this is his answer?
To spend eternity like you guys,
cooped up in some hideout thinking of new ways to bribe kids?
No, no. That's not for me! No offense.
How is that not offensive?
You know what I think?
I think we just dodged a bullet.
I mean, what's this clown
know about bringing joy to children anyway.
You ever hear of a snow day?
I know it's no hard-boiled egg,
but kids like what I do.
But none of them believe in you, do they?
You see, you're invisible, mate.
It's like you don't even exist.
Bunny! Enough.
No, the kangaroo's right.
The what? What did you call me?
I'm not a kangaroo, mate.
Oh, and this whole time I thought you were.
If you're not a kangaroo, what are you?
I'm a bunny. The Easter Bunny.
People believe in me.
Jack. Walk with me.
It's nothing personal, North.
But what you all do, it's just not my thing.
Man in Moon says it is your thing!
We will see.
Slow down, would you? I've been trying to bust in here for years.
-I want a good look. -What do you mean, bust in?
Don't worry. I never got past the yetis.
Hey, Phil.
Keep up, Jack, keep up!
I always thought the elves made the toys.
We just let them believe that.
Very nice! Keep up good work.
I don't like it! Paint it red!
Step it up, everybody!
Fruitcake?
No, thanks.
Now we get down to tacks of brass.
Tacks of...
Who are you, Jack Frost?
-What is your center? -My center?
If Man in Moon chose you to be a Guardian,
you must have something very special inside.
Here.
This is how you see me, no?
Very big, intimidating.
But if you get to know me a little...
Well, go on.
You are downright jolly?
But not just jolly!
I am also mysterious,
and fearless,
and caring!
And at my center?
There's a tiny wooden baby.
Look closer. What do you see?
You have big eyes.
Yes! Big eyes. Very big.
Because they are full of wonder.
That is my center.
It is what I was born with.
Eyes that have always seen the wonder in everything!
Eyes that see lights in the trees and magic in the air.
This wonder is what I put into the world!
And what I protect in children.
It is what makes me a Guardian.
It is my center.
What is yours?
I don't know.
We have a problem, mate.
Trouble at the Tooth Palace.
North! North!
I told you I'm not going with you guys!
There is no way I'm climbing into some rickety old...
...Sleigh?
Okay. One ride, but that's it.
Everyone loves the sleigh!
Bunny, what are you waiting for?
I think my tunnels might be faster, mate, and safer.
Get in!
Buckle up!
Where are the bloody seatbelts?
That was just expression. Are we ready?
Good. Let's go! Clear!
Out of the way!
Oh, no!
Slow down! Slow down!
I hope you like the loopty-loops.
I hope you like carrots.
Here we go!
Blastoff!
Bunny.
Check out this view.
North! He's...
You do care.
Rack off, you bloody show pony!
Hold on, everyone! I know a shortcut.
Strewth, I knew I should've taken the tunnels.
I say Tooth Palace.
What?
What are they?
They're taking the tooth fairies!
Little Baby Tooth, you okay?
Here, take over.
They're stealing the teeth!
Jack, look out!
Tooth! Are you all right?
They... They took my fairies.
And the teeth! All of them!
Everything is gone.
Everything.
Oh, thank goodness. One of you is all right.
I have to say, this is very, very exciting.
The Big Four, all in one place.
I'm a little starstruck.
Did you like my show on the Globe, North?
Got you all together, didn't I?
Pitch! You have got 30 seconds to return my fairies!
Or what?
You'll stick a quarter under my pillow?
Why are you doing this?
Maybe I want what you have.
To be believed in.
Maybe I'm tired of hiding under beds!
Maybe that's where you belong!
Go suck an egg, rabbit.
Hang on. Is that Jack Frost?
Since when are you all so chummy?
We're not.
Good. A neutral party.
Then I'm going to ignore you.
But you must be used to that by now.
Pitch, you shadow-sneaking ratbag, come here!
Hey! Easy, girl, easy.
Look familiar, Sandman?
Took me a while to perfect this little trick.
Turning dreams into Nightmares.
Don't be nervous.
It only riles them up more. They smell fear, you know.
What fear? Of you?
No one's been afraid of you since the Dark Ages!
The Dark Ages.
Everyone frightened. Miserable.
Such happy times for me.
The power I wielded.
But then the Man in the Moon
chose you to replace my fear with your wonder and light.
Lifting their hearts and giving them hope.
Meanwhile, everyone wrote me off as just a bad dream!
"There's nothing to be afraid of.
There's no such thing as the Boogeyman!"
Well, that's all about to change.
Look.
It's happening already.
What is?
Children are waking up and realizing
the Tooth Fairy never came.
I mean, such a little thing. But to a child...
What's going on?
They... They don't believe in me anymore.
Didn't they tell you, Jack?
It's great being a Guardian.
But there's a catch.
If enough kids stop believing,
everything your friends protect,
wonder, hopes and dreams, it all goes away.
And little by little, so do they.
No Christmas or Easter,
or little fairies that come in the night.
There will be nothing but fear and darkness.
And me.
It's your turn not to be believed in.
He's gone.
Okay, all right, I admit it.
You were right about Pitch.
I'm sorry about the fairies.
You should have seen them. They put up such a fight.
Why would Pitch take the teeth?
It's not the teeth he wanted.
It's the memories inside them.
What do you mean?
That's why we collect the teeth, Jack.
They hold the most important memories of childhood.
My fairies and I watch over them.
And when someone needs to remember what's important,
we help them.
We had everyone's here.
Yours, too.
My memories?
From when you were young.
Before you became Jack Frost.
But I wasn't anyone before I was Jack Frost.
Of course you were.
We were all someone before we were chosen.
What?
You should have seen Bunny.
I told you never to mention that!
The night at the pond, I just... I assumed...
Are you saying...
Are you saying I had a life before that,
with a home and a family?
You really don't remember?
All these years, the answers were right here.
If I find my memories,
then I'll know why I'm here.
You have to show me!
I can't, Jack. Pitch has them.
Then we have to get them back!
Oh, no.
The children!
We're too late!
No! No!
No such thing as too late!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Idea!
We will collect the teeth.
What?
We get teeth, children keep believing in you!
We're talking seven continents and millions of kids!
Give me break.
You know how many toys I deliver in one night?
And eggs I hide in one day?
And, Jack, if you help us,
we will get you your memories.
I'm in.
Quickly! Quickly!
Hop to it, rabbit! I'm five teeth ahead!
Yeah, right. Look, I'd tell you to stay out of my way,
but, really, what's the point?
'Cause you won't be able to keep up anyway.
Is that a challenge, cottontail?
You don't want to race a rabbit, mate.
A race? Is it a race?
This is going to be epic!
Four bicuspids over there!
An incisor two blocks east.
Is that a molar? They're everywhere!
You okay?
I'm fine. Sorry.
It's been a really long time since I've been out in the field.
How long is a long time?
440 years, give or take.
Twins!
Jackpot!
Looks like you're a bit of a brumby,mate?
Is piece of pie.
That's my tooth! Sandy! Sandy!
Take it easy there, champ.
He's one of us! Part of the European division.
Crikey!
Yes!
No!
Wow! You guys collect teeth and leave gifts
as fast as my fairies.
You guys have been leaving gifts, right?
The lights.
Why aren't they going out?
They're collecting the teeth?
Pipe down or I'll stuff a pillow with you!
Fine. Have your last hurrah.
For tomorrow,
all your pathetic scrambling will be for nothing.
Left central incisor,
knocked out in a freak sledding accident.
I wonder how that could've happened, Jack.
Kids?
This was always the part I liked most.
Seeing the kids.
Why did I ever stop doing this?
It's a little different up close, huh?
Thanks for being here, Jack.
I wish I'd known about your memory.
I could have helped you.
Yeah...
Look, let's just get you taken care of.
Then it's Pitch's turn.
Here you are!
What gives, slowpokes?
How you feeling, Toothy?
Believed in.
That's what I want to hear.
I see how it is. All working together
to make sure the rabbit gets last place.
You think I need help to beat a bunny?
Check it out, Peter Cottontail.
You call that a bag of choppers?
Now that's a bag of choppers.
Gentlemen, gentlemen. This is about Tooth.
It's not a competition.
But if it was, I win!
Oh, no.
Santa Claus?
The Easter Bunny?
Sandman?
The Tooth Fairy! I knew you'd come!
Surprise! We came.
He can see us?
Most of us.
You guys, he's still awake.
Sandy, knock him out.
With the Dreamsand, you gumbies!
No, stop! That's the Easter Bunny!
What are you doing, Abbey? Down!
All right, nobody panic.
But that's a greyhound.
Do you know what greyhounds do to rabbits?
I think it's a pretty safe bet he's never met a rabbit like me.
Six-foot-one,
nerves of steel.
Master of tai-chi and the ancient art of...
Stop! Sit!
Down, girl, down!
Sandy!
She's rabid! Get this dingo off me!
Oh, no.
Candy canes...
I really wish I had a camera right now.
Sandy, come on! We can find Pitch!
Pretty.
Bunny, hop, hop, hop!
What...
Yes!
I got it.
Sandy!
Sandy, did you see that?
Look at this thing.
Frost?
You know, for a neutral party,
you spend an awful lot of time with those weirdos.
This isn't your fight, Jack.
You made it my fight when you stole those teeth!
Teeth? Why do you care about the teeth?
Now this is who I'm looking for.
Remind me not to get on your bad side.
Okay, easy. You can't blame me for trying, Sandy.
You don't know what it's like to be weak and hated.
It was stupid of me to mess with your dreams.
So, I'll tell you what.
You can have them back.
You take the ones on the left,
I'll take the ones on the right?
Come on!
You might want to duck.
We've got to help Sandy!
No!
Jack!
Don't fight the fear, little man!
Hurry! Hurry, Jack!
I'd say "Sweet dreams,"
But there aren't any left.
Sandy?
No!
Jack!
Jack, how did you do that?
I didn't know I could.
Finally!
Someone who knows how to have a little fun!
Are you all right?
I just...
I wish I could've done something.
Done something?
Jack, you stood up to Pitch.
You saved us!
But Sandy...
Would be proud of what you did.
I don't know who you were in your past life.
But in this life, you are Guardian.
But how can I know who I am until I find out who I was?
You will.
I feel it
in my belly.
Look how fast they're going out.
It's fear.
He's tipped the balance.
Hey, buck up, you sad sacks!
We can still turn this around!
Easter is tomorrow.
And I need your help.
I say we pull out all the stops
and we get those little lights flickering again.
Bunny is right.
As much as it pains me to say, old friend,
this time, Easter is more important than Christmas.
Hey, did everyone hear that?
We must hurry to the warren.
Everyone! To the sleigh!
No, mate. My warren, my rules.
Buckle up.
Shostakovich!
"Buckle up." Is very funny.
Welcome to the warren.
Something's up.
Sophie?
-Elf, elf, elf! -What is she doing here?
Snow globe.
Somebody do something.
Don't look at me. I'm invisible, remember?
Elf! Elf!
Don't worry, Bunny. I bet she's a fairy fan.
-It's okay, little one. -Pretty.
You know what? I've got something for you!
Here it is!
Look at all the pretty teeth,
with little blood and gum on them!
Blood and gums?
When was the last time
you guys actually hung out with kids?
Peek-a-boo!
We are very busy bringing joy to children.
We don't have time...
For children.
If one little kid can ruin Easter,
then we're in worse shape than I thought.
You want to paint some eggs? Yeah?
-Okay. -Come on.
Rimsky-Korsakov!
That's a lot of eggs.
How much time do we have?
All right, troops, it's time to push back.
That means eggs everywhere!
Heaps of you in every high-rise,
farmhouse, and trailer park!
In tennis shoes and cereal bowls.
Oh, there will be bathtubs filled with my beautiful googies!
Okay, that's a little strange.
No, mate.
That's adorable.
There will be springtime! On every continent!
And I'm bringing hope with me!
Too Christmas-y, mate. Paint them blue.
What's over there?
That's a beauty!
Now, all we got to do is get him and his little mates
through the tunnels to the top
and we'll have ourselves Easter.
Not bad.
Not bad yourself.
Look, I'm sorry about the whole...
You know, the kangaroo thing.
It's the accent, isn't it?
Poor little ankle-biter. Look at her. All tuckered out.
I love her.
I think it's time to get her home.
How about I take her home?
Jack, no. Pitch is...
No match for this.
Which is why we need you here with us.
Trust me. I'll be quick as a bunny.
Sophie? Is that you?
We should get back.
Jack!
That voice, I know that voice.
Don't worry, there's still time.
Jack?
Baby Tooth, come on!
I have to find out what that is.
Keep it down!
I'm gonna get you out of here just as soon as...
Jack?
Jack!
...As I can.
Looking for something?
Don't be afraid, Jack. I'm not gonna hurt you.
Afraid? I'm not afraid of you.
Maybe not. But you are afraid of something.
-You think so, huh? -I know so!
It's the one thing I always know.
People's greatest fears.
Yours is that no one will ever believe in you.
And worst of all,
you're afraid you'll never know why.
Why you?
Why were you chosen to be like this?
Fear not.
For the answer to that is right here.
Do you want them, Jack? Your memories?
Everything you wanted to know, in this little box.
Why did you end up like this? Unseen.
Unable to reach out to anyone.
You want the answers so badly.
You want to grab them and fly off with them.
But you're afraid of what the Guardians will think.
You're afraid of disappointing them.
Let me ease your mind about one thing.
They'll never accept you. Not really.
Stop it! Stop it!
After all, you're not one of them.
You don't know what I am.
Of course I do! You're Jack Frost.
You make a mess wherever you go.
Why, you're doing it right now.
What did you do?
More to the point, Jack, what did you do?
Baby Tooth!
Happy Easter, Jack.
No.
There aren't any eggs.
-There's nothing here. -I give up.
-He didn't come. -I don't understand.
Maybe he just hid them really well this year.
-Kids! -I checked everywhere.
There's nothing.
Yes, there is! There is!
I mean, these aren't my best looking googies,
but they'll do in a pinch.
I can't believe it.
I know.
There's no such thing as the Easter Bunny.
What? No.
Wrong! Not true!
I'm right in front of you, mate.
Why wouldn't he come?
They don't see me.
Jack, where were you?
The Nightmares attacked the tunnels.
They smashed every egg, crushed every basket.
Nothing made it to the surface.
Jack.
Where did you get that?
I was... Lt's...
Where's Baby Tooth?
Jack, what have you done?
That is why you weren't here?
You were with Pitch?
No, listen, listen.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean for this to happen.
-He has to go. -What?
We should never have trusted you!
Easter is new beginnings, new life.
Easter's about hope.
And now it's gone.
Let's check the park again.
-Really? -For what? The Easter Bunny?
Guys, I told you, I saw him!
He's way bigger than I thought
and he's got these cool boomerang things!
Grow up, Jamie.
Oh, man. Seriously?
What's happened to you guys?
It was a dream!
You should be happy you still get dreams like that
and not...
Nightmares.
Forget it, Jamie.
There's just no Easter this year.
He really is real!
I know he is.
I thought this might happen.
They never really believed in you.
I was just trying to show you that.
But I understand.
You don't understand anything!
No? I don't know what it's like to be cast out?
To not be believed in?
To long for a family.
All those years in the shadows I thought
no one else knows what this feels like.
But now I see I was wrong.
We don't have to be alone, Jack.
I believe in you. And I know children will, too.
In me?
Yes!
Look at what we can do.
What goes together better than cold and dark?
We can make them believe.
We'll give them a world where everything, everything is...
Pitch black?
And Jack Frost, too.
They'll believe in both of us.
No, they'll fear both of us.
And that's not what I want.
Now for the last time,
leave me alone.
Very well. You want to be left alone.
Done. But first...
Baby Tooth!
The staff, Jack!
You have a bad habit of interfering.
Now, hand it over, and I'll let her go.
All right.
Now let her go.
No.
You said you wanted to be alone.
So be alone!
No!
Baby Tooth!
You all right?
Sorry. All I can do is keep you cold.
Pitch was right.
I make a mess of everything.
Jack?
Jack!
Come on, Jack,
you can't have fun all the time.
Jack, get down from there.
-Jack! -You're funny, Jack.
Be careful.
We will.
It's okay. It's okay.
Don't look down. Just look at me.
Jack.
I'm scared.
I know. I know.
But you're gonna be all right. You're not gonna fall in.
We're gonna have a little fun instead!
No, we're not!
Would I trick you?
Yes! You always play tricks!
Well, not this time.
I promise, I promise. You're gonna be...
You're gonna be fine.
You have to believe in me.
You want to play a game? We're gonna play hopscotch!
Like we play every day.
It's as easy as
one...
Two.
Three!
All right.
Now it's your turn.
One...
That's it, that's it.
Two.
Three!
Jack!
Did you see... Did you see that?
It was me!
I had a family! I had a sister!
I saved her!
That's why you chose me.
I'm a Guardian.
We have to get out of here.
Okay.
Come on, Baby Tooth, I owe you one!
Come on! Let's go!
What's wrong?
None of you can fly?
The lights.
You're all free to go!
We won't be needing any Christmas toys this year,
thank you.
Nor ever again.
They're all going out.
Only six left.
Six precious children
who still believe in the Guardians with all their hearts.
Make that
five.
Four.
Three!
Two!
One.
Jamie.
Okay, look,
you and I are obviously at what they call a crossroads.
So here's what's gonna happen.
If it wasn't a dream and if you are real
then you have to prove it, like, right now.
I've believed in you for a long time, okay?
Like, my whole life, in fact.
So you kind of owe me now.
You don't have to do much.
Just a little sign so I know.
Anything.
Anything at all.
I knew it.
He's real!
Snow?
Jack Frost.
Did he just say...
Jack Frost?
He said it again. He said...
You said...
Jack Frost!
That's right!
But that's me! Jack Frost! That's my name!
You said my name!
Wait. Can you hear me?
Can you... Can you see me?
He sees me! He sees me!
-You just made it snow! -I know!
-In my room! -I know!
-You're real? -Yeah!
Who do you think brings you all the blizzards and the snow days?
And you remember when you went flying on that sled the other day?
-That was you? -That was me!
-Cool! -Right?
But what about the Easter Bunny? And the Tooth Fairy?
Real, real, real! Every one of us is real.
-I knew it! -Jamie, who are you talking to?
Jack Frost?
Okay.
Come back!
-North, are you okay? -Is official.
My powers are kaput.
Look!
Jack!
Are you okay?
What are you doing here?
Same as you.
The last light.
It is you! I mean, it is you!
I knew it wasn't a dream!
Jack, he sees you.
Wait. But where's Bunny?
Losing Easter took its toll on all of us.
Bunny most of all.
No.
That's the Easter Bunny?
Now somebody sees me!
Where were you about an hour ago, mate?
What happened to him?
He used to be huge and cool. And now he's...
Cute.
That's good.
Did you tell him to say that? That's it!
Let's go! Me and you! Come on!
No. Actually, he told me you were real.
Just when I started to think that maybe you weren't.
He made you believe?
In me?
Get Jamie out of here.
Be careful, Jack.
Jack Frost.
Let's end this, shall we?
That little trick doesn't work on me anymore.
This way, this way.
Dead end. Other way, other way!
Jack!
That was good try, Jack. "A" For effort.
He's stronger. I can't beat him.
All this fuss over one little boy,
and still he refuses to stop believing.
Very well.
There are other ways to snuff out a light.
If you want him, you're gonna have to go through me.
Look how fluffy you are.
Would you like a scratch behind the ears?
Don't you even think about it.
I can't tell you how happy it makes me to see you all like this.
You look awful.
Jack. I'm scared.
I know, I know.
But you're gonna be all right.
We're gonna have a little fun instead.
That's it! That's my center!
So what do you think, Jamie?
Do you believe in the Boogey...
Now let's go get your friends.
Cool!
Jamie, how are you doing that?
Jack Frost!
Come on, we need your help!
Is that...
Jack Frost!
-Merry Christmas! -Happy Easter!
Don't forget to floss!
-Cupcake? -What?
Jamie, you were right!
The Easter Bunny's real!
-The Tooth Fairy! -And Santa!
They're all real!
You think a few children can help you? Against this?
They're just bad dreams, Jamie.
And we'll protect you, mate.
You'll protect them?
But who will protect you?
I will.
-I will. -I will.
And me.
I'll try.
Still think there's no such thing as the Boogeyman?
I do believe in you. I'm just not afraid of you.
Yeah, Tooth Fairy!
No! Get them!
Do your jobs!
Yeah, come on, come on.
Crikey!
No way!
I'm just a bunny!
G'day, mate.
Come on!
Let's get them!
Come on, guys, we can do it!
It's all yours, mate.
Thanks, Tooth.
Wrong roof.
Look at that!
I got it!
I know what we have to do.
Guys, come on.
It's over, Pitch.
There's no place to hide.
Jack, look out!
The Sandman!
Mate, you are a sight for sore eyes.
Pretty!
Your center?
It took a while,
but I figured it out.
You're all on naughty list!
Bunny, think fast!
No.
You dare have fun in my presence?
I am the Boogeyman and you will fear me!
No! No.
Leaving the party so soon?
You didn't even say goodbye.
A quarter?
And that's for my fairies.
You can't get rid of me! Not forever.
There will always be fear.
So what? As long as one child believes,
we will be here to fight fear.
Really? Then what are they doing here?
They can't be my Nightmares. I'm not afraid.
Looks like it's your fear they smell.
No, no, no. No!
No!
Are you ready now, Jack?
To make it official.
Then is time you take Oath.
Will you, Jack Frost,
vow to watch over the children of the world,
to guard them with your life,
their hopes, their wishes, and their dreams,
for they are all that we have, all that we are,
and all that we will ever be?
I will.
Then, congratulations, Jack Frost, for you are now,
and forevermore,
a Guardian.
That's my boy.
Keep it together, girls.
You guys, look!
- That's Santa's sleigh. - It's real!
You guys see that?
Everyone loves the sleigh.
Look at that!
Time to go.
It's beautiful.
Happy Easter, you little ankle-biter.
I'm gonna miss you.
Bye-bye, Bunny.
You're leaving?
But what if Pitch comes back?
What if we stop believing again?
If I can't see you...
Slow down, slow down.
You're telling me you stop
believing in the moon when the sun comes up?
No.
Okay. Do you stop believing in the sun
when clouds block it out?
No.
We'll always be there, Jamie. And now,
we'll always be here.
Which kind of makes you a Guardian, too.
Jack!
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：1610169789
My name is Jack Frost.
And I'm a Guardian.
How do I know that?
Because the moon told me so.
So when the moon tells you something,
believe it.