更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
This is a tale about an unprejudiced heart...
and how it changed our valley forever.
There was a time not so long ago...
when pigs were afforded no respect except by other pigs.
They lived their whole lives in a cruel and sunless world.
In those days, pigs believed
that the sooner they grew large and fat,
the sooner they'd be taken into pig paradise.
Haa! Haa! Get up!
A place so wonderful...
that no pig had ever thought to come back.
Yo. Yeah!
Good-bye, Mom.
So when the day came for their parents
to go to that other world of endless pleasures,
it was not a time for young pigs to be sad.
Just another step towards the day when they, too,
would make the journey.
perhaps it was because he was alone.
Perhaps his sadness made him easier to catch.
Whatever the reason, of the thousands of animals
in the piggery that day... only one was chosen.
How's this one, Harry?
Just right for the purpose. How much do I owe you?
It's a runt Harry. A worthless, little runt.
You're too modest, Esme Hoggett.
Nine out of 10 first prizes forjams and jellies... .
is more than a matter of luck
Luck still plays its part.
Our berries were wickedly good this year.
And our water is very tasty too.
Of course, we don't use the town water.
Arthur Hoggett! How's it going, Arthur?
How are those sheep of yours?
Come on, try your luck.
How about taking a guess, Arthur?
All for a good cause.
Don't keep pigs.
Christmas day. Think of it. What a feast!
That'll do, Pig.
The pig and the farmer regarded each other.
And fora fleeting moment, something passed between them.
A faint sense of some common destiny.
Hah. Strange.
First time the little thing hasn't screamed its head off.
Now you'll have to have a guess.
Sixteen pounds, five...
Eew.
Two ounces.
Hooey! Hoggett!
Thanks, Arthur.
We'll be weighing the little pig tomorrow.
We'll phone you if you win.
When you win, Arthur. When you win!
Care to guess the pig's weight, Sir?
Support the Lion's Club.
What could we do with a pig, eh, Duchess?
Just think. Two nice hams. Two sides of bacon.
Oh, and pork chops, kidney, liver,
chitlins, pickle his feet.
Save his blood for bLack puddin.
There's the telephone. Hoggett!
Hoggett! Good news, Arthur. You've won the pig.
Oh.
Pigs Are Definitely Stupid.
What is it, Mom?
That's a pig.
They'll eat him when he's big.
Will they eat us?
Good heavens, no!
The bosses only eat stupid animals...
like sheep and ducks and chickens.
Yea!
It does look stupid, Mom.
Not as stupidas sheep, mind you.
But pigs are definitely stupid.
Excuse me. No, we're not.
Good heavens! Who are you?
I'm a Large White.
Yes, that's your breed, dear.
What's your name?
I don't know.
What did your mother call you to tell you apart
from your brothers and sisters?
Our mom called us all the same.
And what was that, dear?
She called us all Babe.
Perhaps we shouldn't talk too much about,
uh, family.
I want my mom.
There, there.
You've got to be a brave boy now.
I left my mother when I was your age,
and my pups will have to leave me soon.
But I'll keep an eye on you, if you like,
just 'til you find your feet.
The little pig's a bit low.
He's going to sleep with us...
just 'til he finds his feet.
Until he finds his feet.
But, Mom, he'll wet the bed!
Nonsense!
If you do want to do anything,
you'll go out side, won't you?
Good boy.
Yea! Yeah! Yeah! Stomp on him!
What's your name, Pig?
What does he taste like?
Where did he come from?
Comin' through! Hey, get lost!
We've got to do something about that duck.
Ooh! Ooh!
Doodle loo dee doo.
What's that noise?
It's only Ferdinand.
What's Ferdinand?
He's a duck.
He wants to be a rooster.
He hates being a duck.
We'll catch him one day and eat him.
Won't we, Mom?
Yes, dear.
Yech! Who'd want to eat a duck?
Babe, you wait here.
Aren't pigs allowed?
Not live ones.
Sorry, dear.
Only dogs and cats inside the house.
Why?
That's just the way things are.
Whoa!
- Ow!  - Pig pig piggy!
Ooh, what a spectacular feast I've got for you.
Oh, yes! What a lucky little pork chop you are.
Delicious! Oh, yes! Yum, yum, yum.
Who's gonna grow up to be a big, fat pig?
You are! You are! Yum, yum, yum.
Where are we going?
To workwith the sheep.
What's sheep?
Sheep is animals with thick, woolly coats.
And thickwoolly heads.
And men can't look after them without us
Why do they need us?
'Cause we're sheepdogs! Yea!
Not you, dear.
Why not?
We have to do dogs' work.
You're a pig.
Your job is to stay here and eat your food.
We'll be back at the end of the day.
They don't think I'll remember.
Well, I don't forget.
Seems like a sheep's just born to suffer.
Hello? Excuse me.
Darn wolf!
I 'm not a wolf. I 'm a pig. What are you?
Ewe.
Pig. What are you?
I'm a ewe. A ewe!
You're a sheep!
I'll not be calleda common sheep, thank you kindly.
I'm a Border Leicester ewe. The name's Maa.
What's wrong with you, Maa?
Foot rot. And I got me a nasty cough.
And I'm not as young as I used to be.
Seem like a nice young pig. What beyour name?
Babe.
Not like them wolves. Treat you like dirt, they do!
Bite you as soon as look at you, those savages!
Bite you?
And worse.
Some wolves be so bad,
they run a sheep down and tear it to pieces.
Fly would never do that!
Fly, is it? A right vicious creature she be,
I'll tell you.
Not Fly.
all them wolves is cruel to sheep.
Always have been.
Brutal savages! That's what they be.
I wouldn't want to see a gentle soul like you
mixin' with the likes of them.
That afternoon when he saw Fly,
the pig's mind was a tangle of questions.
cruel, vicious, brutal?
What was it that dogs did in the fields all day?
Hello, Babe? Had a good day?
Yes, thank you.
The old sheep had to be wrong about Fly.
And the pig promised himself that
he would never think badly ofany creature ever again.
The morning ofthe terrible crime...
started like any other on Hoggett Farm.
Comin' through! Comin' through! Take off!
I was worried it might have a harsh tone,
but that's quite a nice musical ring.Don't you think?
I walked into O'halloran's Hardware,
and there it was waiting for me.
What a splendid way towake up each morning!
Hoggett, dear. Church.
When embarking on an audacious crime,
a duck needs a willing accomplice.
A creature who is reliable, beyond suspicion,
and above all... extremely gullible.
- Hey! Psst!  - Wha... what?
You look like an intelligent, sophisticated,
- discerning young fella?  - Who, me?
Yeah. Follow me.
Oh, boy! Are you in for some fun!
What are we doin'?  Where are we goin'?
Now the duck knew exactly what he had to do.
The alarm clock had to go.
His very life depended on it.
Do you see it?
Yes
Good.
So I go through the kitchen, across the living room...
- Good, good.  - into the bedroom.
Get the mechanical rooster
and bring it out to you.
What about that cat?
But quietly bring it out to you.
Excellent.
I don't think I can do it.
It's against the rules.
Only dogs and cats allowed in the house.
It's a good rule, but this is bigger than rules.
This is life and death.
It is?
Mm-hmm. Follow me.
Hello!
Look, there's something you should know.
Humans eat ducks!
I beg your pardon?
Most ducks prefer to forget it,
but the fact is that humans like to eat plump ducks
I don't think so. Not the boss. Not the boss's wife.
Come on. Humans don't eat cats. Why?
- Well, they're...  - They're indispensable.
They catch mice. Humans don't eat roosters. Why?
They make eggs with the hens and wake everyone up in the morning.
I tried it with the hens.
It didn't work. So I turned to crowing,
and Lo! I discover my gift.
But no sooner do I become indispensable then
they bring in a machine to do the job!
Ah, the treachery of it!  A mechanical rooster!
Oh, dear me.
Oh, dear you?
I suppose the life of an anorexic duck...
doesn't amount to much in the broad scheme of things.
But, pig, I'm all I've got.
Why do you need me to do it?
- I'm allergic to cats.  - Oh.
They make me sneeze.
Ahh.
Don't worry. I won't wake the cat.
My life is in your hands.
Oh, dear.
Oh, no!
Ah, boy.
No, no, no!
Your foot, your foot! Take the string off your foot.
Wait, wait. Let me put it this way.
Stop. Turn around...
Shh.
No, no! The otherway! Turn...
No, stop! Oh! Stop! Stop, stop, stop!
Don't, don't, stupid. Go outside... now.
But you said you can't do without me.
I can. Trust me, I can.
Are you sure?
- Yes!  - You're positive?
Go outside andstand guard.
Okay. Good idea.
Oh, boy. Want something done, you gotta do it yourself.
- Hmm. - Guard against what?
Ahh! Ahh! Don't worry
Stick with me and please,
I beg you, not one more word.
all right.
Don't sneeze, Ferdie.
just hold your breath.
It was my mistake.
I was trying to loosen things up a little.
But, no. Today proves that it doesn't work.
From now on, we'll all respect the rules.
To each creature its own destiny.
Every animal in its proper place.
And a pig's proper place is under the old cart,
not in the barn.
And absolutely never in the house.
Is that understood?
Yes, sir.
Now, Pig, regarding the company you keep.
Being young, it's hard to discriminate,
so I'll make it easy for you.
I forbid you to talk to or consort with...
that duck... ever.
Have I made myself clear?
Uh... what's " consort" ?
It means, young man, that you must not go
anywhere near that duck.
As for the fugitive duck,
when he shows himself, let him know this
Being a duck he must behave like a duck.
No more of this crowing and nonsense.
He should accept what he is and be thankful for it.
- That goes for all of us.  - Here, here!
Rex continued long into the night.
Elsewhere, there was more talk.
The subject was christmas dinner...
and whether that year the main course would be roast pork.
or duck a l'orange.
And pork is a nice, sweet meat.
Get him!
Get the pig! Get the pig! Get the pig!
- psst! -  Ferdinand! Everyone's been looking for you.
What is this place?
What's happenin' out there?
Rex isn't very happy. Boy, all these new rules!
I'm not allowed to... oops.
Not allowed to what?
Huh?
Pig pig pig piggy!
You didn't see me, all right?
And I didn't see you. all right? Oops.
The time comes forall creatures... when childhood ends...
and the doorway opens to life as an adult.
And so it was with Fly's pups.
Though that time was all too soon for Fly.
Puppy, puppy, puppy. Come on.
Fly?
May I call you Mom?
And so it was that the pig...
found his place in the world of the farm.
And he was happy, even in his dreams.
- Hello!  - Folks, how are you?. Merry Christmas!
How's my favorite girl?
Nanny's got a jelly bean.
Guess what we're having for Christmas dinner?
Roast pork.
I hate pork.
Darn silly carry-on, if you ask me.
The cats says they call it Christmas.
Christmas! Christmas dinner, yeah.
Dinner means death. Death means carnage!
Christmas means carnage!
Eatin' pigs! Blaah! Barbarians!
You're goin' back to the fields, Maa.
Oh, young'un, tragic there ain't more of your kind.
I'll be thinkin' of ya always.
I could come visit you. Maa
I'd like that, but...
Well, we shouldn't hope for too much. Ooh!
And so, it was christmas Eve.
And time had run out for the pig.
Are you doing him tonight then?.
- Mmm.  - Good. The blood'll drain by morning.
Pity
What's that?
Nothin'.
What on earth are you babbling on about?.
Shame to miss out on the best ham prize at next year's fair, is all
Nice plump haunches he's gettin'. Beautiful.
Still... silly to wait, I suppose.
Here it is!
The bird. Yuck. Chicken?
No, it's duck a l'orange.
And, Mother, it looks absolutely superb.
- I'm not going to eat any of it!  - This is fabulous.
Ferdinand!
If you're out here, who's that in there?
Her name's Rosanna.
Why Rosanna? She had such a beautiful nature.
Oh, Ferdinand.
I can't take it anymore.
Really!
The fear's too much for a duck.
It eats away at the soul.
There must be kinder dispositions
in far-off gentler lands.
The only way you'll find happiness is to accept...
that the way things are is the way things are.
The way things are stinks!
I'm not gonna be a goner. I'm gone.
I wish all of you the best of luck.
Where will you go?
No idea. But I'm a clever duck.
I could do with an adventure.
I'll miss you, Ferdie.
Ferdie? No one's ever called me that before.
Hey, good luck, Pig. Huh?. I am outta here.
Bye, bye.
Ow! Would you do me a favor, Pig?
Anything.
Open the gate, huh?
The pig knew it was against
the rules to leave the farm.
But something was definitely wrong.
How lovely, darling. What is it?.
It's a fax machine.
You can send us letters by phone.
At any other time,the pig would've been tickled pink...
by his first visit to the sheep fields
But now there was fear in the air.
Maa and her kind were under threat.
Hey, Frank, feel like pork for dinner tonight?
Young'un, you're alive!
What's happening?. Who are these men?
I'll get him out. Come around, Sniff!
Where's our boss?. It doesn't seem right
What's wrong, dear?. It's the wrong one!
I want the house I saw on the television!
Oh, there, there.
Get! Quick! Get the dog in.
Out of the sheep! come on!
Let's go!
Good dog.
Good pig.
Hey, hey. Dad says his little porker's a watch pig.
Dearie me! If it's not a duck
that thinks it's a rooster,
it's a pig that thinks it's a dog!
A pig that thinks it's a dog!
# BLue Moon You saw me standing alone #
A washing machine, a radio, a new alarm clock.
I think it's a lovely fax machine, darling,
but can't you use it?
We already have one, Mom. That's the whole idea.
We can send faxes to each other.
Don't be afraid of it just because it's new.
These accounts are a real worry, Arthur.
Every month your expenditure is greater than your income.
It's eating up your reserves.
You need to modernize, get some sort of cash rlow going.
You're still using a horse and cart,for God's sakes.
Dad?
Funny, that.
What?
Those chickens, that pig.
What's the pig got to do with anything?
Nothing.
Just look at them. The browns and the whites.
Come, Rex. Come, Fly
Come, Pig.
Come, Pig!
Perhaps he's pleased with you
- for what you did yesterday.  - I didn't do much
Well if it wasn't for you, dear,
they could've stolen the whole rlock.
Is Rex unhappy with me?
Oh, he'll be all right.
just stay out of his way today.
Way to be, Fly. Rex, come by.
That'll do.
You're so quick.
I'd never be able to rly like you can.
Pigs aren't built to rly, dear.
But speed isn't the thing. It's attitude.
They just have to know who's boss.
Out you go.
Mmm!
Get 'em up, Pig.
He wants you to drive them out of the yard.
Away to me, Pig.
Remember, you have to dominate them.
Do that and they'll do any thing you want. Go.
Woof! Woof, woof, woof!
Woof, woof, woof!
This is ridiculous, Mom.
Nonsense. It's only your first try.
But you're treating them like equals.
They're sheep. They're inferior.
Ah, no they're not.
Of course they are!
We are their masters.
Let them doubt it for a second and they'll walk all over you.
Fly, get that pig out of there.
Make them feel inferior. Abuse them. Insult them.
But they'll laugh at me.
Then bite them. Be ruthless.
Whatever it takes. Bend them to your will.
- Enough! - Go on! Go!
move along there, you... You, uh, big butt heads!
Young'un, stop this nonsense. What's got into you?
I just finished tellin' what a nice young pig you be.
Maa, I was just trying to be a sheep dog.
Hah! Enough wolves in the world already...
without a nice lad like you turnin' nasty.
You haven't got it in ya, young'un.
You and I are descended from the great sheepdogs.
We carry the bloodline of the Ancient Bahou.
We stand for something.
And today I watched in shame as all that was betrayed.
Rex, he's just a little pig.
all the greater the insult.
I'm sorry I bit you. Are you all right?.
I wouldn't call that a bite, myself.
You got teeth in that rloppy mouth or just gums?
You see, ladies, a heart of gold.
Ahh. Heart of gold.
No need for all this wolf nonsense, young'un.
all a nice pig like you need do is ask.
Thanks very much. It was very kind of you.
A pleasure. What a nice little pig!
all right, how did you do it?
I asked them, and they did it. I asked them nicely.
We don't ask sheep, dear. We tell them what to do.
I did, Mom. They were really friendly.
Maybe Rex might be a little more friendly if l had a talk with him.
No, no, no. You better leave that to me.
Rex?
I knowit was hard for you today...
watching all that happening.
But surely it's not worth all this misery.
Please, dear, not on such a beautiful night.
You put these ideas into his head!
Two-faced traitorous wret...
Get down! Down, Rex. Fly!
A dark cloud had descended on the valley.
And the pig felt that the troubles were all his fault.
But he was certain
that he knew how to put things right again.
Oh, uh, e... excuse me, Sir.
But I... I... I think all this trouble...
Well, it's not distemper. can't be rabies.
Must be the hormones.
What about Hoggett's notion, the dog jealous of the wee pig?
I don't see that myself.
No. So what should we do?
You can keep him locked up or... snip, snip.
I can do it Tuesday.
No.
Or Wednesday.
Hoggett doesn't want the dog operated on.
He's a breeding dog.
I can sedate him, of course, but
he'll be useless as a working dog.
I'll give you pills to put in his food.
Good dog.
The Sheep Pig.
A pig doing the work of a sheepdog?
With Rex out of action and Fly injured from the fight,
Farmer Hoggett had no choice.
Maa! Maa! The boss has to give you some medicine.
Oh, dear, I thought so! It's horrible stuff, that.
I know, but it's for the best.
Young'un, if you say so.
When the thought first came to him,
Farmer Hoggett dismissed it as mere whimsy.
But, like most of his harebrained ideas,
it wouldn't go away.
What are they doing?
It's a sheepdog trial.
So it's like a competition for sheepdogs?
And their bosses. It's like an obstacle course.
How do they decide who wins?
It's time and mistakes.
You get points for how quick you are.
And they take points off for every mistake.
Everytime a sheep goes the wrong way,
that's a mistake and you lose points.
Looks like fun!
For a sheepdog, there's no prouder moment.
Rex and I used to...
Never mind.
Was Rex a champion?
He had the makings of the greatest champion there ever was,
but it wasn't to be.
What happened?
A while back when Rex was in his prime,
the winterrains brought a great flood to the valley.
Rex and the boss got most of the flock
onto the high ground.
Then Rex went back to look for the strays.
He found them.
They'd been stranded by the rising water.
He tried to herd them across to safety,
but they wouldn 't budge.
Too afraid and too stupid to save their own skins.
It was freezing cold and the water kept rising.
Rex stayed with them right through the night.
By morning, the sheep were drowned.
And when they found Rex, he was barely alive.
Oh, mom!
Two weeks rest in front of the fire
saw him back on his feet.
But his hearing was never the same again.
He'd never want anyone to know, but
he's almost totally deaf.
Is that why he's so, you know, angry?
That's not the half of it.
all this was barely a month before
the Grand National Challenge.
He triedhis best, but he couldn't hear the boss's calls,
and it slowed him up.
The cold truth is that, but for the stupidity of sheep,
Rex would've been the champion of champions.
Good dog.
Now, through here like this.
And then, big hook to the left. Big hook. Big hook.
Through this gate here.
It was at that time that
Mrs.Hoggett began to worry about her husband.
But Farmer Hoggett knew that little ideas...
that tickled and nagged and refused to go away...
should never be ignored...
for in them lie the seeds of destiny.
Close the gate like that, and you're done.
A Tragic Day.
Mom. Mom! Can we start work early today?.
Oh, dear, it's not even dawn yet.
You can go to work when the rooster crows.
Oh, go back to sleep.
Ahem. Um, excuse me. Hello, Sir.
Excuse me, but it's nearly dawn, and...
Sorry to disturb you.
It's nearly dawn, and I wondered if you'd mind
crowing just a few minutes early this morning.
Get out of here!
- Get lost  - o ok..
Whoa!
Now the pig understood why the sheep
called all dogs wolves.
And he was filled with a deep and terrible rage.
Maa! Maa! Are you all right?
Hello, young'un.
Oh, Maa, can you get up?
I don't reckon.
It's over, Maa. The wolves have gone far away.
I'll get the boss up here to look after you.
You'll be all right. You'll be all right!
Oh, Maa! Maa!
Maa! Maa!
Maa!
Home, Pig.
Fly knew that there was only one fate for any creature...
that took the life of a sheep on Hoggett Farm.
But Fly could never believe that
Babe was a sheep killer,
so she remained in the field to do something
she 'd never done before: talk to the sheep.
Tell me. Who killed the old one?
Wolf!
Wolf. is that the only words you half-wits know?
Are you saying it was a dog?
Babe
Where's Babe?
Was it wolf or Babe
Wolf!
Babe!
Farmer Hoggett was carrying something
in the crook of one arm.
A kind of black, shiny tube.
Come, Pig.
The pig had a vague memory
that shiny tubes produced food...
and guessed that some quite unexpected surprise...
would come out of two small round mouths.
Babe!
Wolf!
Quiet!
Fly decided to speak very slowly,
for it was a cold fact of nature
that sheep were stupid...
and no one would ever persuade her otherwise.
Please, please would you be...
so kind as to tell me what happened?
Quiet!
Please, tell me what happened this morning.
The sheep spoke very slowly...
for it was a cold fact ofnature
that wolves were ignorant...
and nothing would convince them otherwise.
Babe came! He saved us!
The wolves killed Maa.
But Babe drove the wolves away!
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you all very much!
Pleasure talkin' to ya.
Hooey! Hoggett!
Hooey! Arthur!
Oh, there you are! Well, what do you think?
That was the police on the telephone.
Said there are wild dogs about.
Apparently the Mitchells lost six lambs this morning.
What on earth are you doing with that gun?.
Oh, I... nothing.
pig of destiny!
It's all very simple. Halfan hour at 350 degrees.
I've given you rabbit casserole for Friday.
Now, for Duchess,
it's liver in the morning, heart for the evening.
Except Fridays, when it's steak in the morning
and cooked liver at night.
Warm it up a bit
but test it, because she bites into it before she knows what's what.
That'll be the bus.
Oh, bye-bye. Have a good time. Bye.
Hello, everyone!
Oh, dearie me, Valda.
I know I have to be at the NationaL Conference.
I am the Assistant General Secretary
of the Northeast Region after all,
but I do worry about leaving that man alone.
Still acting a bit strange?
just silly things.
Odd little things only a wife would notice.
Still he can't get up to too much mischiefin three days.
Of course not.
Go on.
Go on!
Oh! Good evening. Shame about the weather.
Nasty cough!
It had been a long time since Arthur Hoggett...
had had an animal in whose abilities he had so much faith.
And with the National Grand challenge
Sheepdog Trials only two days away,
he wasn 't going to let the fact that his animal was a pig deter him.
He had been worried, for he was a truthful man,
that the heading might say "Name of dog. "
And then whatever he put would be a lie.
But as it happened,
luck, for the moment, was running with him.
It's allright, really! I'm just, well... bless you.
Whoa, whoa! Uh, easy, whoa! Ah.
So, ah... what's happening?.
Oh, no.
Shh. Easy, easy.
Hold still. Hold still.
There are many perfectly nice cats in the world.
But every barrel has its bad apples.
And it is well to heed the old adage,
"Beware the bad cat bearing a grudge. "
How are you feeling?
A bit tired.
You'll need a good sleep to put you in top condition tomorrow.
Don't stay up too late. Good night.
Good night, Mom.
Oh, do forgive me for scratching you, dear.
I got a bit carried away.
It's a cat thing.
Oh. Well... But, oh...
Feeling good about tomorrow, are you?
Mm-hmm. It should be all right, I think.
I probably shouldn't say this, .
but I'm not sure if you realize..
how much the other animals
are laughing at you for this sheepdog business.
Why would they do that?
Well, they say that you've forgotten that you're a pig.
Isn't that silly?
They even say that you don't know what pigs are for.
What do you mean? What pigs are for.
You know... why pigs are here.
Why are any of us here?
Well, the cow's here to be milked.
The dogs are here to help the boss's husband with the sheep.
And I'm here to be beautiful and affectionate to the boss.
Yes?.
The fact is that pigs don't have a purpose.
just like ducks don't have a purpose.
I don't...
all right, for your own sake, I'll be blunt.
Why do the bosses keep ducks?. To eat them
So why do the bosses keep a pig?.
The fact is that animals that don't seem
to have a purpose really do have a purpose.
The bosses have to eat.
It's probably the most noble purpose of all...
when you come to think about it.
They eat pigs?
Pork, they call it. Or bacon.
They only call them pigs when they're alive.
But, uh, I'm a sheep pig!
The boss's husband's just playing a little game with you.
Believe me, sooner or later, every pig gets eaten.
That's the way the world works.
Oh! I haven't upset you, have I?
Mom? Mom!
Good heavens!
What on earth are you doing out in the rain in the middle of the night.
You should be looking after yourself with such a big day ahead of you.
Are pigs for eatin'?
Who told you that?
The cat told me.
Pigs don't have a purpose except to be eaten.
Is it true?
It's true. For many pigs, it's true.
So my mother, my father,
my brothers and my sisters, all...
Probably, dear.
Do you want to talk about it?
No, it's all right. I understand.
I'll be all right.
Even... the boss?
Yes, dear.
Babe?.
Babe!
Babe's run away. Rex?
Please?
Call the boss.
He's over here.
Hold on, Pig, you'll be home soon.
He's got a cold, but
that doesn't explain a pig not eating.
He's got me stonkered, Arthur.
But I can tell you this.
If you don't get fluids into him soon,
you're gonna lose him.
C'mon, son. Pull yourself together.
The boss needs you.
Here we go. Come on, Pig. Ah, come on.
There's my boy. Come on, then. Come on.
# If I had words to make a day for you #
# I'd sing you a morning golden and true #
# I would make this day last for all time  #
# Then fill the night deep in moonshine  #
# If I had words to make a day for you #
# I'd giveyou a morning golden and true #
# I would make this day last for all time #
Listen, Arthur, I'll tell you what we can do.
You're listed third, but we can put you last in the program.
However, you must be here by 3:30
otherwise you'll be disqualified.
All right.
And welcome back
to the National Grand Challenge Sheepdog Trials...
coming today from the Kingsmith Show Ground in the heart of sheep country.
The weather's been patchy,
but we've already seen some wonderful work by these talented dogs.
Stay there.
Excuse me, sheep. Hello! Hello! Good morning to you all!
I've never met a sheep with such a strong, dark face.
Are they feeding you well?
Babe, I'll try.
All right, blockheads! Pay attention over here!
Now, you pay attention to what this pig has to say...
or I'll come in there and rip you to shreds!
Hadn't thought of this. Keep talking to them.
I'll see what I can do.
Doesn't it look a picture?.
Our show ground on the telly!
Apart from the weather.
Look! There's your Bert!
Bert Ford and Sweep doing very well.
Sweep's having a little trouble with this gate, clive.
A lot of trouble actually.
Don't worry, Valda. just a little slip up.
Look, he's doing much better now.
Too many loose sheep.
And Sweep's usually such a reliable dog.
Hey, whoa. Stop!
If those sheep won't talk to Babe,
the boss is going to look like an idiot.
I don't know what to do.
There is one thing. I gotta go!
I'll try to be back in time.
Ahem. It must've been terrible weather for you,
out in the field with all this rain we've been having.
Hey, that dog's in a hurry.
Come on, Nick, I got a beer and a TV waiting.
The last entry is pig. Owner, A. Hoggett.
Is that Hoggett?
I think it was!
Huh? He said Hoggett. It was clear as a bell.
Must be another Hoggett.
We only have the two dogs, and they certainly...
aren't...
Wolf! Wolf! Wolf! Wolf!
Shut up, you morons! The little pig's in trouble.
What trouble has come to our Babe, wolf?.
The sheep at the trials won't talk to the little fellow.
They won't listen. He doesn't know what to do.
Don't know what we could do to help.
It's not right to give help to a wolf.
You wait here, wolf.
You'll have to speak up. I'm a...
little hard of hearing.
I asked you to wait here, wolf.
Do what you're told by an old sheep for a change.
We'll see what we can do for you
Work completed. Restore power.
Very frustrating to be sitting up here...
wondering what's causing the delay.
We have someone on their way to the judges' rooms now.
We'll tell you what's causing the problem as soon as we find out.
perhaps it's a drug test, Eric? Yeah, it could be.
I've never heard ofa drug test at a sheepdog contest before.
Neither am I
We've got somethin' here that might be of use to our pig.
Password! Password!
Before we gives you anythin',
you'll be makin'us a solemn promise.
- Yes?  - Treat us civil!
Yes! You gotta treat us nice-like.
I'll try.
No bitin'!
That's right. Wolf must avoid bitin' us sheep... at all costs!
all right! I'll try that too.
It'spreposterous!
We'd be the laughing stock of every sheepdog organization...
in every civilized country in the world!
There's no rule...
We'll see about that when the adjudication committee
have finished their meeting
I mean What will we have nextyear,
a Laughing hyena doing show jumping? I suppose.
But the most important of all,
you must promise...
never ever to let this password we be about to give...
to be used against any sheep anywhere.
I promise you that. I'll make sure the pig knows it too.
We have the promise!
'Tis for Babe.
Maa would have wanted it.
Baa, ram, ewe. Baa, ram, ewe.
To your breed, your rleece,
your clan be true. Sheep be true.
Baa, ram, ewe.
Is that it?. Is that the password?.
Mr. Hoggett,
the judges would like me to convey to you...
their disappointment
that a man such as yourself,
with a long and honorable association with the work
of National Sheepdog Association,
should see fit to rlout...
the historic conventions which have long ruled our sport.
However we find there is no rule, as such,
which would prevent your... animal... being entered.
The committee has ruled that
if you wish to proceed,
there is nothing we can do to stop you.
What do you wish to do?.
There appears to be some movement down there now.
I expect if there are no further problems,
we shall see Hoggett and his dog pig.
U nusual name. Strange name, isn't it?. Pig.
Anyone for a game of cards?.
Oh, good grief! Look!
Entry number 23, mr. A. Hoggett with pig.
This is just too crazy to believe.
And if that isn't enough.
We have a stray dog on the field.
They trying to round him up?
The dog's gonna give a few tips on how to be a sheep pig.
Well, it's up to him now.
Away to me, Pig.
Baa, ram, ewe. Baa, ram, ewe!
To your breed, your rleece,
your clan be true. Sheep be true.
Baa, ram, ewe.
What... what did you say?
Get yourself a dog, Hoggett.
There, there, Esme. It's not the end of the world.
Is hejust going to stand there until his time runs out?
Or could this be some sort of protest?
may be we should line up an interview with the sheep pig?
Or the sheep pig's trainer.
He's a lively sort of fellow by the looks of things.
Good heavens!
It's Babe!
Oh, beautifully done!
I can't tell you how grateful I am to y'all.
Now, for one last favor.
If the three ladies with collars
would kindly walk out of the ring,
I'd be very much obliged.
And so it was that in all the celebration,
in all the hubbub of noise and excitement,
there were two figures who stood silent and still...
side by side.
The pig did it! The perfect score!
Yippee! Yippee!
And though everysingle human in the stands
or in the commentary boxes...
was at a complete loss for words,
the man, who in his life
had uttered fewer words than any of them...
knew exactly what to say.
That'll do, Pig.
That'll do.
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：274796078
And a one and a two and a three. Hit it.
# Ifl  had words to make a day for you #
# I'd sing you the morning golden and new #
# I would make this day last for all time #
# Give you a night deep in moonshine #
# If l had words to make a day for you #
# I'd sing you a morning golden and new #
# I would make this day last for all time #
# Give you a night deep in moonshine #