更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
You're just having a bad dream. That's all, baby.
That's all it was.
Bad dreams make you think you've seen things that you haven't.
You know what I do when I have a bad dream?
I close my eyes and I think of something nice.
Like being here with you.
Hurry up, sweetheart. We're gonna be late.
Shit.
Jack?
Did you see someone ring my doorbell?
No.
Okay, thanks.
I cleaned everything away, sweetheart.
Everything is exactly the way it was before.
They're clean and shiny. Look. Look. You see?
Okay, all right. Just close your eyes.
Well, hello, sailor.
Hi!
Permission to come aboard?
Honey, hold this.
So sorry we couldn't make it yesterday. Somebody was working late again.
How're you doing, Sal?
I'm good. How are you?
I'm all right.
Look at you.
Do you like it?
You look great.
Really? I just kinda threw it on.
She's had outfits laid out for a week.
You're such a liar. You know my husband.
I don't listen to what he says. You know that.
I brought my really good friend, Heather. She's so nice.
Promise me you'll be attentive.
How're you doing, man?
She's not to bring anyone.
You don't like her? Believe me, she's the best looking of Sally's friends.
Which it doesn't say much.
I asked you not to.
You're living on a boat with an 18-year old boy and you're saying no girls.
Greg, this is Heather.
She's a very good friend of mine, and I just thought you guys should meet.
Hi.
Can you just excuse me for a moment?
Jess. You okay?
I don't think so.
Hey. What happened?
Hey. What's the matter?
I'm sorry.
You've got nothing to apologize for.
What is it? Are you okay?
I'm just tired.
Well, listen, we don't have to go today if you don't want to.
No, we do. I-I wanna go.
You sure?
Yeah.
Yeah? Okay, come on. Come up here.
This is Sally and her husband, Downey.
This is Heather, Sally's friend. You remember Victor.
So let's go sailing!
Okay.
Hey.
You okay?
Is Greg okay?
He's fine. He's upstairs.
You've been asleep for a couple of hours.
I had this terrible dream.
What about?
I don't remember.
I wouldn't worry.
Apparently bad dreams cure you of real life stress.
As indeed does champagne. You want some?
Yeah.
Downey, wanna give me a hand, please?
Actually, Victor, I'm a guest of the Captain's, but yes, I witt help you.
Victor, what was that back there at the harbor?
What?
I asked Jess if she was all right and you said no.
You told me she was bringing the little boy along.
When I was walking with her in the harbor I asked where he was.
She couldn't remember.
She stared into space for like 20 seconds
and then she said he's at school.
So?
Well, it's Saturday. Ain't no school today.
Her son goes to a special needs school and it's open every day.
Be nice to her.
All right.
Do you boys sunbathe together?
Sometimes.
The champagne is not great but it is cold. Want some?
No thanks.
Okay, more for me.
Hey, how are you feeling?
I'm sorry, I didn't realize how tired I was.
You apologize one more time, and I'm gonna throw you overboard.
Here.
You all right?
Yeah.
He thinks we're a fishing hoat.
He's gonna go hungry.
You want to steer?
Nah.
Go on.
Which way do I aim?
You're gonna aim that way.
It's easy, right?
So, she's a waitress at some diner.
At least there they talk. They became friends.
Oh, and she has an autistic son.
So they're just friends.
Sally!
What do you want me to say? I'm sorry she has a retarded son?
Yeah!
Well, I'm sorry. You know, that's not Greg's problem, that's hers.
What is it, is it the shorts?
No! Heather, Greg's been my friend for a really long time.
I can't just sit back and watch him get shaken down.
She isn't doing that.
Well, I hope not because Greg is far too trusting.
I'm kinda linking the boy.
Uh, no, you're not. Can you please go up there and talk to Greg?
I really think the two of you will be perfect for each other.
And I really don't like seeing him with her.
Jess, are you ready?
Yeah, let her go.
Yeah.
Woo!
So, how do you know everyone?
Victor, he's staying with me for good.
He got in troubte at home. He had to get away.
I found him sleeping behind the store at the harbor.
You know, we got talking, and now he lives here.
Just like that you let him move in?
Well, I got three rooms. I can't sleep in them all.
And Downey, I've known him since I was a kid.
Sally, his wife, I know her from high school.
I dated her for like four days in the eighth grade,
so technically she's my ex.
They seem really nice.
Yeah. Except for the fact that every year they feel obliged
to bring me an eligible girl.
Maybe they think you're lonely.
Do I give off lonely to you?
Sometimes.
When I come to see you at the diner, I'm not lonely, I'm hungry.
Obviously yesterday was different.
What happened yesterday?
Yesterday I was not hungry.
I came in with the sole purpose of inviting you sailing.
You did?
I did.
Turn at port side. We're losing wind.
Let me check it for]ust a sec.
So, things are okay with Tommy?
The same.
Every day is the same.
Tommy likes the things to be a certain way. Yeah.
If I do one thing differently, I lose him.
What's the matter? I've never seen you like this before.
I don't know. I just, uh, I just feel guilty when I'm not with Tommy.
That's because you're a good mother.
But you can't be everywhere all of the times.
Hey, guys. Oh!
How is it going?
We're good.
I was]ust wondering if I could steal Jess away from you.
Salty's dying to tatk to her.
We're kind of in the middle of something right now.
No, no, it's okay. I-I should circulate.
Hey, just for the record,
I'm not interested.
Yo, what the fuck?
Wind's dropped down on us.
It's not dropped, it's gone.
This is crazy.
You ever seen this before?
Yeah, yeah. Just not quite so sudden.
Are we okay to get home? There is no wind.
Yeah, yeah. We got an engine. It's not a problem.
It's just, it's weird.
Greg?
Is that normal?
Okay, I'm fucking freaked, what the fuck.
Triangle to coast guard. Over.
Coast guard, go ahead. Over.
We've just gone from seven knots to absolute zero. You've got anything unusual? Over?
Nothing showing up. Over.
It's darkening up pretty quick out here. Looks like an electrical storm. Over.
Help me. Please. Can you hear me?
Help me. Please, help me.
Killing everyone. They're dead. They're all dead.
We hear you. What's your position? Over.
Distressed caller, we hear you. What are your coordinates? Over.
Coast guard, did you hear a distress call? We're not getting it anymore. Over.
Distressed caller, make another transmission. What is your position?
Greg?
Get below deck now. Get the life jackets.
Out it. Out the sail.
Vic, get the main sail down.
Get it down.
Vic!
No!
Get back.
Jess, take my hand.
Grab on.
Heather!
Vic!
Jess.
Are you okay?
All right.
Downey?
Are you guys okay?
Have you seen Heather? She got lost through the window.
No. Come on, come on.
Heather!
Greg! Help me!
Sally. Sally.
Just give me your hand.
Heather!
Are you guys okay?
Yeah.
Are you all right?
Tommy's at school, yeah?
He'll be looked after until we get back. He'll be all right.
Thank God. Yo! Help us!
Help us. Help. Help us. Over here.
Oh, God.
Hey. Hey.
Wait. Come on, over here!
There, there. Over there. I can see someone.
Yo, we need some help down here.
Help us, please!
Hello. We need some help down here.
Yeah, he's seen us. He's seen us.
Oh, thank God.
Jump, jump, jump.
Okay. Jess, come on, come on.
Jess. Come on.
Come on, come on, take my hand. Okay.
Okay. You okay?
You okay? Yeah?
Hey.
How is it?
See? I told you.
Hello?
Hello!
Do we wait?
No, let's go to the bridge.
We'll get the captain to put a call out to the coast guard.
We'll get a search for Heather.
Oome on.
Do you think Heather would've made it on board?
Honey.
There's a chance, isn't there?
Yeah. Yeah, there's a chance.
Hello?
Hello!
Somebody please help us?
Hello?
Where the fuck is everybody?
You don't even now where we're going.
Well, we're just, just walking for the sake of it.
You all right?
I feel like I know this place.
I recognize this corridor.
Liners, they look pretty similar.
No, that's not it.
Come check this out.
This is the same ship. This thing's old.
Jess.
Oome on. Oome on.
1932. It's the same. Here's where we boarded.
Oh, yeah.
Aeolus.
Aeolus was the Greek god of the winds and the father of Sisyphus,
the man condemned by the gods to the task of pushing a rock up a mountain
and let it see roll back down again.
That's a shitty punishment. What did he do?
He cheated Death. No, he made a promise to Death that he didn't keep.
I studied it but I can't remember. Can we just keep on moving, please?
Hello?
Whoever it was might wanna come back for these.
Let me see?
These are mine.
These are my keys.
What are you talking about?
They're mine.
Bullshit.
This is, this is my house key.
This is my, my car key. This is my son. See?
Wait. So you had them with you on the yacht?
Yes.
It's gotta be Heather.
Come on.
How else did they get here?
It was Heather dropping her keys but not bothering to say, "I didn't drown."
Why not?
Come on.
Heather?
Looks like you get your welcome party, just not the welcome.
Heather!
Yo, Greg, what time you got?
Eleven thirty.
Heather.
Heather!
Where is everyone?
Sally! Please. Please.
I don't know where everyone is but the ship's not deserted.
I mean, maybe some of us think that it is but it's not,
so let's just go to the bridge.
We'll find the skipper and then we'll go home.
I saw someone.
Fuck.
Wait.
Hello?
Did you see who it was? Was it Heather?
I didn't see.
I'm sorry.
Where're you going?
Why don't you just help me out here?
What?
Just wait for Vic.
It's fine.
Why can't we go with him?
Let's just do as Greg says and wait here for Victor, okay?
Fine.
I think Victor's in danger.
I'm not worried about Victor.
I'm sorry I'm acting weird. It's just I'm having deja vu
every time I turn a corner.
No, no. No.
I know this place.
No, you don't know this place. You're just in shock.
That's funny.
What is it? What is it? Is it Tommy?
Is it guilt? Is that what it is? Do you feel guilty?
Hello?
Hello.
We're on the third floor. The bridge is exactly two floors above us.
Greg, that was blood. Are you just gonna ignore it?
I know guys that work on ships like this.
They see us, they get bored. They're just letting off some steam.
What? They rescue us from the sea and then they just hide for fun?
Yeah.
Well, what's your theory?
I don't know, but I'm not, but I'm not in shock.
I'll be in the ball room. I'm getting off this ship.
Jess, fuck! Don't you see that this is all just in your mind?
Jess! Ships don't just magically appear out of nowhere.
They have skippers. I mean, in your world right now they don't.
My world is waiting outside school for his mother to pick him up.
Don't talk to me about my world.
Jess. Jess, I'm sorry.
Is that blood?
Babe, come on, we're supposed to meet them in the theater.
Heather!
Oh, my God. Shit.
Sally. Sal, come on.
Let's just go to the theater.
Downey, I can't see anymore blood. I don't think she's in here.
To be honest with you, I don't think she's even on the ship.
Okay. So whose blood was that?
Hello?
Downey? Sally?
Victor. What happened?
Oh, my God.
Stay with me, Greg. Stay with me, man.
Stay with me, man.
No. No!
You fucking bitch! You shot him!
What?
He said you shot him.
I didn't!
Fucking liar!
I wasn't even with Greg!
He's dead! He's dead! Look!
God, you're a bitch!
Get your hands off him!
I didn't do it! I was with Victor.
Someone attacked him.
Someone?
You think I did it?
Why did you tell us to come to the theater?
I didn't. L... Sally, I didn't.
I didn't.
My God, you're a fucking skitso.
Sally, no.
Sally!
No!
Downey!
Let it go. Let it go.
No!
Don't shoot. Please.
Please, don't shoot. Please.
I have a son. I have a son.
Shit.
Who are you? Tell me!
Who are you?
What the fuck are you saying?
It's the only way to get home.
What?
You have to kill them.
Kill them! Kill them! Kill them!
Over here. Come on. Hey!
Help us, please!
Help!
Hey. Hey.
Help us!
Please!
There, there. Over there. I can see somebody.
Hello?
Looks like they decided to scratch the welcome.
Let's go to the bridge.
We'll get the captain to put a call out to the coast guard.
Hello!
Hello?
Where the fuck is everybody?
Do you even know where we're going?
Well, we're just, just walking for the sake of it.
You all right?
I feel like I know this place.
I recognize this corridor.
Liners, they look pretty similar.
No, that's not it.
Jess, come on.
This is the same ship. This thing's old.
Yeah. 1932.
It is the same. Here's where we boarded.
Yeah. Aeolus.
Aeolus.
Aeotus was the Greek god of the winds and the father of Sisyphus,
the man condemned by the gods to the task of pushing a rock up a mountain
only to have it roll back down again.
That's a shitty punishment. What did he do?
He cheated Death. No, he made a promise to Death that he didn't keep.
I studied him and I can't remember. Can we just keep on moving?
Hello?
Heather?
Hello!
Heather!
Sally. Please. I don't know where everyone is.
But the ship's not deserted.
I mean, maybe some of us think that it is but it's not,
so let's]ust go to the bridge.
We'll find the skipper and then we go home.
I saw someone.
Hello?
Hello.
Shit. How did you get here so fast?
Victor, you got, you gotta listen to me. We don't have much time.
Oh, what's going on? Where's Greg?
He's dead.
What?
No, I mean, he was dead. He's not dead now.
What are you saying?
Downstairs right now is a copy of myself.
Me, walking and talking with Greg.
Right.
There.
There's birds.
No, that was Downey's body.
I just left Downey back there. How did you get here so fast?
That's what I've been trying to tell you.
No. Downey was there. It was Downey's body.
There are bodies all over this ship.
Your body is on the floor at the restaurant with a hole in your head.
Listen, I'm gonna do you a favor, okay?
I'm not gonna tell anyone about this.
It's the truth. Victor, we gotta get off this ship right now.
You're saying there's two of you now.
Yes.
And I'm dead in the restaurant.
You were killed.
Okay. So, I'm dead. Downey's in the water. He's dead, too.
Is Sally okay?
See where I'm going with this, right?
If we are dead and there's two of you,
how are we all gonna get off this ship?
We should never have boarded this ship.
I knew something was wrong.
I should've forced you to stay on the yacht and you'd all be alive.
I've gotta tell you I feel pretty alive right now.
Soon you're gonna be dead. Everything that happened to you, happened before.
I can't even believe I'm talking this shit.
You will die and then, then Downey and Sally and then Greg.
I didn't do this. I didn't do it.
We're on the third level.
Greg, that was blood. You just gonna ignore it?
I know guys that work on ships like this.
They see us, they get bored. They're just letting off some steam.
Don't you see that this is all just in your mind?
Ships don'just magically appear out of nowhere.
They have skippers. I mean, in your world right now they don't.
My wortd is waiting outside school for his mother to pick him up.
Don't talk to me about my world.
Who are you?
Listen, listen to me.
Please, you have to listen.
Kill them all.
If they board, kill them.
Jess. Jess, you gotta kill them.
Please, you have to listen.
Don't let them board.
No, no. No. Please, please. Stop, stop them.
If they board, kill them.
Jess. Jess, you gotta kill them.
No, no. No. Please, please, stop. If they board, kill them.
Please, please stop. Jess, Jess, Jess.
Fuck you!
Shit.
Tommy.
Is that blood?
Babe, come on. We're supposed to meet them at the theater.
Victor.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
You know I didn't mean to hurt you, right?
Now, I'm gonna try and get us off this ship, okay?
Sally.
Sally?
Victor?
What happened?
You're not me.
You see? I'm not crazy.
Victor.
This didn't happen before. Don't you see?
You tried to strangle me, remember?
Now, you gotta be strong. I'm gonna get the others.
Downey, do something.
Stay with me, man.
Do something.
I don't know what to do.
Is he dead? Is he dead?
Greg. Greg.
You fucking...
Listen, I'm not gonna hurt you. We don't have much time.
Don't you point that thing.
Move!
Go, go, go.
I hit her. I think I hit her.
What's going on? Who was that?
It's starting over again. That's what's going on.
Let's go.
We can't leave without Greg.
We'll come back for Greg. I promise. Let's go, come on!
We can change the pattern. Don't you see?
We change the pattern, we're not trapped. Then we get off this thing.
She's fucking mad.
You think?
You have to listen to me.
No, I don't have to listen to you.
Was it me that shot you?
I don't know.
Whoa, wait. Could we just take a breath for a second?
Okay, Jess, I am prepared to listen to you
and even to believe you, but you gotta make some sense.
I'm making perfect sense. I'm gonna get Victor, then we get off this ship.
Wait here.
And don't trust anyone.
If anyone comes, you shoot them.
What are you talking about?
You shoot them.
What?
Victor.
Victor?
I said who is it?
It's me, Jess.
Jesus Christ, what the fuck happened to you?
A long story.
Where's Victor?
He's dead.
He fell over the side.
How do we know you didn't kill him?
You don't.
If you wanna live, you'll follow me.
Downey!
Ignore it.
What's going on?
Is said ignore it.
Where are you? Call out.
No, t'm not]ust gonna ignore it. What is going on?
Where the fuck are you?
Call out! You're in danger. You're in danger.
Who is that?
Not who you think?
So, what are we doing in here?
Sally!
Wait!
I'm sorry but I love my son.
Sally?
That wasn't me.
Hello? Hello?
Please, can you hear me?
Help me. Please, help me.
She's killing everyone.
They're dead. They're all dead. Please...
Sally?
What's your position? Over.
Sally.
Distressed caller, we hear you. What are your coordinates? Over.
Coast guard, did you hear a distress call? We're not getting in anymore. Over.
Greg.
Greg, is that you?
Distressed caller, make another transmission. What is your position?
Greg, can you hear me? Greg.
Shit.
Sally?
Oh, my God, what happened to you?
Get away from me.
It wasn't me, Sally. I didn't do this to you.
It wasn't me. Where is Downey?
I don't know where he is.
You killed him.
What?
No, I didn't. I didn't kill him.
I swear.
You're crazy.
Why are you doing this?
Sally, I know it's hard but you gotta trust me.
Gotta trust me, okay?
Listen, you gotta hold on.
I think it will return again.
The yacht, the Triangle, I think it'll come back.
If it does, we'll escape, me and you together.
We'll re-board it and escape.
Please.
Don't hurt me.
Sally, I'm not gonna hurt you.
If you hold on,
you can see Downey again.
Hey, come on. Over here.
Hey. Hey. Help.
It returns when they're dead.
It returns when everyone's dead.
Do you think Heather woutd've made it on board?
Honey.
There's a chance, isn't there?
Yeah. Yeah, there's a chance.
Stop this thing.
Stop this fucking thing.
Please.
I wanna go home.
He's dead. I mean, he was dead.
He's not dead now.
I was hiding and I saw this version of myself,
and she had blood on her face, and then I killed her.
I killed her on the front of the ship.
Listen, I'm gonna do you a favor, okay?
I'm not gonna tell anyone about this.
It's the truth. You gotta listen to me.
No, I'm not listening to another word you say.
You will die, and then Greg and then Downey.
Don't be scared, Victor. I can save you.
I know how to save you.
You should try and eat, babe.
Jess?
Jesus, what happened to you?
Where's Greg?
Greg told me to tell you we should meet in the theater.
There's a theater?
Yes, it'just that way.
Where are you going?
I'll see you there.
Okay, she's really starting to freak me out now.
Don't you see that this is all just in your mind?
Ships don't]ust magically appear out of nowhere. They have skippers.
In your world right now maybe they don't.
My wortd is waiting outside school for his mother to pick him up.
Don't talk to me about my world.
Jess.
Jess, I'm sorry.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Okay.
Take it easy, man.
Just take it easy.
What did we do? We're not part of this boat.
We just got here, okay? We've been walking around. There's no one on it.
I can go right now. I will go.
Okay? Just... Just take it easy.
Take it easy.
Okay?
Jess?
Jess.
Jess, what are you doing?
Wha... what is this? Why... what are you wearing?
I don't want you to see my face.
Why?
Because this is not me.
I'm somewhere out there in the yacht and you're with me.
And after I kill you, we'll return.
Is that right?
You know, why-why don't you just put down the gun first?
Okay? Come on.
You see, the boat comes back when you're all dead.
I've done everything exactly like before.
But when the boat comes back, I'll be ready, I'll be waiting.
I'll be on the landing bay. I won't let any of them board, even the other me.
I'll make them all stay on the upturned yacht.
Okay.
Jess, we'll do whatever you want.
Okay? Just, just put down the gun.
Come on.
I'm so sorry.
No, no, no, no!
Greg!
Oh, God! What happened?
It was Jess.
You fucking bitch! You shot him. He said you shot him.
I wasn't even with Greg!
He's dead! He's dead!
My God, you're a fucking skitso.
Downey!
Please.
Don't kill me.
I have a son.
Who are you?
Tell me!
They'll return.
Who are you?
They'll return. You have to kill them.
It's the only way to get home.
What the fuck are you saying?
It's the only way to save our son.
You have to kill them.
Kill them? Kill them?
Hurry up, Sweetheart. We're gonna be tate.
What's fun in buying you things
if you're gonna leave them in the fucking garden!
I'm sick of telling you this, Tommy.
I ain't buying you anymore toys if you can't look after the ones you've got.
Now what?
Oh, I'll just clean it up, shall I?
Yeah, I'm]ust cleaning the fucking mess!
What's the matter with you, huh? What's the matter with you?
Just one day off is alt I ask. Just one fucking day off!
I don't know why you can't paint a picture like a normal kid.
You get this from your father.
He was an asshole, too.
Shit.
Jack?
Did you see anyone ring my doorbell?
Tommy?
Sweetheart, come here.
Come here. Come here! It's okay.
Mommy's fine, you see?
Mommy's fine.
You're just having a bad dream. That's all, baby.
It's all it was.
Bad dreams make you think you've seen things that you haven't.
Things are gonna be different now, Tommy.
Mommy won't lose her temper anymore,
even when you do things wrong.
And she won't hurt you.
I know she won't hurt you.
You know how I know that, Tommy?
Because that woman that did those things to you is not Mommy.
This is Mommy. Mommy's nice.
Shit.
Tommy, stay in the car.
I'm gonna bury it, okay?
We have to go. We have to get out of here.
Stop screaming, babe.
Please, Tommy, it is just blood.
Stop screaming!
Tommy, look. See? There, it's gone.
See? There. It's gone.
Are you all right?
Who are you?
Just a driver.
No point trying to save the boy.
There's nothing anyone can do that's gonna bring him back.
Can I give you a ride?
Yes.
Take me to the harbor.
Hey.
I'll leave the meter running.
You will come back, won't you?
Yes, I-I promise.
Jess.
Do you know me?
I feel like I do. Greg talks about you enough.
Where is Greg?
Where do you think?
Come on, you're late.
You're the one with the kid, right?
Yeah.
How come you didn't bring him along?
He's at school.
You sure about that?
Yes.
Are you okay?
I don't think so.
Hey, what's the matter? What happened?
Hey.
I'm sorry.
You have nothing to apologize for. What's the matter?
I'm just tired.
Listen, we don't have to go today if you don't want to.
No, I do. I-I wanna go.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Yeah? Come, come here.
This is Sally and her husband, Downey.
This is Heather, Sally's friend. You remember Victor.
Let's go sailing.
Okay.
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：1610169789