WWW.52HALFCD.COM
时代影视论坛 荣誉出品
影片压制&字幕制作：liubinqing
That way
Xiao Cheng, would this end up like last time?
Don't worry
We've got everything here
Even gloves
We won't leave fingerprints
Go over there and take a look
Somebody is coming
Stop!
Pal, we are penniless
This is outrageous!
Taking police officers as thieves
Freeze!
Oh, it's the cops
We're scared
Tell the truth, it's late
What are you two doing here?
We are...
We are...putting up posters
Right
Putting up posters late at night?
Officer, you don't believe us
Let us demonstrate
Broom
Glue
Put up a poster
Okay
Officer, see, it's done
We are so skillful
Don't fool me
That doesn't look like a poster
It's highly competitive nowadays
Advertisements have to be creative
Right...have to be creative
Don't work too late
The society order is worse than before
See you, bye
We'll go home after finishing this job
You shut up. Let's go now
That way
Nothing there
Nothing
Over there...
Hey, anything there?
Nothing
Then why don't you come down now?
What are we supposed to do now?
Let's go
Looks like we've got nothing again
Real bad luck
So do you have another plan?
I do
What is it?
Let's go home
Then we won't get anything
Let's start working
Nobody there
Nobody is there
But the re" re valuables
What happened?
What are you doing?
Doesn't matter, just an accident
Use plan B
Are you ready?
Yes
Let's go now
Go
Shit, go hide away
You are no good
But we are bound together
I am coming in
You are really horny
The proverb goes, "t steal your friend's wife"
My friend is away, so I try my best
So what have you done?
Use my charm
Forget it
My husband has style
Me too
My husband has beautiful hair
I had beautiful hair when I was young
My husband is good in bed
Me too
My husband delivers newspapers
I deliver newspapers too
So you two are in same business
Come on
What?!
You're so bad
What are you afraid of?
I am your husband's good friend
Damn
Come on
No
Are you alright?
I'm alright
Why are you so careless?
I have something for you
Really?
Yes
You two are really kinky
Don't try to explain
You know what you are doing
We've known about your affair
No only you know and I know
He also knows
Do you know?
I know
You two...
I don't even know who you both are!
She is not your wife?
Not really
Oh, I'm sorry
It's a mistake...
I'm sorry
Sorry. I make a mistake...Oh
Really...sorry
Sorry
A mistake
It's a mistake
A real mistake
He used to go through windows
Sorry
Goodbye
Bye-bye
Sorry, goodbye
One moment worth a thousand gold bars
We just spoiled the occasion
One moment worth a thousand gold pieces
You two go on
Don't stop
Thieves, thieves...
Uncle Bill, congratulations!
You are free again
It's very boring inside
Just want to go out and get some air
Please come back when you have time
No, thanks
I won't be back again
Uncle Bill
It's so good to see you getting out
Let me wipe off your bad luck
Wipe once, money comes
Wipe twice, big fortune comes
Last wipe
Gone all the bad, comes all the good
Who teaches you such rubbish?
Where's my darling?
Over there
My darling, Carol
Look at this horse
I take good care of her
Not even a drop of sweat on her skin
If so, she might get dry skin
Uncle Bill, your darling
...gets sick often
and has a bad temper
She'll be better when she has a boyfriend
That makes sense
Uncle Bill, let's have tea
Fine
Come with me
Okay
Let's go
Okay...wait a sec
"Fat Kee Restaurant"
Uncle Bill, the shark's fin soup is tasty in here
It's better than the veggie bean curd soup in jail
You can try if you don't believe me
This meal is our treat
Help yourself and order whatever you want
Waiter...
What are you doing?
Are you blind?
I'm sorry, miss
I'm not blind, my eyesight is not good
Be careful next time
I'm sorry
Gosh, just get another purse
Don't run, stay there!
Why you keep running away from me?
You think I, the Big Bro, can't pay
You think I have no money
You don't believe I have money
You don't know I have money
I haven't paid yet
How do you know I have no money?
Give him a good scolding
See, he wears a nice suit
How is it that he can't pay for his bill?
Needless to say!
Big Bro, I...
I... what?
Lucky he's a gentleman
As compared to me you're pretty easygoing
Big Bro, be cool
We are reasonable people
Yes...
It's not easy to tell
you are a nice guy
It's nice to have tea with a friend
Let me treat you a cup of tea
Thanks
Next time, maybe next time
There's always next time
Goodbye
I'll treat you next time
Bye
That guy is really something
Where's Uncle Bill?
He's out, will be back soon
Let's have tea first
What?
You know what
Nuts
Don't know what you are talking about
Whafs this?
This is a purse
Give it to me, I am taking it back
A kid is a kid
Always get dizzy with his success
Look at you
Do you want to spend your life in jail?
Do something else while you're still young
There're lots of things to do, don't do this
Gaining at others' expense is vile & lowly, you know?
r think of getting married and have children?
Yes
Don't even think about it
You'll hurt your children
You are still young
You can do what you want, but not this
You have to change before getting married
Turn from the bad ways and be good again
Understand?
Understand
Raise your head and be a good person
Okay
That's good
Raise your head and be good
Uncle Bill, have some tea
This is my purse
How come it's here?
That's strange
Someone steals it
Who'd dare to pluck a tiger's hair?
How dare...I...
Luckily you have Uncle Bill here
Uncle Bill
What a shame
Captain...
Raise your head and be good
Xiao Du
Whafs the rush?
Captain...
Did you drop the money?
How many times have you done today?
None
None?
None, really?
Search him
Please don't
Shut up
Let me do it...
I've done nothing
Oh, my purse
Come back
Captain...
Still want to go
My purse is stolen
I want to look for my purse
Your purse is stolen
You've got your match
Let's go to get the tiger
Tiger?
Is that true?
Of course
Let's go, Kitty
Uncle Bill
The shark's fin soup is good in here, isn't it?
I won't lie to you
Captain, that old guy inside
is a pro in this trade
Take a good look
This have nothing to do with me
I have to go
Captain...
Still want to run?
What are you two doing here?
Captain...
He can't get away today
He is...
He is the one we're looking for
That's mean...
We are looking for him all day
Cut the crap, take him back
I'll go first, Captain
Then go
Captain, your team is efficient
Captain, what do you want to eat?
The usual
Okay
Where's my purse?
Captain
Shut up
Yes...
Damn it
Move aside...
Let go of me
Sorry. I'm sorry
Take care
Uncle Bill, where are we going to?
To my family
Your...family
You two orphans don't have one
Uncle Bill, you're blessed
Follow me
Don't know what he's going to do
Uncle Bill
"Yuan Ji Bean Curd"
Where are the young ladies?
Old lady, please come again
Take care
Hey, she ignores you
Miss, why don't you take a look at me?
Let me introduce myself
My family is Lee, first name Cha
Richard is my English name
I come all the way to pay you a visit
Do you want to buy bean curd?
Yes
But I have to check if or not your bean curd is smooth
How much do you want?
Can I try some first?
What do you want?
Put them on my hand
The bean curd is smooth and smells good
I really love them
Tonight I'll be satisfied with just the beancurd
Sir, you haven't paid yet
Sorry
The money is in my pocket
You take it by yourself
Why don't you take the money?
Come on
Take it
If you don't take it, I'm leaving now
What are you doing?
Hey, think you're a monk taking alms
Had your food and not paying for it!
No
I want to pay but she doesn't take the money
Yes
She's generous
Right
You don't have to pay, right?
That's right
She didn't get the money, right?
She didn't
I'll get it
Did you get it?
Lucky I haven't got hurt
Go on...I'm asking you to eat
What are you doing?
Now I'm really eating bean curd
Let him go. You've already taught him a lesson
Forget it
Just that
You really don't give me face
Rubbish. Pay me the money
Damn you
Let's forget it
You bitch
You wait and see
Don't go away
Big Bro, shall we go now?
Sure, let's go
Be careful
Little brat
Stay longer and I'll beat you to death
You have to beat up these guys
Sis, if someone bullies you next time
You have to tell me
Ah Yuan, Ah Ji
Why are you so upset?
Brother Wai, where's the dumplings?
Oh, I forget to bring the money
So you haven't bought the dumplings
I'll buy you more tomorrow, okay?
Right
I'll buy tomorrow for sure
It's okay if you buy them after tomorrow
Brother Wai, why are you so late today?
I had some work to do
That's why I'm late
Yuan, we...
Sorry---excuse me
Yuan, I...
Sorry, excuse me
Hey, miss
Can you let me talk to your sister?
Okay, I'll give you a chance
But...
But what?
Help me take the soy beans inside
What?
Help you take the soy beans? I'm a Captain
So you want to do it or not?
No
Brother Wai
Yuan, what's up?
Just listen to her this time
No next time
That's better
It's over there, hurry up
That's the bitch
That's her
So many people here
Probably want to scare your sister
Hey, beat her up
What are you doing?
Leave me alone
Stop fighting
Let me go
Oh, shit
Yuan
Brother Wai, they are...
Let me go
That bitch is playing tough
Let me give you a few slaps first
Captain
What?
We have to teach this little bitch a lesson
Let her go
Let her go?
Give me some face
Are you crazy?
Look at my nose
Can't let her go
Don't even give me some face?
No
My nose is broken again
Beat him up
Let me do it myself
Okay
Beat me?
Hey, you...
Come with me
You dare to lock me up?
So what?
Do you know what will happen to you?
I know
What?...
Let's go
Brother Wai, wait
Brother Wai...
Okay, I know
Brother Wai, buy more buns tomorrow
Let's dance...
Sorry, excuse me
Captain
Stop...
Still run, stop
I'll shoot if you don't stop
I just ask you to stop
Why are you keep going?
You've talked a lot
I don't know if it's true or not
Yes
Take a close look
Oh, it's Captain
Now you know
I am going to charge you with
disturbing public order and
stealing from other people
Now I have to lock you up
Ah, lock me up
Don't you know
the bald detective Karl Maka
is my brother?
Karl Maka? Who is he?
We're two of a kind
We've gone through many tough situations
I've saved his life
That's right
He's so famous
If you haven't met him you should've heard him
And also
The renowned private eye Mr. George Lam
He's my cousin
His partner, that over-aged Teddy Robin
used to work for me too
So you are...
Listen,
I'm a friend of Hiroshimataro Tsui Hark
The consulate general to Japan
Friend means buddies
Maybe I get the wrong guy
You're right
With my high position and reputation
I won't do anything against the law
Right, Captain?
I'm sorry, really sorry
Uncle Bill, let's forget it
Right, you're very kind
Okay
We forgive you this time
Let's go
Stop
I'm really sorry
Please say something good about me to Maka
My name is Tie Liwai
Well, I'll see
But you have to remember
Lower your voice when asking people to stop next time
Yes, I won't shout next time
Thank you...
Come and buy these colorful figurines
Take a look
You two wait here
I want to buy something home
Don't go away
How much is this one?
Twenty cents each
So expensive
That's not expensive
How about this one? How much?
This one is fifteen cents
Fifteen cents, I don't want it
We're wasting time here
Let's go to Uncle Bill's home first, okay?
Granny, I'm hungry
Let's go to buy some buns
Where is it?
No. 48, Jinchuen Street
Xiao Qi, it's there
Over there, look
It's here
Right
Let me go inside first
To see what his daughter looks like
You go inside
What are you afraid of?
If I'm right
She must have a long neck or flat ass
Or limbs like frogs
Or goldfish eyes and a lion's mouth
Don't be so mean okay?
Believe it or not
Hide away
I'll go and take a look first
Please
Xiao Qi, look at this girl
Countryfolk have rough hands and feet
They wear shoes without socks
Right
They wear clothes but prefer not button up
Right, they don't button up their clothes
And they sit down with legs wide open
Right, with legs wide open
And trouser legs rolled up high
They walk like ducks and goose
And work around clumsily
This is the kind of a woman
you should always avoid
If you got stuck with her
You would never get rid of her
That's real trouble
It is
Are you alright?
That's awesome
I'm alright
You two little brat
Having nothing to do but tease girls
Hey, tiny tot
It's you who hit us first
What do you want?
Want to pick a fight?
Tiny tot, do you want to hit me
Xiao Ji, what are you doing?
What happened?
These little brat want to pick a fight
There's a miracle
Forget it.. Just ignore them
Come inside and work
Come in
Tiny tot
Without this sister you're finished
Can't keep your mouth shut
Xiao Ji
This bean curd is for selling
You go to hell
Stop throwing
Stop it
Where're the brats going?
Beauties
What are you two doing?
Dad...
Dad?
Throw some more
Uncle Bill
Dad, have a cup of hot tea first
I come all the way home
Just want to see you two
And you just treat me like that
Dad, Xiao Ji doesn't do it on purpose
No, I do it on purpose
Xiao Ji, you can't do this to Dad
Why not?
Although he's my Dad
he never took up his duty as a father
A father sends his children to school
Have you done this?
A father loves and teaches his children
Without a word
You have left home a couple of years
You never think about home
Just leave the two of us
making bean curds at home every day
Cutting bean curds, selling bean curds
And being teased by people
Sis
We have bean curd three meals a day
And you
What kind of father you are
Mom died but her mind was not in peace
Don't you feel sorry?
Ah, what a...
...bean curd story
It's full of tears
And very touching
Makes people feel sad
and tears rolling down
Quiet
You're right
It's my fault for not taking care of family
It's my fault not sending you to school
I never do what a father should do
Never pay any attention to you two
That's all my fault
I'm wrong, I'm useless, I'm no good
I should not go to Nanyang
to take up that miserable job
And let you two eat nothing but bean curds
Now...who should I blame?
My daughters don't want me as their father
I should not stay here anymore
This is not funny
Don't stop me, I want to leave
Uncle Bill
I am leaving now
How about us?
I said don't stop me
You know my heart is soft
If you stop me, I won't leave
I have to go
After I go,
don't know when I can be back!
I am really leaving
I have to go
Dad...
I'm still here
I forget something
Dad...my words are too harsh
Please don't go
Go? Go where?
Okay...
Now this is a real family reunion
We can enjoy a good meal together
And go to bed early after dinner
Right, now we are a family again
So help yourself
Dad
You two brats are not my family
Uncle Bill
I'm not your uncle
I can give you food, but no shelter
If you two stay here
I cannot go to sleep
Then we will...
Go back to the hotel after dinner
Go back to the hotel
How come you two are so early?
We...
Come in first
Good morning, Uncle Bill
Morning...
We don't feel well
Didn't have a good sleep?
No...
It's real sickness
Right
Feeling sick?
The pulse is normal
You don't have any sickness
My purse is empty
You are sick too?
I'm desperate for money
Everybody has this kind of sickness
You won't die
Go and wait for me at the teahouse
Okay...will order tea and wait for you there
Let's go
Uncle Bill, it's full house
Full house
There's a seat over there
The prison has seats
Ready for you guys
So we meet again
There's really a connection between us
Stop playing dumb
I've checked out
all the big names you mentioned
They're all actors
Don't be too serious
Life is just like acting
Yes, Captain
Life is a stage
A stage is life
You're right
So you three go back to jail with me
and start playing inmates
Do you want me to lock you or you do it yourself?
Uncle Bill, this is horrible
Pick one yourself
Brother Wai
Why do you have so many handcuffs?
They are for the thieves
For thieves
Dad, do we have thieves here?
What? He's your father?
You don't call a stranger Dad
Brother Wai, how many thieves are here?
Three
Three, that many
Where are they?
I let them go
Really? You let them go
I pity them
So I let them go and start a new life
That's very kind of you
And you are very intelligent and understanding
Very good
Very smart
I really appreciate you
Old sir, we both understand this
Of course
I will never...
pick pockets again
Reporting!
Captain, there's an emergency
The Chief asks you to go back now
Old sir
Okay...
I'll take care of myself
Don't worry
No problem
Right, go to do your work first
Come and have a chat with my dad some other time
Let's go
Yes
Uncle Bill, now we...
Have no sickness anymore
I have
Take the clothes
I
Uncle Bill, you go first...
Chief
Is there an emergency case?
Recently we've found drug dealers
in several neighbouring cities
According to our information
The headquarters might be in our county
Our county
Right
You leave us alone now
Yes
This is the information from our seniors
You have a look
The dealers are related to the Fengyue Society
It is related to Fengyue Society
Go to investigate now
But Chairman Lee of the Society is your cousin
If I got hard evidence
I'll arrest my relatives in accord with the law
Yes, sir
Boss...
That's a good fight
Thank you, Boss
What?
Do you want to fight with me?
You go first
Madam
Go and get some rest first
Yes
Why are you so late?
If I didn't come, you wouldn't miss me, right?
Darling, I always miss you
According to Sunzi's theory
There are thirty-six strategies
Strategy within strategy, strategy upon strategy
But all strategies are in fact one strategy
What strategy?
Play on one's psychology
Play on one's psychology?
That's right
We share a common psychology
And psychology works the same way
In a way, it's guessing what people think
Uncle Bill
First we've to understand how psychology works
If we were caught
psychology cannot help
It helps
I am psychologically well prepared, right?
And how is that?
Don't let people slap your face
I'm not ready yet
You slap me first
Shut up
This is outrageous!
In our trade
You have to be agile and smart
Use your brain
Remember the formula:
Look around all directions
Make decisions promptly to solve problems
Uncle Bill, I understand
He understands
Hey, pal
Have you ever seen such a big bird?
No, eh?
Look at it
It can fight, it can sing
It can even stay here and not fly away
Oh, it flies away
My bird flies away
My bird has gone
My bird
Catch a goat with two fingers
I've learned everything
What do you think?
Don't push me to the limits
You don't know your limits
See what more tricks you get?
See, there's one
Sir, please forgive me
I know I'm wrong, I deserve death
But I don't want to die
So I slap myself instead
I'm a normal person I should not be in this trade
Now I am going to get some honest work
That's really touching
Uncle Bill, now you're moved
You're crazy
You hit me
Not only I want to hit you
The bystanders also want to hit you
Stupid ass
Uncle Bill...
We're both stupid
Not as smart as you
That's true
Don't think all people are fools
Uncle Bill, what do we have to do?
Right
Learn from the beginning
From the beginning
I am a fast finger
Sir
What?
I love stealing
And won't let you know I'm in love with you
I'm sorry
Don't want you to get angry with me
You never show any concern towards me!
Father, thank you
You are the only one I want
Running around you
I am running around you
Just want to hold you tight
Now in my dream
You don't speak a word
And I don't speak a word
Only if you want to be with me
You can have everything I love
I love stealing
Today I want to steal you
I am running around you
Excuse me, excuse me
I am running around just want to hold you tight
Now in my dream
You don't speak a word
I don't speak a word
Just want to walk with you everyday
You can have everything I love
I love stealing
Today I want to steal you
I am running around you...
Let's go watch a movie
What movie?
Chase under the Moonlight
Ah, one runs away and the other chases
Hey, don't run
I'll get you
Kid, you can't run away
Okay, I'll let you run
Still want to run?
I'm sorry
Run
You can't run away
Kid, now you get caught
See where you want to run?
Still want to run?
I've got him, let me go...
I've got him
This must be yours
You can keep it
Let's go
Sir, Big Bro, Uncle, Master
You have a kind heart
Please forgive us this time...
We've done the wrong thing
We're mean
We're shameless
We should not do such things
We have hands and feet
So we have to run now
Excuse me
No need to excuse
Let's go that way
What a coincidence!
We meet again
It's a coincidence
A coincidence
Shit, we meet again
One more
Lucky I didn't fall
Get them
Wait for me
Chase
Still want to fight?
I jump...
One, two, three
Please
Bye bye
You steal my purse
You...steal...
I hit you because you steal my purse
Hey, who steals your purse?
He steals my purse...
Pal, why you steal his purse?
Do I look like a thief?
Not really, then he must be the one
You...
He accuses you of stealing his purse
I stole his purse?!
When did I steal his purse?
Tell me when did I steal his purse
Hey, when did I steal your purse?
Something's going wrong with Uncle Bill
Cut the crap and help out
When did I steal your purse, huh?
Pal, tell me
He said I stole his purse
Do I look like a thief?
No
Why do you accuse me of stealing your purse?
Pal, did you steal his purse?
I really haven't stolen his purse
Not really
I can prove you haven't stolen a thing
We can prove
You can't just leave
Let's go
Get up
Now do I look like a pick pocket?
No...
It's a mistake...
Please come in, welcome
Please
Sir, welcome. Please come in
Welcome...
Sir, please
Welcome, please come in...
Welcome
Now I realize life is beautiful
That's because you haven't experienced much
I...
Let's go
Remember, don't just take small advantages
Don't try to grab a little only to lose a lot
Of course
Will make the little into big ones
I'm gonna bet on big
Last 6 times it's already opened "big"
Uncle Bill, I want to look around over there
Miss
Are you the TV star Chen Xiumei?
I'm Lin Xiumei
Such a beautiful lady
She should be Chen Xiumei
I'm pretty sure of this
Damn
So inconsiderate
What are you laughing at?
Why are you laughing?
Are you done laughing?
What's so funny?
You're still laughing
Laughing is an art
Your style of flirting with girls
is really very funny
So you're an expert at courtship or what?
Sure
Better not talk too much
Remember
Smile, a bigger smile, laugh
Then you can have every girl you want
Sounds too simple
You don't believe me, right?
There's a girl over there
Very pretty
Right
Then learn from me
How?
Don't be too pushy
One step at a time
Keep smiling
Smile, a bigger smile,
Laugh
I've done it!
What's going on...?
A funeral
Who's that?
It's you
Help!
You bloody kid, see what you've done to me
Bye bye
Blackjack, win all
Hey, I quit...let's go...
I win again...
Give it to me...win again
Bet on the big
Uncle Bill, sit down
I'll be back soon
What the hell!
You seem back from Nanyang?
Right
Heard that you have a rubber plantation, right?
No
No?
Then your father
must be a...Chief Commander
No
And your son must know how to print banknotes
Do you print US banknotes?
Printing banknotes? No
You have nothing great or powerful
Then why are you so bold?
I have some guts, so what?
It's outrageous
This chair is mine
What's wrong...?
Keep going...
You can have my seat
This is a lucky seat, you take it
I'm lucky too
It's not that easy to lose
But I do have money
It's like throwing sand into the ocean
Save your money for medicine
Oh, this is all I've left
Place your bet
Sir, please place your bet
Haven't seen the Ace yet?
Can I separate these two cards?
No
It's not a pair so you can't separate them
But he can do that
Can I separate them?
Then I'll separate them
It's 20 points and you still want to separate?
Good luck to him
See, I win big money with just a small bet
Don't be cocky, now I made a bigger bet
Deal
I've told you
It's like throwing sand into the ocean
The dealer has 18 points
Everyone wins
Except this gentleman who raised his bet
Do you still want to gamble?
Gambling is just like embroidery
You should not rush
If I gambled like you
I would lose everything in no time
Go to hell
Stop talking
Place your bet...
Okay, I'll make a bet
Hey, brother
These girls are good at dancing
They are the best
That girl on the right
Her body is sexy and she's hot
If she went to bed with me for one night
I would die for this chance
That's my daughter
I mean the one next to her
That is my wife's daughter's sister
I mean the one next to the next one
No more next
Do you know
who is sitting next to you?
I don't know
I am the father of those five girls
I'm sorry
I'll buy you a drink
Let's watch the show
Look...People are looking up to me.
They're looking at my glamour.
My body is glittering...
like many rockets crashing through.
Applause...People are applauding.
Shit, that's awful
Dash, Dash, Dash...
The centre of space is trembling.
I feel as if I'm riding a platinum elevator...
That singer has such a big mouth
Big mouth is okay
If she has a gentle heart
Big mouth ruins everything
That's not fun
What do you mean?
Use your brain and think
Even the earth seems fascinated and it's dancing
Ladies and gentlemen, next we have
a spectacular magic show coming up:
An air plane out of the air
Excuse me
Uncle Bill, how are you doing?
Winning or losing?
Uncle Bill never wins an argument
But when do I lose money?
This man next to me almost lose everything
Losing money just like bleeding
Deal
That man on the right
is not gambling here
He wants to cause trouble here. Keep an eye on him
Do you want to increase your stakes?
Okay...
Wait a sec
The cards are no good and you still want to
Sure I want to increase my stake
If I increase my stake
I could only add one extra card
If I didn't make a bigger bet
I didn't have to add an extra card
Just waiting for the dealer to blow me up
If you don't, I want to
Deal
Eight, nine...
Eight, there's some hope
A small number...
It blows up
You evil spirit
Always picking up the wrong cards
Now you don't pick the card
You know I want the big ones
Do I blow up your points?
You blow up your own points...
What's going on, pal?
What's going on?
Look at him
Why he doesn't pick up cards like these?
Why don't you pick up the cards?
I have too much money I don't want some more
Well, that's a lot of money
Of course
But they're all blank paper
He's cheating
Cheater
No entry
Stop for a while
I want to tell you something
What?
It's serious business
What serious business?
Do you want to listen or not?
Go ahead
I overheard the old guy talking to Captain Tie today
that tomorrow they would go to
Huaguo Hotel to have a meeting
What kind of meeting?
It's about your opium trade
Seems they are quite sure who's the boss
So what should we do now?
What should I do?
It's better to get rid of him
I have to make a quick move
And find someone to kill him
Dragon, are you sure about this?
Sure
This is a perfect move
Uncle Bill, why start a fight?
Don't ask, go quick
It's red, it's green
My back is broken
Hey, enough. Let's go
After them...
Brother Wai
When will you come back?
After five or six days
Have you finished yet?
A big guy like you, just keep talking
Too much sweet-talk
Xiao Ji...
Xiao Ji, when I come back
I'll give you two bottles of perfume
Okay, I believe you one more time
Don't think you can buy with some perfume
If you didn't keep your promise
I would tell Dad
about you two
What are you talking about me?
Dad...
Uncle Bill
No wonder I have a hunch today
Dad...you
Don't talk about it
It's tough to be a nice person
Uncle Bill, you are going to...
Where...to go?
You came here when I went out
It's late and you still don't want to leave
Right...It's late now
Go home and go to bed, right, Dad?
Yes, Uncle Bill
I have to go now
Dad, it's tasty
Oh dear, look at you...
Even if I offer a big dowry
No one is willing to marry you
Stop eating now
You have nothing like me
Except your pompous look
You're right, Dad
Looks perfectly like you
Right?
Go to bed early tonight
We have things to do tomorrow morning, okay?
Right, go to bed early
Wash your hands before you go to bed
It's in the genes, I can't help it
"Huaguo Hotel"
I have a meeting up there
You guys wait here
Yes
Thank you, I can take this by myself
Go and talk to him
Uncle Bill...
Why come so early?
Uncle Bill, we want to...
Buy some bean curd
Yuan
Selling bean curd is a tough job
Let me help you
I don't need your help
Yuan, let me help you
I don't need that
I can help...Fat Ass
You would help?
You two stop showing off here
Just waste your energy
Xiao Ji
Don't be partial to them
When Brother Wai comes back from the town
He'll teach you a good lesson
Does Brother Wai go to town?
Yes, he has work to do there
He goes with the Chief
Now this is our big chance
Yuan, are you free today?
Let's go to see a movie
Shit
What shit? It's so early
Shit, Uncle Bill
Why didn't you tell me early?
Last night was a chaos
How could I tell you?
Xiao Ji, give me the coat
Tell me...
Louder
Let's go
Dad...
That old guy is lucky
Such a big bomb didn't kill him
He is not killed. Then what should we do?
Don't worry
He's not safe even in the hospital
I have another plan
Hi
Uncle Bill, you said it's a drill
Why do you take this for real?
A drill or not
You have to do it for real
You act too real
Take a look at them
They're seriously beaten
They are lucky
If it's me, I have something more powerful
You...what
I...
Okay, stop talking now
We have to act according to our plan
Where's the Chief's room?
The VIP room on 2nd floor
We are sent by our God
To deliver gospel to the Chief
To save this lost lamb
God bless you
You can't go upstairs
Whafs the matter?
They want to visit the Chief
We come to save the Chief
Sorry, you can't go upstairs
But God has given the permission
You can't go upstairs...
Listen to me
Whafs the matter?
Officer, they insist to visit the Chief
Sorry, the Chief needs some rest
Please go home
My God
Listen, I know you are a good doctor
But you can only heal his body
We come to save his soul
If you didn't let us in
Then you'd have rejected God
First, Love the almighty God
Second, We have to worship God on Sundays
Third, Don't indulge in adultery
Fourth...
Okay, stop preaching
You can go inside now
Don't stay too long
Follow me
Open the door
We believe in God, not come here to preach
May God bless the Chief
Get well soon and come back to me
Peace on Earth
Lord please listen to our prayer
Please give your blessings
So prices will go down but not up
Lord please listen to our prayer
Please give your blessings
Police and hawkers become one family
Lord please listen to our prayer
the name of all the saints and the holy spirit
Amen
Open your hymn book and turn to page thirteen
That's enough...don't talk any more
The Chief needs a lot of rest
We haven't sung our hymns yet
Please go outside and sing, okay?
Thank you very much
Okay, we'll go out first
Let's try to strike a note
May God bless you...
Big mountains can be moved
Small hills can be relocated
May the Blessings always be with you
Remember the Lord
May God bless you
May God bless you...have peace
Uncle Bill
Peace...
Big mountains can be moved
Small hill can be relocated
Blessings never leave you
Uncle Bill
God
Stop shouting
I rather kill the innocent then let you go
You're vicious
God will never forgive you
God? I'm a Buddhist
What are they doing there?
Give blessings to the Chief
Blessings?
Are you alright?
Are you okay?
Use a girl as killer
Shit, that's tricky
Tricky...! almost get killed
You are now in one piece
I'm sure you should be okay
Right, it must be the nuns
Wait
It's not that simple
Stay calm
Find out what they want to do next?
Now what should we do?
If this is not finished we'll get into trouble
Big Bro, now we are...
Shut up
Now I have the last straw
Whafs that?
Give Captain Tie an order
to take the old guy back home
Take him home?
Don't you understand
But...
Don't hesitate
Do it now
Madam
Captain Tie, you've been working hard
Not at all, this is my job
It's very late
You can leave with the doctor and nurse
Right, I'll take care of the Chief
And his cousin
has brought his men here
You don't have to worry
Okay then
Let's leave now
Let's go
Please
Madam
I think the Chief should be okay
You don't have to worry about him
Don't worry
I'll take care of him
Sure
Then I'll come back tomorrow
Captain
What's going on inside?
Everything goes smoothly according to the plan
You go back and be prepared
Okay
Captain, how about me?
You come with me
What about him?
He...
I know
I'll protect Uncle Bill
Take this
What drug is it?
Don't ask
Its effect is quick
Then we can accuse them
for poisoning the Chief
But...
It should be okay
I'll wait outside
We have to take action now
Zhengqing, you're up
Don't talk
Listen to me
Doc said if you take this shot
You would need no more
You want to kill your husband
Who are you?
I'm Zhengqing
You're not
He...
Who are you?
Who do I look like?
Get him
Do you want to die?
Young lad, you don't have to pay respects
Uncle Bill
Why are you so late?
Can't beat these people
No, I just run out of air
Let me help you breathe
Catch him, quick...
What are you doing here
Thank you
Don't mention it
How are you doing?
Give Cheung some help now
Seriously injured
Look at you
Your nose and eyes are swollen
Are you okay?
Just hurt a little
Not little
Is it serious?
Take a look yourself
Then I'm finished
We're all finished
Go up
Chase him
Uncle Bill
Wow, this is grand
Uncle Bill, we've made great contribution this time
Do we have a reward?
Not only a reward, you'll have a medal
A medal
Commander...
Commander?
Commander
You do a good job
I'll give what you deserve
Thank you, Commander
These three guys...
They offered great help
I want to meet them
Okay, please come here
Commander, let me introduce
This is Ma Cheung
This is Dong Bill
This is Qiu Qi
Hi
They're...what are they doing?
Uncle Bill, please turn around
It's good for you
I don't want to show my face
I will scare people if I showed my face
You are such a fool
I don't have a pretty face too
A kind heart is the most important
Right
Our Commander treats people fairly
Turn around and salute to the Commander
Oh, it's you
I
Come and get these three guys
Wait
Uncle Bill, you...
I stole from him
Commander
At least they have helped us
Please don't be too harsh on them
Don't be too harsh?
Alright...
Serve three months in jail
Three months in jail...
Uncle Bill, what's it like in jail?
It's very comfortable
Uncle Bill, I've never been in jail
Then you should try
You'll get used to it
Let's go
Uncle Bill, when you were here last time
what was it like?
Right...
When I was here
A servant made my bed
I had meat and soup for every meal
Sun bathing during the day
Playing mahjong at night
Uncle Bill, it sounds very comfortable here
Not only that
They even give me a big welcome
Don't believe? Just yell 'Uncle Bill is back again!'
Okay, then I'll shout out: 'Uncle Bill is back again'
Uncle Bill, you're so good
I am running around
Trying to hold you tight
Uncle Bill, you're so smart
Thank you...
We want to change cells