Max!
Come here.
Let's not make the sisters wait.
Her name is Frey.
She's new here too.
Can you read?
This is a giraffe. They lived in Africa.
You can read?
Yes.
There are many robot servers, and they serve you all day.
If you live there, you'll never get sick, or old.
I'll take us there, one day.
-Really?     -Yes, I promise.
Frey and Max.
Forever.
Max, are you stealing again?
It breaks my heart. Why do you do it?
To save up ?
You want to buy a ticket to go up there?
That place is not for you, or me.
It's not fair, sister.
Why can't I go?
There are things in life that can't be explained.
We just have to accept them.
But one thing I know for sure.
You're a very special person.
One day you'll do something marvellous.
You were born for it.
My little Max.
Max, muy bueno!
Off to work, huh? Gotta get up early, to work that line.
Wanna make the world a better place?
That's real funny, I have a job. Chistoso.
Por favor ninos! You think I got money?
Do I look like I have money?
How about you, you got a little money?
Come on, whatta you got in there?
Wait a minute.
Oh, it's 5 bucks. Hey, wait a minute. I got 5 bucks, I'm rich.
I can buy my ticket to Elysium, huh?
Alright.
Please form an orderly queue. Your bus has arrived.
I don't have anything.
Checked. Move on.
Morning, Officer.
Extensive criminal history. Multiple felonies. What's in the bag?
Hair products, mostly.
I'm just fucking with...
Hey... I'm just going to work, man. There's nothing in the fucking bag.
Come on, I...
Misdemeanor: citizen disobedience.
Just going to work, man. Come on.
-Checked.     -Nothing in there, is it?
Zero-tolerance policy applies to all citizens.
No shit?
You must report immediately to your parole officer.
Thank you, Citizen.
No, thank you.
Frey, fracture in bed 2.
Max?
Frey...
I thought you were...
-When did you get back?     -Been back for a while.
-I see things haven't changed.     -No, this wasn't even my fault.
Of course not.
-Let me have a look.     -How is it?
Pretty bad break.
So you're a nurse, huh? You did it!
Yeah.
That's great.
You still stealing cars?
No, God, I don't do any of that stupid shit anymore.
I work at Armadyne. On the line, you know? Working...
-Frey, they need you up on the 3rd floor.     -Be right there.
-So, you know, now that you're back...     -Just a second.
Just a second.
Dominica, can you take over here?
Hey, listen. Now, you know, 'cause you're back and everything.
Max, I'm so sorry I have to go.
It's good to see you. Stay out of trouble.
I do.
Look...
I know why you left the neighborhood, I understand.
If I was as smart as you I would have left too.
Have dinner with me. Just...
I'll settle for a coffee.
-No.     -Aww.
Have I gotta break my other arm to get attention?
-Stop.     -...'cause I will do that.
My life is complicated, Max.
I just, I... I miss you.
-My shift ends at 8 on Wednesday, OK?     -Yeah, all right.
-Coffee.     -Yeah, coffee. Right.
Get out of here.
All parolees must have weapons inspection
Hello.
Before we start, I'd just like to explain...
Max da Costa, violation of Penal Code 2219. Today at bus stop 34-B.
Yes, that's exactly what I wanted to talk to you about.
See I believe there's been a misunderstanding.
Immediate extension of parole by a further 8 months.
Wait, What? No, no, I can explain what happened.
I just made a joke. And, you know...
Stop talking.
Police officers noted violent and antisocial behavior.
We regrettably must extend parole.
Elevation in heart rate detected.
-Would you like a pill?     -No!
Thank you, what I'd like to do is expl...
Stop talking.
Personality matrix suggests a 78.3% chance of regression to old behavior patterns.
Grand theft auto, assault with a deadly weapon,
resisting arrest.
-Would you like to talk to a human?     -No, I am OK. Thank you.
-Are you being sarcastic and/or abusive?     -Negative.
It is a federal offense to abuse a Parole Officer.
Understood.
Hey, da Costa!
-You're late for your shift.     -Yeah man, I had a little thing...
No, no. You can't work with that. You're out.
No, no, I'm good, man. I can work.
It's coming off later today. I'm fine.
-You're good?     -I'm good!
OK, I'm docking you half a day.
-Yeah, alright.     -You're lucky to have this job.
No weapons detected. You are clear for entry.
Please keep your workstation tidy.
A tidy workstation is an efficient workstation.
Hey check it out, man. I think he likes you.
Think he got his face peeled today? He looks good.
Attention: all workers must reach weekly quotas.
Please report any unsafe activity to your supervisor.
If we don't have a clear path to up-side,
our investors are going to start losing a lot of confidence.
What do you think I've been doing here, on Earth?
D'you think I enjoy breathing this air?
-No, of course, but...     -I'm doing everything possible...
to restore profitability to this company.
The company that I built.
Now, if you will excuse me,
I have to not speak to you people any longer. Thank you.
Closing 34!
Firing 34.
Tag her, quick!
Let's go, we don't have much time.
We have 3 transporter codes, Spider.
OK, pull'em up on screen.
Codes have been accepted.
Fire up the shuttles!
We're going up!
-Welcome.     -Hello, ma'am.
-Take a look at the garden.     -We will, thank you.
-Hello, Madame Delacourt.     -Hello.
Hi, Ivan, how you've grown.
Hi. You alright?
-Fine. Are the kids here?     -Yes, with Dominica.
I have a present for you. Wanna see? It's in the salon.
Go get it with your mother.
-It's, by the canape.     -OK
Bye.
Ma'am, would you care for a refreshment?
Demand's cancelled.
Sorry for disturbing you, ma'am. We have a number of undocumented ships inbound.
Good afternoon, Defense Secretary Delacourt.
3 undocumented ships are approaching Elysium airspace.
Emergency orders 6 and 7 are now in effect.
Protocol 22/B39...
Attention, incoming vessels.
You have made unauthorized entry into Elysium airspace.
-Dad!     -It's OK!
We will be forced to take immediate action.
You are in violation of Elysium airspace.
Standard warning didn't work.
15,000 kilometers and closing...
-What do you want us to do, ma'am?     -Activate Kruger.
Ma'am, according to Executive Order 355 we are unauthorized to use our assets on earth
I am authorizing you.
Yes, ma'am.
Agent 32--over. We are sending the packet--over.
Welcome, Agent Kruger!
10,000 kilometers and closing.
Sending coordinates to asset.
Three target data.
Shoot them down!
Green light, 21-B. Green light.
Missiles away!
Shit.
Impacto inminente. 10...
8... 7... 6...
5... 4... 3...
2... 1...
Two ships destroyed. 46 total casualties.
Impact in 5...
-Last missile was a miss.     -Ridiculous!
Only one made it.
Ma'am, the ship has breached our atmosphere.
First undocumented ship just touched down.
I want everyone coming out of that vehicle apprehendeded.
Identification confirmed.
Scanning.
Reconstruction process initiating.
No!
We have 32 arrests, 13 casualties, and 2 illegals at large, Ma'am.
Reconstruction complete.
You are under arrest, under the 68-C Immigration Act.
-All illegals are now in custody, ma'am.     -Yes.
Send them to deportation, Get them off this habitat.
Secretary Delacourt, please report to President Patel immediately.
Secretary Delacourt, report to President Patel.
What up, man? ?que te paso?
Lo es siempre, the police, man.
-Are you OK?     -Yeah, don't worry about it.
Max, I gotta talk to you. You know...
-No!     -What do you mean no?
You didn't even hear what I was gonna say.
-Alright, go ahead.     -OK.
You know the house of Doseta's up on the hill?
Yeah, the one with all the guns.
Yeah, they have five cars. New ones.
It's gonna be three of us. Tomorrow, at lunch.
-Lunch time?     -That's the plan?
Jesus Christ.
-You have a better plan?     -Yeah, just take one guy.
Go before the sun comes up. You take the two fastest cars.
Torch the batteries on the other ones.
Fuck you. Fuck you!
I got you, cojone!
Oh please. You're the best. Give me one year.
-I'm not going back to prison.     -One year, please!
Look at you! You used to be a legend, and now what?
The time is 5:50 am.
No weapons detected. You are clear for entry.
Closing 34!
Attention, doors are not aligned. Worker attend.
Hey, you're holding up the line.
No, no, I got a jam!
Attention: workers may not use the restroom more than once per sh...
-What've you done, da Costa?     -No, I'm just trying to reset.
Let me look.
-The pallet's pinched.     -Yeah, It didn't move.
-Just go in there.     -No, I mean...
Look, you go in there right now...
or we'll find someone who will, and you can go clean out your locker.
-Come on, man.     -No, no. That's the deal, OK?
In you go!
Let's go, people, back to work!
Fuck.
No, no, no, stop!
Hey!
Hey, come on, vamos!
Too late!
Extraction!
Sister, they beat me up.
I only want to live there.
See how beautiful it looks to us down here?
Yes.
Well, now...
See how beautiful we look to them up there.
Keep this.
Now it belongs to you.
So you never forget where you come from.
What happened?
You have been exposed to a lethal dose of radiation.
You will experience catastrophic organ failure.
In five days time, you will die.
What is going on? Why has production stopped?
-He's been exposed ...     -Don't breathe on me.
-Cover your mouth.     -I'm sorry, sir.
Does his skin fall off, or something?
I don't want to replace the bedding in there. Just get him out.
-Yes, sir.     -Right, thank you.
Mr. Carlyle, your shuttle is ready for departure.
Please sign this to receive medication.
Miporol--extremely potent.
Will keep you functioning normally until your death.
Please take one pill with each meal.
Thank you for your service.
At 15:00 hours yesterday you shot down two shuttles, killing 46 civilians.
Your mandate is to deal with illegals 'quietly'.
I am aware of that.
And then there's the use of this... agent.
A Mr. M. Kruger.
15 human rights violations...
Rapes, kidnappings, torture.
The man's been diagnosed with serious psychological issues.
We made it explicitly clear to you that we're no longer using sleeper agents.
Tell me something, President Patel.
Do you have children?
I'm not the one being reviewed here.
Then I will assume you do not.
Perhaps, if you did have children,
then you would behave in a manner
that is more conducive to the longevity of this habitat.
I understand, it is not the fashion to think and to act as I do.
I understand that perfectly.
But when they come for your house...
or the house you built for your children,..
and your children's children...
It won't be PR and campaign promises that keep them out.
It will be me!
I've heard enough! This is your final warning.
Any further unauthorized actions, and you will be removed from office.
And let's discharge this agent Kruger permanently.
All in favour?
Good. Effective immediately.
You want some beer?
You have been discharged from CCB.
Please return all weapons to local embassy.
Fuck your 'Politikster'! Fuck you!
Look...
Max...
Max!
What's wrong? What happened?
Jesus, let me help you. Let's go.
Max, what happened?
-Max, what happened?     -I shouldn't have gone in, man.
Gone in where?
I took a full dose, man.
A full dose.
You're gonna be OK. Let me help.
-You're gonna be OK, Max.     -They gave me Miporol, man.
They gave me... Miporol.
I got five fucking days! I only got five days!
You have to take this.
-They can fix this shit on Elysium, man.     -I know.
-I'm gonna go see Spider.     -Max, Max!
Take the pill!
There you go!
To see Spider, you need money.
I'll give you everything I have, but it's not enough for a ticket.
He's going to give me a ticket.
He's gonna give me a fucking ticket.
Frey, you know we've done everything we could to help your daughter.
But I had a meeting today with the board,
and they're recommending that we send her home with you.
How can I work here and leave her at home?
You know it can happen any minute, Dr. Faizel.
I know, if she has another seizure, of course bring her back here.
But until then she's discharged.
This isn't Elysium. We can't just heal her.
Max!
It's been a while, my brother!
How's life at the factory?
-I need to ask you a favour.     -What? I can't hear you. What?
I need a ticket. Up there. And an ID.
Yeah, sure sure.
Absolutely. You prefer aisle or window?
I'm being fucking serious, man.
Listen, I'm gonna come back and work for you.
Anything you need. I'll fucking pay it back.
You know what?
This... is...
priceless.
This is priceless.
Yeah, let me ask you a question.
Do you have any idea how many idiots
come in here saying the same kinda bullshit?
I got little kids coming here every day.
Max, if I were you, I'd get the fuck out of here, right now
Max, No...
I did 3 years for you.
Everything I did for you, you're gonna get me up there.
-Can you feel this?     -Go ahead and shoot.
I got so much radiation in my body right now,
you're probably getting a little sick yourself.
-You really dying?     -I'm fucking dying, motherfucker.
See this? It's over. I put the gun down.
Put the gun down! Put the gun down! Get out of here!
OK!
Listen, I've been looking for someone to take a job for me.
But no one here had the balls.
You said you'd do anything, right?
Max...
-OK.     -I'm OK.
This...
my friend,
this can be your ticket up there.
One last job for me, you earn your way up.
What is it?
Take an Elysian asshole, right?
A billionaire who's down on Earth for some business...
He's, he's here for, whatever. We hijack him.
-Fuck that!     -Relax.
The guy's like much worse.
Forget his watch, forget his ride, forget all that shit.
This, is what you take.
Organic Information, right out of his head.
I'm talking about bank codes, passwords, login data...
Access to billions.
All you have to do is plug into his brain, download the data to yours with this baby,
and bring it to me.
This is crazy, Max.
Once we verify the data, I'll give you a one way ride, all expenses paid.
Even throw in some snacks and a drink.
All you have to do is walk into a house and use the med-bay, and you're cured.
Sandro will do the surgery. You know him?
-Fuck...     -Christ!
I'm good.
Actually, you seem all weak.
And fucked up, so...
You know what? I have...
This is crazy, let's get out of here, Please, listen to me.
What the fuck am I gonna do?
I'll have them install...
...this!
A third generation Axo-suit.
We hook this into your nerval system, and it'll make you as strong as a droid.
You're already under the knife, right?
Let's get out of here, please.
I want a 4 man team. But I pick them.
I'm sending my own data wrangler.
Brain to brain, that is real tough.
OK, but I'm taking Julio. He gets a ticket up there, same as me.
Yeah, sure.
OK, I'll go get the boys ready.
Wait!
It's gotta be John Carlyle.
The CEO of Armadyne, Carlyle?
That's the mark.
Secretary Delacourt, Mr. Carlyle has arrived.
You are here to persuade me to renew our Armadyne contracts, yes?
Astute as always.
Come with me.
I'm not interested in your little ideas.
I am interested in something much larger.
This habitat is dying.
There is a political sickness inside of it. A tumor that needs to be removed.
You and your company are in need of revenue that is drying up.
So...
You built the Torus.
Can you override the servers and place a new president in power?
A coup?
Are you suggesting a coup?
Is it possible?
I could write a reboot sequence.
It'd shut down the entire system, and at that point...
you can encode a new President, yes.
Then that is what you will do.
And you will have your contract secured for the next 200 years.
Missile Defense Batteries, Droids, everything we need, to protect our liberty.
all guaranteed, of course, by your new President.
Go! Get to work, Mr. Carlyle.
This is the guy.
-He's the guy?     -This is him.
Sit down.
We're gonna cut you up good, homie.
Play nice, amigo. Play nice.
Let's get him an ID first.
Give the chief one of my identification codes.
Get that ready.
Arm up.
Weonly have
What did you find?
And we'll merge it with the DNA. Now you fit in.
Like you were born there.
Now it's time for the real fun.
Hey, man.
Yo.
This gonna hurt?
Yeah bitch, it's gonna hurt.
It's gonna hurt good.
When we're done with you, you're gonna be a  ninja.
Mariana!...
Bring down the bone saw!
This ain't gonna kill me.
You'll be airight. Not bad.
Max.
I'm here.
We got this, man.
We got this?
Yeah!
Hey!
He's awake!
Made it, huh?
Surprise!
You can still jack off, alright?
How's everything going?
Ready to kick ass?
What the fuck did you do to me?
Gave you a way out.
Shit.
What's up, partner?
How's that suit working out for you?
That shit is tight!
Show me.
Hold this.
Is it a family heirloom?
Wait for it.
Air-bursting ammunition.
Designate your enemy...
and any round you fire will explode around a 5 meter kill radius.
And...
safe detonation rounds for this bad boy.
That'll work.
Move out!
Sir...
Your shuttle is ready.
Do you read me?
Yes.
Alright, here's the deal.
We'll wait outside the factory until we see the shuttle leave.
One of you opens an explosive round in it,
goes to the crash site and gets the data.
OK, copy that.
Alright now, let's go! Let's play ball!
You nervous?
-No.     -No?
I'm shitting myself with fear.
-I'm not gonna fucking die.     -No.
Go, go, go!
Acceleration to supersonic speed in 15 seconds.
Come on, come on, come on!
Critical engine failure.
Ma'am, we have an Elysium citizen on Earth in danger.
Data coming up now...
Citizen identified. John Carlyle. N8321...
I see you, motherfucker!
I have a situation here.
Kruger, do you read me?
Ah, Ms Delacourt. How lovely to hear your voice.
There's a citizen carrying sensitive brain data out of the city right now.
Some thieves are trying to hijack it.
What's in it?
That's classified.
You don't call a recently deactivated agent to retreive classified fucking information!
The government doesn't know about this, do they?
I can ask for whatever I want, can't I?
Please brace for impact
Please remain calm. You have sustained zero injuries.
Oh, that's a real comfort.
I've got one condition. I do this, I get re-instated.
Fine.
I've recommissioned 2 of your preferred agents.
Completely confidentially, of course. They should be at your position any second.
Send me the mission data.
Let's go, guys. Out of the cars!
Droids, there appears to be some type of wheeled vehicle, with one
Two occupants.
They are armed and I'd like them dead.
Droid!
It's jammed!
Identified, Max da Costa. Federal Parole number 61492-8-557.
It's jammed, man!
Got it!
He's reloading!
-Guys! We got the bastard!     -Go! I got you covered!
Go, go, go!
Don't fucking move.
Bring it!
There's another one!
Die, motherfucker!
Don't hit the mark!
No, no! He got hit!
Citizen has sustained a cardio-thoracic trauma.
Blood pressure is dropping.
-It's not in the head!     -Is he breathing?
-No, it's in the chest!     -Well, fucking good, man.
Hold his head, hold his head.
Let me see your brain.
Come on, Come on!
-Yes.     -Is it working?
Yeah, we're syncing.
You have no idea what you're doing.
One minute to target, sir.
We're syncing. Come on, baby, here we go.
It's gonna work. We got it.
It's a data heist, ma'am. They're downloading now.
Guys, we've got incoming.
Fuck me!
Come on, guys, hurry up.
That's a Raven. That's Military.
-Alright we got this, 97...98!     -Hurry up, they're coming.
-Almost there!     -99!
In! Here we go!
Shit! Data must be corrupted!
Wait. Hold on.
I can't read the data. It's scrambled! I can't read the data.
What?
-Come on, guys! We gotta move!     -What the fuck does 'scrambled' mean?
Fuck this!
No, No! Run it again! Run it another time!
-Get off me, man! I'm bailing!     -Please. Run it again.
Fuck you! Let's get out of here.
Where the fuck are you going, Sandro?
Let's get outta here! Goddamit!
C'mon man.
Get out of there! Let's go!
We gotta go! Come on! Come on!
Hey, boss, we got a runner.
Fire!
That's what I'm talking about!
Fuck, man!
Target moving south-southwest.
Move back! It's coming!
We got another one.
Again!
This is wrong! This is all wrong, man!
Going into holding pattern, sir!
Where do you think you're going?
Come on!
Fuck!
Motherfucker!
Come on!
No!
No, no!
No! Get up!
Get up!
No!
We've got one assailant leaving on foot, ma'am.
They have the data. Repeat:
The thieves have the data.
Apprehend the target at all costs. Do not damage his brain.
Let's go! We got a runner, boys!
The citizen has suffered catastrophic blood loss leading to cardiac arrest.
Time of death, 17:45.
Come on, where are you hiding?
What's that?
Looks like a herd of pigs, boss.
Fuck you, man! Find him!
Take us back to the crash site, to see what they left behind.
Roger, that.
Thanks.
Hey boss, I think you better come look at this.
This is a record of what we picked up
being transferred between Carlyle and the criminals.
That's why she wants it so badly.
He's got the keys to the kingdom in his fucking head!
Now we just need to find him.
Gonna let the girls out.
Searching grids 3 through 11.
I'm authorising a Full Containment Order.
Issue a No Fly Zone for Los Angeles.
-All of Los Angeles?     -The murderer's still out there.
Until we apprehend him, no one leaves the surface of that city.
What the f...?
Max.
-Hey, sweety!     -Hey.
We can go home.
Am I better?
I'm gonna get the car, OK?
Be right back.
Frey...
Max!
My God, what happened to you?
-Shit, I'm gonna get the medics.     -No, no!
-I can't go in there.     -Max!
-I can't go in...     -Max, listen, you need a doctor, OK?
People are looking for me. They're gonna kill me.
-I came here for you. I need your help.     -Max!
You've got to go through the system to get treatment.
Please help me. I don't wanna die.
Max!
Stay awake!
-I wanna see the man.     -Mama's gonna help him, OK?
Try and sleep.
Don't sleep!
You're too heavy for me. Max, help me!
Come on!
Max, you can do it, come on!
No, wait. Let's turn you over!
Max, Max, wait.
-Thank you.     -Who did this to you?
I don't know. I got-I got hurt at at work.
I had to take a job from Spider to try to get up there and get healed.
It went bad, now I'm in trouble.
Mommy?
Hey, sweety, come here!
Who is that man?
His name is Max. Mommy knew him when he was your age.
-It's Matilda.     -Hi!
You can go watch cartoons, OK?
I'll be right there.
I didn't know you had... I'm so sorry, I need to go.
-Wait, Max, you can not leave.     -I shouldn't have come here. I have to leave!
Max! She's dying. She's in the final stages of leukemia.
I told you my life complicated. I need you to help me.
-I've no idea how to do this.     -How to do what?
-Get her to Elysium.     -I can't help her. I...
I would if I could.
How about this? Fake citizenship. If you took her there,
-could you heal her with this?     -It doesn't work that way.
This is coded to me, it's locked to my DNA.
The people looking for me. They... You don't understand who these people are.
If they find me here, they will kill all of us.
The only thing I can do to help you is leave. I promise you.
-She's all I have.     -I'm sorry.
You have bandages.
Yeah. I got bandages.
What are you doing?
I don't want you to be sick. You wanna hear a story?
N.., ah...
There once was a meerkat who lived in the jungle.
He was hungry and he was small.
So small.
And the other big animals had all the food, 'cause they could reach the fruits.
So he made friends with a hippopotamus
OK, stop!
It doesn't end well for the meerkat.
Yes, it does 'cause he can stand on the hippopotamus' back
to get all the fruits that he wants.
-What's in it for the hippo?     -The hippo wants a friend.
I'm sorry.
Hey, boss.
I think we got him.
Yank this fucking cunt!
-Mommy, is everything OK?     -It's OK, sweety.
Clear!
What is this?
Good afternoon.
Sorry to come bursting into your home. Didn't mean to...
traumatize your young daughter.
Me and the boys here are looking for a young gentleman...
who was in this very house a moment ago.
We're hoping you can tell us where he went.
No.
I...
-I don't know where he is.     -I don't believe in ...
...committing violent acts in front of the kids.
So I just need you to close your eyes, sweetheart.
-It's OK.     -I really need you to tell me.
Hey?
-You remember now?     -Mommy!
Close your eyes, keep your fucking eyes closed.
Keep her eyes closed.
Please, I don't know where he is.
He was wounded, I helped him and he left.
Please!
D'you fucking hear that? No loyalty nowadays, hey?
What's this here?
-This a hospital you're running here?     -She's sick.
She's sick? Let me have a look at her... Alright!
-Don't touch her.     -See that? Protective instinct, here!
I said don't touch her!
I'm just trying to get a word with your child.
Don't touch her!
-Bring her. Come!     -Where are you taking her?
-Now I've got something you want.     -Sweety, it's OK.
It's OK, darling. It's OK.
Sit down! Shut up!
Stop!
No, no, don't shoot him! Put the gun down! Let him come!
-You got something, didn't you?     -What?
That's why they shut down the sky... what is it?
Wire transfers? Corporate intel? You gotta have something big in there!
No. I fucking got nothing, man!
It all got scrambled. Julio is dead. You owe me. Let's go fucking now!
We can't! The flight system is jammed!
Nobody is going up there.
-Until when?     -Till I don't fucking know.
-I gotta fucking get up there!     -Everyone needs to get up there.
My guys are working on it.
See if they have a hope in hell of ever getting back online.
But, for now...
Let's just take a look at that head of yours.
Get away from me, man!
Look at me, if they shut down the whole fucking sky,
for what's in your head...
Maybe the key to opening it could be in there too, right?
Come on.
Alright.
They will hunt you to the edge of the world for this.
What is it?
It's a reboot program for Elysium.
Whoever has this, has the power to override their whole system.
Open the borders...
Make everyone a citizen of Elysium.
This can save your life.
-We can save everyone.     -When can I go?
They're trying to hack through the signal jam, but soon...
-Don't bullshit me, when can we go?     -I dunno.
Five days... a week?
Fuck you, I don't have 5 days! I got hours.
My guys are working on it.
You're always working on it, You can't get me up there.
I don't know why you try sending people up there,
they just get fucking shot down.
Not with what's in your head! That's what I'm talking about!
We would control the system. We would be in charge!
We can change the course of fucking history!
Back up then.
What I have in my head, is worth a lot to them, right?
Don't do this.
If that falls into the wrong hands, they could shut us out for good.
Listen, man, I'm going up there right now.
If you can find me, and I'm healed, you can have all of this.
-But I'm not fucking dying.     -This is wrong, Max, don't do this.
Don't shoot him! Don't shoot him!
It's OK. It's OK.
I always wanted a wife.
Just couldn't quite settle down, you know? Too much temptation.
But you...
You make me ready to settle down.
You really make me want to settle down, baby.
-Holy shit, sir.     -Eh?
You better come take a look at this.
-What is it?     -Check this fucking oak.
Turn us around.
-Take it.     -Right, sir.
Open the door.
Stop right there, and you're gonna do exactly what I say.
Or I'm gonna blow my fucking head off, you understand?
Yeah!
You can have everything in my head!
Just take me up there, and get me in a med-bay.
-What I have is very valuable.     -We can fix you up.
Put you in a med-bay, Sort all this cock-up.
Let's go! We'll take you up there.
Weather's nice, air's nice and clean. Likely you'll dig it.
-Don't you fucking try anything!     -Step aboard!
Come meet the boys, come on!
Don't be shy, they won't bite.
Let me introduce you. This is Drakie. This is Max.
What is news?
Let's fly!
Yes, ma'am, we apprehended the subject.
-Open the skies, we're coming up.     -I'll expect you in 19 minutes.
-Cancel the No Fly Zone.     -Yes, ma'am.
Hold it...
Hold it. What is that? ...
Are we back? Marcelo! What the fuck is that? Are we back?
We're back online, Spider.
Frey...
I'm sorry. I'm gonna make this right.
-We've got him.     -Alright. Where is he?
He's leaving Earth... Heading to Elysium.
Manuel! Rico! Get weapons! Let's get up there.
Echo leader 234, requesting landing in sector 22.
Roger that Echo leader 234. You are clear for entry...
-I see you got the G-1 there.     -Hey, back the fuck up!
-Or what?     -I'll let it go.
What you gonna do? Huh?
I want what's in your head, boy. Kill him!
Grab him, Deck!
What do you want us to do, ma'am?
I want everyone coming out of that vehicle apprehended by Homeland Security.
Evacuate everyone on the level five clearence out of the building, now.
I warned you of this.
An unlicenced vehicle just crashed potentially threatening the Torus.
All because of your inability to act. Evacuate him.
-Get your hands off me.     -This is an act of war.
That puts the CCB under my control.
Now, if you'll let me do my job.
I'm sure you have a fund raiser to attend.
Let's go, sir.
Max!
Take me out of here, Max!
I'm trying!
Air quality reaching toxic levels.
Get me out of here!
It is recommended you exit the craft immediately.
Run!
Fuck!
2 Illegals heading northeast in zone 3
You deal with those two. I'll handle this pussy.
Welcome to the spectacular properties from your...
Error
No!
No citizen detected.
Please she's sick, help us. She's gone into a coma.
Please!
Shouldn't we remove this thing?
Can't, till we get all the data.
It's wired into him neurologically.
The data is intact, yes?
Data looks intact.
Warning
We can still pull this data out of him, which will kill him.
Oh, it's fine.
How long before you can download and turn the system online?
Not long, Ma'am.
Keep everything in a restricted cloud. Lock down all access.
Starting prep right now.
And get these two out of here.
Roger that.
Kurt, you wanna go get the boss' chicks?
Yeah, good.
Give them the runaround.
Keep them busy.
Got him!
Let's go!
Alright. 50 exabytes, buddy. Are you ready?
What are you taking out of him?
Hey! What're you doing to him?
What's gonna happen to him? Hey!
Rise and shine.
-Get up!     -Max.
Max. Max. Max!
Get in there!
Yes. Boss got fucked up, eh?
Ate that fucking grenade, eh!
His brain is fine. But he's gonna be pissed when he wakes up.
Remember what cock-up happened in India when he lost his hat?
Kruger.
Boss?
It's Crowe.
Where is he?
All right, all set. Let's reach the data.
I got the needle prepped. You wanna grab this?
Grab the needle! Grab the needle! Grab the...
-Where did they take the girls?     -The Armory.
Where the fuck is that?
Level three.
Lethal radiation poisoning detected. You require urgent medical attention.
You idiot! Do you realize what you've done?
You crashed an unlicensed vehicle into a suburban area.
Your orders were to keep this covert.
Do you even remember what that means?
Have you completely lost your mind? You're useless to me.
If the administration realized what we're doing,
they'd hang us both for treason.
For God's sake, Kruger! Are you listening to me?
Yes.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm listening.
I'm sorry that we crashed the vehicle and ruined someone's lawn.
But nobody is gonna hang us for treason.
We do the hanging!
Put your hand on it, keep pressure on it.
How tough you be now, eh?
Right boys, Elysium is about to get its first proper president.
She needs some medical attention.
I was gonna heal your daughter.
But now, I'll make sure she's never healed.
Drakie, don't trust any of those politicians!
Clear out this whole building!
Thank you, boss.
I'm gonna find that little gangster.
I'm gonna take what's in his head. This place is mine now.
You want to come to my fucking house and play?
Let's play!
I'm going to annihilate that little motherfucker.
Hey!
What the hell was that?
All members of CCB please go to the nearest exit and proceed calmly to...
Go, go, go!
No.
Citizen deceased
Emergency systems are now online
Please follow indicated procedures
Spider!
Do you read me, Spider?
Max, where are you.
The thing in my head, it can make everyone a citizen here, right?
Yeah.
You know how to get it out, right?
Yes.
You're sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
OK, listen to me carefully.
Armory selected.
Set.
Turn me on.
OK.
Crowe, get rid of those two.
My pleasure, boss. My pleasure.
Where are you, Pikey? Where are you?
How is it, girl?
Let's play.
-Come on, I'll be nice. Gentle, I promise.     -No. Please.
-Come on.     -Get off me!
-Want me to hurt the girl?     -No.
Then come here.
Fuck!
She alive?
For now.
Stay behind me.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
I have a plan.
D'you hear that sound?
That's the sound of me coming for you.
I'll find you! I'll hunt you down!
Frey, we have to split up.
-What?     -Listen.
You're gonna go to the surface, OK? Take this.
Find a house, get her to a med-bay.
-Max, it won't work.     -Don't stop. Don't stop...
She doesn't have an ID. It doesn't work.
It will this time. I know how to fix it.
-Surface selected     -Go.
Come with me.
-I'm right behind you.     -No.
I promise.
OK, a mother and her daughter just went up in that elevator.
They're going to the surface headed for a med-bay.
Send one of your guys make sure they get there.
And we have our deal.
Right to a med-bay, man.
-Let's go.     -Let's go.
-Go, go, go!     -This way!
Hurry up, man.
...emergency lock down...
Almost there. Almost there.
What's that?
It's just a ... bitch!
That's what I'm talking about.
Fire has been detected...
Hold the door! Hold the door!
...have been shut down.
-Come on! Come on!     -Go, go, go
Let's go!
Fuck. C'mon!
Go! You first. C'mon!
Come on! Stand up!
Stand! Stand up! Come on!
Stand up!
You little fucker.
I'm gonna take your fucking head off!
Dude, you should definitely stand up now!
No!
Stay there.
Fuck!
-You think you could get through me?     -Come on, Max! Come on!
I'm just getting started.
Come on.
Don't give up now. Get up, come! Come on!
You want more than this? I know you.
You look a little bit dizzy, eh?
Did I get you?
Are you bleeding? You must get that looked at.
Hey, boy?
You wanna heal that little girl?
You just need to come through me.
You got some fire in you, boy.
You almost had me.
We die together, boy.
Come on, man, let's go.
Let's go, man, let's do it. Come on!
Ready? Let's go.
Get the guards, now!
Alright.
This'll do it.
Hurry.
OK, we're good, we're good.
We're good.
What?
Max.
It's OK. I know.
There's no coming back from this.
No med-bay can heal you.
Alright, give it to me.
Take it.
OK.
You just have to press that button.
Frey?
Max? Max where are you?
I'm gonna have to break my promise.
I can't make it back up there.
You remember what I said when we were kids?
Yes.
I'll take us there one day.
-Really?     -Yeah, I promise.
You wouldn't believe what I'm looking at right now.
Tell Matilda I really liked her story.
I figured out why the Hippo did it.
Come on!
You go first. Come on!
We all have something special, Max.
Something we're destined to do.
Something for which we were born.
Fuck you!
Let go of me!
Come on, please.
My baby. My dear.
Stand down, Officers.
Arrest him.
I can not arrest a citizen of Elysium.
What?
Doing a great job.
Guess who Elysium belongs to now?
See how beautiful it looks to us down here?
Now look how beautiful we look from up there.
Now it belongs to you.
So you'll never forget where you come from.
My little Max.
字
字幕
字幕製
字幕製作
字幕製作 ★
字幕製作 ★ 至
字幕製作 ★ 至宏
字幕製作 ★ 至宏上
字幕製作 ★ 至宏上人