更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
-B.P. is spiking. -Oh, God, I'm in pain!
-When did it start? -Last night.
Is your wife due soon?
-Not for another 5 weeks. -I'm fine,
-I'm getting better. I'm getting better. -What's the B.P.?
Still high.
We can fix it, don't worry.
Nolan... Nolan...
What?
Tell me something, please. Tell me anything.
You're gonna be okay. Alright?
I want you to lay back down.
-Okay. -Lay back down and breathe.
Just breathe.
Wait here.
Oh, my baby!
Do think a strong category 4 or a 5...
so certainly devastating...
deaths which occurred at the cone, which you'll see in a moment.
The cone will cross right through New Orleans,
but as of 5 am Central time just, look at this storm.
I mean, meteorologically speaking it really is a perfect hurricane
with high cloud tops high and visible.
Oh, my God. Everyone move to the lobby upstairs!
O.R. lobby! O.R. lobby! Take the stairs! Second floor.
Let's go. Let's go!
Sir? I need you to go upstairs.
The Doctor told me to wait here.
I understand, but the doctors will know where to find you. Okay?
Just before dawn Katrina heads north west straight for the coast.
Down a hair from its 175 miles per hour peak,
and New Orleans buckles in for a bumpy ride...
Manuel Diego!
Is there a Manuel Diego here?
Mister Hayes? Walk with me.
So, how is she?
It is a she. Did you know that?
What? Know what?
You have a baby girl.
A girl?
Let me show you where we're keeping her
but do know that we'll need to monitor her for the next few days.
The NICU is, is overcrowded
so I've got her in a private room.
Okay. So, how's Abigail doing?
We transfused all that we had. I want you to know that.
Doctor Mendolson and I we did all we could, but...
her liver had given up.
She bled out.
I'm sorry.
Okay. Okay, so...?
Mister Hayes.
I'm really sorry.
She expired at seven this morning.
Not Abby.
No.
-I'm sorry. -Not my Abby. She's fine.
Tell me she's fine.
I swear to God you better tell me she's fine right now.
Just tell me she's okay. Let's just, let's go see her. She's okay, right?
Mister Hayes, let...
Don't touch me, though. I want you to tell me.
Just tell me she's okay.
I'm sorry, Mister Hayes.
No, not sorry. I don't want sorry. I want...
Mister Haynes,
let me take you to see your daughter.
Yeah.
Here at the end.
There she is.
What is this?
This is a ventilator.
Your daughter hasn't yet learned how to breathe on her own, so...
this is giving her a little help.
Now we got an I.V. drip to feed her nutrients and...
she'll be big and healthy before you know.
You have any questions?
How's Abigail?
-I'm gonna give you something, It'll help you. -No. Listen to me.
I'm okay. It was just a stupid question.
It's okay. It's alright.
I'm gonna have a nurse check on you.
How long will this baby need the machine?
Your daughter? The best guess is... 48 hours.
But it's still too early to tell.
You'll know you're out of danger is when she starts crying.
The first time she does it's always a good sound.
-I'll be back. -Alright. And, Doctor Edmonds...
with this storm are you gonna be moving people out?
It's a hurricane.
Look, people are gonna tell you
it's better at Charity, or Lindy Boggs.
It won't be. Stay with your daughter, Mister Hayes. Okay?
I don't know you.
I'm panicky. It's just going bad for me.
I see a gun and I see this guy going for it,
so I start wrestling with him the best that I can.
Mind you? This is all happening in the middle of the day,
right outside of the bank, in the parking lot. Sorry.
-That's when I rob all my banks. -Hush.
So the driver gets out of the car and he comes running over.
Meanwhile I'm playing keep-away with the guy for the gun,
-but the driver doesn't go for the gun. -He goes for the money.
The duffel bag.
So he grabs the duffel bag, the driver, and he runs back to the car.
Mean while Mr. pantyhose face is screaming...
He was, like, "Larry! Larry don't you dare!"
Yeah. So, Larry, the getaway driver, hightails it out of there.
He's peeling out, he's just about to the street
when this little car comes out of nowhere...
-My car is not that little. -It's a little car.
It got the job done, didn't it?
You wanna tell the story or should I finish?
Okay. Anyway, I get out, I run over,
and I mace him as he's getting out of his car.
Yeah, it was hairspray.
There's no mace about it. That was hairspray.
I blinded him and he couldn't run.
I did my job. And the police got there shortly afterwards and...
-we saved the day... Yeah. -Yeah.
-That's how we met. -Yeah.
Oh my god you two.
-You're like an old married couple. -I worry about your kids.
-Oh, we're not having kids. -No, we're not married.
Abby.
I don't want the baby now.
I want you back.
I want you.
Please...
Sir?
You can't be back here.
She's my wife.
She's my wife
I'm sorry. But this area is off limits.
Well, she shouldn't be on the floor like this.
We're running short on staff today, there's a backlog.
Well, whatever, let's get a body bag or something,
we'll put her in a body bag...
There really isn't anywhere else for her to go.
It will only take a minute. Let's just get her on some higher ground please.
Come on, get her feet.
Okay.
Thank you.
I mean that.
It's okay.
I'm sorry for your loss.
How did she die?
Giving birth to our daughter.
Well, at least you have a child.
That's good news.
Thousands of others sound sleep when the noise started.
It was Katrina hammering away at the roof, trying to get in.
You have one saved message.
Hey love. I know I said I was okay but my heart is racing and, okay,
so, should we chance that out to the hospital,
or do we try to get out of town, because I,
I don't know if it's just nerves or something serious.
You decide. I trust you.
To replay this message, press...
Hey love. I know I said I was okay but my heart is racing and, okay,
so, should we chance that out to the hospital,
or do we try to get out of town, because I,
I don't know if this is just nerves or something ser...
-Mister Hayes? -Uh, yeah.
Hi. I'm Shelly.
Hi. Nolan.
This is my turf, so if you need anything, you let me know.
-Okay. -Okay? And I've got something for you.
It's your daughter's birth certificate.
You have a name for her?
No. We talked about it.
I liked Haley.
But my wife liked anything but Haley.
Yeah.
Well, Katrina seems to be a popular name right now.
You know, ah... Abby's favorite place...
my wife, she...
she really liked this tree, it was in a park by our house...
a few years ago, it was struck by lightning.
We'd have picnics there.
She always said it was a safe haven.
Because of that old saying that...
-lightning never strikes twice in the same place... -Yeah. Right.
Do you think that's real?
About lightning?
Well, yeah, I suppose so.
Well, maybe is not just lightening.
What happens if the power goes out?
The generators will kick in. We'll be okay.
This place has weathered storms before.
And most of our equipment has battery backup.
Alright.
It's gonna be okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You heard her. Everything's gonna be okay.
-Hey, what's going on? -Come on, we gotta go.
-This way people! -Alright, everyone stay together.
-Hey, what's going on? -Evacuating. We got three drivers. Come on.
Everyone to the rear entrance.
-Hey, Doctor Edmonds? -Mister Hayes.
-I thought you said it was bad everywhere. -This is not my call.
Calm and orderly, please!
Is there something wrong with the hospital?
We're overcrowded and understaffed.
The administration just got nervous, that's all.
It's just a partial evacuation.
Okay. Then what are you gonna do with my daughter?
That ventilator isn't portable.
If they order a full evacuation,
we'll get you a private ride to Charity. Okay?
-So, you come back then? -No, I'm not leaving.
If there's something I can do, just let me know.
Sure.
Stop the storm.
Let's move!
Hey! You missed the party, man.
Yeah, it looks like it.
You going to Charity?
What?
Charity Hospital, man. People are leaving.
No. I have to stay here.
You know we're closing the cafeteria in a few minutes.
Do you think you can get me some food?
No, man. The nurses took what was left. Sorry.
You think maybe you can get some coins?
The ones on the first floor,
they're gonna be picked over, but if you take the stairs up to four,
there's gonna be a little waiting area outside surgery.
Okay. Thank you.
They're sending me out on the next bus.
Tulane they got food, but no cooks.
-Alright. Well, good luck. -You too.
Wait.
Some luncheon meat.
No bread, but salami, some turkey...
Take it, man.
-Nah. No. I can't take your food. -I don't need it like you do.
I was about to get mad.
-I appreciate it. -Don't eat that all at once, though.
Yeah, finally some good news.
A levy that has broken on Lake Pontchartrain from New Orleans.
This is new video that we have just gotten in,
we're seeing it for the first time.
Nothing to stop this water from just pouring in right now...
What the hell is that?
What's that?
No, no, no, no!
Yes... Okay.
No.
No, don't do this to me.
Stupid machine.
No.
No. Hey! Hey, we got a bad battery in here!
Hey, is anybody on this floor? Nurse?
I need a battery. Battery. Battery.
Alright, hold on.
Alright.
I hear you'!
Come on, you, stupid battery!
Won't hold a charge.
Hey! Can somebody get their ass in here, please?!
I could really use some help!
Hey, is anybody here?!
Oh, my God! The first floor's flooding.
Hey, we're in 204.
Room 204, please!
Somebody please!
Nolan?
Shelly.
The levees broke. The streets are flooding.
The back entrance is still okay. You can go out that way.
No, wait. We gotta get her out of here then.
We gotta get out the whole thing.
The battery's old and it's only taking a small charge.
If you look at it, it's only good for 3 minutes.
Move her where?
We could roll it out. Put it on the bus and get it out.
There's no buses.
We can go up a couple of floors, go to the roof top
and wait for a helicopter to come and...
No. The power is out
we can't get that thing up the stairs by ourselves.
We'll have to wait 'til the power comes back on
and then we'll get you a Medevac.
-What, so we're stranded here? -Just until power comes back.
Where's Doctor Edmonds at?
He left an hour ago.
-What? -He went with some of the ICU patients.
He was going to come back with the bus drivers,
but then the levees broke and...
Shit!
Pump!
Okay, well, I'm not leaving!
Shelly listen, I'm not leaving, so, think about it.
What else could we do? Come here. What else can we do?
Okay.
What?
I'll go get help.
Okay? Just hang in there.
Yeah. Well, okay. Go.
-Okay? -Yes. Please, go. You're right.
Go, please, but, hurry, Shelly.
Come on, alright? Hurry!
I'm told that the New Orleans Police
put out a call to all of its officers saying...
if you have a boat bring it here, help us.
But the officers who have boats cannot get to them in many cases,
because the roads are floaded to their homes.
I don't think you want some, huh?
You don't. It's not good for babies.
That's the good stuff.
That's what's good for you.
You like it, don't you?
No.
I'm not going crazy, I just feel like talking.
Your mother,
she had a hard time sleeping at night.
But in the day time,
she was this real force of nature, she just...
She ran her own business, and...
She carried herself like a drill sergeant, you know.
She...
she was bulletproof.
That's what she was.
But at night she had these...
she'd have these stress dreams and...
I'd lay there in bed and...
I would, I would just say anything really, I'd tell her how much I loved her,
and I would tell her how everything was going to be okay.
And...
you know, most of the times, she'd sleep the entire night through.
You would have really loved her.
Let's see what else we got.
Baby blanket?
Latex gloves. What are these?
Diapers.
I didn't even think about that. You probably need your diaper changed.
We got daddy diaper directions.
We don't need you. Go away.
Little diapers for a little baby.
Why isn't that working?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, this is bad.
God! What has your Mom been feeding you? Charcoal?
Alright. Let's get this one out of there.
Okay. Where am I putting this?
Let's get a couple of pieces going.
How does that feel? Does it feel alright?
Someone please get the next one. 'Cause I am tapped out.
Did they give you one of these reports to fill in?
No.
God! I hate paperwork.
I'm Nolan, by the way.
Abigail.
-Pleasure to meet you. -Nice to meet you.
I got suckered. I thought they were gonna deputize me or something.
What a gyp.
Yeah, I don't think it works like that.
Well it should. I totally stopped that getaway driver.
-You saw that, right? -No, No, I saw that.
-That was really good work. -Yeah.
-Yeah. You've done that before. -Yeah, clearly.
Maybe you can get a reward too. For walking into the other guy.
-Oh, you mean the guy with the gun. -Yeah, that one.
-That guy. -That guy.
-Yeah. -Yeah.
What if I don't wanna be deputized?
Well then what are you asking for?
Dinner.
That sounds lovely.
Okay. Alright, but I'm driving.
-Oh, yeah? -I just figure,
in case on the way we see a jaywalker and you,
all of a sudden, get this urge to run him over...
-Yeah? -Yeah.
-Really? ...You had to go there. -Yeah.
-Yeah, we gotta avoid that stuff. -You know what?
When I'm deputy tat's gonna be legal.
Yeah, we had our first date that night and then,
what, a month later we moved in together.
Everyone thought we were being crazy, but,
I don't know, it just felt right with her.
I don't know how else to say it. It just felt right.
That's not even the best story. When I proposed...
What?
What now?
Shit!
No.
You're kidding.
Shit! Alright, I'll be back.
Okay.
Shit!
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
The sticker.
Shit.
Okay.
Okay. Okay, okay, okay,
Dammit wait! Wait!
Are you kidding me?
Bingo! Bingo!
Good.
Orange ones.
Okay, good. Okay, good.
Grab some more.
One more over there.
I got the orange ones. I got the orange ones!
Hold on, baby.
Okay,
Alright. I can do this. That's right.
Yeah.
Good.
I'm back.
Everything's gonna be all right, sweetheart.
Yeah, everything's gonna be okay.
And those problems are likely to linger, Brian.
The water is a problem for, throughout the metro area.
People are being told to boil it and electricity is also the problem.
Hardly anybody has it
and isn't likely to have it for up to a month.
This is your Mom.
She was on a panel at a convention.
And... the convention was on event planning,
It was really just an event to discuss planning other events.
I keep this picture because...
she'd argue that she didn't look cute when she was angry.
And she used to hate it when I told her that.
Yeah.
Pretty cute, huh?
Let me see what else we have.
I hear you.
Okay, here we go.
This is when I proposed to your Mom.
Let me preface by saying that before I started dating your mother...
she hated the idea of marriage.
She said it was "the death of the individual."
Yeah. So she plans this romantic getaway to this beach.
It was really a business write-off
because the hotel was trying to get her to host events there.
And... I don't know,
I just thought it'd be a perfect time to pop the question, so...
I had my grandmother's ring restored.
They gave these to me before your mother went into labor.
You know.
Well, we went to dinner that night.
And it was this...
it was a fancy restaurant at the end of this pier.
It was perfect, really, so, you know, the drink order came and...
I dropped to one knee, pulled the ring out...
she got mad.
She got so mad at me,
her nostrils flaring, all-the-way mad.
I didn't know what was going on.
She gets up and she throws her napkin down on the table.
I thought I was gonna shatter into a million pieces.
That's why I asked her. "What's wrong?"
And she pulled out this ring.
She said, "You, idiot, I was gonna propose to you!"
That's when this roving photographer snapped this photo of us.
What else do I have?
You know that's somebody I would have liked you to met.
You two are quite alike, really.
This here? This is your life.
This is you at 3 months.
Kinda look like you're laying in a hammock. You think?
Let's see what we got.
Oh, this is when you had us really worried.
You were trying to get all your nutrients from your Mom.
You were doing the best you could, but, we didn't know.
This was a month later. You see that?
Your Mom was on this crazy diet, she was taking vitamins and supplements,
everything that she could to keep you healthy
and you just kept hanging on.
You're a fighter.
That's what the Doctors kept saying.
Kinda like your granddad.
All action and no words.
Now you got me.
Time for me to do the heavy lifting.
I gotta put in my hours.
And I'm on the clock.
There's been some huge health concerns
with poisonous snakes out there, fire ants
and mosquitos infecting the city. Have you heard much
about how concerned health officials are about those folks whom...
weren't fortunate to get out.
When you start working again, I'll hear you.
Radio.
Yes.
Okay.
Be right back.
Hello? Hello, can anybody hear me?
Hello?
Hello, can anybody hear me?
Come on!
No! Go, go, go!
This is Commander John Engel of the U.S. Coast Guard.
Anyone broadcasting on this channel, over.
Please, respond, over.
If you can hear this but cannot respond, turn to channel twelve
-for evacuation emergency precautions. -I hear you! No! Stay on!
Yeah. Hello?
Hello. Hey, can you hear me? This is Nolan Hayes.
I'm at Saint Mary's Hospital.
I got a baby on a ventilator that needs a rescue team.
Right away, please. She needs to be moved!
-Anyone attempting to enter the city in the next... -Hello?
-Evac... -Hello?
-Please... -Hey, can you hear me?
Remain calm, avoid traveling or wading in the water.
This message will repeat.
What?
A little while ago you were giving me two minutes.
I want two minutes! Please, two minutes. Come on!
You're playing dirty, Mister Machine.
No. Okay.
Okay.
Yeah.
How flooded do you think the generator room is?
Yeah. I'm gonna go check. Alright? I'm gonna go check.
Stupid machine.
Oh, man! Damn!
Jesus!
Yeah!
Alright. Here we go. Get you over there.
1  2\nOne, two...
Son of a... bitch!
Are you kidding me? Come on!
Alright.
Shit!
No! No. No, no. God!
Yes. Yes.
Yes. Okay.
1  2\nOne, two...
Come on. Ready?
Come on!
Don't be a pussy. Let's go.
1  2  3\nOne, two, three...
Yes!
Okay. Okay. Alright.
I'm going. I'm going!
Come back. Come back, please.
I didn't mean to be gone for so long.
Yes. Thank you.
Thank you, machine. Thank you.
No.
Now, the Coast Guard has been spending much of its time...
with 17 helicopters in the area,
rescuing people in and around the area,
literally pulling people off rooftops...
All empty.
Gimme something. Come on!
Okay. Okay, he's getting closer. He's getting closer!
Okay. I got you.
Shit!
I know, sweetheart.
I know.
I hear you.
Okay.
What?
We're gonna give this one more try.
What am I gonna do when I get to the roof, huh?
Okay.
Yes.
Bingo!
Oh! Shit!
No!
Hey! Hey! Right here!
Yeah, come on!
Come on down!
Come on. Yeah, we're here!
Yeah, come on!
You come pick us up first!
No, wait! Wait! Wait!
No! Come back! Come back!
Goddammit! Goddammit!
That was our way out. That was our way out!
Hospital already without power or supplies,
sniper fire hold up effort to evacuate patients.
Another hospital official said
a gunman tried to take a nurse hostage...
demanding a seat on a helicopter...
Hello?
Where you at?
Oh, I got you.
You may as well just come out.
What the...?
Hey, buddy.
What are you doing in there?
You okay?
Are you tangled up there?
Oh, you're tangled up, huh?
Just take it easy. Stay.
Well...
Damnit!
Alright, well, I'll be back.
I'll be right back.
Son of a bitch.
Well, what do you say?
Easy.
Okay?
Oh, come on. You don't wanna bite the hand that frees you.
Alright? Now be a good dog. We're gonna do this.
Let's get this.
Don't you bite me.
Big ass teeth.
Don't bite it. That's okay.
Come on. I know. I know, I know, I know, I know. Hold on.
It's okay. Easy. I'm getting this off.
Alright.
Good job.
Good boy.
Hang in there, Abby. Okay?
What are you doing out there in the hall?
Don't be a stranger. It's okay. Come on. Come say hey.
Come on.
Don't be scared, you, big chicken.
Okay. I know what you want.
There you go.
Go ahead.
That's what I thought.
So, pooch, you have a name? Hm?
Shadow?
Spot?
Or Storm?
Storm. Kind of fit it right now. Storm, it's good.
Work with me, man, these, these are cool names.
Brutus. You gotta like Brutus.
That's like a compliment.
It's gonna take a while, obviously. You might as well take a nap.
Clearly you're smarter than I thought,
Sherlock. You like Sherlock?
Sherlock.
It's kind of cool.
Well, it's settled, then. You're Sherlock.
Oh, but you got a tag. Let's see what your real name is.
Rescue dog, huh?
Hope you're embarrassed.
Pretty amazing, huh?
Yeah? What do you think of this?
Gets old in about two seconds. Trust me.
Baby, come on. We gotta go.
It's this earring is not cooperating.
Yeah, we're gonna be late.
How do I look?
Holy hell!
What?
Okay. Okay.
We don't have time for this.
We don't have time? Hmm?
You'll get us late! Ah! You spoiled my makeup. Nolan!
-That's our reservation. -No, it's not.
Yeah. I should pick that up. Can, can you please...?
That did not feel like married sex at all.
Yeah. Yeah, we should get dressed before my wife gets back.
What? What did...
That was the start of you.
Okay.
Back at it.
See? I told you this was exciting.
What do you want now?
Oh. Okay, Mister Machine.
Okay. Okay.
It this the last one?
Okay.
Last one.
You hanging in there, Abby?
That looks good.
Okay. Good.
I wanted this.
Okay, good.
This is for you.
You play fetch?
You play fetch? Oh, yeah. You play fetch.
Let me see what you got.
Let it go. No, this isn't tug of war.
Okay. Let me give you a better throw. Okay?
Down the hall., Come on, Let's go.
Yeah, buddy. Come on. Down the hall.
Down the hall. Down the hall. All the way down the hall.
Alright, Abby.
Let's see how crafty Daddy can be here.
Okay.
Okay. This should work.
Let's just try it like that.
Stretch it tight.
Thank you.
No. That's mine. I gotta focus on this right now.
But you can watch. Watch this.
What am I still doing here?
Where's that dog going?
Hey, brilliant, I got your saline bag right here.
Sherlock?
Oh! Thank you, God.
Thank you so much for coming.
What are you doing in here?
I'm just doing anything I can to keep my baby alive.
You been in here since power went out?
Yeah. I can't leave.
You know, I gotta keep this thing going.
I've been stuck here without power.
Looks like you already scavenged this place real good.
Yeah.
Hey. What's going on out there?
What's going on with the power?
The whole city's out, man.
Quarter mile of power lines over on 17th, just gone.
They gonna have to lay new wire first.
What about the relief groups? What about the...
What about the Red Cross and FEMA,
and those guys?
Who are you with?
Whoever, man. You got any food?
What?
I'm gonna take these, man. You can keep the rest.
No, don't you do this to me. Look at this.
Look at my situation, man. Look at the baby here.
Don't you go and start taking my food. This, I need help.
It's not my problem.
Just go get me some help.
There ain't nobody out there gonna help you, man.
I'm being real nice lettin' you keep all the Cokes.
Look, alright? I just need help.
I'm gonna give you my watch, okay? Here, take this.
I want you to take my watch.
I'm gonna give you some money.
What am I gonna do with a watch, man?
I'm desperate. Okay?
That's what I have. I'm desperate here, okay?
So I'm pleading with you as a stranger. Look at my situation, man.
I just want you to go out there and just tell somebody about me.
Tell them what's going on. That's free. That doesn't cost you anything.
-Just... -All the other people out there now,
you don't want them to know about you.
They're a lot worse than me.
Folks raiding all the pharmacies.
Can't go ten minutes without hearing another gunshot.
Now you stay real quiet here.
But, listen, I don't know what somebody else's going to want!
I'll put you down, man!
Okay.
-Call off your dog, man. -Easy.
-Call off your dog! -No, Sherlock, don't.
Relax.
Okay.
Sherlock!
Hey, Sherlock!
Get off me!
Hey! Drop the bag! The dog just wants the I.V. bags!
Why the hell does he have these?
You were gonna bring these to me.
You bastard!
She was a nurse! She was a nurse!
I don't even question why I do it.
I just do it.
I keep cranking this thing,
then I check on the baby.
I'm gonna crank until my arms fall off or I'll die trying.
I know.
You're so stubborn.
I love that about you.
-I don't get it. -Get what, baby?
This. Why this?
This wasn't supposed to happen.
I know.
But sometimes you just have to hold onto whatever you can.
I won't be a good father. Not like I was a husband.
Yes, you will.
Do you remember Marc's birthday party?
Yeah.
We were all loitering in the parking lot, and...
the plan was to go to the dive bar next door,
keep the party going.
But you said that we couldn't make it because I had to work the next day
and you had to get me to bed.
-Yeah, and you were pissed. -Oh, yeah.
But secretly...
I loved that.
Because I knew right then and there,
you'd be an amazing father.
But, I need you. You know?
I don't wanna do this without you.
You have me.
You always will.
She is you and me together.
You're not alone, Nolan.
Abigail.
She's listening.
She recognizes your voice.
Abigail...
I'm so tired.
I'm just tired.
If they don't have a radio they're not exactly sure what's going on.
We actually had one gentleman giving us some sort of Morse Code...
with his flashlight this morning in the early darkness,
trying to signal to us...
16\nSixteen...
17\nseventeen...
Yeah, I'm coming.
Yeah.
Yeah, and soon you're gonna be breathing on your own.
Baby, almost.
Just a little longer.
Doctor said 48 hours, so that should be pretty soon.
Just hang on a little bit longer. Okay?
And then we'll go home.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's good.
Yeah. I'm getting you home.
I should have done this yesterday.
-Nothing's gonna be here, man. -You don't know that.
-Yeah. Look at this place. -I know.
It's been gutted.
Lenny said it was just one dude guarding it.
Take... I'm gonna take another one of you guys.
Okay, if I just take one...
Hello?
What the hell you doing?
If dude is still here,
might as well call him out now so I can pop him and be done with it.
So, the cops are gone and all of a sudden you wanna shoot everybody.
Well, yeah.
Holy shit!
What?
Them fools left the pharmacy open.
Oh, I'm getting so high tonight.
You, dumb-ass. You know what's better than getting high?
Getting rich.
Spoken like someone who never been high.
Get all the hydrocodone on the top shelf, grab it all!
You hear that?
Lobo, hold up.
Jase! What is it?
Goddamn, man!
What the fuck?
A baby?
Hey, yo, Lobo,
it's a bab...
Fuck.
It's okay, baby.
Yeah. Daddy's got you.
Daddy's got you.
Shit!
Here.
Can you hear me?
1  2\nOne, two.
Let's go.
Abby...
Save the strength, sir.
-Abigail. Abby...
You got a smart dog there, you know that?
Abby...
My baby...
What?
-Did you hear that? -Hear what?
That's a baby.
-It's a baby? -That, that's a baby.
Holy moly! It's a baby!
-My God! Is it yours? -Yeah.
Yeah.
I know you, baby. I know you.
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：1610169789