更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
When I was a child,
my mother would tell me a story
about how the Devil roams the Earth.
Sometimes, she said, he would take human form
so he could punish the damned on Earth before claiming their souls.
The ones he chose would be gathered together
and tortured as he hid amongst them, pretending to be one of them.
I always believed my mother was telling me an old wives' tale.
My mother's story would always begin the same way,
with a suicide paving the way for the Devil's arrival.
And it would always end with the deaths of all those trapped.
I'm good. I feel good. I feel amazing.
You know the main reason why people go back to drinking?
No.
Guess.
The Eagles.
Resentment.
Are we seriously talking about this again?
It's important.
Your ability to forgive is gonna determine
the quality of the rest of your life more than anything else.
Look, some things are beyond forgiveness.
You're already on your way.
You've taken responsibility for your actions.
That's more than half the battle right there.
But to truly feel free,
you may need to finally start believing
in something greater than yourself.
That sounds good.
It does.
But when I think about the guy that killed my family,
I have a tough time believing in much of anything.
I'm just saying, leave yourself open to it.
Can we just have breakfast for once?
Talk about normal stuff.
I'm your sponsor. You can talk about normal stuff
with everybody else.
Hey. Got a good one for you.
Yeah?
Yeah, it doesn't make sense, right?
A guy hits a truck with this kind of force from a two-story building?
Definitely a jumper.
Are you sure he wasn't thrown?
He's got a rosary in his hand.
Not the kind of thing you grab in a panic.
Right.
- Elsa. - Bowden.
Hi.
There's no glass on the ground.
The truck wasn't here when he made impact. It must have rolled.
Uh-huh.
Your guy jumped from that building.
And what? Your dead guy turned the corner, here?
These things are made to bounce trucks off.
You got to be kidding me.
Let's walk it.
Yeah.
Larson.
Hey! Hey, lady, you got to sign in.
Oh. Where's Ramsey? He knows me.
Ramsey's out sick. You got me.
And that means you gotta sign in.
I mean, do I look like such a threat?
Don't blame me. They got procedures.
Keep dreaming, dawg.
You have to cover the sign in.
Some lawyers on 39 need this right away.
You're not taking the stairs again.
What else am I gonna do to stay in shape?
To 39? Just get on the damn elevator.
Come in.
It's too tight for me.
You can squeeze in.
No.
Hold, please.
Thank you.
Forty-two, please.
You bet.
Now, see, this I can do.
Could you hold that?
Uh. Sorry.
Thanks for your help.
Don't mention it.
Uh-uh, this is not good.
Oh, come on, man.
Don't do this.
Come on, Timonen, put a stick on it.
How we doing?
Same score.
- Thanks. - Yeah.
Why is elevator six in inspection mode?
- Huh? - Elevator six.
A full house. Two queens, three jacks.
- Call Dwight. - Yeah.
Yo, Dwight, you got a problem.
Tell me about it. I'm already up on 35 fixing it.
The elevator?
No, the broken window.
You're not fixing the elevator?
Screen says six is on inspection mode.
We got people stuck in there.
Are you sure you're reading that right?
Your eyes ain't what they used to be.
You know what? I'll ask your mom to read it for me
next time I got her bent over the console.
My mom's 78. Have at it.
Ooh!
Yeah. Listen, buddy, just go up to the machine room
and check it out, okay?
On my way.
Just trying to get something to jump-start it.
Don't you have emergency procedures?
I don't know, I'm just a temp. I just started working here.
Well, don't you service these things?
Try hitting the emergency button.
Don't you keep up your equipment?
I don't know. Like I said...
Don't you have a walkie-talkie?
No. I didn't think I'd need it.
- Don't you think it would have been... - Won't you shut up?
Yeah, take it easy.
I mean, seriously!
You don't have a walkie-talkie?
Hey, people, we see you in there.
We're stuck!
Hang tough, we got the building engineer on his way.
When was the last time you heard somebody say "hang tough"?
- What did you say? - Nothing.
Is he picking a fight?
Can one of you look towards the camera
and say something loud and clear, please?
Your building sucks!
I can't hear you.
The speaker in the car is supposed to let us talk both ways,
but you can hear me?
It's working on this end, yeah!
He just said he can't hear us,
didn't say we should talk louder.
Okay, um, give us a sec.
Well, this is reassuring.
I got to be somewhere.
You're not gonna get a signal in here.
I just need to call my job so I don't get fired over this.
Typical bullshit.
Do any of y'all have a signal?
I've got one bar.
Hello? This is Larson.
Can you please connect me to my job at the security desk?
Can you hear me?
Tell them to get us out of here!
Hello?
They'll just have to deal.
Well, at least we got tunes.
Don't sit under that apple tree with anyone else but me
Come on, grandma, you know the words.
Anyone else but me
Don't be a jerk.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Miss Manners.
Did I offend your noble sensibilities?
Why don't you lay off, pal?
Why don't you suck a butt?
This is great.
Let's just pick on the nice guy for bringing a little levity.
Maybe we should all just stop talking for a while.
Sure.
Okay, I was just joking. I'm joking.
Hey, Dwight, are you there yet?
Almost.
Hey, look, man, I'm just glad you're dating again.
I'm just glad you're glad.
You know what I meant. You know, after all your troubles...
I know what you meant.
So, how's that been going for you?
Good.
Ninety days tomorrow.
Wow, 90 days!
It seems like just yesterday since we...
Not to me, it doesn't.
You wouldn't happen to have a broken window up there, would you?
Yeah.
Facing this direction?
Mmm-hmm.
Big enough to fit a person through it?
I suppose.
Please stop sweeping.
I'm declaring this a crime scene.
Car 602.
What the hell is that?
Look out!
You might want to secure that better.
Okay, okay!
In her story, innocent people always die.
Poor souls just trying to help out,
who didn't realize what they were dealing with.
He doesn't take kindly to those who stand in his way.
Hey, old man.
It doesn't say inspection mode here. Circuits look fine.
Okay. Try flipping elevator six.
I'll tell the people in the car. You count to 20, then do it.
Cool.
"Inspected and certified August 12 by G. Carson. "
Hey, what do you say we go visit G. Carson when we're out of here?
Tell him what we think of his inspecting prowess.
People, we're gonna flip off the lights for one sec
to see if there's a short in the breaker.
You're gonna cut off the power?
Does that mean we could drop?
You'll be fine. I just didn't want you to...
- What's happening? - Come on!
Nothing. Nothing. Just relax.
Come on.
Get off me!
Sorry.
What's wrong with you, man?
When I was younger, my brother locked me in a trunk
for six hours.
I have trouble with tight spaces.
Oh, great.
Come on.
Can we get out through that?
What are you gonna do? Shimmy up the cables?
You'll be a lot safer in here.
Anybody know where the bathroom is in this thing?
Did it work?
Nope, they're still stuck.
Let me go check the mains in the basement.
All right, thanks a lot. Wow.
What's going on?
You know that window on 35?
Yeah.
Looks like somebody might have jumped through it.
Today?
Yeah. This morning.
Thanks for bearing with us, people.
We should get you back on line in a few minutes.
It's been minutes.
How long is it going to take?
When we get out of here, you're gonna need a good rest.
"Mattress Mania"?
That's us. Everybody's had their mattress too long. Am I right?
You didn't follow that advice about flipping it every few months
and now you've worn a groove into it,
and you think, "Well, I'm used to it.
"So, hey. But I do miss the way it felt
"when it came fresh out of that bag. "
Look at those shoes, they've been through the mill.
They're saying, "Someone deserves a better place to lie down. "
Are you insulting my shoes?
The point is, a new mattress will cost a lot less than you think.
You don't have to be as well-off as this one.
I'm not that well-off.
What makes me good at selling mattresses
is I can look at a person's clothes
and know exactly how much they can afford to spend.
And you, lady, you're no Super Sleeper.
Oh, my God. They keep playing this song over and over and over.
Can't they just turn the music off?
Did you just touch my ass?
What? You wish, sweetheart.
I don't know who you think you are, but keep your hands off me.
Whatever.
Oh!
They must be working on the lights again.
Hey, Dwight.
Dwight.
I'm here. I'm heading into the pit.
They just lost power in number six again. Is that you?
No, you can't do that from here, D.L.
Huh. That's strange.
I'm looking at elevator six right now.
I can't see anything wrong with it.
The lights keep shorting out. The passengers are getting scared.
See if this helps.
Come on, come on.
Oh, God.
Anything?
No. No change.
The only other thing I can think to do
would be going back up to the roof, climbing down
and resetting the car manually.
Yeah, yeah. Good. Do that, do that. Call me when you get there.
All right.
Hey.
What?
All right.
Get out of here.
Off you go. Off you go. There you go.
Oh!
Shit!
"Inspected by G. Carson. "
What was that?
What?
I thought I heard...
Ah!
Shit.
Are you all right?
I'm just...
I think someone pulled my blouse. I'm... I'm...
- You're bleeding. - Here. Here. Stand up.
Let me help you.
I think I got cut.
What's going on in there?
I don't know. They're just scared.
I think that lady got hurt.
Did she?
Yeah, see that?
What in the world?
Oh, my God.
What's he saying?
I can't tell what he's saying.
I can't tell what you're trying to say.
Turn off the... Turn off the music!
Maybe they don't like the music.
- The music's still on? - Yeah.
Turn it off. It's probably driving them nuts.
Okay. How?
There's a kill switch right behind the...
Right under the key box.
Thank you!
What happened to her?
It feels like something bit me.
Wait, wait. Does anybody have anything sharp on them
that might have cut her,
- she might have cut herself on? - No.
Why you got blood on you, man?
She fell into me.
So you cut her?
What? No. No, something must have happened to her
and then she fell into me.
She probably did it to herself!
- Come on! - Bit her own back?
You think this is a bite?
No, nobody got bit.
What else could have done that?
- I'll tell you. - I don't know.
A serrated blade could have.
You wouldn't happen to have a knife with
a serrated blade on you, would you?
No.
Okay. You mind if we search your pockets?
Yes, I do mind. You mind if we search yours?
Go right ahead.
Maybe she has a serrated blade on her!
Are you seriously suggesting that I would do this to myself?
I don't know.
Give me another reason to kick your ass.
Please, bro, take it easy, okay?
Bro?
I'm not your bro.
Can you turn towards the camera
and show us what happened to you, please?
Oh, my God. Whoa!
Okay, we gotta call the police.
We have a possible 240 at 333 Locust Street.
333 Locust? That's gotta be right around...
...here.
Strange.
602 responding. Happen to be right outside. Put me on it.
Copy that, 602.
That's convenient.
I don't make the calls, they just come for me.
Go.
Markowitz!
Hey, how's your girlfriend?
Shut up.
What are you doing?
I thought I saw something.
What do you mean? Like what?
Something.
Okay. You see it?
Yeah, yeah. Look, that's just...
That's just grain in the image.
That's, you know... It's a mistake.
It's like when people see Jesus in a pancake or something.
No. No. No.
Ramirez. Ramirez, you're freaking me out. Come on.
Hey, hey. Hey, listen to me.
We need to convey calm. These people are relying on us, okay?
So stop this shit right now.
Come on.
Come on!
I don't even know why we're trying this.
We're in the express shaft.
There's not gonna be another opening till the 23rd floor.
Maybe we're close.
Could this elevator fall?
I doubt it.
Because we gotta be 20 floors up, just dangling over nothing.
Can we stop talking about this, please?
One more time.
On three. One...
Oh, no, no, no.
Stay away from me, man.
I can help. I want to get out of here, too.
Why don't you sit your creepy ass down in the corner over there?
We can all keep an eye on you.
Are you ready? On three.
One, two...
Three.
I'm just over here.
And why do you think this might be an assault?
She seemed to be having words with one of the other passengers
just before it happened,
and now it looks like they're all keeping an eye on him.
Which guy? That guy, right there.
Do we have communication?
Yeah, we have an open line here.
You can talk, but we can't hear.
Hello, everyone. This is Detective Bowden, Philadelphia P.D.
We're working hard to get you out of there. Shouldn't be much longer.
Please just remain calm.
How soon till we get in?
Engineer's working on it now.
Usually, we get these things going pretty quick.
This engineer work for you guys or the elevator company?
Works for us.
Okay. Call the elevator company
and have them send someone, okay?
And have the Fire Department send some guys.
You got it.
At least one of your staff is aboard.
Oh, yeah, the guard there, he's a temp, actually.
Ben something. I don't know. He started yesterday.
Okay. Call the temp agency and get all the info they have on him.
And the others?
We don't have names for the others.
- What? - He should see the face.
- No. - What face?
- No. Nothing. - I saw a face.
- Look, there's no face. - Tell him about the face.
No. Look, Ramirez is kind of religious. Just ignore him. Trust me.
I'd like to get a sense of who you all are.
Stop it right now, comprende?
One at a time, I'd like you to hold up
your driver's license to the camera
so I know who I'm talking to.
That's a good idea.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Try and get it closer to the camera.
The letters are too small.
Is there a sharpness setting on this thing?
No, that's as good as it gets, right there.
You can put your ID's away. Thanks.
Do any of you have a pen on you?
No one?
Here you go.
I want you to account for everyone on the visitors' log.
Find out which of these people
didn't show up for their appointment.
You got it.
You sure?
Okay.
Keep him away from me.
Must be working on the power again.
The geniuses have done a bang-up job so far.
Any other exits?
No, sir, that's everything.
Hey. I got some info on your guard.
What have you got?
Check this out. We got...
Hey. Something else is happening.
Is he dead?
602, we have a possible 187. I need backup.
How do you rewind this thing?
Rewind, fast forward and that's frame-to-frame.
Frame-to-frame.
Everyone, just keep breathing.
We're gonna get you through this. Just take it easy, okay?
So today, someone committed suicide,
a woman got hurt, now a man is dead.
Yeah, what are you trying to say?
Look, how many times have you seen a child fall
and barely miss the edge of the table with their head?
Why is it so rare that they hit it?
Get to your point.
Look.
What are you doing? You're embarrassing yourself.
When he's near, everything goes wrong.
Toast falls jelly-side down, children hit tables
and people get hurt.
Hey. The police do not want to hear this stuff, Ramirez. Okay?
So just stop. Now.
Sometimes he takes human form
and torments the damned on Earth before stealing them away.
Where I come from, we call it
The Devil's Meeting.
Is this guy for real?
Look, I'm sorry. Ramirez.
You must consider that one of those people
- might be the Devil. - All right. Come on.
I need you to stop telling campfire stories
and get your head in the game.
It's okay. It's all right.
Markowitz, look at this guy right here.
Yeah.
Lights go down, they come back up,
he's closer, but he's moving away.
What were you saying about the guard?
All right. Yeah. He's a real piece of work.
Assault, assault, assault.
Beat a guy into a coma with a baseball bat. That's great.
These the kind of guys you hire for security?
Like I said, he's just a temp.
Some temp.
Could that mirror break from him hitting it?
Then how did...
What's that cop doing out there?
He's probably trying to figure out
which one of us is the murderer.
In the story, men would always try to fight him with force,
but some battles can't be fought with weapons.
Will you all please clear a space
between the camera and the body
so I can see him?
Don't touch the body. This is a crime scene now.
Though I know you're stuck in there,
I expect you to do as little damage to it
as humanly possible, got it?
Any luck with the elevator company?
They're out of business.
I guess that figures.
A shard of glass sliced up and into the jugular.
This is definitely not an accident.
Who chooses a contained room with three witnesses for a killing?
Unless they're so worked up, they can't control themselves.
These people are shook up, but they don't look murderous.
I'm missing something here.
I need a volunteer to help me out.
There's a piece of paper hanging out of his pocket.
Very carefully, I want you to take it out and hold it up to the camera.
"Vince. " It looks like "McCormick. "
The return address is for the Better Business Bureau.
They have an office on 35.
- You got a freight elevator? - Yeah.
I've never seen a person die.
Neither have I.
It's pretty awful, huh?
So, what, you have?
Yeah, I spent some time in Afghanistan.
You see some things you wish you hadn't.
Wait, so you've been trained to kill people?
How's your jumper shaping up?
Hey.
Can you take a look at this suicide note? Most of it makes sense,
but then it ends with, "I can hear the Devil's footsteps draw near. "
Usually, suicide notes are either all crazy or all rational,
but this one's both.
It's strange, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
This one? Elevator key.
Key's not catching.
All right. Try the Halligan.
Something's jamming it.
Look, if I can...
If I can get up there, I can maybe figure out what's wrong with this thing.
I'm a mechanic. I'm pretty good with this sort of thing.
He's trying to escape. He's trying to escape.
He's trying to escape!
- He's trying to escape! - Stop! Stop!
Stop it! Stop! What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
We're all gonna stay right here until this thing is over.
You knew what I was doing! I told you what I was doing!
I don't know you!
It's not our policy to discuss cases under review.
It kind of damages the reputations of our member businesses.
Look, someone just killed him on his way here.
I need to know who knew he was coming here and who wanted him dead.
The line would stretch around the block.
The guy was a real scumbag.
Three years ago, he started one of those Ponzi schemes
and when it collapsed, a lot of people lost their asses.
One guy even killed himself over it.
Do you have a list of people that got burned by him?
- Yeah, the ones that filed. - I'm gonna need it.
So, what do you say we get to know each other a little bit better?
Here. Come on. Frisk me. Search me.
See that I'm not carrying anything suspicious.
Come on!
You're next.
There's a good chance one of our people didn't sign in.
How's that?
'Cause that person might be on this list.
What's this?
Our victim lost a lot of people a lot of money.
These are the ones that filed complaints.
The killer's probably smart enough not to be on both lists.
Look for the one that didn't sign in.
Did you just want video of the guy who died,
or also the girl that got hurt?
All of it since they got in the car.
Okay.
Detective.
You see?
That's what you're talking about?
Everybody believes in him a little bit,
even guys like you who pretend they don't.
What's this?
An apology note left at the site of a hit-and-run.
My wife and son were killed down on Bethlehem Pike five years ago,
but that's okay, because whoever did it is sorry.
You can tell by the heartfelt apology
on the back of a car wash coupon.
So, no, I don't believe in the Devil. We don't need him.
People are bad enough by themselves.
Stop the tape.
Back it up.
Faster, faster.
There. Now, play it.
She was acting like he grabbed her.
What is she up to?
Folks, do me a favor, keep your hands off each other.
Leave the police work to me. I'll be in there any moment.
Won't I?
Stop it.
I don't like him touching me. He's touching me.
I don't like it!
Stop pushing him onto me.
Stand back.
Hell, no. I know you're not doing
what it looks like you're doing!
Spray that in here, you're gonna blind all of us.
- I'll do it. - Seriously, put it down.
Lady...
Dwight, where are you? You gotta stop disappearing, seriously.
Dwight.
Hang on a sec.
Dwight, you gotta get us in that car right now. Where are you?
I can't.
Dwight, I need you to stay on walkie!
Man...
Can you see this? Huh? You see this?
"Use by October 21, 1987."
She was scared. Relax.
She tried to pepper spray me, man!
Dwight, where are you?
We're being saved.
Come on, pick up. Pick up!
They hear something.
They hear your guy moving in the shaft.
Then how come he's not answering?
Dwight? Dwight, this is serious. You need to pick up, Dwight.
Thank you!
Pick up, Dwight. Pick up.
Oh, no.
No, no. Hey! Hey! Hey! Oh, no. Hey!
Hey! You all right?
Hey! Come on.
Come on! Hey!
Dwight, where the hell are you, man? Come on!
What floor did Dwight enter the shaft from?
He entered from the roof.
What are they looking at?
Dwight. Dwight, pick up.
Looks like he fell. He's impaled right on top of the elevator.
Hurt real bad. Possibly dead.
Hey, Bowden, I think the people in the elevator
can hear our radios.
Yeah, that's confirmed.
Can you switch to channel eight?
The car's stuck on 21.
Markowitz, tell the Fire Department looks like they have to
go through the wall on 21.
This is Lustig. You can't just go through the wall.
Sure we can.
That's why you have insurance.
Fire command, go to eight, please.
There she is.
Sarah Caraway.
We know the security temp is Benjamin Larson
and we know McCormick.
What other names are unaccounted for?
Jane something. Looks like "Kowski. " The older woman.
Find me footage of this guy.
This way, ma'am.
- Let's go. - All clear.
Okay, this time slow.
You gotta be kidding me.
Did she just steal that lady's wallet?
So Vince was a scam artist, this woman Jane's a thief,
Sarah there is a liar and our guard is a thug.
Quite the crew we have here.
I still haven't seen this guy here.
What was that?
It's okay. Hard drive crash.
I got it. Number 2.
Here we go.
Any other angle on the lobby?
Just the main entrance.
There.
Okay, rewind back.
Faster.
There he is. Stop it.
Where's that satchel?
He doesn't... There's no satchel in the elevator.
Shit.
Oh, no.
What's happening?
I can't take this anymore!
Don't come near me, any of you!
Maybe, if I could just check the wiring...
What the hell's going on?
Please. Please turn on the light.
Turn on the lights!
That's it. Shut down the building.
Bring everyone down to the lobby.
Nobody comes in or out but us.
Which guy do you think is doing this?
There are three people in there and they're all capable.
Well, she's not doing it.
I'm ruling nobody out.
Fire Department wants to know if you have a shut-off valve
before they get through the wall, just in case.
Yeah, it's in the basement.
I'll go.
They're bad people, that's why they're here.
No, two of them are here because they just got on the wrong elevator.
Yeah, and I just happened to have the wrong job
and you just happened to take the wrong call.
He never does this in secret.
There's a reason we're the audience.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on, hold on.
No one's getting in this building right now.
I know. I'm supposed to meet somebody upstairs.
You're gonna have to call them and tell them you can't make it.
Can you just tell me what's happening?
He always kills the last victim
in front of the person they love most
to make cynics of us all.
No, no, no. Don't touch her.
I'm not gonna leave her just hanging there.
Where you gonna put her?
I haven't thought that far ahead.
Funny how all this stuff starts happening
right after you start working here.
Seems to me, you're the only one
who knew where the cables are.
What are you doing?
Trying to close her eyes.
That doesn't work, not until they're dead for a few hours.
Okay, you enter the building with a satchel.
You see a sign-in desk you wanna avoid. Where do you go?
- Restroom. - Yep.
Got it.
Could those be used to rig an elevator?
I have no idea, but he doesn't sign in and then he hides these?
What the hell is that?
I wish he'd stop.
I don't even know your name.
I'm Ben.
I'm Sarah.
I'm Tony.
So where'd your claustrophobia go?
Excuse me?
I've never seen claustrophobia come and go like that.
- You trying to say something? Then say it. - Yeah, yeah.
Okay, I'm saying I didn't do this,
and I very much doubt that she did, so that leaves you.
I'm saying I think this claustrophobia thing...
I think it's an act.
Yeah, I'm saying I think you're a liar.
Kill him, Ben!
Kill him before he kills us!
Kill him!
Stop it! Stop!
Stop it! Get us out! Get us out! Get us out!
Back away from each other now! Get off!
We're gonna keep you safe and here's how,
everyone get to a corner and place your hands on the wall
so everyone can see that you're not up to anything.
Go ahead. Do it!
You won't have to keep this up long.
The building is surrounded by police.
In a hypothetical conversation that I'm not really having,
how would this story of yours end?
They all die.
That's it?
Yeah.
This is not your fault.
They made the choices that brought them here.
Hey. You're gonna love this.
What have you got?
She has a criminal record, too.
Three counts of blackmailing rich married men.
Now where this gets interesting,
is couple of years ago, the arrests stopped. Guess why.
Tell me.
Well, her name is Sarah Caraway.
"Caraway" Caraway?
Yeah. She married into the family.
So she shoplifted an heir.
Yeah, something like that, I guess.
What's she doing here?
According to the sign-in sheet,
she was gonna see a lawyer on 42 named Wayne Kazan.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Hey, listen up! Quiet down! Quiet down!
Hey, quiet!
Philadelphia P. D!
I'm looking for a Wayne Kazan.
Is there a Wayne Kazan down here?
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Heads up. Did you have a meeting today with a Sarah Caraway?
I don't know. Do you have a subpoena?
Come on, you can tell me that much.
I might have. Why?
She was attacked. Who has motive to hurt her?
Well, you know I can't divulge personal information.
Come on, man. Give me something.
Give me something to work with here.
I'm trying to save your client's life.
Come here.
I guess I'd do what you guys normally do
and start with the person closest to her.
- Thanks. - And just so you know,
my specialty is forensic accounting.
Markowitz, get Mrs. Caraway's husband on the phone.
Should be okay now.
All right, get in there.
I might have found the problem. It's a bad wire.
Looks like it could be shorting out the circuits.
Okay.
Easy. Easy.
That's it.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Vasquez, we're gonna need the large Target saw up here
as fast as you can bring it.
Look, we need two more on 21, okay, guys?
Any luck getting hold of the husband?
No, not yet.
I called his office and his secretary said he'd call me right back.
Back up! Heads up, heads up! Come on!
Heads up! Back up!
Move out of the way! Get away! Back up!
What happened? Anybody see what happened?
Medic!
He came through the door.
Breathe. Breathe.
Lustig.
Back away! Back away! Move back!
Get everybody back. Back away!
Put your hands back on the wall.
It hurts.
Put your hands back up on that wall.
Or what?
Just leave her alone. She's in pain.
Don't you see what she's doing?
Chick's a twist.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, that's what we used to call people like her in the Marines.
Suddenly out of the blue, everybody would start fighting with each other.
Tempers would flare, people would start getting hurt.
But then we realized it's just the new guy
telling everybody what other people said,
stirring shit up where there wasn't any.
Until one night when we beat the living shit out of that twist.
And then, just like that,
everything would go back to normal.
Are you threatening me?
I just want you to know that I know.
Why don't you just shut up and keep your hands on the wall?
Sarah Caraway's husband won't talk to us.
He lawyered up.
Her lawyer told me she's locating all his money.
I bet she's about to leave him and he might know it.
That would definitely give him motive to kill her.
But if he's trying to kill his wife,
why are Jane Kowski and Vince McCormick dead?
This is Matt with Caraway Security.
I need someone from maintenance
to come down and shut the bay doors.
Sarah Caraway's husband doesn't own Caraway Security, does he?
Meet me in the office!
He's not done yet.
It's the Kensington sniper all over again.
What's a Kensington sniper?
A few years ago, a guy shot four strangers and then his own wife,
trying to make a personal killing look like a serial.
The guard works for the woman's husband.
I think the two victims were just a decoy.
The guard is gonna kill her.
I need to be in that elevator right now!
- Move! - Right.
Please don't let him kill me, Ben.
I won't.
Come over here next to me and I'll keep you safe.
Don't worry. Come on.
Hold up your cell phones.
Use the screens as flashlights.
Don't let it go dark in there.
Keep the light on each other.
Keep shining it all around the elevator.
Don't you do it. Don't you do it.
It just doesn't make any sense.
Oh, my God. It is you.
Please, lady.
They can't hear you. You don't have to pretend anymore.
We both know who did this.
Yeah, we do.
Put down the glass and get your hands on the wall now!
I should kill you right now.
I should kill you right now before you try anything else.
I should cut you right now.
And what'll be your defense? Huh?
"She killed them all, so I had to kill her"?
Yeah, something like that.
You take me down,
they're pinning all of this on you and you know it.
A big, tough guy like yourself.
This is what he does.
He wants us to doubt everything.
Markowitz.
- Markowitz? - We're getting close, boss.
Hurry up!
How would I do it?
Do what?
According to your story, how would I save them?
There's no easy answer.
You're never gonna get these people
to see themselves as they really are
'cause it's the lies that we tell ourselves,
they introduce us to him.
Look at what you're doing.
Don't think just because I'm a cop
I don't know what you're going through right now.
I've been to hell.
Six months ago, I...
...checked into a hotel and I nearly drank myself to death.
The thing is, when you're self-destructing,
it looks like it's the world's fault.
Like you're dealt a series of shit hands, but that's not real.
Okay? It was all on me. All of it.
I realized my only way out of hell was to take responsibility
for what I had become.
You are responsible for this.
You realize that, don't you?
Take responsibility for what you're doing.
Put down the glass.
I'll put this down if you do, too.
Okay?
We'll call a truce.
Good.
You're doing the right thing.
Sir, we found a woman who thinks she knows someone in the elevator.
Send her in.
No.
Get in there! Get in there! Now!
We're through!
This is the woman I was telling you...
Hold her outside!
Tony.
You know him?
He's my fianc? He had a job interview here today
and he didn't want to bring his tools in with him.
I was late picking them up.
Tony what?
Janekowski. Tony Janekowski.
Jane Kowski is Janekowski?
He signed in. Then who is...
Come on, breathe. Right there. Come on, breathe.
Breathe! Come on, come on. Please breathe.
It's her! It's her.
Get in there already.
- Who are you? - Today?
I'm an old woman.
Grab her the moment you get in.
Are you ready for your turn, Anthony?
I'm sorry.
The whores, the liars, the cheats and the deserters,
it's always the same thing.
You know who I am now.
Yes?
Take me.
I intend to.
No, take me instead. I deserve this.
You don't believe that.
Yes. Yeah, I do.
I should never have left.
It's my fault. It's all my fault.
You think you can make some kind of bargain?
Take me instead. Please.
Stop saying that!
You think this will make you good?
You're not good.
I know.
You think you can make up for the choices you made?
No.
You think you can be forgiven?
Channel eight.
I killed a mother and her son on Bethlehem Pike
five years ago.
It was a hit-and-run and I was never caught.
I'm so sorry.
No.
Damn.
I really wanted you.
Come on, come on, come on!
Where is she?
Where'd she go?
I'll take him in.
That was my family on Bethlehem Pike.
That was my son.
I've been waiting for this moment for five years.
All the things I'd say to you
and what I'd do.
The thing is...
...I forgive you.
After my mother would finish her story, she would always comfort us.
"Don't worry," she'd say.
"If the Devil is real, then God must be real, too. "
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：1610169789