更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
With every sun comes a new day.\nA new beginning.
A hope that things will be better today\nthan they were yesterday.
But not for me.\nMy name is Eep.
And this is my family, the Croods.
If you weren't clued in already by the animal skins
and sloping foreheads,\nwe're cavemen.
Most days we spend in our cave,\nin the dark.
Night after night, day after day.
Yep, home sweet home.
When we did go out, we struggled to find food
in a harsh and hostile world.
And I struggled to survive my family.
We were the last ones around.\nThere used to be neighbors.
The Gorts, smashed by a mammoth.
The Horks, swallowed by a sand snake.
The Erfs, mosquito bite.
Throgs, common cold.
And the Croods, that's us.
The Croods made it, because of my dad.
He was strong,\nand he followed the rules.
The ones painted on the cave walls.
Anything new is bad, curiosity is bad.
Going out at night is bad.
Basically, anything fun is bad.
Welcome to my world.
But this is a story about
how all that changed in an instant.
Because what we didn't know\nwas that our world...
was about to come to an end.
And there were no rules on our\ncave walls to prepare us for that.
You are supposed to wait\nfor my signal. Eep?
Boo.
Ow! No!
We've been in that cave forever.
Three days is not forever.
It is with this family.
Eep, would you come down here?\nYou're being so dramatic.
No, Sandy, come back here.
Remember the signal.\nGood girls wait for the signal. Ugga.
As soon as I get Sandy, I'll go back in,\nand you can give the signal.
No, I mean, you're already out now.
I'm waiting for the signal, Dad.
Never mind, Thunk. Just come out.
But if you don't give the signal,\nhow do I know you're my dad?
The signal isn't so you know it's me.
It's so you know I wasn't eaten\nby an animal.
Then why is the signal an animal noise?
Doesn't that just confuse things?
I don't know.\nI'm still waiting for the signal.
Mom, we're ready to leave.
Mom?
Still alive.
It's still early.
And you're still fat.
Breakfast formation!
I want to see some real caveman action\nout there. We do this fast.
We do this loud.\nWe do this as a family.
And never not be afraid!
Yay, breakfast.
Who's up?
We'll flip for it.\nCall her in the air.
Heads!
Tails. Thunk is in. Positions.
Okay. Thunk...
Go.
Come on, Thunk.
Way to go.\nTake it to the cave.
Release the baby!
Get them, Sandy! Go!
Get them, Mom!
Old lady down!\nEep, avenge me!
Thanks.
Eep!
Heads up!
Hey Dad, can we eat now?
Just wait till we get home.
Eep, put on the brakes.
Eep!
- Who is hungry?\n- All right! Good one, Dad.
Here you go, Thunk. Drink up.
- Sorry, Dad.\n- Looks like fast food tonight.
That's all right. I ate last week.
Two knuckle warning!
Come on, Croods. Go, go.
Come on, come on. Darkness brings death.\nWe know this.
The moon is full. Bath night.
- Run for your life!\n- You too, Mom.
I don't want to lose\nmy protective layer.
Mom, you've got ants.
See? Sandy doesn't fuss.
Is she still out there?
You know she hates the cave, Grug.
Please come back tomorrow.
How could she not like the cave?\nIt's so cozy.
It is a little dark, Grug.
It's not that dark.
Eep!
Eep?
Come on, I have to close the cave.
Eep!
Okay, okay.
Come on.
Eep! Come down!
- That was too close.\n- I was watching. I was fine.
- What were you doing up there, Eep?\n- I don't know.
- What were you looking for?\n- Nothing.
- Then why did you go up there?\n- I don't know.
Why don't you know?
Stop looking for things.
Fear keeps us alive, Eep.\nNever not be afraid.
What is the point of all this?
What was that?
Why are we here?\nWhat are we doing this for?
No one said survival was fun.
Nothing is fun.
- Would you come down here?\n- Grug.
- Eep.\n- Grug.
- Yes.\n- Off!
- Yes, I know. Okay, I'm trying to...\n- Off.
I just don't see why\nshe needs her own ledge, that's all.
- That's what this is about.\n- She's working through some things...
and she needs her own space.
What things?\nHow long is this going to take?
Really?\nShe already doesn't listen to me. Hey!
See? She's listening.
If she wants to survive,\nshe has to follow our rules.
How about a story?\nEep loves those.
That's a good ide...\nHow about a story, huh?
Yeah, tell us a story.
Okay. Can I borrow that? Thank you.
Eep, your old favorite.
I haven't played with that thing in years.
Tonight we'll hear the story\nof Krispy Bear.
A long time ago,\nthis little bear was alive.
She was alive\nbecause she listened to her father...
and lived her life in routine\nand darkness and terror.
So she was happy.
But Krispy had one terrible problem.
She was filled with... curiosity.
- Grug.\n- Yes. yes.
And one day, while she was in a tree...
the curious little bear\nwanted to climb to the top.
And no sooner than\nshe climbed to the top...
she saw something new and died!
- Just like that?\n- Yes!
Her last moments of terror\nstill frozen on her face.
Same ending as every day.
I get it, Dad. I will never do\nanything new or different.
Good man, Thunk.
All right, everyone\nsharpen your teeth, and let's pile up.
Air.
You talk.
I'm a person, like you.
Sort of like you.
Okay, okay.
Hey, hey, hey!
Would you mind not...
That tickles.
Hey, hey, hey!
Quiet!
I'm not supposed to be out here.
Eep is gone.
What? Grug!
Stay in the cave.
Wow. You are really strong.
Hey! No! It's mine.
- Please! Wait.\n- No!
- It's dying! I can fix it!\n- No! I caught it!
Please! Please.
I hate the dark.
Come on, come on, come on.
It does what you tell it?
Yeah. Sort of.
The sun?
No, no, no. Fire.
Hi, fire.
It's not alive.
But you said it was dying.
Sorry.
It comes from where you come from?
No. No, I make it.
- Make some for me.\n- Okay.
Make!
It doesn't come out of me.
Make! Make it!
You do this a lot.
Are you dead?
Can I have your fire if you're dead?
Hey, those are cold!
You think? Listening shells, activate.
I concur.
Tiger girl, we need to leave immediately.
I don't even know you.
I'm Guy.
Guy?
And this is Belt.\nCook, conversationalist, navigator.
Also, keeps my pants up.
What are "pants up"?
Who are you?
Eep.
Let me clarify, Eep.\nThe world is ending.
What?
I'm calling it "The End."
How do you know?
I have seen it. It's coming this way.
First, the ground is going to shake.\nThen it breaks open. Everything falls in.
Fire. Lava.
I don't mean to sound too dramatic, but...
Believe me, everything we are\nstanding on will be gone.
We got to get to high ground.\nI know a mountain, that way.
It's our only chance.
Come with me.
I can't.
Okay.
Here.
If you survive, call me.
Thank you.
Hello?
Hey!
Dad!
Are you hurt? What took you?
Nothing. I left on my own.
You what?
Dad, let me explain.
You never let me talk.
You're grounded.
Hey!
Eep!
Mom.
Grug! What happened?
You know what, I am so mad right now\nthat I can't talk to her.
Eep?
You will never believe it.\nI found something new.
New!
New is a big problem!
Wait, wait!
Eep. Stay inside the family kill circle.
- It wasn't bad.\n- "New" is always bad.
No. He was nice.
What? Excuse me? He?
I thought he was a warthog,\nbut then he turned into a boy.
Strange.
Usually it's the reverse.
Eep's got a boy hog. Eep's got a boy...
There was a boy.
Watch. I'm going to call him.
What is wrong with you?
It was dangerous.
It was beautiful!
You want to see dangerous? Here!
My sniffer!
Okay, that's it!
We're going back to the cave...
and you're going to stay in there\nuntil you're older than...
her!
What!
You can't keep me inside forever!
He said this would happen.
Get to the cave!
Go!
Look out!
Stop!
Is everyone okay?
Yes.
Grug, the cave...
it's gone.
No.
You really need to see this.
We should go there!
No. No one is going anywhere.
What else did that boy say?
Grug?
Just go! Just go!
Go!
One, two, three, four, five...
Six.
Where are we?
I don't know. I'm not sure.
Down.
In a lower place.
But one thing is for sure,\nwe can't go back the way we came.
Sandy? What is it?
No, no, no. Wait. Come back, Sandy!
We can't be out in the open like this.
We need a cave.
Now, step where I step.
Okay. Stay quiet.
Hopefully, nothing big\nknows we're here yet.
Wait.
Okay.
Wait!
Wait.
Okay.
So, Dad...
just to be clear, are we looking for\nthe exact same cave?
If it was me...\nI'm just throwing this out there...
if it was me choosing the cave...
I would go with a smaller cave.
Wait.
Dad?
I'll take care of this.
All right, Dad, get them! Go get them!
Now you got them right...
Man, they're really...
I'm loving this.
Dad, I got it.
Just stop running into their fists.
Grug, when you're done,\nwe should get going.
That's right. You can't get past this!
Climb! Climb! Climb!
Cave!
Go! Go!
Come on! Hurry up. Let's go.
Look! This cave has a tongue. Awesome!
Okay.
That's one, two, three, four, five, six.
And seven...
if we're counting Chunky the Death Cat.
It's scared of the dark.
Wait, we're scared of the dark.
Kill circle!
Eep!
- Cavies!\n- "Cavies"?
Cavemen! Stand back!\nThey're practically animals.
- You see their bony, sloping foreheads?\n- Yeah.
The huge primitive teeth?
Yeah.
The excessive body hair.
That one has got a tail.
Yeah.
All right. Close your eyes.\nI'm going to have to take their lives.
No! It won't help.\nThey're my family.
What?
The sun is in his hands!
No, no. It's "fire."
Where did it come from?
He made it.
Make some for me!
It doesn't come out of him.
Make. Make it!
You're a lot like your daughter.
Great, now he's broken.
It's a baby sun.
Hey, stay back.\nWe don't know what it wants.
Now, we'll all sit here\nand wait for the sun to come back.
And tomorrow we'll find a new cave...
and pretend today never happened.
Isn't this fun, Eep?
Eep, don't touch him.
Goodness knows where he's been.
Dad, Sandy is hurting fire.
Sandy, no. Fire is not a plaything.
What a cute little guy.
Hey. Stay back.
No, no, no, wait!
It likes me.
Hey! It's biting me!
Thunk! Try hiding from it\nin the tall, dry grass!
No, stop. Please, I'm only nine.
They're biting me!
More fire babies.
So, your dad, he is trying to kill me.
Yeah. But I won't let him.
Hold on, son. Come back!
No, stop! Let me go!
Get out! Out! Out!
Eat up, babies!
No, stop touching me!
Die!
I win!
They're not so scary\nonce you get to know them.
Who are you people?
I'm sorry.
We're the Croods!
And you are?
Guy.
Hi, Guy.
Wow!
It looks like magic.
And smells like food.
No, don't eat it, it's new.
Still alive!
Come on, keep eating.
Hey, where is Guy?
No!
Going somewhere?
The mountain? High ground?\nEnd of the world, remember?
That already happened.\nIt destroyed our cave.
No. That was just the beginning of the end.
The end of the end is still coming.
Eep. Drop it.
We can't let him go!
What if we don't find a\ncave before sunset?
What if it takes a few days?
What if the birds come back?
We need his fire, dummy!
Fine. You're staying with us\nuntil we find a cave.
What? No, I'm not.\nDon't make me a part of this!
Stay here if you want, but let me go.
I've got a dream...
a mission, a reason to live!
Not anymore.
I've got an idea.
Let's go to that mountain.
It's too far.
Dad really has his heart set on a cave.
There are caves on that mountain.
Have you been there?
It's a mountain.
Mountains are safe.\nMountains have caves.
And water. And sticks.
Mom? Did you hear that?\nI can get my own stick!
Yes. Sticks and caves.\nCaves and sticks.
Crazy sticks. Let's go.
Quiet!
That thing is weird.
No, no, no. It's okay, Sandy.
That's just Belt.
I've made a decision.
We're going to that mountain.
Don't ask me why. Just a hunch.
Just feels right.
I don't know, Grug.\nWe've never really walked that far.
I don't think my feet can do that.
I'll never live long enough to get there.
Let's do it.
Come on, just think.
Our whole family packed together\non a long, slow, trip across country?
Days and nights with just each other.
We'll tell stories. We'll laugh.
We'll become closer as a family.
Get her off!
If you're not ready to challenge her,\nthen don't look her in the eye.
Could you keep your big giant arms\non your side of the trail?
Isn't this fun?\nWe're taking our first trip together.
Stop shoving,\nor I will pull out your tongue!
Do you want me to\nturn this family around? Do you?
Because I will\nturn this family around so fast!
Dad, I gotta go!
- Come on, you can hold it.\n- I don't think so.
Sandy, take that out of your mouth.
I'm touching...
Dad, I still gotta go!
Fine. Just go behind one of those\nlumpy things and make it fast.
- Something bit me!\n- I don't blame it.
Dad, can I take a turn carrying him?
No.
- How about now?\n- No.
- Now?\n- No.
Now?
I can do this all day long.
No, no, no and still no.
I'm not dying on an empty stomach.
Grug, we're all pretty tired!
We'll eat when we get there.
It's taking too long!
I'm grabbing a snack.
Don't do that. He will cut you.
That's not food, he's a pet. My pet.
What's a pet?
An animal you don't eat.
We call those "children."
No man should have a pet.\nIt's weird and wrong.
- It's food!\n- No, please!
Not that. That!
Food fixes everything.
Show me your hunting face.
Not you. You're still grounded.
Come on, Thunk.
My feet hurt.
- You look tense.\n- I'm not tense.
Angry girl wants to be doing\nwhat they're doing.
I wasn't ready.
Hang on, Thunk, I'm coming!
Why are you doing this?
What are they doing?
Hunting.
Get it off! You stay away from me.
No, seriously, what are they doing?
You've got a ton of eggs.\nJust make another egg.
Now you're just rubbing it in.
There, who's hungry for scorpion?
What happened to the egg and the bird?
We lost him.
But when the bird stepped on me\nand pushed me into the ground...
the scorpion grabbed a hold of me...
and one thing led to another\nand here we are eating him.
So, win-win.
Not enough. Not enough!\nI need more.
I need more.
Look at that.\nShe's not going to eat me, right?
You're too skinny.
If she was going to eat anyone\nit would be...
Mom!
She's locked her jaw!
Get a stick! Get a stick!
Stay away!
You sick old monster!
Hurry! Put the stick in her mouth!
Hold her still. Use a rock.
Ugga, would you just hit her legs?
Why are you rolling away?
I just want something to eat.
You have bug for dinner. Plenty of bug!
Please.
I'll let you help me hunt.
Really?
Don't wait on me. They're all over me.
Tell my story.
Okay.
What do you call this?
A trap.
What does it do?
Well...
How long have you been alone?
So, what do we do?
How's your acting?
You're good at this.
No. Sorry.
Okay.
- Yeah, that's yours.\n- Excuse me.
Your other hand...
- That's my arm.\n- Okay, I'm moving it.
It didn't step in your trapything.
Yeah, I noticed!
Where's Eep?
She's awesome.
Eep!
Dad, no!
It's an avalanche of flavor.
Looks like we won't be\nhaving any leftovers.
What are "left overs"?
When you have so much food to eat,\nyou have some left over.
We never have that much food.
Grug, how about a story?
That's a good idea. How about a story?
Yeah, tell us a story!
Once upon a time,\nthere was a little tiger...
who lived in a cave with her family.
There were a lot of rules...
but the big, simple one\nwas to never leave the cave at night.
And the door was so heavy,\nyou'd think it would be easy to remember.
So easy to remember!
I know.
But, while everyone was asleep...
she went out anyway.
- No!\n- Yes!
And no sooner than she did,\ntheir cave was destroyed...
and everyone had to go\non this long, sucky walk...
with some weirdo they met...
and die!
The end.
I did not see that coming. Twist ending.
My stories never end like that.
Yes! Two stories in one night!
Okay. But it won't be as good as Grug's.
Once upon a time,\nthere was a beautiful tiger.
She lived in a cave\nwith the rest of her family.
Her father and mother told her,\n"You may go anywhere you want...
"but never go near the cliff,\nfor you could fall."
And die. Good story.
But when no one was looking...
she'd go near the cliff...
for the closer she came to the edge...
the more she could hear,\nthe more she could see...
the more she could feel.
Finally...
she stood at the very edge.
She saw a light.
She leaned out to touch it...
and she slipped.
And she fell.
And she flew.
Where did she fly?
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
A place with more suns in the sky\nthan you can count.
It would be so bright.
A place not like today, or yesterday.
A place where things are better.
Tomorrow isn't a place.
You can't see it!
Yes, it is.
I've seen it.
That's where I'm going.
We are going to shut our eyes and sleep.
And when we wake up...
we're going to find the place\nthat has everything we want.
Tomorrow?
A cave.
That was too close. It almost caught us.
I was watching. We were fine.
We gotta move faster.
Do you people have any other speed\naside from "wander"?
I'll take a shamble at this point.
Hey, do you have a minute?
How did the tiger fly?
I only share when I'm outside the log.
I'm funny that way.
Leave this to me.
Hey, Thunk...
you have a spider on your face.
He's loose!
Do not step on those weird pointy rocks.
Do you mean these rocks?
Do not step on these rocks!
Step aside, girls.
Hello? Nobody's listening!\nNo one is listening.
You cannot walk on those!
Get back here now!
There goes our chance for survival.
And our log!
Okay.
Jumping doesn't help. It does briefly...
but it doesn't get better.
Don't walk on your hands.\nThe hands do not help at all.
Come on.
I can help you...
but we're going to have to\nmake a few changes around here.
The log ride is over.
Drop the log.
Now, kick it away.
Farther.
Really?
Okay, smart "Guy"...
now what?
Good fish, good fish.
Okay. Now you can look.
I love them!\nWhere are my feet?
They're still there!
Okay.
You're really heavy.
Really?
Thank you!
Hey. Wait!
Okay.
She's up. We're good. I'm good.
These shoes are great!\nWhere do you get these ideas?
I'm calling it a "brain."
I'm pretty sure it's\nwhere ideas come from.
Dad, I don't have a brain.
We've gotten along just fine\nwithout brains until now.
Cavemen don't need brains.\nWe have these.
That's what I'm talking about!\nIdeas are for weaklings.
Now, let's get to that mountain!
Wow! I love those!
Good fish. Don't eat my feet.
So, how did the tiger fly?
She jumped on the sun...
and rode it to Tomorrow.
No, no, no.
Hi, Dad!
Bye, Dad!
You've seen rain before, right?
We don't get out much.
Eep, looks dangerous.
Dad, you say that about everything.
Careful.
Really? Okay.
No, no, no. Not cool!
So, the bear says, "Your cave? I've been\ndumping my bones here since last week."
Last week!
That's a funny story!
It's not a story. It's a joke.
What's a "joke"?
Just making something up\nto make you laugh.
- One for you.\n- Thanks.
One for you. And this one's for you.
Okay.
Okay! That's enough!
I don't see why the kids\nneed their own shells.
So if anyone gets in trouble,\nwe can call the others.
Wait, you're saying we should split up?
We can try more paths at once.
It's the fastest way through.
Croods stick together.\nYour way isn't safe.
They can handle it.
We can do it, Dad.
No, no, no.
It's my job to keep you safe.
I'm still in charge\nand we are not splitting up.
Except for you two.
And that's final.
Hello?
Is everyone all right?
We're okay, Grug.
Dad? I'm freaking out a little bit.
Just tell me what to do.\nWhat do I do? What do I do right now?
Stay where you are. I'll find you.
No. Too slow.
Everybody, keep moving forward\nand we'll get out.
Dad?
Yeah.
Okay.
Remember, never not be afraid.
You can do this!
It's going to be okay,\nit's going to be okay.
I'm going to pass out.
Sandy. Sandy!
Give me another one.
You dropped these.
Come with me.
Here, boy! Catch!
Gran?
Mom?
Wow.
Grug?
I'll go get him.
Good boy! Who's a good boy?
You are! Yes, you are! Look at you!
You need a name. You want a name?
I'm going to call you Douglas.
Can you do tricks? Roll over.
Come on, Douglas, roll over.
Good boy, Douglas!
I was in love once.
He was a hunter. I was a gatherer.
It was quite a scandal.
We fed each other berries, we danced.
Then my father smashed him with a rock\nand traded me to your grandfather.
Croods!
Get down here.
Grug, they're okay. Guy is with them.
Guy is with them. Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you for bringing me\nthat interesting Guy update.
Okay. I'm going to go up...
and why don't you join us\nwhen you stop being a big drag!
Sleep pile?
How about a story?
Anyone?
And then Torg said,\n"Know it? I drew it."
That makes no sense.
I know it was hard for you\nto bring us along...
but they had the\nbest day of their lives.
Thank you for that.
I want to show you something.
More suns in the sky than you can count.
Every sun that crosses our sky\ncomes to rest up there.
Tomorrow.
That's where we'll be safe.
I'm going with Guy.
No. Not my little girl.
Come with us.
I can't go without Grug.
That makes one of us. Count me in.
Really, Mom? Now?
Grug has no idea how to protect us.
In fact, he has no ideas at all!
No, that's not true.\nWhat about that one time when he...
Face it.
If he actually had an idea of his own...
I'd have a heart attack and die!
Grug?
- Dad!\n- Dad!
He's a big guy. How could he\njust disappear like that?
Hey, wait! Let's ask that ugly lady\nif she's seen Dad.
Haven't seen him.
What are you doing?
I was up all night, because\nall these ideas just kept coming to me.
Is that a snake?
Belt, new and improved.
It's even self-tightening!
What is that on your head?
It's called desperation.
I call it a "rug." Rhymes with "Grug."
And this one, I call it a "ride."
Rhymes with "Grug."
That doesn't rhyme...
It's going to get us\nplaces faster than shoes.
Yeah! Try to keep up!
I wish I had a ride.
And painting is a thing of the past.
I call this a "snapshot."
Let's do it again. I think I blinked.
I call them "shades."
The sun doesn't hurt my eyes anymore.
Where do you get these great ideas?
Since I don't have a brain...
they're coming from my stomach,\ndown deep below...
and then up again into my mind.
Grug, we have to keep moving.
See, I got ideas. I got thoughts.
Like this. I call it a "mobile home."
Isn't that something?
And I'm calling this one a "lifterator."
Mom?
I know. It's bad.
I almost feel sorry for him.
No, I don't.
What are you trying to do, Grug?
See, I thought if I could have ideas...
Iike Guy...
maybe Eep would listen to me.
And maybe she wouldn't\nwant to go with Guy.
Grug.
Is that what this is all about?
And I also thought\nit would kill your mother.
So win- win.
We're here!
Cave!
Everyone inside.
Hurry up. Let's go.
Let's go. Go!
No!
No more caves, Grug.
What?
We're going to jump on the sun\nand ride it to Tomorrow with Guy!
Wait. So you're all going to do this?
Thunk?
Sorry, Dad.
You have to stop worrying for all of us.
It's my job to worry!\nIt's my job to follow the rules!
The rules don't work out here!
They kept us alive!
That wasn't living!\nThat was just not dying.
There's a difference.
Ugga, everyone,\nyou have to listen to me.
We would be dead if we listened to you!
We have to follow Guy now.
Guy.
Guy? Run.
This is pointless!
We're running out of time.\nEverything is collapsing.
You're being irrational\nand counterproductive!
Big words anger me!
Keep talking.
Countermeasures!
You remember how you were\nthis morning? You changed.
Idea man. Modern man.
I am a caveman!
No, no, no, wait!
No!
What is this stuff that saves you\nfrom my punches?
Tar.
No. I have to get back to them.
Stop struggling.
No!
Grug, stop!
No one gets out of this.
Believe me...
I know.
Your...
Family. Yeah.
Sorry.
I was little when it happened.
Last thing my parents told me was...
"Don't hide.
"Live.
"Follow the sun.
"You'll make it to Tomorrow."
You followed the light.
My daughter is a lot like you.
No.
She's like you.
She loves you,\nbut always forgets to say it.
Just like you forget to tell her.
I guess I was just busy\nkeeping them all alive.
It's okay. That's what dads do.
That's right.
But we can't do that from here.
We need one of your ideas.
Come on. You can do it.
Belt! Emergency Idea Generator, activate!
I've got it.
Wow.
Yeah, I know. But he's doing\nthe best with what he has.
Let's go.
There he is.
Belt, I want romance, drama, sincerity.
Move me.
Okay, he sees us.
That's our cue. Now, work it!
He's not coming over.
I don't think our puppet\nlooks scared enough.
Scared? I'll show you scared.
Hand me those acting sticks!
Hold on!
Yes! You did it.
- Grug!\n- Dad!
Hey! We're okay!
Yeah.
We're okay.
Grug, your call.
Take us to Tomorrow.
Hurry!
Come on! We're going to make it!
You were right.
There it is! The sun!
We can do it!\nWe can ride it to Tomorrow!
Run!
I don't understand.
The sun was right here.\nIt was right here.
We have to go back to the cave.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Stay together. Let's keep moving.\nMove, move, move.
Everybody, hold my hand.
Thunk, let's go. Go, go, go.\nLet's stay together.
Grug. What's wrong with you?
Grug, we'll die if we stay here!
Grug, listen to me.
We've got to get back to that cave.
No more dark.
No more hiding.
No more caves.
What's the point of all this?
To follow the light.
I can't change.
I don't have ideas.
But I have my strength.
And right now...
that's all you need.
No, we don't know what's over there.\nMaybe nothing!
It's too risky!
It's a chance.
I'll take that chance.
I've wanted to throw you away\never since I met you.
That's a joke, right?
What's a "joke"?
He made it!
He made it.
Okay, Thunk. Your turn.
You're not coming, are you?
When you make it, so will I.
No!
You did good.
Dadda!
Gran...
No mush. Just throw me.
Wait.
You surprised me today...
Iunkhead.
Still alive!
Time to go.
No.
I have too much to say to you.
I need to fix everything,\nand I don't have time.
I can fix it.
This works good.
What do you call it?
I was thinking of calling it a "hug."
Because it rhymes with "Grug."
But you can change it if you want.
No. I like "hug."
I love you.
I...
Dad...
I'm scared.
Never be afraid.
There!
I see him!
Hey!
Hey, I did it!
Back! Stay back!
Stay back!
They're in trouble.
Hang on, I'm coming!
How do I get across?
I have to think. What would Guy do?
What would Guy do, what would Guy do?
What would I do?
Hold this.
I have...
an idea!
Run!
Yes!
Douglas?
Hey, I know that guy.
Hold on!
It's not safe here.
I'll tell her.
I never got to tell him.
Eep, if your dad were here,\nhe would tell you to...
Get out of the way!
Wow. You sound just like him.
Dadda!
He did it!
He's riding the sun.
But, not very well.
Everybody out of the way!
- Dad!\n- Grug!
Where's the danger?\nWho blew their shell?
I love you, too!
One, two, three, four...
five...
six...
and seven.
And a half.
And eight.
Nine.
Douglas! Dad, you saved him!
A boy has to have a pet.
Turns out I'm a cat person.
No.
You really need to see this.
We should go there.
Yes! Coming through!
Wait!
This is me. My name is Eep.
And this is my family, the Croods.
If you weren't clued in\nby the suntans and pets...
we're not exactly cavemen anymore.
Let's do it again. I think I blinked.
Our world is still plenty harsh and hostile...
but now we know the Croods will make it.
Because we changed the rules...
the ones that kept us in the dark.
And because of my dad,\nwho taught us that anyone can change.
Release the baby!
Sort of.
So, from now on,we'll stay out here...
where we can follow the light.
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：1610169789