更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
Victor, I don't know that it's...
Mom, you have to wear the glasses.
- It's 3D, honey. - Yes, Of course.
So that's where my candlestick went.
Isn't that your grandmother's tablecloth?
Yeah.
- That looks great.
Whoa! I just felt like I was attacked!
Send in the marines!
Over here, men! This way!
- Oh! - Whoa!
Watch out!
- Sparky! - Sparky, that's you!
You tell them, Sparky.
Whoo!
Oh, my!
Bravo!
- Oh! - Oh, Oh!
- Oh!
- Um... - Oh!
Maybe just unplug it.
Well, it certainly was exciting.
Yeah, it was a big finish. Well done, son.
I can fix this. Come on, boy.
All that time he spends up there.
A boy his age needs to be outside with his friends.
I don't know that Victor has friends, dear. Other than Sparky.
That's my point.
I don't want him to turn out, you know, weird.
There's nothing wrong with Victor. He's just in his own world.
Easy, boy.
See you later, sweetie.
Have a good day.
Victor! Come on, honey. You're going to be late.
Go put Sparky in the back yard.
Come on, Sparky!
Good morning, Mr. Burgemeister.
Your dog has been sniffing around my Dutch Dazzlers.
The other day I caught him peeing on my flamingo.
I'll keep an eye on him.
You better.
Yes, sir.
Go on, Sparky. That's right!
Good boy. See you later!
Where do you think you're going?
School.
What about that dog of yours?
She's not in the house and she's away from your tulips.
I want you to remember something.
While your parents are away, I am in charge here.
Yes, Uncle Bob.
Dutch Day is coming up, and I don't need any trouble.
- How's your song coming? - Okay.
Keep at it!
Dutch Day is a big day for me.
Yes, sir.
Good morning, children.
I am Mr. Rzykruski.
I will be your new science teacher.
Apparently, Mr. Holcomb had an incident.
He got hit by lightning!
Well, that is bad.
But he did not get "hit" by lightning.
Lightning does not hit a person the way one is hit by a baseball or a cabbage.
Lightning is simply electricity.
The cloud is angry. Yes. Making storm.
All the electrons are saying, "I am leaving you!"
"I go to the land of opportunity!"
The ground says,
"Yes, we need electrons trained in science just like you!"
"Come. Come! Welcome."
So both sides start to build a ladder.
This man, he comes out to look at the storm.
He does not see the invisible ladders.
When the two ladders meet... Boom!
The circuit is complete
and all of the electrons rush to the land of opportunity.
This man is in the way!
Ahh!
But it is very rare to have such an incident.
But it's not rare.
Lightning happens to people all the time here.
There's a thunderstorm almost every night.
My dad got hit twice.
They built New Holland on an abandoned gold mine.
I heard it was a cemetery.
That's where they buried the miners.
It's the windmill that does it.
Turning, turning the air until the sky itself rages against the night.
No. Cemetery. Definitely.
Students, on your way out, take a permission slip for the science fair.
First prize is a huge trophy!
- Hello, Victor.
Hi.
Mr. Whiskers had a dream about you last night.
How do you know?
Because this morning he made this.
Oh.
Did you get that out of the litter box?
It's an omen.
Last month he dreamed about Bob.
He fell in a manhole.
He dreamed about Toshiaki
the day he pitched a perfect game.
And Nassor the day he got knocked unconscious.
If Mr. Whiskers dreams about you,
it means something big is going to happen.
You can keep it.
One day you'll dream about me, won't you, Kitty?
Hey, boy. How are you doing?
You'll be my partner, right, Victor?
Because you have to have a partner for the science fair,
and whoever is your partner is going to win.
You know the most about science so pick me as a partner.
I have lots of ideas!
We can make a death ray!
It says no death rays. See?
Oh, man.
I still want to do it. Come on.
Who else would be your partner?
You don't have friends and neither do I.
I'm sorry, Edgar. I just don't need a partner.
I like to work alone.
Will you sign my permission slip?
Dinner's ready.
Victor, have I ever talked to you about what I do for a living?
You're a travel agent?
I sell dreams.
I tell people, "You can sail to Italy."
"You can do the hula in Hawaii."
- Will you sign my form? - I'm getting to that.
Okay.
In my job, sometimes you have people
who don't want quite the same thing, right?
Say a husband wants to play golf in Scotland
but the wife wants to paddle down the Amazon.
All right, you've got two conflicting ideas here.
And it's my job, Victor, to help them meet halfway.
Say... Scottsdale, Arizona.
He gets to golf, she gets Indians.
But there's no river. And no jungle.
- Nobody gets what they want. - Exactly.
And wrong.
They both get what they want because they compromise.
You'd like to do the science fair and that's great.
I'd like you to try a sport. Say, I don't know, baseball.
Science fair, baseball. Science fair, baseball.
How do you choose? Guess what? You don't have to.
No reason you can't do both.
You meet in the middle. Everyone's happy.
Look at what Toshiaki's doing.
He's keeping his eye on the target, never losing his concentration.
Strike three! Next batter!
I want you to concentrate on your project for the science fair.
Come on, honey!
Whoa. Nice catch, Sparky.
Come on, Victor, please.
Tie Sparky up and get your head into the game.
Time out!
Sorry, boy.
Hey, Sparky.
Play ball!
Strike one!
Nice try, son.
When conducting an experiment, trying is the important thing.
It is okay to fail as long as you keep trying!
Eh?
Come on, Victor. You can do it, honey.
- Strike two!
Yes!
Come on, honey!
Victor, run!
Sparky!
No!
He was a great dog. A great friend.
The best dog a kid could have.
When you lose someone you love, they never really leave you.
They just move into a special place in your heart.
He'll always be there, Victor.
I don't want him in my heart. I want him here with me.
I know.
If we could bring him back, we would.
Try and get some sleep, sweetheart. Things will seem better in the morning.
Just like lightning, the nervous system is electricity.
We are wires and springs and cables to send the messages.
Even after death, the wiring remains.
Watch as the muscles respond to the electricity.
Hi, Victor! How was school?
Okay.
Shoo!
I'm sorry, boy.
You're alive!
Sparky!
I can't believe it! You're alive!
I can fix that.
It worked.
It really worked.
Victor!
Victor, breakfast!
Victor?
Are you up here?
Shh.
Quiet down, boy.
Victor?
Sparky, Shh!
Quiet.
Victor!
Shh!
French toast or waffles?
Uh, waffles.
Then I'll need my waffle iron back, Mr. Director.
It's my science project. It's a robot.
- A robotic bucket? - Yes.
- For mopping, I suppose? - Yes.
Maybe when you're finished, you'll let me use it.
Sorry, boy, but I can't let anyone know about you.
They may not understand.
So, you need to stay here today.
No, couldn't be.
What?
I know. And Helen said she thought they were
putting up some kind of TV antenna on top of the roof.
In the middle of a thunderstorm?
That's what she said.
I don't believe it.
And did you get that big power surge the other night?
Jack thought it was a fuse box,
but apparently it affected the whole neighborhood.
Sometimes I wonder just what goes on in that house.
I just don't feel safe walking by there.
Sweetie, you okay? Here you go.
So anyway, Jack loves it here,
but if the schools weren't so great,
sometimes I wonder if we'd be better off closer to my mother.
Sparky?
Hmm.
- Hi, Victor. How was school? - Good. Got to go.
Sparky?
There you are.
Good boy. Sorry you had to stay here alone all day.
What's the matter, boy? Are you okay?
Hmm. You're a little low.
Are you hungry, boy?
All right, here. Let's top you up.
Victor? Could you come down here, please?
Victor!
Your friend is here.
Edgar?
Hey.
Edgar, what are you doing here?
- I know. - What?
I know.
- Know what? - You know.
No.
I think I know what you know I know.
Look, I don't know what you think I know, but I don't know it.
Your dog is alive!
That's impossible. - I know.
I know it is so impossible, but you did it.
You did it!
So, show me how, or I'll tell everyone.
- Oh, Mrs. Frankenstein! - Shh.
May I have a cookie, please?
Oh. Yes, of course.
All right, come on.
Oh!
I think the wind and the lightning are part of the same thing,
some kind of strange force.
But the wind isn't strong enough to bring an animal back from the dead.
For that, you need lightning.
So when can I do it?
You can't. This isn't an experiment. It's my dog.
Show-and-tell, Victor.
You show me, and I won't tell.
Can I help you, young man?
I'd like to buy a fish.
Certainly. Which one?
This one.
What do we do now?
What happened to it? What did you do?
I don't know. It should have worked.
It's invisible. It's an invisible goldfish.
- Why is it invisible? - I have no idea.
You can't tell anyone. You understand that, right?
Not until we figure out how it works.
Okay, Okay.
- Promise? - Promise.
How are we supposed to see an invisible goldfish?
Put your finger in. You can feel it.
Ah! It bit me!
Let me see it.
It's my science project, and it's top secret!
Mmm.
Yeah? Well, our science fair project is even cooler.
- What is it? - Double top secret.
Sea-Monkeys?
We got to come up with something better.
- Bigger. - I know.
The science fair is in two days.
I know.
- You're the smart one! - I know.
Hmm.
Okay, okay. Sit still. Shh.
Sparky, no! Shh. No! Shh!
Sorry, boy, but we can't risk anyone seeing you again.
Shh!
Toshiaki says you have an invisible fish.
- No, he didn't. - So, you don't?
I didn't say that. Who said I did?
Toshiaki says it's your science fair project.
If it was, I couldn't tell you.
So it isn't,
or it is?
No. Yes.
I'm confused.
Do you have an invisible fish?
Okay.
But you have to keep it a secret.
Swish your finger around. You can feel it.
It's just water. There's nothing there.
No, it's invisible.
Huh?
I don't know what kind of game you and Victor are playing,
but that trophy will be mine.
Victor.
Something's wrong with my fish!
- What is it? - It's not there any more.
Maybe it just hopped out. Did you have the lid on it?
Yes, ever since
I left your house.
I mean, it was there when I went to bed.
I'm thinking maybe they don't last.
They're only there for a little bit and then they're gone.
No! Sparky!
- Sparky!
Don't worry. I can fix that, too.
Good night, boy.
Mmm.
Are you sure this is going to work?
No. That's why it's called an "experiment."
We have to collect data.
Do we have to collect it on me?
- Ready? - No.
Ten, nine, eight...
We could use a test dummy or something.
...seven, six, five...
Computer simulation.
...four, three, two...
- I have to pee! - ...one.
Whoa! Whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Oh!
Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Ah!
It's working! It's working!
What were you boys doing on the roof?
- Science. - Science.
As mayor of New Holland,
you have entrusted me with your safety.
So I can't sit idly while a teacher endangers our children.
The man is a menace!
She's right! He's crazy!
Have you looked through this science book they're using?
Apparently Pluto isn't good enough to be a planet any more.
When I was a kid, Pluto was a great planet.
This guy comes along and rewrites the rules!
In fairness, he didn't write the textbook.
Mr. Mayor, Edward Frankenstein.
- Your neighbor, of course.
I just would like to say that our son Victor
is just crazy about the new teacher.
Thinks he's great.
My Cynthia has been asking
all sorts of strange questions about things I've never even heard of.
Shouldn't we at least give the man a chance to explain himself?
Yes.
Please come up, Mr. Menace.
Ladies, gentlemen.
I think the confusion here is that you are all very ignorant.
Is that right word, "ignorant"?
I mean "stupid," "primitive," "unenlightened."
You do not understand science, so you are afraid of it.
Like a dog is afraid of thunder or balloons.
To you, science is magic and witchcraft because you have such small minds.
I cannot make your heads bigger,
but your children's heads, I can take them and crack them open.
This is what I try to do, to get at their brains!
Oh, my.
Thank you.
Oh, jeez.
Be quick, boy. They'll be home any minute.
Praise be New Holland
Streets so wide and sidewalk
The sidewalks. Okay.
Praise be New Holland
No! Shh. No!
No, no, no! Shh!
Victor?
Hi, Elsa. What are you doing?
Practicing my song for Dutch Day.
It's nice.
- Did you get a new dog? - No.
- I heard a bark. - Yeah, that was me.
You are barking?
Hmm. You must really miss Sparky.
Uh, I got to go. Bye.
Bye.
I feel so sad for him, Persephone.
He really misses his dog.
Where's Mr. Rzykruski?
All I know is I'll be teaching the class for the rest of the semester.
Do you know anything about science?
I know more than you do.
Mr. Rzykruski knew a lot.
Well, sometimes knowing too much is the problem.
What about the science fair?
Oh, it's still on, but it will be judged by someone who's not insane!
Me!
Now get cracking, and may the best person win!
I can't believe they let the gym teacher be the judge.
She's not even interested in science.
Back home, everyone is scientist.
Even my plumber wins Nobel Prize.
Your country does not make enough scientist.
Always needs more.
You should be a scientist, Victor.
Nobody likes scientists.
They like what science gives them, but not the questions, no.
Not the questions that science asks.
Actually, I have a question.
That is why you are a scientist.
I was doing my experiment, my project, and the first time it worked great,
but the next time it didn't.
I mean, it sort of worked, but then it didn't.
And I don't know why.
Then maybe you never really understood it the first time.
People think science is here, but it is also here.
The first time, did you love your experiment?
Yes.
Ah.
And the second time?
No. I just wanted it over.
Then you changed the variables.
I was doing it for the wrong reason.
Science is not good or bad, Victor.
But it can be used both ways.
That is why you must always be careful.
I can't believe I broke my arm for nothing.
None of us are going to win! E has an invisible fish!
No, he doesn't. You fell for a parlor trick.
You're saying he faked it?
That fish you showed us, was it real?
It was, and it was dead, too.
You brought an animal back from the dead?
No, Victor did.
With lightning, and boom, and sss.
Impossible.
I swear! I mean, he already brought back his dog.
He brought back Sparky?
Mmm.
Victor will win the science fair unless we can do better.
Bigger.
You say you know Victor's secret?
Now is your chance to prove it.
Now, where's my muffin tin?
Victor.
Sparky?
Sparky! But you're...
Sparky's alive!
Sparky?
Hey, come on!
Mom? Dad? What's going on?
Sparky! No! Sparky!
Sparky. no!
Sparky, come back!
Sparky!
Hey, hey! Just a minute!
No! I have to go find Sparky!
Victor, what have you done?
You said yourself, if you could bring back Sparky, you would!
Yes, but that was different because we couldn't!
It's easy to promise the impossible.
What you did was a very serious thing.
Crossing the boundary between life and death.
Reanimating a corpse!
It's very... Upsetting.
I just wanted my dog back.
Oh, sweetheart.
We'll help you look for Sparky
but when we get back, I think we need to have a little talk.
Understood?
Yes.
Now, let's go find your dog.
Sparky!
Sparky, are you in there?
Mom, Dad! I'm going to check the school and the park.
You guys do the town square, okay?
Got it.
Sparky!
Cool.
Interesting.
It has something to do with the lightning.
I don't really understand it.
Oh, but I do!
Tonight, we shall bring the dead to life!
Sparky! Where are you?
Sparky!
Sparky! Sparky!
Thank you. Thank you so much.
And now it's my pleasure
to introduce this year's Little Dutch Girl,
my niece, Elsa Van Helsing.
I don't think this is safe.
Nonsense! We have the fire chief over here.
You know, a lot of girls would kill to be in your place.
I'd welcome death.
Praise be New Holland
Streets so wide and sidewalks clean
Modest homes at modest prices
Everyone's hope and dream
I'm going to win.
No, I shall win the science fair.
Hmm.
In our houses tight and safe
We have nothing to fear
Ah.
The tomb of Colossus.
Soon you shall be awakened
and we shall be reunited once again!
Ah, Shelley.
Praise be New Holland
May your windmills spin forevermore
Isn't she adorable?
Mm.
Mr. Whiskers?
Hello!
Is someone there?
Rise, Colossus.
Rise from your tomb!
Huh!
Shelley?
Sparky!
Sparky?
Sparky, it's okay, boy. It's just me.
I thought that you were gone.
I never want to lose you.
Promise you'll never go running off, okay?
Come on, boy.
Was someone else here?
- Victor! I need your help. - Did you see those things?
- They were like... - Sea-Monkeys!
You know how on the package, they're like,
in a happy kingdom and everyone's smiling?
- Yeah? - They're not like that at all.
- Victor! I need your help. - I asked him first!
My problem bigger!
Yeah, he's right.
Okay, let's go!
And now for our next act,
we have something really big.
No! Get away!
Oh, oh!
This way! In here!
Go, Colossus.
Kill! Kill!
Kill!
Colossus?
Mm! Mm-mm!
Get away from me!
Your Sea-Monkeys. Are they freshwater or saltwater?
Freshwater.
Freshwater animals can't tolerate salt.
Hey! Over here!
Cool.
Help!
Get back!
Stay away from us!
Sparky!
No, no, no, no!
Whoa, stop! You put me down! I gave you life!
Victor! Victor, I need help. Please!
Shelley?
Persephone!
Persephone, are you okay?
- Here, Mr. Whiskers.
Here, kitty, kitty, Mr. Whiskers.
- No!
Persephone!
Bring her back!
Mr. Whiskers.
I'm coming, Elsa!
What happened?
Sparky! There you are.
Are you all right?
What you got there, boy?
Let me through!
I knew it. It's the boy's dead dog!
That's Elsa's wig. Where's my niece?
He's killed the little girl!
After him! Kill the monster!
Help!
Stay away from us!
Get him!
Where's my niece?
Look out! It's on fire!
There's Elsa!
Help!
Ow!
Elsa!
Sparky!
Victor!
- Help! - Hang on! Don't let go!
I can't reach!
Hang on!
I can't hold on much longer.
Sparky!
Victor!
Stay back. It's too dangerous.
That's my son in there!
Oh! Oh!
Victor!
- Victor! - Honey, are you all right?
Sparky!
No!
Victor,
is there anything we can do for you?
You said that I need to let him go.
Sometimes adults don't know what they're talking about.
Start your engines!
Give it more juice!
Turn off your engines!
It's okay, boy. You don't have to come back.
You'll always be in my heart.
- Sparky!
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：274796078
Love
Love is strange
Oh-oh
When there's beauty on the inside
The outside there's nothing to ch-ch-change
Oh, after! know
Oh, after it I want this song to love
With someone watchin' over me
Rain or storm the only place I wanna be
Is close to the heart of everything you'd ever need
The lightning's not frightening
When you are with me
Oh, 'cause love is not always
What you think it'll be
Love
Oh-oh
Love is strange
When there's beauty on the inside
The outside there's nothing to ch-ch-change
Strange love Strange love for one another
Can't judge a book by its cover
Love
Love is strange
Oh-oh
When there's beauty on the inside
The outside there's nothing to ch-ch-change
The lightning's not frightening
When you are with me
Oh, 'cause love is not always
What you think it'll be
Love Oh-oh
Love is strange
Oh-oh
When there's beauty on the inside
The outside there's nothing to ch-ch-change
Strange love Strange love for one another
Can't judge a book by its cover