I got a feeling this is going to be a riot
(SIX DAYS PLAYING)
I don't read the news papers
Because they all have
ugly print
Bring it on, bring it on
Bring it on
At the starting of the week
At summit talks you'll hear them speak
It's only Monday
Negotiations breaking down
See those leaders start to frown
It's sword and gun day
Tomorrow never comes until it's too late
You could be sitting taking lunch
The news will hit you like a punch
It's only Tuesday
What time is it?
You never thought we'd go to war
After all the things we saw
It's April Fools' day
What time is it?
Tomorrow never comes until it's too late
You hear a whistling overhead
Are you alive or are you dead
It's only Thursday
What time is it?
You feel a shaking on the ground
A billion candles burn around
Is it your birthday
What time is it?
Tomorrow never comes until it's too late
Trying to be smart
Get your ma on the phone
Tomorrow never comes until it's too late
Trying to be smart
Think tomorrow's come I think it's too late
Another day
Tomorrow is another day
Nice ride.
It does the job.
What job, delivering pizzas?
Well, it's not the ride, it's the rider.
What the hell was that?
What?
Hey! You talking to my girl?
Oh, shit. Here we go. Yeah.
She was just admiring my ride.
BUDDY 1: "My ride."
My grandma's Buick could smoke
that piece of shit, trailer trash.
Well, what about your daddy's Viper?
This beast's got 500 horsepower
and a Borla exhaust system.
It does 0 to 60 in like 4.3 seconds...
That's about right. That's about right. Yeah.
Wow. You can read the brochure.
(CAR DOOR BANGS)
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(BOYS BOOING)
(MAN WHISTLING)
BUDDY 3: What a pitch, baby. What a pitch. I like that.
BUDDY 1: What's he gonna do?
Let's make it happen. Bring it.
BUDDY 3: I got your... I got your back.
Why don't you nice boys let your cars do the talking?
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
I only race for pink slips.
This car goes for 80 grand.
What would I do with a broken-ass piece of shit like that?
(ALL BOOING)
CINDY: How about me?
Winner gets me.
(MAN CHEERING)
Cut it, let's cut it. Let's go, go, go, go!
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(CAR ENGINES REVVING)
Blast-off, baby!
CLAY: First one out the other side...
BUDDY 1: It's time. Let's go!
Ready, boys? Make it interesting, Clay.
(WHOOPS)
Shit!
(ALL CHEERING)
(WHOOPING)
Yeah!
I thought you loved me.
(WHEELS SQUEALING)
Oh, well.
What the hell?
Guess I got a new date for prom.
Clay, stop the car! Shut up!
Clay, stop the car!
Shut up!
Stop it!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Clay, please stop! Please stop!
(SCREAMING)
Can I get a copy of that?
You think this is a joke, huh?
You see Ken and Barbie over there?
They're gonna walk out of here without even a slap on the wrist.
Mommy and Daddy are too hooked up.
But I like screw-ups like you.
You know why?
'Cause you're 100% guaranteed conviction.
Where's my car? I crushed it.
You did what?
Sit down! You're done. Easy, easy.
You're done. You understand me? You're done.
And all before your eighteenth birthday. Now sit down.
Sean.
What the hell were you thinkir, huh?
CASE WORKER: Mrs. Boswell? Please.
It's, uh, it's Miss.
Officer, is it, um, illegal to smoke in here?
It's a tough state.
And it's a pretty clear-cut case.
He'll be lucky if they don't try him as an adult.
This is our third town in two years.
Your sors got two priors for reckless driving,
willful destruction of property.
This makes it strike three.
They're definitely gonna want to get him off the streets.
BOSWELL: Well, there's just got to be another way.
So, where are we moving this time?
We are not moving anywhere.
(BABY CRYING)
(DOORBELL BUZZING)
Sean.
I thought you were gonna be here on the 7th.
Today is the 7th.
Well, look, just hold on one second.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Come on in.
This is it.
You know, Sean, I was, I was gonna be there.
But your mom, she said the 7th, see,
and we're a day ahead of you in Japan.
Well, you're here now, and that's good.
So, how is your mom?
Where do I sleep?
Now, Sean, you know she had no other choice.
I mean, it was either this or juvi hall,
I mean, you just can't keep moving away
every time you get into trouble.
Worked for you.
Look, neither of us asked for this.
But I promised your mom I'd take care of you.
So you just go by the rules her and I agreed to,
and I'm sure you'll manage just fine.
Rules?
Yeah, rules. Real simple.
You go to school,
you come back here right after.
And I don't want to see or hear
about you anywhere near a car.
(SIGHING) Here, the bedroom is yours.
Make yourself comfortable.
Lights out in 10.
(TV CHATTERING)
(ALARM RINGING)
(ALARM STOPS RINGING)
You got to be kiddir.
(THE BARRACUDA PLAYING)
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Wrong train.
I'm new here.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Boswell, yes, ma'am.
(THE BARRACUDA CONTINUES PLAYING)
TWINKIE: Japanese food is like the Army.
Don't ask, don't tell.
Name's Twinkie.
Hey, I noticed you ain't have a laptop.
Yeah?
I'll hook you up. Half price.
No, I'm cool.
60% off. Hmm?
Since we're both army brats and everything.
I ain't got no cash, man.
And I ain't an army brat.
All right, all right.
Well, what about a cell phone, huh?
Everybody needs a cell phone.
No offense,
but I'm probably not gonna be here
long enough to remember your name.
Then you gonna need some new shoes to book town with, man.
You like Michael Jordan?
I love Michael Jordan.
Check this out.
Brand new Jordans. Not even out yet.
LeBron James couldn't even get his hands on those.
You selling that Sparco steering wheel?
Hell, no. That's mine right there.
Man, I even paid retail for it.
What you drive?
My ride? Yeah.
My ride's one of a kind.
Show me.
Thought you werert stickir around.
All right.
(OOH AHH PLAYING)
My life be like Ooh Aah (yeah), Ooh Ooh
Ooh Aah (yeah), Ooh Ooh
My life be like
It's times like these that make me say
Lord if you see me please come my way
Leavir bread crumbs for when I stray
Rely on sacrifice and the price you paid
Feel me like a fingertip (fa-finger tip, fa-finger tip)
Slamming, huh? Look at that car.
Tryir not to quench your fire with the things I do
At least let me drive.
SEAN: Y'all better have some real cars around here.
TWINKIE: Okay, I see somebody got jokes, huh?
Well, all right.
I don't know if you're ready for them, though.
You look a little nervous.
What up, Tosh?
(TOKYO DRIFT (FAST & FURIOUS) PLAYING)
I wonder if you know How they live in Tokyo
If you see me then you mean it Then you know you have to go
Tick, Tick, Tick
I wonder if you know How they live in Tokyo
If you see me then you mean it Then you know you have to go
For when you blow your wad, man.
(RAPPING IN JAPANESE)
(CAR TIRES SCREECHING)
Tick, Tick, Tick
Hear that?
It's still not right for the way I drive.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
I don't need a computer to tell me about my throttle response.
Okay. Then we're done here.
You wouldn't have that problem with a V8.
Boys.
All they care about is who's got the biggest engine.
I'm a guy. It's in my DNA.
So y'all race with these things, huh?
Cute little toys.
You know, I almost didn't recognize you without your slippers on.
Don't you mean uwabaki?
Neela, right?
You're a quick learner.
So, where you from, anyway?
Here.
No, I mean, not where you live.
Where'd you come from?
Does it really matter where I'm from?
Who's the tourist?
What's with you and the schoolgirls, D?
You're moving up in the world.
You gotta elevate your company.
Wednesday, Wednesday, meet Thursday.
God. Girl.
Ladies, hold that thought, all right?
All right, beautiful. Hold up.
Hey!
He was just leaving.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
I'm sorry. I don't speak Japanese.
Understand that? Gaijin?
Takashi.
We were just talking.
This isn't your scene.
That word you called me, gaijin or something or other,
what does that mean exactly?
Means, turn around,
keep walking.
That's exactly what we gonna do.
Come on, man, let's roll.
TWINKIE: Yo, look, man, he's yakuza.
Now, see, that's funny,
'cause I thought this was, like, a free country
where a girl could talk to whoever she wants.
You know who I am, boy?
Yeah. You're like the Justin Timberlake of Japan, right?
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Leave.
Damn, man. You know yakuza? The Mafia?
TWINKIE: Look, sorry, DK-san.
Monkey didn't have his banana today.
Hey, D, let's go.
It's time to race.
(MIMICKING MONKEY)
Hey, good luck, Timberlake.
You're the one that's lucky, 'cause I'm about to race.
Then let's race.
DK: With what, huh? Your skateboard?
Easy to sound cocky when you got no ride.
Take mine.
Let's race.
What? I wanna see what the kid's got.
Can he drive?
You know what DK stands for?
Donkey Kong?
Drift King.
Drift?
What do you mean, drift?
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
Still need a dictionary?
TWINKIE: You know that real famous painting?
The one of the woman who's smiling all the time?
SEAN: The Mona Lisa.
Right, right, right. Mona Lisa.
Well, look, man, this car right here's
like the Mona Lisa of the drift world.
Han rebuilt this bad boy from ground up.
We talking forged pistons,
bigger turbo, new rods, new crankshaft.
Hey, man, Hars labor ain't cheap, man, you feel me?
Well, if I needed a 30-second lesson on how to drift...
All right, look, man, there's lots of ways you can do this, all right?
Hand braking is the easiest,
so the first thing I want you to do,
I want you to rip that e-brake.
All right, after you rip the e-brake,
then I want you to power over.
You know what?
Just don't mess up Mona, all right?
All right.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
(ENGINES REVVING POWERFULLY)
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Ready.
Set.
Go!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(CRASHING)
TWINKIE: I told you.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Damn it!
(SHOUTING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Damn it!
(ALL BOOING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Don't leave town.
Do you know what time it is?
I thought it was around 7:00.
You know, US is a few hours behind.
Looks like the party was better here, anyway.
Have you been racing, Sean?
You're out of here.
Go ahead.
You don't get it, do you?
You have nowhere else to go.
If it doesn't work out here,
you're going to jail. Do you get that?
This isn't a game.
And I'm gonna tell you one more time,
if you're gonna live under my roof,
you're gonna go by my rules or get out.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
Get in.
I'll get you your money.
Why you talking like you have a choice?
There's a guy in there with a paw
that owes me some money.
A paw?
Go get me my money.
Okay.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Han said,
okane.
Han said, okane.
(GRUNTING)
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Let's go.
(RESTLESS PLAYING)
HAN: You're in the pickup and delivery business now.
I might call you once a week or once an hour.
I don't care if you're sick as a dog
or in bed with Beyonce.
I call, you show.
Only if you teach me how to drift.
This ain't a negotiation.
I wasrt negotiating.
(RESTLESS CONTINUES PLAYING)
(VIDEOGAMES CHATTERING)
(MAN SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(CHO LARGE PLAYING)
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
What's he doing here?
He's paying me back for that crumpled beer can
sitting in my garage.
Hope he's not driving.
Gaijin.
When is your next race?
I'd really like to be there.
Why not be in it?
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
You heard me.
Ready to lose another car, Han?
I'm ready to take that '86 Corolla off your hands.
All right.
Put up the '72 Skyline.
Done.
What do you think, Morimoto, huh?
Get him out of here.
We have business to discuss.
Your shipment's late.
Since when are you so worried about the details?
When is the shipment arriving, Han?
Just sit pretty and let me handle it.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPING)
Hey, Dad, it's me.
Uh, I had to stay after school
for some extracurricular activities.
So I'll be home a little later.
Sir.
You really need to stop following me around.
What are you doing here?
I thought I'd stop by and ask your boyfriend
for some drifting lessons.
Trust me.
You don't wanna be a part of this world.
It's good enough for you.
You don't know anything about me.
Well, why don't you think I know?
'Cause I'm a gaijin? An outsider?
Let me guess.
You're an army brat who moved around a lot.
Your mama and daddy was never home.
So you walked around pissed off all the time.
And now you found your family with these drift nuts.
Zero for one, cowboy.
Why can't you go find a nice Japanese girl
like the rest of the white guys around here?
(MAMACITA PLAYING)
Mamacita, oh my God, I think your on fire
Do you want me to get you water
Is everything okay back there?
I can handle DK.
I thought he's yakuza.
His uncle's yakuza.
He's just playing gangster in his little storage room.
But I need him.
He keeps Uncle Kamata from poking around too much.
What do you mean?
Well, his uncle gets a piece of the action
from everyone on his turf.
We're on his turf.
50% of something is better than
100% of nothing.
So have you raced DK?
Why not? Is he that good?
What's the point of a race?
To see if I'm better than the other guy.
Just proves you're faster, that's all.
If I were to race, it would have to be
for something important.
Or why else do it at all?
Why are you letting me race?
'Cause you're DK's kryptonite.
And you owe me a car.
She wanna break it down, break it down, break it down, break it down
She want some reggaeton, reggaeton, reggaeton, reggaeton
Oh, shit.
(BEEPING)
I make ya smile right
What the...
Police cars here are only factory-tuned.
You can do better than 180 k,
they can't catch you, so they don't even try.
'Cause its just nice you lookin different sayir to yourself
You know what?
I'm beginning to like this country already.
When my chain keep linkir like Christmas lights
Mamacita, oh my God I think your on fire
Do you want me to get you water
Danny!
You're looking good.
(JAPANESE SONG PLAYING)
HAN: Disco.
HAN: We gotta catch up.
Get you a drink on me, huh?
Let's go.
HAN: Aha. Easy now, ladies.
Come on.
Hey Mami, you sexy, hey Mami, you sexy
What's up? How you doing?
Hey, baby.
Hey Mami, you sexy, hey Mami, you sexy
Hey Mami, you sexy
Can I get that number
Big hot pockets, feya, ugly
Corny, busted, chopped, straight fugly
British guys playing rugby
Brooklyn boys who wanna thug me
Skanky, cranky, foogly, oogly
Slammin dudes that wanna do me
G'Doonk G'Doonk, skoonky, flavors
HAN: Keep your hands off the kid, girls.
He's underage.
Country boys and them boys in the city
Ladies, ladies, ladies.
Disneyland for grownups, huh?
All these girls, man, they look like...
What, models?
Check it out.
See, Tokyo is the fashion capital
on this side of the planet, all right?
Now, imagine you been posing all day.
I mean, that's a lot of hard work.
Not only do you get tired, but, on top of that,
you wanna have a little fun, but you can't
'cause you don't even know nobody in town.
And most of the guys around here are
too chicken shit to even try picking up one.
So what do you do?
Man, you talk to the little dude who makes you laugh.
Yeah.
Look, man, I don't just think outside the box.
I tear it up.
That's my thing.
Yo.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
You should slow it down papi
You sound like a carbon copy
HAN: Sean!
But you're just plain sloppy
Hey Mami, you sexy
(THERE IT GO (THE WHISTLE SONG) PLAYING)
It's dipset Bitch
There it go Baby don't stop now
(WHISTLING)
There you go Damn shorty look good
And I'm thinkir about gettir at her
Okay, time to whistle at her
Ay girl, you make my whistle blow
There it go Bring it here baby
Top down and I'm at it again
It's hot now and I'm at it to win
You heard me
Who want it with me
Nobody wanna it with me Oh, I'm so fly
Oh, Mami, Back up
Move it till you feel something hard on your back
The red Evo's yours.
If u want it come and get it I ain't kiddir I'm with it
Here it go, go
So, girl, let me see you get low
There it go Yeah, just like that
What do you mean?
You're representing me now.
What you think, I'm gonna let you roll in a Hyundai?
So, girl, let me see you get low
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Oh, man.
Damn it.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
My mother, she's blind in one eye
and she can drift better than that.
Han, where did you find this guy?
Will someone please teach this guy how to drift?
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
SEAN: Is that yours?
Sure is.
What happened?
I don't know. I found it this way at the base.
It's got potential.
Yeah, maybe. We'll see.
You know, Sean, the Japanese have a saying.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
"The nail that sticks out gets hammered."
You're gonna be late.
(BELL RINGING)
Sean!
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(STUDENTS CLAMORING)
Come on, man, you broke it.
(STUDENTS CHEERING)
Hey, whoa, whoa.
There must be a misunderstanding.
Out of my way, or you're next.
Take it easy.
Look, man, I don't do refunds, all right?
Okay, let's go, then! Let's go!
Touch me again...
Here.
Try not to break this one.
(SPITS)
Say, man!
What the hell is wrong with you, huh?
Now everybody's gonna want exchanges around here.
Damn!
Not easy saving the day, is it?
Maybe you could give me some pointers sometime.
You're doing all right.
Thanks.
Hey.
Yeah?
Sorry about the other night.
Your life isn't any of my business.
It's okay.
(ROUND ROUND PLAYING)
Foul!
Ain't no damn foul. That was a foul.
Yo, you in my face. That was a foul.
EARL: Hey, Han, sort this wanker out.
A wanker?
What do I look like, a zebra?
So, how did you end up over here, anyway?
Well, you know those old Westerns
where the cowboys make a run for the border?
This is my Mexico.
Why'd you let me race with your car?
You knew I was gonna wreck it.
Why not?
'Cause it's a lot of money.
I have money.
It's trust and character I need around me.
You know, who you choose to be around you
lets you know who you are.
And one car in exchange for knowing
what a mars made of,
that's a price I can live with.
Look at all those people down there.
They follow the rules, for what?
They're letting fear lead them.
What happens if they don't?
Life's simple.
You make choices and you don't look back.
SEAN: So, if you don't drift to win,
what do you drift for?
HAN: You really want to know?
Yeah.
Okay. Let's go.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR STEREO)
HAN: There's no "wax on, wax off" with drifting.
Learn by doir it.
The first drifters invented drifting
out here in the mountains by feeling it.
So feel it.
Again!
What's in this bag?
You'll see.
How much you got?
Keep going, keep going.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
I'm so good, man, I could sell rubbers to a monk.
Again.
(INAUDIBLE)
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Watch it. Watch it. Not too early, now.
Go, go, go, go!
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Don't lose it! Don't lose it!
(WHOOPING)
(KEYS JANGLING)
WOMAN: Hey, Han.
(WOMAN SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Hey, Twink. Get this man a bunk.
(SHOUTING)
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
Pleasure doing business.
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
TWINKIE: Yeah, baby. I told you. I told you, didn't I?
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
It's actually not bad.
I didn't even have to put ketchup on it.
See, I'm not a total gaijin.
I hate that word.
It's what they used to call me when I was a kid.
I thought you were born here.
Well, "outsider" can mean many different things.
My mom died when I was 10.
She came out here from Australia
when she finished high school.
And all I know about her is that
she went to work in a hostess bar.
DK's grandmother took me in.
Well, my parents split up when I was three.
Me and Mom moved around a lot.
Mostly 'cause of me.
Well, it was all 'cause of me.
Kind of made myself an outsider, you know,
without even thinking about it.
But I realize now,
outsider or insider, it doesn't really matter.
All that matters is knowing what you really want
and going after it.
We used to come up here when we were kids.
Even before we could drive we'd cut class, sneak out,
come up here, and watch the older kids drift.
Things were different back then.
Once I got my license, I practically lived up here.
Back then, kids just drove whatever they had.
You know, we just made do.
No one bothered us.
The day I got my license
is the day I got my first speeding ticket.
The day after that, I won my first race.
I beat this rich kid by three lengths.
I gotta admit, it felt good.
It felt like...
Like everything else just disappears.
No past and no future.
No problems.
Just the moment.
TWINKIE: Boy needs to chill.
Hey, Twink, I'm gonna grab another set.
Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa! Another set?
No. Look, that was your third set today.
I mean, them tires ain't cheap.
DK, grab a chair.
We're about to roast some marshmallows.
Yo, come on, man, look...
Stay away from her,
or the only thing you'll be driving is a wheelchair.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Find yourself a new driver.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
I'm all right.
HAN: What'd you expect?
You didn't just play with fire,
you soaked the matches in gasoline.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
It's over.
All this over a gaijin?
I am a gaijin.
You've changed, DK.
You say I've changed.
But we're not so different, you and I.
We're both products of fuckups, aren't we?
They say your mom was the best trick
in all of Kabukicho back in the day.
Leave my mother out of this.
If we hadrt taken you in, you'd be just like her,
doing anything for a buck.
Think anyone would take a second look at you
if it wasrt for your uncle?
We're the same, Neela.
Difference is I know who I am and where I belong.
Do you know who you are?
Do you know where you belong?
Hey.
Come on.
(MAN SPEAKS JAPANESE)
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Hey, brother.
I vouched for you!
Put my reputation on the line for you!
We were partners!
You think you can keep your side deals from me?
Come on. We ain't in the Boy Scouts.
This is what we do.
Takashi!
DK: What about now? Hmm?
Is this what we do?
Man, you need me.
You'd still be shaking down teahouses
for chump change if it wasrt for me.
(SHOUTING IN JAPANESE)
Get in!
SEAN: Go! Go! Go!
SEAN: Come on.
(SHOUTS IN JAPANESE)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
Sean. Sean!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Takashi.
(SPEAKS JAPANESE)
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Okay.
I'll go with you.
Neela.
See you when Daddy's not around.
I'm putting you on a plane tonight.
SEAN: Dad...
Sean, don't argue with me.
I did this. I can't run away.
I can't.
Sean, I'm your father.
I'm responsible for your well-being.
And I'm responsible for my mess.
I gotta do this.
Can you understand that?
At least you're not redoing my mistakes.
You all right, man?
We're leaving town.
Look, I know some people...
I can't do it, Twink.
Look, DK wants your head.
All right?
And the trouble you just made for Kamata?
You're done here, bro.
Maybe I should talk to Kamata.
What?
DK answers to him.
I know I just didn't hear that.
I gotta end this. I'm gonna go talk to him.
What, are you crazy, huh?
Han is dead, all right!
Plus, you can't just walk into Kamata's place, man!
It's all I got.
Something I think Han would've wanted you to have.
What's this?
You're gonna need it if you're gonna make it
out of Kamata's place alive.
Don't you need it?
No, it's cool. Look, I'll figure it out.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Sean.
You need to leave.
You came to the wrong place.
I didn't come here to see you.
KAMATA: Takashi.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
You think
you can walk in here, dump some cash and walk out?
I know I'm only returning what belonged to you
in the first place, sir.
But that's not why I really came.
I came here to apologize.
I know your nephew and I have embarrassed ourselves badly.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Sir, I'm here to offer you a peaceful solution.
How do you plan to accomplish that?
A race.
(CHUCKLING)
DK and I have caused nothing but problems for you,
for us.
And I'm asking you to allow us to settle this,
once and for all.
We race
and the loser leaves town for good.
I've already beat this piece of shit once!
Good.
Then it should be easy.
The cops took all the cars.
Hey!
That's why she's spitting.
SEAN: We almost there, Twink.
Couple more tweaks.
It's not the car I'm worried about, man.
DK picked this road for a reason.
This is his mountain.
He's the only one to ever make it to the bottom.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(CAR ENGINES REVVING)
(ALL CHATTERING)
Yeah!
Yes!
Come on.
Yeah! Come on!
Come on, Sean.
Let's go! Let's go!
Sean, you the boss. Let's go.
Damn! Come on, man! That ain't right.
(ALL GASPING)
(ALL CHEERING)
BOY: Yeah, baby!
That's what I'm talking about, man.
TWINKIE: I told you!
(KAMATA SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(TOKYO DRIFT (FAST & FURIOUS) PLAYING)
I wonder if you know How they live in Tokyo
If you see me then you mean it Then you know you have to go
Fast and furious
Tick, Tick, Tick
(RAPPING IN JAPANESE)
Hey, yo, Sean! Yo, Sean!
Hey, check this out, man.
This dude over here wanna race the new DK.
Heard he's been beating everybody around Asia, too.
Not tonight, Twinkie.
Said he knew Han.
Said Han was family.
All right.
Let's race.
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(BANDALEROS PLAYING)
Nice ride.
I won it from my friend Han, a few years ago.
I didn't know he was into American muscle.
He was when he was rolling with me.
You know this ain't no 10-second race.
I got nothing but time.
(ENGINES REVVING)
You ready, kid?
Come on, Sean! Come on!
Ready!
Set!
Go!
QQ1610169789
(CHO LARGE PLAYING)
You so crazy, you so crazy
Far East to West Mic Check
1, 2, 3, 4
(RAPPING IN JAPANESE)
Cho large
So hot so hard We cho large!
You so crazy, you so crazy
(RAPPING IN JAPANESE)
We got big jewels, big cars
Big watch with a pair of Bapesta's
Ice cream with an astronaut
You don't understand mammy We cho large
This that bape shit
Shake it like you ape shit
So hot so hard We cho large!
You so crazy, you so crazy
You so crazy