更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
Just packed up a real money load, and it's comir your way.
Look for "Rodgers" on the side of the truck.
Don't forget my share of the deal.
Shit!
- Tuna on white, no crust, right? - I don't know. How is it?
Every day for the last three weeks you've been comir in here...
and you've been askir me how the tuna is.
It was crappy yesterday...
it was crappy the day before, and guess what.
- It hasn't changed. - I'll have the tuna.
- No crust? - No crust.
Thank you.
Talk to me, Jesse. This ain't workir, brother.
It's your fuel map. It's got a nasty hole.
- It's why you're unloading in third. - I told you it was third.
I lengthen the injector pulse another millisec...
and just tune the NOS timer, you'll run nines.
What's up with this fool? What is he, sandwich crazy?
No, V. He ain't here for the food.
Chill out, bro. He's just slingir parts for Harry.
- I know what he's slingir. - He's tryir to get in Mia's pants.
- What's up, guys? - How you doir, Mia?
How you livir, girl?
Hey, Dom. You want somethir to drink?
Ah, he's beautiful.
I like his haircut.
Vince.
Vince!
- What? - Can I get you anything?
You look good.
Thanks a lot, Mia. See you tomorrow.
Sure.
- Tomorrow? - Oh, I love this part.
Try Fatburger from now on.
You can get yourself a double-cheese with fries for 2.95, faggot.
- I like the tuna here. - Bullshit. No one likes the tuna.
Well, I do.
Jesus Christ, Dom! Would you get out there?
I'm sick of this shit! I'm not kidding, Dom!
Get out there!
- What'd you put in that sandwich? - That's really funny.
All right.
- He was in my face. - I'm in your face.
Relax! Don't push it! You embarrass me!
Get over there!
Jesse, give me the wallet.
"Brian Earl Spilner." Sounds like a serial killer name.
- Is that what you are? - No, man.
Don't come around here again.
Hey, man, you know this is bullshit.
- You work for Harry, right? - Yeah, I just started.
You were just fired.
Hey, Dominic, I appreciate what you did in a big way.
Dominic, I owe you.
Brian, you're messir with my business.
When Dominic drives, he's golden.
Kids pour in here, want everything he has, every performance part...
and they pay cash!
- What did Dominic say? - You don't wanna know.
- What did Dominic say? - He wants you outta here.
- He wants me outta here? - Yes!
- And what did you say to Dom? - What do you think I said?
I told him, "Good help is hard to find."
Relax.
I need NOS.
- I need NOS. - No.
My car topped out at 140 miles per hour this morning.
Amateurs don't use nitrous oxide.
I've seen the way you drive. You got a heavy foot.
- You'll blow yourself to pieces. - I need one of these.
One of the big ones.
Actually, no. Let's make it two.
And, Harry, I need it by tonight.
Hey, hold up, hold up. Look at this snowman right here, man.
Sweet ride. What you runnir under there, man?
- Making me find out the hard way? - Hell, yeah.
You brave. You brave. They call me Hector.
I got a last name too, but I can't pronounce it, so...
Brian Spilner.
Typical white boy name. Know what I'm sayir?
See that over there?
That's mine. It's my baby. But I ain't cuttir her loose tonight.
- Why not? - 'Cause I'm goir legit.
Tryir to get on the NI RA circuit. You heard about that?
Hell, yeah.
- So what's up with you, man? - I'm just waitir for Toretto.
Shit. Better get in line.
- This yours? - Yeah. I'm standir next to it.
That's funny. You know, Edwin happens to know a few things.
And one of the things Edwin knows is...
it's not how you stand by your car.
It's how you race your car. You better learn that.
Oh, shit. Here they come. It's on.
- Dom, how you doir? - Hey, Camille.
You been doir yoga?
You did? Of course you did. Monica.
I smell skanks.
Why don't you pack it up before I leave tread marks on your face?
- Letty, I was just talkir. - Whatever.
Okay, Hector.
Yeah? What's up, man?
- What's up? - Edwin.
- How we doir this tonight? - One race.
Two-G buy-in. Winner takes all.
- Hector, you're gonna hold the cash. - Why Hector?
He's too slow to make away with the money.
- Good luck, guys. - Wait. Hold up.
I don't have any cash, but I do have the pink slip to my car.
You just can't climb in the ring with Ali 'cause you think you box.
He knows I can box.
So check it out. It's like this.
I lose, the winner takes my car, clean and clear.
But if I win, I take the cash, and I take the respect.
Respect.
To some people, that's more important.
That your car?
I see a cool-air intake.
It's got a NOS-fogger system and a T-four turbo, Dominic.
I see an AIC controller.
It has direct port nitrous injection.
Yeah, and a stand-alone fuel management system.
Not a bad way to spend $10,000.
You see that shit?
He's got enough NOS in there to blow himself up, period.
What do you say? Am I won'thy?
We don't know yet. But you're in.
Let's go.
What the hell's goir on around here?
Street's closed, pizza boy. Find another way home.
Goddamn street racers.
Iog on 22, code three. Tension is high.
They've blocked the street.
Edwin...
this is yours, whether you win or lose.
But if you win, you get her too.
You're gonna win.
I'm gonna win.
We had a reported homicide, 187, at Barakian liquor.
I've got a 187 in Glendale. Cops are all over it.
We're good to roll. I repeat, good to roll.
- Let's race! - Right.
Go!
Hell, yeah!
Damn, that guy's fast.
Let's go! "Menage a"!
No! Monica!
Shut up!
Let's go now, baby!
- Here's what you want, right here. - There you go.
You were racir a bunch of skateboards.
My sister holds the money.
Count it.
And you're my trophy.
Hey, Monica! What's up, baby?
What's your problem, nigga? You didn't win.
Fuck you, then!
- Was that fun? - Got a problem there, huh, buddy?
- What are you smilir about? - Dude, I almost had you.
You almost had me?
You never had me. You never had your car.
Granny shifting, not double-clutchir like you should.
You're lucky that hundred-shot of NOS didn't blow the welds on the intake.
Almost had me?
Now me and the mad scientist gotta rip apart the block...
and replace the piston rings you fried.
Ask any racer, any real racer.
It don't matter if you win by an inch or a mile.
Winning's winning.
Available units, we have reported street racing along Hawthorne...
Oh, shit! We got cops!
Go!
Dom, get in the car! Go!
Toretto, stop right there!
Get in!
You're the last person in the world I expected to show up.
I thought if I got in your good graces, you might let me keep my car.
You are in my good graces, but you ain't keepir your car.
You drive like you've done this before. What are you, a wheel man?
You boost cars?
- No. Never. - Ever done time?
Couple of overnighters. No big deal.
What about the two years in juvie for boostir cars?
Tucson, right?
Yeah, I had Jesse run a profile on you, Brian Earl Spilner.
He'll find anything on the Web, anything about anybody.
So why bullshit?
So what about you?
Two years in Lompoc.
I'll die before I go back.
- Oh, great. - What?
It's gonna be a long-ass night, that's what.
Follow us.
I thought we had an agreement.
You stay away, I stay away.
Everybody stays happy.
We got lost, Johnny. What do you want me to tell you?
- Who's "we"? - My new mechanic.
Brian, meetJohnny Tran.
The guy in the snakeskin pants, that's his cousin, Lance.
So when are you gonna give me a shot at that Honda 2000 of yours?
- This your ride? - It was. It's his now.
No, it's not. I haven't taken delivery.
Then it's nobody's car.
Somebody put in the wrench time.
- What do you think, Lance? - It's an amazing machine.
Yes, indeed.
Let's go.
I'll see you in the desert next month.
Be ready to have your ass handed to you.
You're gonna need more than that crotch rocket.
I got somethir for you.
What the hell was that about?
Long story. I'll tell you later. Let's get outta here.
NOS!
So, what the hell was that all about?
It's a long story.
We got a 20-mile hike. Humor me.
A business deal that went sour.
Plus, I made the mistake of sleepir with his sister.
Yo, Spilner.
You want a beer?
Oh, shit.
We were all there, right? Falling behind.
- With all that nitrous. - Yeah.
Yo, Dom. We were just about to go lookir for you, brother.
- Where were you? - There were mass cops there.
They came in from every direction. Their shit was orchestrated.
- This your beer? - Yeah, that's my beer.
Yo, Einstein. Take it upstairs.
You can't detail a car with the cover on.
Can't even get that right.
You all right?
Am I all right?
It was just a question.
Yo, Dom! Why'd you bring the buster here?
'Cause the buster kept me out of handcuffs!
He didn't just run back to the fort!
The buster brought me back.
You can have any brew you want... as long as it's a Corona.
- Thanks, man. - That's Vince's, so enjoy it.
You...
Hey, bro, you got a bathroom?
Yeah, upstairs. First door on the right.
He's got no call beir up in here.
- You don't know that fool for shit! - He's right, Dom.
Vince, there was a time when I didn't know you.
That was in the third grade!
Yeah, so, what girls are here?
- You name it. You want mine? - You need to shut the f...
- You don't have anything? - You look a bit tired.
I think you should go upstairs and give me a massage.
Look at all our guests.
How about we go upstairs and you give me a massage?
Crazy lady.
You know you owe me a ten-second car, right?
Ouch.
Oh, shit.
Did you wipe the seat?
Oh, Jesus Christ! Would you cut the shit already?
Come on!
Come on. Let's go get me a drink.
Come on, man. We were just about to get along.
- So, what do you want? - Anything, long as it's cold.
My brother likes you. He usually doesn't like anybody.
Yeah, he's a complicated guy.
Yeah? What about you?
- I'm simpler. - You're a shitty liar.
Well, I'll take that as a compliment.
- But there's a problem. - What's that?
You need to get some sleep.
And you definitely, definitely need a shower.
Come on. I'll take you home.
Show me your hands. Very good. Now open the door.
Put your hands on your head. Behind your head.
Face the front of the vehicle, walk backwards towards the rear.
Take two steps to your right. Stop right there.
What'd I do?
Shut up. He's clean, Sarge.
Damn! Muse, will you take these things off?
- Shit. You put 'em on so tight. - I like realism.
- You like realism. - You never know who's watching.
Nice crib, Sergeant. It's a lot nicer than that last place you confiscated.
Ain't it? Eddie Fisher built this house for Elizabeth Taylor in the '50s.
See? Even the cops are Hollywood in Hollywood.
Here he is, fresh from Toretto's hot rod heaven.
That was an $80,000 vehicle, officer.
- Wait. You tell him what happened? - He knows what happened.
- Send the bill toJohnny Tran. - The kid's givir me attitude?
That doesn't speak very well for police-FBI relations, Tanner.
- I walk in, the guy's already givir... - All right, all right.
We'll talk, okay? Let's talk about it.
Muse, why don't you make us four iced cappuccinos, please.
- Come on. - Regular or decaf, Sarge?
Decaf, I think.
Four hijackings in two months, and we don't have anything.
DVD players and digital cameras alone are won'th a million-two...
which brings the grand total to six million plus.
We're in the political crosshairs now, Brian.
That's why you're undercover.
You want that detective badge fast, kid. And you wanna know something?
The FBI can help, if you come through for us.
- What does the truck driver say? - He gave us the same M.O.
Three Honda Civics, precision driving...
the same green neon glow from under the chassis.
Lab says the skid marks came back the same:
Mashamoto ZX tires.
So we know that it's somebody in the street racing world.
We don't make this case soon...
the truckers will take matters into their own hands.
I tell 'em we're close.
You gonna make me a liar?
Look, what do we know?
We all know this world revolves around Toretto, right?
I'm not sayir that he's necessarily the one that's poppir these trucks...
but I can guarantee the both of you that he knows who is.
- It's just a matter of time until... - You want time?
Buy the magazine. We don't have time.
Just get me something I can use.
Is Harry cooperating?
Yeah, like a guy who's gonna do time for receiving stolen property if he doesn't.
What kind of vibe is he getting from Toretto?
He's scared of him, but he doesn't think he's jackir trucks in his spare time.
- He's too controlled for that. - Wait.
Not that I want to contradict Harry's fine judge of character...
but Toretto did hard time for nearly beating a guy to death.
He's got nitrous oxide in his blood and a gas tank for a brain.
Do not turn your back on him.
Hey, Tanner. I'm gonna need another car.
What about parts and service?
- Hold off on that. - What should I do with this?
All right, what the hell is this?
What do you got there?
- This is your car. - My car?
I said a ten-second car, not a ten-minute car.
You could push this across the finish line, or tow it.
Couldrt even tow that across the finish line.
No faith.
I have faith in you, but this isn't a junkyard.
- This is a garage. - Pop the hood.
- Pop the hood? - Pop the hood.
TwoJZ engine.
- No shit. - And what did I tell you?
- I retract my previous statement. - You know what?
This will decimate all after you put about 15 grand in it...
or more, if we have to overnight parts from Japan.
We'll put it on my tab at Harry's.
Yes!
I gotta get you racing again so I can make some money off your ass.
There's a show in the desert called Race Wars, and that's where you'll do it.
Tell you what. When you're not workir at Harry's, you're workir here.
If you can't find the right tool in this garage, Mr. Arizona...
you don't belong near a car.
You don't belong near a car.
He owns you now.
Tell me what you think about this.
Koni adjustables.
Gonna save us about two pounds.
And they're gonna give us better traction for the hole shot.
All right?
This is your basic layout of the car...
and that's pretty much what it could look like when it's finished.
Red, green.
Man, you should be goir to MIT or somethir.
Yeah, right.
No, I got that... Oh, what's it called?
- That attention disorder... - ADD?
Yes, that shit. Yeah.
You know, I was good in algebra and, like, math...
and shit.
Everything else I failed.
Dropped out of school. I don't know.
It's just somethir about engines...
that calms me down, you know?
- I'm outta here. - Come on, dog.
Vince, get over here and give us a hand.
Looks like you got all the help you need, brother.
- Mia! - All right already.
- The chickers dry. - I'm comir out already.
Hey, hold up.
Because you were the first out of everybody here...
to reach in to get the chicken, you say grace.
Dear heavenly, uh...
Spirit.
Spirit. Thank you.
Uh, thank you for providing us with a direct port...
nitrous, uh, injection...
four core intercoolers and ball-bearing turbos...
and, um, titanium valve springs.
- Thank you. - Amen.
- Not bad. - Amen.
He was prayir to the car gods, man.
- These are the best. - What do you want?
- Practice. - Thank you, girl.
Look who it is.
Old Coyotes 'R' Us.
I thought you werert hungry, pumpkin.
- You know, I gotta eat. - He's always hungry.
All right, sit down.
How you doir, Mia?
- Jesse, hand me that chicken. - Let's eat some grub.
- Want some of that chicken? - Did you rent a movie or somethir?
Need a hand?
No, I'm good. You can go join the boys watchir the movie.
Well, the cook doesn't clean where I come from.
I'd like to go there.
I think we should go out sometime.
No, I don't date my brother's friends.
That sucks.
- I guess I'll have to kick his ass then. - I'd love to see that one.
No, I would... I would pay to see that one, actually.
Wash my car when you get done.
- What was that? - No, Mia.
I'm talkir to the punk.
And wear your favorite dress, 'cause when you're done...
I'm puttir you on the street where you belong, cutie.
Is this thing broken?
What's wrong with this thing?
V, what was that Cuban restaurant you wanted to take me to?
The one with the peccadillo and the...
- Red candles and the wooden table? - Yeah, the plantain too.
- What was it called? - Cha Cha Cha.
Yeah, that's it.
Well, you can take me there.
Friday night at 10:00. Is that good for you?
- Yeah, it's perfect. - Good.
- There's no popcorn? - Make your own goddamn popcorn!
All right. Now that's valet parking.
- Harry. - What's up, dog?
Excellent, brother. Come on in, man.
- Check it. It's yours. - What do we got here?
- Hired some new help, huh? - Don't even think about it.
- What's up, Hector? - How you feelir?
Pretty good. What do you need?
I need you to hook me up. Three of everything. I made a list.
Why don't you look that over.
- When do you need this stuff by? - Tomorrow. Today.
- Now. - Right.
White boys work fast, don't they? Beto.
That's right.
You said you need three of all this?
Yeah, three of everything. What do you think about that?
Check this out.
He moans like a cop.
Brian, this is one of those times...
when you need to be very clear about what you say.
Nod if you understand me.
Nod!
Sit up.
Tell me what the hell you're doir down here.
Oh, shit. What I'm doir.
I owe... I owe you a ten-second car.
And what this is about, this is about Race Wars.
I just went in there, and Hector is gonna be runnir...
three Honda Civics with Spoon engines.
And on top of that, he just came into Harry's...
and he ordered three T-66 turbos...
with NOS, and a MoTeC system exhaust.
So, what are you saying?
You're gonna go around and check everybody's shit out...
one garage after another?
Yeah.
Because Dom, you know...
I can't lose again.
He's a cop.
He's a cop!
You a cop?
Let's go for a little ride.
Walk!
All right, kid, stand watch.
There's no engines.
What are they plannir on racir with? Hopes and dreams?
I don't know, but I know they're sneaky as shit...
and they've got enough money to buy anything.
What?
Dom, we got a wolf pack.
It's Johnny Tran, and he's comiryour way really fast!
All right, we got company.
Spilner!
Come on. Move!
Let me ask you a question, Ted.
Do you see anything wrong here?
- We got no engines, do we? - No!
- Do we? - No!
Nissan SR-Twenty motors will pull a premium one week before Race Wars, huh?
Yeah, probably.
You're a smart fence, Ted. Maybe too smart.
What are you feelir, Lance?
Forty weight?
Fifty weight?
A forty weight sounds nice.
Where are they, Ted? Where are they?
- Enough! - Where are they?
They're in a warehouse.
They're in a warehouse, man!
Kiss my shoes?
Let's go get our engines.
My superiors are flying in from D.C. Day after tomorrow.
I want somethir to show. Now, we have a top-echelon fence...
with a lube hose in his mouth, automatic weapons...
a jacket full of priors on every one of these Asian punks...
a garage full of DVD players and generally psychotic behavior.
Why not move on Tran now, see where we are when the dust settles?
Because all we have is behavior. Let me get some hard evidence...
because what we have now is circumstantial...
What we have is probable cause and truckers arming themselves...
for some good old vigilante mayhem.
Tell us about Hector.
Latinos with spear guns. Give me a break.
Hector's still working on the engines for the cars...
but the tires don't match.
Will someone just give me a cigarette?
- Get him a cigarette. - Don't get him a cigarette.
- I thought you quit. - Yeah, I did quit.
- Just give me a cigarette. - Get him a cigarette.
- Tell me about Toretto. - He's too controlled for this.
I mean, what? Going suicidal on semi trucks? No way.
I mean, maybe his buddy Vince, but he's too stupid to pull it off.
I think the kid sister's blurring your vision.
- What do you say? - I don't blame you.
I'd get off on her surveillance photos too, buddy.
Knock it off. What? Are you going native on me, Brian?
Have you read Toretto's file lately?
- Yeah. I memorized that file. - Yeah, well, read it again.
No. Better still. Take a look at these.
Remember I told you about the guy he nearly beat to death?
Toretto did this with a 3/4-inch torque wrench.
He's a model of self-control.
I need a few more days.
What it's gonna do is it's gonna spool up.
I got this set up for 24 psi.
You got big plans tonight?
Yeah. We're going out to dinner.
You break her heart, I'll break your neck.
That's not gonna happen.
I wanna show you something.
Wow.
Me and my dad built her.
900 horses of Detroit muscle. It's a beast.
- Know what she ran in Palmdale? - No. What did she run?
Nine seconds flat.
- God. - My dad was driving.
So much torque the chassis twisted coming off the line.
Barely kept her on the track.
- So what's your best time? - I've never driven her.
Why not?
Scares the shit out of me.
That's my dad. He was coming up in the pro stock car circuit.
Last race of the season.
A guy named Kenny Linder came up from inside in the final turn...
and clipped his bumper and put him into the wall at 120.
I watched my dad burn to death.
I remembered hearing him scream.
The people that were there said he had died before the tanks blew.
They said it was me who was screaming.
I saw Linder about a week later.
I had a wrench, and I hit him.
And I didn't intend to keep hitting him...
but by the time I was done, I couldn't lift my arms.
He's a janitor at a high school.
Has to take the bus to work every day.
And they banned me from the tracks for life.
I live my life a quarter-mile at a time.
Nothing else matters... not the mortgage, not the store...
not my team and all that bullshit.
For those ten seconds or less...
I'm free.
So how is it, anyways, that the gang came to be?
- What? - The gang.
The gang? No, they don't call themselves a gang.
- What do they call themselves? - They're a team.
- They call themselves a team. - How is it the team came to be?
Well, that's a whole lot of history.
I've got time.
Vince grew up with my brother.
He didn't ever actually grow up, as you can tell.
But they were friends as kids. And Letty, she lived down the street.
Always into cars, though, ever since she was ten years old.
So, naturally, my brother always had her attention.
- And then she turned 16... - And then she had Dom's attention.
Yeah. Yeah, it's funny how that works, isn't it?
Yeah.
How is it thatJesse fits into the whole thing?
Well, Jesse and Leon just sort of showed up one night...
and never ever left.
It's just the way my brother is. Dom's like...
He's like gravity.
Everything just gets pulled to him.
Even you.
The only thing that pulled me in was you.
Being friends with your brother is just a bonus.
That's good.
That's good. That's nice to come first every once in a while.
You wanna go for a drive?
- Yeah? - The hijackers have hit again.
Bilkins made his decision. We're gonna move onJohnny Tran...
and his guys at 1700 hours, unless you say otherwise.
If you agree, just say yes.
- Yeah. - Who is that?
Just a wrong number.
Yes, sir. Yeah, I know, but...
Yeah, yeah. Yes. Yes, sir.
Yeah. I got it.
The DVD players were purchased legally.
All we've got on Tran and company are a couple of weapons charges...
and some outstanding speeding tickets.
- So they're out. - Yeah. Father bailed 'em out.
Is this the kind of intelligence I can expect from you, O'Conner?
- You're gonna put this on me? - I can put it on whoever I want to.
- Perks of the job. - No way you're gonna put this on me.
Wait a minute. Let me tell you.
I don't care if you have to put a gun to someone's head...
and blow your cover to smithereens.
You got 36 hours to crack this bastard...
or you might wanna be thinkir about another career.
It's Toretto, Brian. It always has been Toretto.
Tran and Hector are... They're just fumes.
Well, I know you've been lying to me. My question is this:
Have you been lying to yourself because you can't see past Mia?
He won't go back to prison.
Well, that's a choice he's going to have to make.
There's all kinds of family, Brian.
That's a choice you're gonna have to make.
You ready for this, jumpy?
Yeah.
Nice car. What's the retail on one of those?
More than you can afford, pal. Ferrari.
Smoke 'im.
- So what's wrong, Brian? - Nothir, man. I'm fine.
Come on. Obviously something's off.
Look. I have my good days, and I have my bad days, like anybody else.
Brian, don't lose that cool. That's your meal ticket.
My meal ticket? What? I can't pay for my own shrimp?
- I got your shrimp. - That's one thing about me.
You don't understand. I don't need handouts. I don't take handouts.
I earn my way, every step.
I just gotta make a little something extra on the side, like you.
What do you mean, like me?
- What's that supposed to mean? - That's what I mean.
- What does that mean, like me? - Don't try...
I'm not stupid, all right?
I know there's no way you paid for all that shit under the hood...
There's no way you paid for all that shit under the hood of those cars...
by doing tune-ups and selling groceries.
Now, whatever it is you're in on, I want in on it too.
- What is this? - Read it.
- What is this for? - It's directions.
To Race Wars. We'll see how you do.
Then we'll talk.
- How's it goir, bro? - What's up, man?
Welcome to Race Wars.
Great. Thanks a lot.
Baby. Hey, baby.
You should watch from the side. I wouldn't want to get exhaust on you.
- Put your money where your mouth is? - How 'bout I race you for that ass?
You want ass, why don't you hit Hollywood Boulevard?
You want an adrenaline rush, it'll be two large.
Right here, right now. What's it gonna be?
You got it.
Another one bites the dust.
Come on. What do you got? What ya got?
See ya.
Whoa. Bri, what's up?\nWhoa. Bri, what's up?
What's up, Jesse? What do you have in your hand?
Throwing down the pink slip, just like you.
- The pink slip to what? TheJetta? - Yeah.
- You can't bet your dad's car. - It's all right.
I ain't losir. This fool is runnir a Honda 2000. I'll win.
That way, me and my dad can roll together when he gets out of prison.
They're gonna throw him right back in prison after he kills you.
Shit. I'm up.
Visualize the win. Visualize the win, Jesse.
- I'm serious. Listen to me, man. - Who you racir?
Don't do it. I bet you he's got more than a hundred grand under the hood.
Too soon, junior.
Shit!
Oh, God.
Heads up, bro. We got problems.
- What? - Jesse.
- Where's Jesse goir? - He just raced Tran for slips.
Oh, shit.
- Where's he going? - He went to the car wash.
Whatever. Go fetch my car.
Go fetch your car? We're not on your block anymore.
You'd better watch who you talk to like that.
SWAT came into my house, disrespected my whole family...
because somebody narced me out.
And you know what? It was you!
Go! Let him go!
Get off of him! Get off of him!
Dom, chill out, man. Come on. Let's go.
I never narced on nobody! I never narced on nobody!
- I'm asking you not to go. - I'm doing this for both of us.
Don't give me that crap. You're doing this for you.
- Why are you asking me to stay? - Why do you insist on doing this?
Dom, please, don't.
- What's goir on? - What?
- You know what I'm talkir about. - No, I don't, Brian.
So what? You always have tears in your eyes when Dom drives away?
- What is the matter with you? - Come on.
What's your brother racir off in the middle of the night for?
I'm talkir about the trucks. You know about the trucks?
No, Brian. What trucks?
Jesus Christ.
- What? - Listen to me.
Mia, I'm a cop.
What are you talking about, Brian? What is this?
Ever since the first time I met you, I've been undercover.
I'm a cop.
You bastard.
Get off of me, Brian!
Listen to me!
Everything I ever said I felt about you was real, I swear to God.
You have to believe me. But right now, this isn't about you and me.
Your brother's about to pull a job, and we're almost out of time.
Those truckers, they're not laying down anymore.
They may make it through the night, but every law enforcement agency...
in California is comir down on 'em.
If you don't want anything to happen to your brother, to Letty...
to Leon, to Vince, you have to just get in that car with me right now.
You have to help me.
Mia, you are the only person that can help me right now.
Please, Mia. Please help me.
Civics are stashed somewhere outside ofThermal.
They wouldn't double back. And Highway 10's too well-patrolled...
so what does that leave us with then?
That leaves us with all this.
- Nextel. - Yes, this is Officer O'Conner...
serial number 34762.
I need a cell phone trace.
- What's the cell number? - Mia, what's the cell phone number?
Come on, Mia. She needs Dom's cell phone number now.
323-555-6439\n323-555-6439.
Thank you. You get that?
All right. We're one man short. Letty, I need you on the left side.
Your sister's right about this one. This don't feel good.
Don't do that.
- Something's wrong. - Stop.
We shouldn't be doing this withoutJesse.
Look. This is the mother lode. We've been on this for three months.
After this, it's a long vacation for everyone.
- Let's go. - I hope so.
Listen. The other night I had a dream that you and I...
were on a beach in Mexico.
- Really? - Really.
Come on. Let's make this happen.
- Keep on those scanners. - Copy that.
All right. Let's go.
Yeah?
We traced the number to the northbound 86...
mile 114 outside Coachella.
- We'll keep the trace open. - Let me see this.
All right. I think we're about 40 miles away.
What are you gonna do?
Okay! Go time!
We're all good, man. I got nothir on the scanners.
Keep goir.
Don't! Get back in!
- He's got a damn shotgun! - Back off! Get him off of there!
Shit.
Get me off this thing! Pull up!
- Unook yourself! - Come back!
- Do it! - Pull up!
- I can't... - You can do it!
Pull up! I'll jump!
Come on!
I'm pullir up to distract him.
Come on, boy.
Shot doesn't get better than this.
Son of a bitch!
Take me off of here. I'm gonna unook the wire.
Try it again. One, two, three!
Unook yourself!
- I can't get my arm free! - Vince, grab my hand!
- My arm! - Listen! Give me your hand!
- I can't get my hand free! - I'm gonna pull you off!
Dominic, hold on! Listen to me!
Shit!
Hold on!
Move out of the way! I'm comir to get him!
- Yo? - Pull back for Letty.
- Get her out of there! - I'm on it! Go!
I got her! You get Vince off that truck!
Come on, baby.
You okay?
Come on, girl. You all right? Come on. Let me look at you.
Come on. We gotta go. Let's go.
- Take the wheel! - What do you mean?
Put your foot on the gas!
- What the hell are you gonna do? - I'm gonna get him.
- Put your foot on the gas! - Okay!
- All right. Keep it steady. - I got it!
All right. Hold on, Vince!
He's having a hard time holding on! Get me a little closer!
All right!
- Closer! - I'm moving in!
Hold it right there!
- Go! - You gotta hang in with me!
We're gonna get you off this thing! Give me your arm!
Look at me. Don't let go.
Come on, Vince! Throw this arm around me!
Don't let go.
Come on, Vince! Get closer!
Vince, get closer! Come on!
Here we go.
Gotta jump.
Shit.
It's gonna be okay, baby. I love you.
Watch her.
Come on, Vince. Hang in there!
If we don't get him to an ambulance in ten minutes, he's dead.
- Hold this. Hold the pressure. - I got it.
Don't let go. Hold his arm up.
Yeah. Yeah, this is Officer Brian O'Conner.
I'm off-duty M.A.P.D.
I need a life flight rollout right away.
My twenty is Highway 86, mile marker 147.
I got one trauma victim, about 24 years of age, six foot...\nmaybe 200 pounds.
He's got a deep laceration to his right arm with arterial bleeding.
And he's got a shotgun wound, close-range, to his left leg.
Yeah.
Yeah. And he's going into shock.
Put the gun down now!
- Move your car. - Bullshit. Put it down now!
- No more running. - I'm not running!
- Where's Leon and Letty? - They're long gone.
Then it's over. I didn't call the police, but don't push me.
- Put the gun down! I swear to Go... - You are the cop!
You're a cop!
Brian, I gotta find Jesse before they do.
- I'm all the kid's got. - I'll call in the plates.
P.D.'ll pick 'im up way before Johnny even gets near 'im.
- Move your car. - Dom, stop it! It's over! Please!
Mia, stay out of it. Move the...
I am so sorry. I don't know what I'm doir.
I'm so scared right now. I don't know what's goir on.
- What were you thinkir, man? - I don't know. I panicked.
I'm sorry. I don't know what I'm doing. Will you please help me?
Call 911. You, call 911!
I used to drag here back in high school.
That railroad crossing up there is exactly a quarter-mile away.
On green, I'm goir for it.
That's not what I had in mind.
- You know what you're doir?
I owe you a ten-second car.
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：1610169789
I live my life a quarter-mile at a time.
Nothing else matters.
For those ten seconds or less...
I'm free.