更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
DOMINICAN REPUBLIC
All right, we're good to go.
- You got this? - You bet your ass, bubba.
Let's make some money!
Everyone in position.
l thought we'd be robbing banks by now,
not some gas truck in the middle of nowhere.
Down here, gas is gold, bubba.
Yeah, But banks don't move.
Anytime you get near a bank...we have to break your ass out of prison.
Kill the chatter! Game time.
l wouldn't piss him off, guys.
Yeah, yeah, I hear you.
Hey, you greedy bitch!
Okay, guys, we're gonna have to hit this hard and fast.
We got four K left before the downgrade.
Locked and loaded!
This is all you, Han.
Liquid gold.
We're clear.
Okay, T, you're up.
Let's see if you can get it under six tries this time, huh, T?
What are you talking about? I'll do it in one try!
Lt's more like three. Come on, Tego, keep it real.
Just one K left. We're running out of road. Get in there, brother.
I got it, I got it.
Shit!
T, cut loose! Unhitch, unhitch!
- Don't be crazy.lose your load! - What do you think I'm trying to do?
...idiot,just release!
- Spray that hitch! - I don't have a hammer!
Just do it!
Hold on! Hold on!
No shit!
Hold onto something tight!
Letty!
- Give me your hand! - I can't reach!
You got to jump!
Jump!
Letty, jump!
I've got you!
Dom...
Dom?
Dom!
Mi primo is running security on the airbase.
Says that there's going to be a couple of refueling planes arriving.
HAN: How you doing?
OMAR: Money, money!
Good.
OMAR: Yo, why your stack is bigger than mine always?
I'm supersized, baby.
Go have fun.
Cops just raided our garage in Baracoa.
They were real interested in you.
Heat's on and we just sent up a flare that's gonna lead them right to us.
l say we move out first thing in the morning.
Nah, it's me they want.
And if they catch me,
they're throwing big numbers at anybody with me.
Han, we had a good run.
Time for you to go do your own thing.
Heard they're doing some crazy shit in Tokyo.
Have you seen Letty?
There she is.
I hear Rio is nice this time of year.
The cops are getting hungrier.
Then I guess we're doing our job.
I'm a walking target.
I don't want you around when they catch up to me.
"Ride or die," remember?
Dom, how long have we been doing this?
And now all of a sudden, out of nowhere, it's too dangerous?
Come on.
We'll figure it out. We always do.
DOWNTOWN LOS ANGELES
- I don't know shit! - Give me a name!
- I don't know shit, man! - Give me a name!
David Park! David Park's the guy you want!
Please!
Thank God. Listen, he's in a mood because yesterday was his cheat day,
and then today, some genius brought in donuts.
Great.
Sorry I'm late.
Complaints keep rolling in after your little downtown Olympics, O'Conner.
Tell me that reinstating you wasn't a mistake.
- I got a name. David Park. - That's it?
That's all you got? David Park?
I could throw a fortune cookie out this window and hit 50 David Parks right now.
- It's Korean, not Chinese. - Whatever.
Park is a scout that recruits street racers to be mules for the Braga cartel.
We find Park, and we bust the bad guys.
PANAMA CITY,PANAMA
Dom.
Mia, I told you not to call me here.
Dom, it's Letty.
She's been murdered.
We have gathered here to pay our final respects to...
Let us reflect on her journey...
"The Lord is my shepherd, I shall not want. He makes me lie down..."
Facial recognition software matched Toretto
about 1 0 minutes after he crossed the border.
I don't get it.
I thought he'd show.
I told you not to come. They're staking the place out.
- If they find you... - They won't.
Come on. Look at you.
Letty wouldn't let them junk it.
Even though it is a goddamn curse.
When she came back, she was always in here,
working on it day and night.
It was weird.
It was like she knew you were coming back.
I want to see the crash site.
I just got off the phone with Deputy Director Lawson.
If we don't make serious inroads into the Braga case in the next 72 hours,
they're gonna shut us down.
I know I'm a newbie here, but why the clock now?
Because it's been two years,
and the last three agents we sent to infiltrate his organization
came back in body bags.
He's moved more heroin across the border than Escobar did in 1 0 years.
This guy is becoming one of our biggest national threats,
and we don't even have a picture of him.
We don't have prints! Not even a goddamn DOB!
What's the status on David Park?
lsn't he our ticket into the Braga organization?
We're running the name through city and county databases, sorting the possibilities.
We've got over 500 already.
Park's insignificant. Sounds like another jerk-off to me.
It's not. Without Park, Braga wouldn't have drivers to move his shipments.
Cross-check traffic. lllegal modifications.
Street racing. This guy will definitely have a record. We'll find him.
We better.
What do you know?
Your boy Toretto's red Chevelle has been spotted in his old neighborhood.
I'm going to bring his ass in.
Not in your car you're not.
It's straight ahead.
You found something back there.
There were burn marks on the ground.
The kind that could only be caused by nitrometh.
There's only one guy in all of L.A. that sells that.
Nothing you can do is gonna bring her back, Dom.
If I were Letty, I would ask you...
No, I would beg you, please, let this go.
Before it's too late.
It's already too late.
I love you.
Miss Toretto.
I'm Michael Stasiak, FBl.
Let's you and I have a little chat.
Hi. This is Forsythe in Evidence.
I need Stasiak down here right away to sign some greenies.
Thanks.
Hi. Hey.
Okay, I narrowed it down to 50 or so David Parks.
What I'd like you to do is run the make and model on each one of them.
- All right? - Okay. All right.
Thank you.
Hey, Tyler, we got a transfer.
You want to come with me?
Toretto.
When'd you get back in town?
I'm looking for a car you did an engine mod on.
Nitromethane tank. Ford full-size. Continental tires.
Look, what are you doing, coming in here like this, huh?
This ain't your scene anymore, boss.
Don't ever put your hands on me again, okay?
Say hi to your sister for me.
A Korean kid brought it in. David Park.
It's a green Ford Torino.
Please don't drop this on me!
I'm almost done.
Why don't you tell me why you dragged me here, Brian?
You know they're going to capture Dom. Maybe worse.
I don't want you getting tangled up in this. So stay away from him.
That's what you have to say to me after five years?
All of a sudden, you care what happens to me.
What I did to you was wrong.
I'm sorry. It was... It was the hardest thing I've ever had to do.
I'm sorry, too, Brian.
I'm so sorry that you had to come into my home and pretend to love me.
I'm so sorry that you ripped my family apart.
I'm very sorry that that was hard for you.
I lied to you.
I lied to Dom. I lied to everybody.
That's what I do best. It's why the Feds recruited me.
Maybe you're lying to yourself.
Maybe you're not the good guy pretending to be a bad guy.
Maybe you're the bad guy pretending to be the good guy.
You ever think about that?
Every day.
I always wondered,
why did you let my brother go that day?
I don't know.
Shit.
Brian!
I got the cross-checks on David Park back and have a list of possibles.
- What do you got? - All right. A 45-year-old male in a '06 Scion
- with three reckless driving tickets. - No.
- An '01 Chevy Tahoe. - No.
Two Mini Coopers, a '06 and a '07, a Toyota hybrid.
- Hell no. - A '98 Saturn, a '95 Sebring.
A '98 Nissan 240 with an illegal mod.
Wait. That's it.
- What? - The 240 with the illegal mod.
- How do you know? - 'Cause that's something I'd drive.
Don't! Don't! Don't!
Green Torino, running nitro.
- Whose car? - I don't know, man.
I'm just the middleman. I swear! I'm just the middleman!
Wait, wait, wait.
I don't know shit, man. I swear. I just run cars for Braga, all right?
All I can do is get you in the race! That's all I can do!
What race?
Help! Come on, hold on!
Let me up, man! Come on!
Come on, man, I don't know shit! Just let me up!
I told you, you got to talk to Braga!
Bring him up, Dom.
God! Don't drop me! That's all I know!
Bring him up.
You here to take me in, O'Conner?
- Shit! Shit! - Shut up!
Letty was my friend, too.
You weren't anyone's friend.
Yo, can you guys talk about this later? Now pull my ass up!
She was running for this guy, Braga, and things went bad.
Please!
I'm going to get these guys, Dom.
Now let me do my job and bring him up.
I'm going to kill this Braga.
God!
And anyone else who gets in my way.
Hey!
Don't let go.
O'Conner!
O'Conner! If you ever release a witness of mine again...
- That's enough! - Don't touch me.
- I'm fine! - That's enough.
- You're through, O'Conner! - I said that's enough!
Stasiak, go get yourself cleaned up.
What? He hit me first! You...
This isn't the Cub Scouts!
Now, go on! You're bleeding on my floor.
O'Conner, do you know the difference between a cop and a criminal?
- What? - One bad judgment call.
Keep your shit in line, son.
Have a good time.
Take a seat.
Good news. We have intel that Braga's number two, Ramon Campos,
will hold a street race in Koreatown tomorrow night
to fill a slot on his team.
They've already chosen three drivers from previous races.
Our newest informant, Mr. David Park,
has been kind enough to get us into the race.
O'Conner, you're up.
Let me guess, winner gets the slot.
All right, so these are all the imports the city has in impound.
- Okay, nice. - Pick your poison.
All right, 2206. I crashed one of those.
341 8 and 2765.
Okay, so which one do you want?
I want them all.
Standard issue tracking device.
Boss wants to know where you are at all times.
You want to play with it?
Hey!
What are you looking at, nutsack?
I don't know. You tell me.
The racer wants what Dwight's got.
See, but, ladies, Dwight's already on the team.
You got to be fast if you want to drive for Braga.
- Is there a problem here? - No.
You one of Park's guys, blondie?
Yeah. Yeah, I am.
Follow me.
See you later, punk.
You, too, punk.
BulI's-eye, co?o, come on!
We can do this all day.
You all know why you're here.
Good drivers
are a dime a dozen.
Man, every corner's got a chingadera tuner racing for pinks.
That's not what Braga has got me looking for.
Braga wants someone that would sell their abuelita to be behind the wheel.
Someone that drives their 1 0-second cars not in a straight line,
but to push it and make it through places no one else would take it.
Real drivers.
So, what are we hauling?
For the money Braga's paying, you don't need to know.
You just said you wanted real drivers.
A real driver knows exactly what's in his car.
Mira, real driver,
nobody's forcing you to race.
You the boss?
Or am I talking to the boss?
Do I look like a boss?
My job is to find the best drivers, period.
Whoever wins the race gets the info. We cool?
Are we cool?
Yeah, we're cool.
No, we ain't cool, man.
Who's closing these streets?
No one. That's the point.
PIease wait whiIe directions are downIoaded.
Proceed to the highlighted route.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six...
- You sure you want to do this? - A lot has changed.
...four... You're right.
...three,
two,
one,
go!
Right turn ahead.
You are now five miIes from your destination.
How's my ass look, Chia Pet?
Ghetto Smurf.
Dead man driving.
Come on!
Right turn ahead.
Shit!
Damn.
Rerouting.
Proceed straight ahead.
Shit.
- Rerouting. - Just shut up!
You are 2.6 miIes from destination.
Oops, I didn't see you.
You are now four and one-haIf miIes from your destination.
- U-turn, if possible. - Are you kidding me?
You are now 4.2 miIes from your destination.
Sorry, car.
You are now one miIe from your destination.
Yeah, guess who's back, Dom?
Let's go!
Nice car, baby!
Bitch!
You are now one-quarter mile from your destination.
Too early, Dom.
No!
Still a buster.
You have reached your destination. Goodbye.
At least we know you can't beat me straight up.
I didn't know there were any rules.
Now that's what I call real driving.
No, that's bullshit, man!
Go cry to your mama, eh?
You work for Braga now.
When the GPS calls, you follow.
Driver's license.
What driver's license?
Thumb.
Cell phone number.
The print is for Campos.
The number is for me.
Yo, nutsack!
Let me tell you something, man, muscle beats import every time.
You know what I'm saying? Every time!
Ladies, let's get on back to Papa Dwight's.
Papa Dwight wants you to take off your shoes.
Dwight likes feet. Take off your shoes.
So beautiful.
Dwight likes this foot a lot.
Yes, baby!
- Daddy Dwight loves... - FBl!
I didn't do nothing, man! Dwight didn't do nothing!
- Hey, no! Stay, stay! Where you going? - Bye, Dwight!
No, what did I do?
You're under arrest for distribution of meth.
Meth? Dwight's never touched that shit, bro!
Dwight has now.
Yo, that ain't mine! No!
You know that's never gonna stick, right?
Yeah, it's not supposed to.
Live it up! Live it up!
Yeah, Corona.
That's too bad about Dwight.
Having the Feds raid your house the same night you make the team.
So unfortunate.
I wish I could say I was surprised to see you here.
What's to stop someone from telling them you're a cop?
Probably the same thing that's keeping me from telling them why you're really here.
- What up, fellows? - Hey, how you doing?
- Great. You having a good time? - Yeah, a great time.
Come on, let's have a better time.
How's your car? It took a nasty bump.
lt'll be ready.
I also heard you just got out of County.
Yeah. Mmm-hmm.
You know a guy named Jim Garcia?
Nah. Big place. Lots of names, lots of faces.
And you, you're wanted by a lot of people, homes.
Yeah, that kind of heat can't be good for business.
Yeah, well, that depends on how you look at things.
I go down, I do time.
I do real time.
I don't know about your other drivers, but when I see flashing lights in my mirror,
I don't stop.
Do you know each other?
He used to date my sister.
I see.
- You're a lucky man. - How's that?
You're still breathing.
To the ladies we've loved and the ladies we've lost.
So, what's Braga about?
You know, he's just one of us.
Came up from the streets. Down for el barrio.
Now he's a shot caller.
The boss of bosses.
See all these cats in here?
Any one of them would die for Braga.
lncluding you?
Especially me.
Enjoy the party, fellows. Club's yours.
Whatever you want, booze, broads, it's all good.
Braga's mine.
I'm taking the whole house down.
Good luck.
Something interests you about this car?
Just admiring the body work.
Are you one of those boys who prefers cars to women?
I'm one of those boys that appreciates a fine body, regardless of the make.
Your car?
It's Fenix's car.
You'll meet him at the rendezvous. He'll be leading you.
So now
that I know your taste in cars,
tell me, what about your women?
It all starts with the eyes.
She's got to have those kind of eyes that can look right through the bullshit
to the good in someone.
20% angel, 80% devil.
Down to earth.
Ain't afraid to get a little engine grease under her fingernails.
That doesn't sound anything like me.
It ain't.
- Hi. - Hi.
- I got a gift for you. - All right.
A dirty shot glass, just what I always wanted.
I got these from the club last night.
There's two sets of prints here. Run them both.
I know one of these is Campos'. I think the other might be Braga's.
And you're gonna have to go beyond lnterpol.
So, that means I have to contact individual agencies,
and that could take weeks. Okay.
Yeah.
That's your third traffic violation in less than three blocks.
Slow it down, O'Conner.
Sure thing, Dad.
He stopped.
We lost him.
He killed the tracker. We don't know that.
I'm telling you, he killed the tracker. We don't know that yet!
Get the bird overhead.
Right now, I'm moving north, 33', 56'...
All clear.
Base, fIag nine, I'm at AngeIs 5.
I don't have a taIIy on the target. Repeat, I don't have a taIIy on the target.
They're gone, there's no one down there.
Damn it!
This ain't right, bro. Nobody said nothing about being locked in no truck.
Tell me about it.
Hey. Hey!
Yo! Where do you think they're taking us?
Don't matter.
We're all just along for the ride now.
Welcome to Mexico, boys.
There are helicopters and surveillance cameras
that scan for heat signatures at the border.
But there are blind spots that I can guide you through via satellite.
There can be no margin of error, so you must follow my every direction.
Any questions?
I thought Fenix was gonna be here.
He'll meet you out there.
All right, everybody, sync up.
Good luck, gentlemen.
SateIIite Iinkup engaged.
Keep proceeding northbound at current speed.
Stay cIose to Fenix.
He'II Iead you across.
I got a heat signature northbound along Legardo Ravine.
Thermal imaging window on the Mexico side's gonna be down for about 45 seconds.
Get the camera on it.
Manual override. Rerouting camera to designated coordinates.
Hurry it up. You guys have been tagged.
Shit.
Toretto, get back in formation.
Reimaging commencing.
I don't see anything.
They're gone.
Get the helicopters to cover it.
Base, we're 40 seconds out from Legardo Ravine.
They're sending a heIicopter.
You have 30 seconds.
North 32' 33', west 1 1 6' 49'.
The window is cIosing fast.
You need to get out of there before they send ground support.
Fifteen seconds.
Base, target is at two miIes.
You're running out of time.
You need to get out now!
Base, we're at north 32' 33', west 116' 49'.
We have no visuaI contact. RoII ground units for confirmation.
Sloppy!
Very sloppy!
What are you doing, man?
Come on.
Get out.
Come on, man.
Come on, today, man. Come on, let's go.
Hey, don't touch me. Hey, don't touch me, man!
Hey, I said don't touch me, man!
Hey, look, dawg, don't put your hands on me.
Hey, Malik, chill, bro.
Yo, man, what's up with your boy?
Hey, boss man!
What did you say?
I said only pussies run nitrometh.
You looked under my hood?
I'm talking to you.
Got something on your mind?
'70 Plymouth.
Her name was Letty.
Yo.
Where's my money?
And somebody wrecked her car.
I wrecked her car.
You remember her face?
Huh?
'Cause I don't.
Last time I saw it, it was burning.
Now what?
I'm going to enjoy what happens next.
Dom, get in!
Get in! Come on!
Come on! Get in the fucking car! Let's go! Hurry up!
What have you got, Trinh?
We're contacting agencies in multiple countries.
Unfortunately, most of them have to manually scan their prints for us to upload.
O'Conner's on line five.
And, sir, you should see this.
Thank you.
Talk to me, O'Conner.
- Where the hell have you been? - I got the shipment.
"l got the shipment," or "we got the shipment"?
What are you taIking about?
Traffic cams in the area picked up pictures of you and Toretto together.
Listen to me, O'Conner. Bring in the shipment and bring in Toretto.
But I thought the point was to get Braga. We got an opportunity here.
Brian, the clock stopped ticking.
Bring them in. Are we cIear?
O'Conner?
So this is what $60 million looks like.
Yeah, we got to get you to a doctor.
We got to find a place to hide this.
I got a spot.
502, wet reckless. I need a 48-hour hold.
Out back. Any spot you can find.
You sure about this?
Yeah. The last place they'll check, their own impound yard. Trust me.
You know, I've been thinking,
when you blew up your car back there, you blew up mine, too.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
So now you owe me a 1 0-second car.
- Is that right? - Yeah.
Now we're even.
Is this your way of keeping me away from him?
- You're the only one I could call. - He's my brother, of course.
The bullet's not in there.
I'm gonna clean it and stitch it up. It's going to hurt.
I bet you're going to enjoy this.
A little.
- Want some of this? - Yeah.
It's spicy.
I like it hot.
Dom, what are you doing?
You reached first, you have to say grace.
Thank you, Lord, for blessing this table.
With food, family and friendship.
You asked me why I let Dom go.
I think it's because at that moment,
I respected him more than I did myself.
Yeah.
One thing I learned from Dom is that nothing really matters unless you have a code.
And what's your code, Brian?
I'm working on it.
Shit. Hey, Dom.
- When were you gonna tell me? - Dom, what are you doing?
When were you gonna tell me you were running Letty?
- Let me explain... - When were you gonna...
Dom, stop!
- You don't understand. - I don't understand?
Stop!
She did it for...
Dom, stop!
Dom, stop it! Please stop!
She did it for you, Dom! She did it for you!
Letty came to me to clear your name in exchange for bringing down Braga.
She just wanted you to come home!
I'm sorry, Dom!
I'm sorry!
You better have one hell of an explanation. You disobeyed a direct order.
- Where's the shipment? - It's safe.
It's safe.
Look, we could use the shipment to parade in front of the media,
get a few hundred pounds of heroin off the street,
but Braga's just gonna send another shipment next week and the week after that.
Let's use the shipment to lure Braga out
and lop the head off a multi-billion dollar cartel.
And how do you suggest we do that?
A hand-to-hand exchange with Braga.
He'll never show.
He can't afford not to.
You got a plan?
There's a price.
We bag Braga, you let Toretto walk.
- Yes? - It's Dom.
I was just thinking about you.
You know, when I gave you my number, I was hoping you'd call.
But not under these circumstances.
What circumstances? Me being alive?
Don't take it personaIIy.
It's just business.
I got some business of my own.
Get Campos.
It's them.
Uh-huh.
Was that how Braga inspires loyalty? Killing his drivers?
One can always find more drivers.
It's just good business.
I want to trade.
Braga doesn't negotiate.
Fine.
You explain to him how all of a sudden $60 million worth of product disappears.
I know that can't be good for business.
What do you want?
Six million cash, delivered by Braga himself.
I don't Iike being shot at.
I ain't gonna put my neck out again unless he's got something to lose, too.
He'll never go for it.
Either I deal with Braga, or you do.
When and where?
Sir, players are onsite. Holding positions at the perimeter.
All right. Listen up. Everybody stay frosty.
We don't move a muscIe untiI O'Conner gives the signaI.
When he gets the money, you know what to do.
Well, the good news is, when we get this guy,
you walk out of here a free man.
Is that what they told you?
Yeah, that's the deal.
You still put milk and cookies out for Santa Claus?
Yeah.
Here.
ln case things go shitty.
Just like old times?
Yeah.
You dropped something.
- That's what you wanted, - right? Dom...
He's harmless. Don't worry about him.
And he's really sorry about Letty.
Where's our stuff?
You mean the stuff that used to be in here, right?
Well, you'll see it when we see Braga. That was the deal.
No worries.
Braga keeps his word.
$2 million.
You get the rest when I get my property.
- Stasiak. - We got a match.
The fingerprint's Braga's 1 00%.
Just waiting on faciaI confirmation via fax.
I got a question for you.
You wearing pink when you were clawing your way out of el barrio?
Order all agents to move in.
We got confirmation. Primary suspect wearing gray suit.
Let's move.
Sir, O'Conner hasn't given us the signal yet.
What part of that didn't you understand? We just got confirmation. Do it!
Secure primary suspect in gray suit. Repeat!
Secure primary suspect in gray suit.
You're thinking what I'm thinking, right?
He ain't Braga.
Oh, shit.
Drop your weapons! FBl!
Get down!
Get out of here!
Get out of here, Dom!
Run him down.
Go!
Campos is Braga!
Come on.
Approaching primary target.
Primary suspect is secure.
He was under your nose the whoIe time.
Now Braga's escaped.
Toretto's heading south, probably long across the border by now.
Do you have any idea the kind of trouble you're in, O'Conner?
I was doing my job.
He ain't the first bad guy you helped escape the law's grasp.
As of now, you're being taken off active duty,
until this house can mount a formal inquiry.
What about Braga?
That's no longer your concern.
We now know where Braga is, right?
Customs tracked him via satellite to his home base in Tecali, Mexico.
Mexico is out of our jurisdiction.
The fact is
the brass will be so busy holding press conferences over the seizure,
we'll skate under the radar.
I thought we signed on to do the right thing.
Everyone's looking for you.
I'm right here.
It's nice to see you've gone with the times
and switched to electronic fuel injection. Looks good.
Buster became a gearhead.
I'm going with you.
I don't plan on bringing anyone back.
I know.
Hit that throttle.
Hey.
How do you say goodbye to your only brother?
You don't.
I thought you weren't gonna show up.
You saved my life.
I'm willing to return the favor.
This will help get you to Braga.
Dom.
Going in there is suicide.
I have no choice.
You must have loved her very much.
So this is where my jurisdiction ends.
And this is where mine begins.
- welcome to the house of the lord, Sr.Braga. - Don't worry father, everthing's go.
To help us get to heaven.
Please receive this blessing.
You ain't forgiven.
You boys want to arrest me?
...in here.
No, we're beyond that.
You can't buy your way out of this one.
You and me...
You and me, we're not so different.
You're no hero.
You're right.
And that's why you're going back across the border.
But Fenix is mine.
You got it.
Shit!
You'll make it a couple of miles out, if you're lucky.
You know where you're going?
You want to borrow my GPS?
Where are your boys at?
Are they going to show up or what?
Careful what you ask for.
Just stop. Just stop the car.
Don't shoot the boss, idiots.
Right behind you.
Dom, head to the tunnel. Let's use the tunnel.
Get out of here, Brian.
You sure you know where the tunnels are? You sure?
Yeah. I'd hold on.
This might hurt.
You're in my world now, baby!
That's it, baby! End of the road.
Now what?
Game over.
No, no, no.
Come on!
Hey!
Get me out of here!
Pussy.
Let me see that.
Yeah. Just keep pressure there.
You'll be all right.
You gotta get out of here.
I ain't running anymore.
I gotta ask you something.
Yeah?
You know I would have won that race if you didn't cheat, right?
You hit your head hard.
Don't make me laugh.
All rise.
Please be seated.
Please rise, Mr. Toretto.
I've listened to the testimony
and taken into special consideration
Agent O'Conner's appeal of clemency on behalf of Mr. Toretto.
That his actions directly resulted in the apprehension
of known drug trafficker Arturo Braga.
However,
this judiciary finds that
one right does not make up for a lifetime worth of wrongs.
And as such,
I find that I am forced to level the maximum sentence under California law.
Dominic Toretto,
you are hereby sentenced to serve 25 years to life
at the Lompoc maximum security prison system
without the possibiIity of earIy paroIe.
This court is adjourned.
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：1610169789