更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
Go! Go!
[ Cheering ]
Yo,Jimmy, man, give me the status.
Tell me we good. We got it, man.
Beautiful. It's gonna be an all-timer tonight.
[ Engines Rewing ]
All right, all right, all right. Fire 'em up!
We go live in five.
It's time for ignition and straight automobile pimp.
Let's do it, man. Let's go.
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
[ Chattering ]
Ow, girl! Sorry! My bad!
All right, ladies! We're good!
We're good.
That's it, babies. [ Speaking Spanish ]
Come on, Tej. Let's get this race going!
Whoa, whoa, man. Wait a second, man.
You cats are first wave, man. Where's your fourth at?
Yo, it was Joaquin, but he had to work the graveyard shift. What?
Graveyard shift, man? Yo, why don't you run with us, Tej?
Hell, no, I'm not runnin' with y'all, man.
Either you find a fourth or you don't race.
- How 'bout that, huh? - We should find two...
so we don't have to roll with skirt here.
[ Spanish ]
Oooh! Idiota.
[ Spanish ] Whoa. Whoa. Wait a second.
Why don't I just find y'all a fourth and we settle this on the streets, huh?
- Bring him on. - Anybody I want?
- [ Spanish ] - No matter who it is.
Yeah. [ Beeping ]
[ Man ] Yeah. Yeah, man. You wanna race tonight?
- Yeah. You know I could use the money. - You got four minutes.
- All right. I'll be there. - [ Chuckles ]
[ Techno ]
[ Rap ]
[ Rock ]
[ Electronic ]
The race starts in four minutes. [ Cheering ]
All right, girls. Let's do this.
[ Foreign Language ]
2 furious I'm too fast for y'all, man
Drah, 2 fast Drah, 2 furious
I'm too fast for y'all, man
You think you gonna win baby? What you think?
You better. We got rent to pay. I know this.
You just came home from doin'a bid
Tell me what ya gonna do  Act a fool
Somebody broke in and cleaned out your crib
Boy, what you gonna do  Act a fool
Man, that ain't sticky That's sticks and stems
2 fast, 2 fast 2 furious, 2 furious
[ Cheering ]
[ Spanish ]
I'll get you when you get a car worth racing.
[ Engine Revving ]
Yeah. There's our fourth right there.
- Shit. It's Brian. - [ Engine Revving ]
[ Laughs ]
[ Cheering ]
[ Man ] Yeah, Brian.! [ Woman ] I love you, Bullet.!
What's up, Tej? What's happenin', dude?
Thanks for the invite. No problem at all, man. Just, uh--
Just remember me when you wax, a'ight?
They got deep pockets? [ Chuckles ] Real deep.
- What's up, Suki? - What's up, Bullet?
- What do you say we kick it a nickel? - [ Spanish ]
Nobody said nothin' about raisin' the stakes.
If that's the case, why don't you ask these nice people here...
to back off the line so you can go home? [ Crowd ] Oooh.!
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Okay. Thirty-five large.
Three cinco. [ Spanish ]
[ Spanish ]
Thirty-five large, huh?
Either that or you can go home, brah.
Yeah.
- It's all there. - [ Tej ] It better be.
Damn, Suki. Uh, when you gonna pop my clutch, huh?
As soon as you get the right set of tools.
Yeah, a'ight.
All right, back up. Back up. Let's go. Let's go.
[ Engine Revs ] Whoa!
Back y'all asses up. Back up. Back up.
Before you turn into barbecue around here.
It's not a game. This is serious.
All right. Back up. Back up. Get off the street.
Let's go. Back it up. Back it up.
Everybody keep your hands real, real clear, all right?
'Cause I got a surprise for y'all this evening.
[ Engine Revs ] [ Cheering ]
Go, SlapJack! Go, baby! I got this. I got this.
[ Spanish ]
[ Revving Engine ]
Ready.
Go!
- Oh, hell, no! - [ Tires Squealing ]
Aaah!
Aha!
You ain't passin' me, dawg. You ain't passin' me. Come on!
What you got, man?
I told you you weren't gonna pass me.
[ Growls ]
- Move, bitch! - Ha!
[ Growling ] [ Grunting ]
pendeja.!
[ Spanish ] Uh-uh. Not tonight, baby.
Bend over, boy.
[ Grunts ] Damn, girl!
Last turn. Last turn.
Oh, too wide!
Home stretch, baby!
[ Yelling ]
Whoo-h-h-hoo! Let it go, dawg!
[ Spanish ]
Yes!
[ Laughs ] I can smell you!
Yo,Jimmy, hit it, baby. Hit it!
[ Bell Ringing ]
A'ight. Y'all see that?
Told y'all I had a surprise.
How you like that for a finale?
Bridge.
- Oh! - Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
Shit!
Huh? Oh, hell, no!
Whoo! Smack that ass!
[ Laughs ]
[ Coughs, Groans ]
Yes!
Tell me y'all saw that, man. Bullet and Suki sprayed the bridge,
and I need to start making y'all pay to see this shit.
I got over 1 0 stacks for my man right here, a'ight?
That's what I'm talkin' about, man. play with it.
Smells good, don't it? Yeah, I'll buy that. Right there.
Right. Y'all see this? Everybody take a real good look.
This what you call mutual respect. A'ight, let's clear out.
[ Cheering ] Anybody down for another race?
Shit!
Hey, uh, make sure you bring that body by the garage later, a'ight,
so, you know, we can work on that front end of yours.
Watch out. 'Cause maybe I will.
[ Chuckles ] Yeah.
What's up, man?
[ Giggles ] Hey, where you going?
It's time to get out of here. Why's that?
[ Alarms Blaring ]
[ Clamoring ]
Oh, shit!
Nissan Skyline. Got him.
Shit! Shit!
[ Laughs ]
Shit--
Shit.
Damn!
Let me see your hands! put 'em up!
[ Man ] This is him. We got him.!
So, how long you been in south Florida? A while.
Before that?
We know you're Brian O'Conner, formerly of the L.A.p.D.
- You've got the wrong guy. - Really?
[ knocking ] [ Door Opens ]
How you doin; O'Conner?
Let's take a walk.
Carter Verone. Born in Argentina.
But he's lived most of his life in Miami.
Now he owns the biggest import/ export business in the state.
Unfortunately, the cartels have been successful getting drugs into Miami.
But they've had a hard time gettin' the cash out.
We've been surveilling him for a year, but we've never been able...
to put him and the money together.
- We've swept his house, his warehouses-- - Nothing.
Customs here has done a great job of getting us this far.
I'm just here to help get them over the top.
I was able to get an agent in undercover...
working travel and logistics for him.
Recently, Verone put her in charge of finding some new drivers.
Right. Although we can't confirm her status right now. You think she's flipped?
She's one of mine. She's all right.
She's been in with Verone nearly a year. Even lives at the compound with him now.
Look, it was the F.B.I.'s idea to bring you in here.
I'm against it. But we need some good drivers...
that can put this asshole and his money together.
You're gonna roll with Agent Dunn here.
And if I don't?
Well, here's a list of the laws you broke in L.A.
Obstruction of justice, aiding and abetting. You know the rap sheet.
Now, we can make this all go away in the interest of justice,
if you're willing to play ball. Yeah.
So what's the idea here? Dunn and I are supposed to be street racers?
That's right.
[ Slurps ]
So, Dunn--
Looks like we're gonna be partners, bro.
Could you tell me right quick what would be a better motor for my Skyline,
a Gallo 1 2 or a Gallo 2 4?
Um-- [ Clears Throat ] The 2 4.
I didn't know pizza places made motors.
See, man, come on. I can't do this.
Seriously, if this is what you're gonna give me,
I may as well take my chances in Chino.
We will get someone else.
No way, man.
The only way I'll do this is if I get to pick the driver.
[ Sighs ] All right, O'Conner, who you got in mind?
This dude I grew up with in Barstow.
Who's that? Roman pearce.
[ Man On p.A., Indistinct ]
[ Cheering ]
Hi-oh! What--
- That's your boy in the Monte Carlo? - [ Brian ] Yeah, that's him.
Yeah, he's got some skills. Mm-hmm.
And he's crazy as hell, I'm telling ya.
In a good way though. He's the man for the job.
He's got quite a record, including three years upstate.
Says here he's on house arrest now. Can't go more than 1 00 yards from his home.
[ Man On p.A.] Roman pearce.!
Whoo-hoo.!
[ Man On p.A. Speaking Spanish ]
[ Mutters ]
He always said he'd be famous.
pearce.!
Roman pearce!
- Yo, whatever happens next, just let it go. - I ain't in it.
[ Whistles ] Rome!
Only my homeboys call me Rome, pig!
- I'm not a cop anymore, bro. - Is that true?
- Blondie here's not a cop anymore? - That's true. No badge.
Whoo! Here we go.
You still fight like shit. You still fight like shit--
You better chill.
What the hell are you doin' here, O'Conner? I'll choke you.
I told you to stay away from--
You should've told me. I did three years, Brian.
I told you it wasn't my fault.
[ Breathing Heavily ]
Why did you come here, O'Conner?
I got a deal for you.
When I needed your ass, you were nowhere to be found.
Now you tryin' to hand out deals?
I need you to come to Miami and drive with me.
If you do, they'll take off that anklet and they'll clear your entire record.
I did three years in jail.
Three years in jail off you, Brian.
I know you better than you think.
Maybe you don't. Maybe you don't.
You guys finished?
This deal legit?
That's right, if you do this job for us.
Told you. Shut up, punk.
So you gonna clean my record and get this thing off my ankle?
That's right. I thought you couldn't wander more than 1 00 yards from your home.
Why do you think I'm parked so close to the derby?
Man, quit playin' like you gonna pass this up.
[ Mutters ]
Wait. Hold up.
Hey, bro, what's going on?
I don't know if I should be trusting you, man.
Just think of it this way. It's an opportunity for a fresh start.
Let's just go do this. I wouldn't need a fresh start...
if it weren't for you. Man, you been using that since the day you got busted.
Now, let's just chill out and go do this. I don't need to chill out.
Yes, you do. And you need to stop blaming me for your every mistake.
And Roman pearce needs to start taking responsibility for his own actions.
You need to go to hell. And you need to go back to Barstow.
I'm not goin' back to Barstow.
Brian O'Conner, Roman pearce, meet Monica Fuentes.
- Do they have background on Verone? - They've been briefed.
Good. All right, here's the deal.
Verone's looking for drivers. I've arranged for both of you to join up.
I've also hired some thugs. You know, to make it legit.
- When do we start? - Right now.
- What are we drivin'? - [ Latin Rap ]
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Don't even think about takin' the convertible.
It might loosen your mousse.
No, that's cool. That's too much chrome for me anyways.
Damn! Where you all confiscate these rims from, man?
Check in with us after you meet him.
You gonna have any problems with these two knuckleheads? I can handle 'em.
They give you any trouble at all, you let me know. Thanks, Markham.
I'll ride with you, cowboy.
Why she gotta ride with you. You get the convertible. Let's go.
That's where I reside
That's where I'll represent till I die
So get changed and put your drinks down
And get sexed up and get wowed for tonight
pit bull like a sex bull like the next truck Mama,you got the next
Turn right here.
[ Tires Squealing ]
So you used to be a cop? Yeah.
How long you been under?
I lost track.
You all right?
You might wanna keep your eyes on the road, playboy.
What, you think we're gonna crash? I haven't decided yet.
What are you doin', Brian?
- [ Tires Squeal ] - [ Laughs ]
He did the ""stare and drive'' on you, didn't he?
He got that from me.
Represent your county your city
Who you know pull Chevys like this
Can't he pace with a trunk in a funk like this
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
With the loose top
And the rims keep spinnin' even when I stop
Murder one, I'll be chillin' Got everybody watchin' but who gonna stop me
The first game, soda
Somebody tries some mo'shit buys some mo'shit
I "T'"doubled 'em switched the game
Got next slope down switchin'lanes
Chevy boys, we like it fast so I drop it in low heavy on the gas
Once we get in here, you're on your own.
[ Chuckles ] Look at that one.
Hey, where did you get them cars, the bottom of a cereal box?
[ Laughs ] Eh! Real funny, Fonzie.
Ass.
Roberto, Enrique, I need pictures of the drivers,
their license plates, their cars, and anything else you can find.
[ Spanish ] [ Spanish ]
[ Whistles ]
Let's go.
Keep your mouth shut and follow my lead, all right?
I got this. No, I'm serious now.
Handle your business. I'll handle mine.
[ Spanish ]
Watch your hands, brah.
Go in line. Let's go.
Carter.
Drivers are here. Good.
Come on.
Stay. [ Spanish ]
[ Indistinct ]
Thank you for coming on such short notice.
My red Ferrari was confiscated yesterday, and it sits in an impound lot in Little Haiti.
It's about 20 miles from here.
The car isn't important. What is important is the package I left in the glove box.
The first team back here with the package will have an opportunity to work for me.
- What, we gotta audition? - Nobody's got a gun to your head.
[ Mutters ]
That's it.
Driver's licenses. pass 'em up.
Before Christmas, guys. [ Spanish ] Go!
Go! Go, man. Come on. Go!
Come on, cuz.
All right, let's see what this thing can do.
[ Blows Horn ]
Agent Markham, I've got 'em heading south on I-95.
Yeah, I got it.
They're running. What a surprise.
Come on. Stick with me, Rome. What you got?
Why must I chase the cat? [ Laughs ]
Smart ass.
- [ Laughs ] - Oh, yeah? You think you're the bomb, Rome?
[ Laughs ]
Let's see if you still got it, Brian.
All right, Rome. I got somethin' for your ass.
Watch this, bro.
Shit.
Yeah, Rome. How do you like them apples?
Show off.
That's the Brian O'Conner school of driving right there, baby.
Crazy-ass white boy!
Oh, shit!
[ Radio.Reggae ]
- Hey, man. - Huh?
[ Woman ] Get yourself on outta the street.!
[ Man ] Boy, that's some bad shit, man.
What do we got?
That's good. Show me his partner.
Cars. Cars. Where are the cars?
Stinkin' boats. Where are the cars?
[ Laughs ]
I need the cars. Where are the cars at?
Look in the center. Look in the center. What?
Chi-ching! Now put your blouse back on. Hater.
[ Cars Approaching ]
[ Roman ] Shit.!
- Don't let 'em get away. - Not a problem.
[ Laughs ] Sit on it, Fonzie!
- [ Siren Blaring ] - What the hell?
Aw, shit! Cops.
- What the hell they doin' here? - Rome, no.!
Time to go.
- Son of a bitch! - [ Monica ] Juvie record for popping cars.
Two years in J.D., then another year for aiding and abetting an armed robbery.
He's clean. Dirty but clean.
Hm. All right.
Hey, man,you got somethin'to eat up in there? We hungry.
Sit 'em by the pool. Mm-hmm.
Nice. Come on.
Hmm. What you checking her out for?
I'm not checking her out.
Yes, you were. No, I wasn't.
I seen you checkin' her out, man. Okay, I was. Now shut up.
You shut up. Don't tell me to shut up.
Both you girlies shut up.
Unbelievable.
[ Mouths Word ] All right.
You sure are cozy in this big ol' mansion.
Sleepin' with the enemy.
No, no, no. Sit down.
Nice Ferrari you got in the driveway.
[ Chuckles ] I'm glad you like it.
Darlin', will you hold that?
We did all that for a damn cigar?
No, you did that for a job.
Do you really think that I would let somebody impound my car?
The boatyard's mine. Oh, by the way,
you two owe me a gate.
- But I'll just take it off your cut. - [ Laughs ]
Off our cut. Yeah.
- I like that. - Good.
What's this job you got for us anyway?
Come with me.
The house has ears in it.
I have something I want you to carry from North Beach to the Keys.
What is it? Just put in the car what I tell you to,
drive it to me and don't let anyone stop you, understand?
Yeah. Any chance of cop trouble?
No. I'm buying you a window of time, but it's not gonna be open very long.
You make it,
and I'll personally hand you 1 00 G's at the finish line.
Make it 1 00 G's a piece, papi.
Look, man, obviously,
your pockets ain't nervous. Hey, hey, hey.
Don't ever touch me.
Ours are empty.
Like I said, we hungry.
I got an idea.
Why don't you two boys join us at the club a little later tonight?
- Yeah. pearl at midnight? - We'll get to know each other a little better.
All right. Sounds good.
We'll see you tonight. See ya.
Hey, you!
Your pockets aren't empty.
- Damn. - I'll take my cutter back.
Stupid ass.
Hey, man, I figured you had, like, 1 2 or 1 3--
You're not too bright, are you? Just get out of here.
Same old Rome doin' the same old stupid shit.
Get off me, man. What, runnin' your mouth? Insultin' people?
Stealin' Verone's shit?
Think I'm gonna let somebody stare me down?
I didn't let nobody stare me down in jail, homeboy.
Think I'm gonna let it fly on a beach?
[ Imitating Verone ] And you, I'll take my cutter back.
His rich ass.
And you're packin'! Like you ain't?
Exactly.
- From here, I do the talkin'. - Looks like you wanna do a little more than that.
Oh, and what's that supposed to mean?
It means you always gettin' in trouble over a female, Brian.
Man, Tej's garage is ridiculous. He's got the best of everything.
Snap-on tools. All these lifts are brand-new. They're only maybe a couple months old.
Hey, yo,Jimmy. What's up, man?
What up, Bullet? That's Rome right there.
When you get a second, I want you to check out...
the Evo and the Spyder and make sure everything's copecetic.
Evo? Where'd you get an Evo from?
Well, it's a long story. I got you, man.
All right, thanks,Jimmy. Come check this out.
It's so hot and humid out here, I can't even wear no drawers.
Yeah, tell me about it. [ Laughs ] Look at all this potential out here.
Don't do that, man. [ Continues, Indistinct ]
Damn!
Damn. Baby.
Girl, you know your boy can help you put that fire out.
Look at the bubble on that--
That's cool. That's serious right there.
You're making me lose money. Don't do that to me right now.
I cannot take that right-- Come on, Ray! Do it!
Hey, Tej parker,
Roman pearce.
Come on, baby-- Basically, he's the man to know in Miami.
He's got his finger in absolutely everything.
It's just the way it is.
What's goin' on, Suki? What's up, baby?
How you doing? I'm good. How you doing?
What's this? What's the latest? It's a work in progress.
It's not finished yet. That's some artistic shit.
You got talent, girl. Yeah, she's good. She's the best.
Do or die. Bring it home, Ray. Bring it home, Ray. Bring it home. Bring it home.
Yeah, baby! pay up! pay up! pay up!
That's how they do it out here, man?
Every day. That's crazy.
Right here, right now. What's up, man? You don't look too happy.
A'ight? Expeditiously, man. I need it quick right here. What's up?
Thank you. Thank you. All right. How you feeling? A'ight?
A'ight. Thank you. Thank you, man.
Not too bad. Whoo!
I'll see you about your money, homey. You race too?
[ Exhales ] No, man.
I hit a wall doin', like, a buck 20 couple years ago, you know?
Ever since then, I just been organizing and collecting, man.
Tej, check it out. He's gonna be in town for a while.
Is there anyway he could use that cot?
What's wrong with your place, man?
No, I don't wanna stay with him. He got bad habits.
[ Scoffs ] A'ight, man. Whatever, man.
Show him around real quick, a'ight? I'll be up there in a minute.
Thanks.
A'ight, who want a chance to win their money back?
What's up,Jimmy? So you ever seen anything like this before?
No. Both of them are wired up like I never seen before.
What? Yeah, man. They got us wired with G.p.S.
That's why Markham knew we were gonna be at that impound lot.
Yo, you the master mechanic. Why don't you just yank that shit up out of there?
I'll try, but this ain't LoJack.
The D.I.S. box, the engine management system, hell, the main harness--
The G.p.S. is spidered into all of that.
Hey, tell me somethin', man. Do I even want to know where the Skyline is, dawg?
Or where you been the past couple of days?
Or where the hell you got these rides from? They're hot.
Yeah, they hot. They wired so hot that whoever's trackin' these things will know...
every time you don't wear your seat belt.
All right,Jimmy, just do what you can do, bro.
- I got ya. - Thanks, man.
Man, we need to get these on the street ASAp.
Hey, bro, check it out.
You see that Cadillac across the street over there?
Yeah. Yeah, well, they've been on us since we left Verone's house.
[ Spanish ]
Elian and Fidel! [ Spanish ]
Hey, man, I'll clean your windshield for you.
- What are you doin', man? - [ Laughs ]
Uno, tres, cuatro, ""fourtro,'' taco.
[ Laughs ] Everything's copecetic, homey. [ Spanish ]
Kiss my ass, putos.
Shit!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
[ Spanish ]
He's gonna blow our cover before we even get started.
Hey, Bilkins, can you tell me what went wrong? That's what I wanna know.
Show me your hands! Come on. Keep 'em up!
- What's this about, man? - Hey, w-what's goin' on?
Hold this. You think you can shoot at me? I'm a goddamn federal agent!
What are you talkin' about? Get your damn hands off me! Get him away from me!
Just 'cause you wear a badge don't mean you can come in and mess shit up.!
- Get your hands off of me! - You're lucky I didn't shoot you.
- Shut up, Rome! - Don't tell me to shut up, Brian!
You almost blew our cover, old man.
You shouldn't have shown up like you did.
What, you didn't know Verone was testing us?
- No. I thought you punks were running. - Running!
That's great. That's real great!
Oh, and if Rome wanted to shoot you, you wouldn't be here right now.
All right. We gotta get this under control.
Hey, that's mine.!
- So? - So tell me what you know.
Well, Rome and I will be making a run for Verone.
I'm not sure when and where. But he did say he bought us a window.
I'm assuming from the local cops.
I can talk to some of the guys at the local p.D.
No. No good. If Verone's got some of them on the payroll,
then we can't let them know our operation.
Exactly. In addition,
Verone told us that he himself would be waiting at the drop.
That's good news. If you're gonna be delivering drug money to him,
- then we can get him for laundering. - No, there's only one problem.
- What's that? - Fuentes-- Verone's tappin' her.
Tappin' her? Tappin' her how? That is crap!
What you talkin' about, homeboy? We know what we seen.
What do you think, O'Conner? You think she's compromised?
- You should know. - What's that supposed to mean?
What? You mean your old pal O'Conner didn't tell ya?
He flipped on Bilkins in L.A. Gave his mark his car keys and let him disappear.
That's why he's not a cop anymore.
So what do you think, expert?
Man, I don't know.
All right. We'll keep an eye on her.
We're out of here.
You let your man go, huh? Drop it. I don't wanna talk about it.
Drop it, hell! I wanna hear about this, homey.
I said forget about it, cuz.
We got Fuentes in with Verone, Markham tryin' to blow our cover...
and we got two wired cars that are no better than that damn ankle bracelet of mine.
I'm-a tell you, brah. You let your man Markham do that shit again in front of Verone,
- that's gonna be our ass. - I know, man. I know.
It's gettin' thick real quick, and we may need a way out.
- We gotta come up with some exit strategy. - Exit strategy, huh?
Yeah.
I like the way that sounds. What you got in mind?
I don't know, man. But we need two more cars.
Yeah. Here they come.
Fonzie and Fabio. Glad you can join us.
We heard you boys wanted to get rid of those CrackerJack toys.
No. Actually we just figured those cars you got deserved better drivers,
which is why we're gonna take 'em off your hands.
- You know, why don't we settle this now? - Wait, wait.
How about we settle this on the blacktop, huh?
Each car does it down and back, tag-team style--
for slips. Loser walks home.
- We came to race. - Well, load 'em up then.
Come on, bro. Let's get these cars.
All right, check it out. There's no way we gonna beat these guys straight up.
The Hemi's puttin' out about 425...
and that Yenko will snap a speed on about five seconds flat.
We're gonna have to pull somethin' out of our ass.
The only thing I can think of is save the spray for the way back, the return trip.
Done deal. All right. Let's do this, bro.
I'm gettin' that orange one.
[ Laughs ] You ain't ready, Fabio!
All right. You each got a barrel to go around down at the end of the road.
The second wave gotta sit tight till your partner crosses this line right here.
First team to go down and back twice wins the race.
At which point,
the losers will hand over them keys.
Otherwise, you'll be eatin' breakfast through straws from now on.
Comprende?
I get it.
Oh, this means you too.
- I got it. - A'ight.
Let's race.
Come on, baby.! You got this, Rome. Let's do it.
Hey, you gone, homey. I got this. This is done. [ Laughs ]
You about to lose your car.
Do it, Rome! Come on. You got it.
You think I'm worried about this fool, man? [ Laughs ]
This is nothin'. [ Engine Revs ]
[ Engine Revs, Loud ]
- Aw, no. - American muscle.
Your engine ain't as big as your mouth. [ Revs Engine ]
Gotta smoke 'em. Gotta smoke 'em. Gotta smoke 'em.
All right, here we go. It's all right, baby. I'm gonna handle this.
Handle it.
Ready and... go!
You ain't ready. I run these streets.
Woo-hoo!
Romey Rome. You ain't heard of me?
Oh, shit.
Oh, yeah!
I'm-a get you. Oh, I'm-a get you!
Where's your big mouth now, boy?
That car's going home with me, homey.
[ Laughs ]
Oh, shit. Eat this, sucker!
Shit!
[ Revs Engine ]
Yeah, boy! Go, Korpi!
Sorry, blondie. How does that dust taste?
I don't know.
[ Revs Engine ] Come on, Rome.
What the-- Good move, kid. Let's see if you got the balls. Come on!
- [ Engine Stalls ] - Whoo!
Goddamn! Come on! [ Engine Starts ]
Come on, Brian. Bring it home, man.
Got two new cars! That's all my man!
- Damn! - [ Laughs ]
Y'all ain't ready, homeboy. Get to walkin', Fabio.
Use them bus tokens, partner.!
[ Rap ] Hey, how you doin'?
Good. What you need? We're guests of Mr. Verone's.
[ Loud Rap, Indistinct ]
[ people Chattering ]
- It's a ""hoasis'' in here, brah. - Yeah.
Lots of potential. [ Chuckling ] Damn. You got a pen?
[ Laughing ] phew. It's about to get serious, brah.
[ pearce ] Look at that girl on the swing right there.
Hey. You guys did something right.
- Verone never socializes with hired help. - Then what's that make you?
- Where's he at? - He's on his way.
- You and Verone don't go everywhere together? - What's that supposed to mean?
Nothin'. [ Sighs ]
Huh. I'm-a go take a piss.
You go do that.
What is his deal? He doesn't trust people that carry badges.
So you talk like you know.
Yeah. I'd been a cop about two months...
when Roman was busted in a garage raid.
He had eight sets of wheels in his possession, each and every one of them hot.
So you busted him? No. I didn't even know what was goin' down.
But, uh, that doesn't really matter to him.
Basically, once I became a cop,
Roman started seeing me as a friend that became the enemy.
You have a little--
Is there anything I can get for you, Mr. Verone?
Just tell 'em to comejoin me.
[ Continues ]
Oh, yeah. I was admiring this.
Yeah, I was looking at it earlier.
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
- Damn. - I wasn't about to give it to you.
What's up? He's here, man.
Where's he at? He's over there. Don't look.
Excuse me. Mr. Verone would like for you to join him.
Let's do it.
See what I'm talkin' about?
[ Verone ] It's all right. Let 'em in.
Go sit down. I'll talk to you in a second.
How ya doin'? Good. You enjoying your night?
Yeah. I'm havin' a good time. Good, good.
She's beautiful, isn't she?
Hmm? Yeah.
She's gorgeous.
You got balls, kid. [ Chuckles ]
I can appreciate that.
Women are a very powerful force.
You see the blond sitting with the gentleman right here?
[ Chattering ]
Five minutes of her time, and she can get anything she wants from him.
- I love your hair. - Watch.
[ Chuckling ]
I wonder where they're going. Sit down.
So, you, uh, lit my man's car on fire. Is that right?
Yeah. I did.
You see, I got a problem with authority.
Hmm. I have that same problem.
For me, it's cops in particular.
[ Chuckles ]
Let's take a walk. Come on. We just got here.
Now we're leaving.
Let's go.
Hey. Come on.
What's all that?
We're gonna have a little fun. [ Cork pops Softly ]
[ Glass Clinks ] [ Champagne pouring ]
- Hmm. - [ Monica ] Thank you.
[ Chattering ]
Let's just stay a little longer. [ Indistinct ]
- [ Chuckling ] - Hey, Carter.
Meet, uh, Detective Whitworth.
One of Miami's finest. Thank you, sweetheart.
Are you enjoying yourself,Detective? Yeah. I was.
I mean, you know me.
Yeah, I do know you.
- You been on my payroll a long time. - Verone, that ain't right.
Shut up.
I got one last job for you, Detective. You hear me?
Look, we've been all through this. Yeah?
Yeah. I said I can't do it.
Hmm. That's the wrong answer. The table.
[ Grunting ]
I'm a detective, Verone! You do anything to me,
the whole force is gonna be on your ass in a minute.
Shut your mouth! You fat piece of shit.
You can stop right now.
[ Whitworth Mutters ] [ Squeaking ]
- What the hell-- What the hell is that? - Sit down.
You're gonna regret this. Just stop right now!
Once the bucket gets hot enough, Detective,
the rat is gonna want out.
Get--
And the only direction it can go is south.
Hey! Get-- Hey!
Hold that. [ Gasping ]
- Get it off me! I'll forget it ever happened. - Shut up.
Did you know that your average rat... [ Rat Squeaking ]
can chew through a steel drain pipe?
You see, you have nothing to worry about when he's screaming, Detective.
It's when he goes quiet that he goes to work.
[ Whitworth ] Stop it.! Stop it.! Stop it.!
Don't be stupid. Stop it now.
You're in charge of the units that are watching my properties, huh?
What I want is, I want a 1 5-minute window...
where everybody-- and I mean everybody-- disappears.
You hear me? I can't do it!
[ Moaning, Whimpering ]
- [ Gasping ] Stop it. I can't do it. Help.! - Okay. Monica, come here.
- Help.! Help.! - Shut him up. Shut him up.
Help! Help!
[ Squeaking ] Help.!
[ Muffled Groaning ] He's biting me!
- Help.! Help.! - What?
[ Muffled Shouting, Screaming ]
- You got somethin' you wanna say? - [ Muffled Screaming ]
He bit me! [ Groaning ]
- Yes, I'll do it.! - Do what? Say it.
I'll do it. I'll give you your window.
[ Gasping, Whimpering ] Just get it off me!
[ Groaning ] Get it off.
You betray me,
and my rat here...
is gonna visit your wife, Lynn--yeah--
your son, Clay, and your daughter, Lexi.
Do you hear me? You understand me? Huh?
You hear me? Yes.
I'll burn your... eyes out! I'll burn 'em out!
[ Whimpering ] Get it off me.
Good. Now you can go. Get it off me.
Get rid ofhim. Let's go. Get if off.
[ Grunting ]
Mm. You boys enjoy the show?
Fifteen minutes, and then every cop in Florida is gonna be on you.
Be at Versailles Cafe, 6:00 a.m., day after tomorrow, ready to drive.
- You understand? - Yeah.
Don't play games with me, or you'll be next. All right?
Help yourself to a little champagne. Let's go.
[ Rap, Indistinct ]
That was a damn rat, man.
Hey.
You ever... touch another man again, and I'll kill you.
You hear me? Look at me.
You hear me?
She was into it, man. What's that about?
And you seen the way she grabbed the dude's head.
She had to, man. He was testing her. You gotta remember,
her ass is on the line, just like ours.
You feelin' this girl way too much.
She just like that crazy-ass trailer-raff from back-in-the-day, Tonya.
Tonya? Man, you went out with her after I did.
I mean, I couldn't let her go to waste.
[Jimmy ] I got you, I got you, I got you.
Is that right? See, we can race for cash,
but when I step on the gas, my nitrous go blast, leave your ass in the past.
And, Tej, you about to lose your garage. Whatever, man.
I'm a low-budget mechanic, but I overcharge.
pay me! Let's go, man! [ Laughing ]
pay me my money. I told you, man.
You a happy man. I'm so glad.
This is my garage, boy. Royal flush!
Give me this, man. Holler, huh! Yes!
Did I talk to him? Talk to him. [ Suki ] Damn.
You can't play a player. put that money back on the table. You know it's my next hand.
Jimmy, how you gonna pay me back if you keep losing to Tej?
How ya doin', bro? I'm gonna crash, Tej.
I'll catch you tomorrow. A'ight, boy.
[ Door Opens ] [ Soft Footsteps ]
[ Gasping ]
- What are you doin' here? - Brian, they're gonna kill you.
I heard him telling Enrique and Roberto.
Once you finish the run, they're putting a bullet in your head.
- You sure you heard 'em right? - I'm sure. I'm sure.
- [ knock ] - Verone's boys is outs--
Oh, I see what they lookin'for-- your little girlfriend here.
- They don't know I'm here. I snuck out. - What are they doin' here then?
I don't know. Maybe they're guessing. Hey, go stall them.
- Go stall them for two minutes. - Check her, homey. Check her.
Find what you was lookin' for?
Hey, buddy. Hi, guys. How ya doin'?
Oh, man, y'all still mad about y'all car?
Don't even trip, homey. Come on, man. You can't take a joke?
Brian, this isn't about being a good cop anymore or-or doing your job.
They're gonna kill you. You guys gotta pull out.
Verone pay y'all to keep a straight face like that?
'Cause if I was makin'money, shit, I'd get that mole removed off my damn nose.
Okay? Okay. Yeah.
How much he pay y'all anyway?
Every time I see y'all, man, y'all got the silk shirts on,
jewelry,you know, lookin'real Miami.
You know? I caught you walkin' up in the club,
you got the hamburger meat all hangin' out, you know?
Don't make that run, Brian. Don't make that run.
Be careful.
- Donde esta? - Quien?
- [ Spanish ] - You ain't comin' on my--
[ Spanish ]
Hey, hey! Where you goin'? You stay right here with us, buddy.
Don't even think about it.
Vamonos.! Stay your ass off my homeboy's boat.
[ Trigger Cocks ]
put the gun down! put the gun down now!
You first, asshole! You first!
I'll shoot the shit outta him! put the gun down!
[ Spanish ]
- [ Spanish ] - Tu primero.!
- put down the gun now! - [ Spanish ]
- [ Spanish ] - put down the gun!
[ All Shouting, Indistinct ] Enough.
- Enough. Shut up. - [ Spanish ]
Shut up. It's over. Come on.
[ Verone ] It's over. Let's go.
Let's have the gun. Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
I'm glad to see you boys are getting along so well.
Because tomorrow, Roberto and Enrique...
are gonna be riding along with you...
just so that we don't have any problems.
I'll see you guys in a bit.
What the hell was she doin' in there, man?
Where'd you go this morning?
I went to breakfast with some friends.
- With friends. - [ Chuckles ]
I do have friends, Carter.
[ Chuckling ]
Okay. I'll see you later.
- Nice shirt, Bilkins. - It's my day off.
Yeah. Well, anyhow, this is the deal.
Last night, Verone threatened a cop into giving us a window.
We're driving to an airstrip, in the Keys, off of Nallwood Avenue.
Verone has a plane there, and he's taking off for good.
- Wait a minute. How do you know this? - Monica.
She's doin' her job. She warned us.
- She warned you about what? - Verone plans to kill us after we give him the money.
Driving into an ambush was never part of the deal.
I'm calling this off. Like hell you are. This is a Customs case, Bilkins.
No one's calling this off unless I do.
Look. This is real simple.
You make the run. You get Verone and his cash together...
so I can move in for the bust.
All right? You don't, I will find enough charges on both of you to make you disappear.
Take these. We're gonna have G.p.S. on you the whole time...
to make sure you don't get any cute ideas.
- And to make sure nothing happens to them, right? - Yeah, right.
The guy's a dick, man. Yep.
Let me get this right.
If we don't do this, then we go to jail.
But if we do it, then Verone's gonna kill us.
It's a hell of a deal, huh?
Yeah. Maybe it is.
But I know this guy's got an ass full of loot...
that he's ready to dump in our cars.
And I can think of two reasons why Verone doesn't need that money anymore.
- Ah, here we go. - You and me.
Just like the old days. What do you think?
I think they messed with the wrong two guys. That's what I think.
Yo, Tej. What's up, bro? What up?
Hey, man, how quickly can you organize?
[ Tej ] Look, folk, if y'all really wanna carry out this plan,
it's definitely the best place to do it.
What do y'all think, man? I think it's perfect. What do they store here?
pump, p-p-pump, pump p-p-p-pump
pump, p-p-pump pump it up
pump, p-p-pump pump, p-pump, p-pump  Hey, man, this thing's clean.
pump it up Just blaze  Strip it down.
pump, p-p-pump, pump it up   We gonna do it like uh, uh, uh
Look, pump it up if you came to get it krunk with a dame and shit that's drunk
You came to get it on More than five O's in your bank
Then get it on Roll up like that stank and get it on
Slank that fitted on Came to get it on  Hey,Jimmy.
Yeah. What up? We have any half-empty bottles of nitrous laying around?
Sure, but I already loaded you for spray.
No. I'm thinkin' we may need it for somethin' else,
'cause our cars may get a little crowded, you know?
pump, p-p-pump pump it up
Man, when you start eatin' so much?
I was in jail, brah.
I know how shitty the grub is on the inside.
[ Laughing ] With the way things is shapin' up out here right now,
it'll be a matter of time before I'm back in there or dead.
So I'm tryin' to eat all I can while I can.
plus the doctor tell me I got a high metabolism.
[ Laughing ]
Man, you remember us growing up?
You know, playing football in the dirt.
You know, gettin' in trouble, all the stupid things we did.
When you got busted, you know, whether I was a cop or not,
you know, if there was anything I could've done,
I would've done it, and I just want you to know that.
Is that why you let that dude go in L.A.?
Yeah. I think that had a lot to do with it.
When I got busted, it wasn't your fault.
It was all on me, Mr. Roman pearce--
wild-and-out crazy, man.
No one can tell me nothin;
- Ridin' solo. - Yeah, well, not anymore.
Not anymore, bro.
I got Verone's Navigator leavin' the residence.
Copy. Sir, we've got Verone on the move to the airstrip.
Good. Let's get a bird in the air. Tell him to keep his distance.
[ Chattering ]
Good and tight. Ready to go. Channel two. Channel two.
You're all set. Thanks.
All set? Yep. Let's do it.
Report.
[ Static Crackles ] What's goin'on out there?
- Team one checking in. - Team two checking in.
- Team three checking in. - [ Man ] Team four. All clear here too.
[ Man ] Team five checkin' in.
[ Man #2 ] This is team six. All clear.
[ Sighs ]
[ pearce ] Here we go. [ O'Conner ] Yeah, so you know what to do.
[ O'Conner ] Just stay cool, keep focused.
Remember, the airstrip's on Nallwood Avenue.
It's the third exit after the bridge.
- Got it. - So what up, man? You ready for this?
Come on, man. Guns, murderers and crooked cops?
- I was made for this, brah. - [ Chuckles ]
- [ Roberto ] Come on. - [ Scoffs ]
[ Knocks ]
[ Spanish ]
I got activity at Verone's trailer property.
Do not move an inch until I tell you to.
[ Spanish ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Grunting ] [ Sledgehammers pounding ]
[ Spanish ]
Load up.
All units, move on the trailer property right now. Move!
Shit! Local p.D. is moving in on our guys.
Three bags in one car, huh? Guess so.
[ Sirens Wailing In Distance ] [ Helicopter Whirring ]
Cops.
- I'm not goin' back to jail. - Where you goin', man? Let's go! Let's go!
[ Spanish ] What is he doin'?
[ Engine Starts, Revs ]
[ Laughing ]
[ Chuckling ]
Okay, now let's get the chopper over them. I want eyes right on top.
You got it. Lima 25, follow G.p.S.
[ Siren Wailing ]
You know what you're doin', man?
Stay with me, Rome. Stay with me. Come on, man.
[ Woman On Radio ] I've got 'em heading south on I-95.
Bring in the aerial E.S.D.'s.
Oh, shit!
- They're catching up, man! - Shut up, man!
- Yeah, nice drivin', Rome. Nice drivin'. - I gotcha, Brian.
Check it out, man!
What was that?
Oh, shit. [ Electricity Crackling ]
- Come on, man. Take the wheel. - No. I can't drive.
Just hold the wheel! I can't drive!
Hold it right there! Just hold it steady, just like that.
What are you doin', man?
Que pasa?
[ Grunting ]
[ Laughs ]
- [ Laughing ] - [ Spanish ]
Whoo! Yeah, man!
Hold.
Bilkins, the bird's in place.
Yeah. We got Verone's Navigator.
All right. Money's in transit. Sit tight.
You're a good driver, man.
Thanks, bro.
We've got the area blocked ahead. They've got nowhere to go.
Oh! What was that?
I've got a visual. Video should be coming through.
We got it. Looks good.
Where are they going?
Oh, shit!
All right, Miami's finest, let's see what you got.
Come on. Stay with me, boys.
- Hey, man. Everyone's here. Time for the show. - Let's give it to 'em.
All right. Let the party begin. Let's go.
This is unit 2599. We have the suspects surrounded.
[ police Radio Chatter ]
[ Engines Starting, Rewing ]
[ Rewing Continues ] [ Calling, Indistinct ]
[ Spanish ]
Holy shit!
It's a scramble, baby. A big one! [ Whoops ]
Yeah! Let's do this!
- Check this out! - [ Laughing ]
We're not tracking them on video.
Must have lost them in the scramble.
Y'all, let's break.
Yeah!
[ Whoops ] [ Spanish ]
All right. We got 'em going west on Beach.
Roger that. I've got 'em.
Customs has a fix on two cars going west on Beach.
[ Man On Radio ] Roger. Follow those cars. Roger that.
Shit. They're cornered.
[ Man ] keep your hands where I can see 'em.!
- put your hands up.! - Whoa. Fellas, fellas.
I know my tags are out of date, but, damn!
What the hell? Where are they?
[ Both Whooping ]
Man.! [ Spanish ] How about them apples, man?
Yeah! That's some drivin' for your ass, baby! Ain't that some drivin' for your ass?
- Good job, man. - Whatever, man.
You supposed to be a stone-face killer.
You over there grabbin' your seat belt. [ Laughing ]
Hey, Tej. Thanks a lot. You're the clutch. I owe you one, big time.
Yeah, Brian, you really do owe me, man.
You really do-- Us. Suki says you owe us, a'ight?
- Yo, Rome. You there, man? Come in. - What's up, man?
It looks like we got just one more trick left, huh?
My pleasure, buddy. Let's do it, baby.
[ Helicopter Whirring ]
Hey. We should grab Verone while we still can. No. Not yet.
What? You lost 'em?
Shit! Those little pricks are running.
- It's your call. What do you want to do? - We're gonna take him down.
He is not leaving here.
Enjoyin' the ride? Man, it's a fast car, huh?
[ Chuckling ] Man, it's a classic.
Old school. American muscle.
[ Laughing ]
Man, this car can do all kinda things, man.
Wanna see? [ Laughing ]
Check this out right here, homey.
Yo! What are you doin', man? Shut up!
[ Laughing ]
- [ Shouting, Indistinct ] - ""Ejecto seato,'' cuz!
It worked.! I love this button.!
- [ Coughing ] - Stay on your toes, puto!
Mr. O'Conner, it worked, baby.
Blow and go. I'm all clear.
- Meet me at the point. Hurry up, man. It's on, baby. - All right. Ten-four, man.
Are you ready? Let's go!
I got this side.!
Raise your hands! Raise your hands! Raise your hands!
Get down! Get down! Get down!
Clear.! We're clear.!
Back it up.!
[ Markham Over Radio ] It's not Verone and Fuentes. What do you mean?
Then where the hell are they?
Get off at Tarpon point.
Tarpon point? There's-- There's no airstrip at Tarpon point.
Who said anything about an airstrip?
Brian. Brian, man, what's the holdup, brah?
- Yo, Rome, there's a new plan. - What the hell?
We're meeting them at the Tarpon point exit, not the airstrip.
- So what are you sayin'? - Like I said, there's a new plan.
Brian. Brian, hello? You there?
Damn! Yo! What the hell is he doin'?
The feds are in the wrong place. Brian's woman is on her own with Verone.
- So-- - So Brian's not comin'.
- It's all right. Let him out. - Get out.
pop the trunk. [ Spanish ]
Hurry up.
- Where's the rest of it? - The other car.
- Another car. Where's the other car? - On it's way.
- On the way, huh? - Yeah. Here's your money.
So you know nothing about the agents that stormed my jet?
The funny thing is that I only told one person about the airstrip.
Hmm.
Customs agents sure are gettin' pretty, aren't they?
put her on the boat.
- Let's go. - Get on the boat.
- Hide the cars and get rid of him. - Back in the car.
[ Engine Starts ]
End of the road.
You know, I like you, but I still gotta kill you.
It's my job.
- [ Clicking ] - What's that?
- What's that? - [ pearce ] It's Barstow, baby! It's about to get ugly!
Let's go. Let's go.
[ Screaming ]
Get your-- Oh, shit!
[ kicks Landing ] [ Grunting ]
[ Spits ]
Come on. [ Grunts ]
[ Engine Starts ]
You had me.
You slipped.
Eleven and a half months, and you slipped once.
put her downstairs.
I'll see you in a second.
I thought you was dead, man. Yeah. Me too. Thanks for saving my ass, bro.
What are you doin', Brian? I don't know,
but if Verone sees a helicopter or Customs boat, she's dead.
Boat. Car.
Boat-- You're not gonna do what I think you're gonna do?
- Yeah, I think so. You got my back, bro? - Yeah.
- put on a seat belt. - Show 'em some real Dukes of Hazzard shit.
We're gonna do this big. Hold on, Rome. Hold on.
Oh.! Brian,you crazy, man.! What the hell you doin'?
- [ Screaming ] - Brian, what the hell you doin'?
Whoa!
Shit!
[ Both Grunt ]
[ Both Groaning ]
My arm. I think I broke my arm, man.
[ Groaning ]
[ Footsteps ]
[ Gun Cocks ]
Get the gun.
[ Grunts ]
It's over, Carter.
- You okay? - Yeah.
I'm great.
We got 'em, man. We got 'em.
Let's get outta here.
Go! Go!
[ No Audible Dialogue ] [ police Radio Chatter ]
That ought to do it.
So, there were three bags total, huh? The three from the boat.
So we good, right? My record's clean?
You held up your end. Your records are clean.
So maybe there was six bags.
I guess we can call it even.
Agent Dunn. Sir.
We found some more evidence.
Come on. Let's take it to the truck.
Don't drop the soap, big homey.
I hope you know that when he gets out, he's gonna kill your ass.
[ pearce Chuckling ]
He ain't gettin' out.
- I'll see you soon. - You think he gonna get out?
He'll be out.
No, for real. You think he gettin' out, though?
We took care of your decoys. They're free and clear.
There's a sedan out on the road for you.
Try to bring it back in one piece. Yeah. [ Chuckles ]
- Thanks a lot, Bilkins. You're all right. - Thanks.
- Thanks for lookin' out, man. - All right.
- So you trust me now? - You a'ight.
[ palms Slap ] [ Groans ]
Sorry. Nice working with you, O'Conner.
Same here.
Mm. I'm-a have to stay out here in Miami, man.
Keep you out of trouble, brah.
You know what I'm talkin' about.
So you gonna kick it in Miami, bro?
Oh, man, I love Miami.
Miami's off the hook.
Open a garage together. A garage?
How we gonna do that, brah?
pockets ain't empty, cuz.
[ Laughing ]
And we ain't hungry no more either, brah.
pump, p-p-pump pump it up
pump, p-p-pump pump, p-pump, p-pump
pump, p-p-pump, pump it up   We gonna do it like uh, uh, uh
Look, pump it up if you came to get it krunk with a dame and shit that's drunk
You came to get it on More than five O's in your bank
Then get it on Roll up like that stank and get it on
Slank that fitted on Came to get it on
Hold up, she want work that twork that
Then again let me hurt that murk that till you gotta hurt back
Can't spit it out Boo,you gotta slurp that
Can't cuddle after we done It wasn't worth that
Joey, I'm responsible for bringin'her back
And we bad, huh  She at the bar stylin' She throwin'it up
She drink a little hypno throwin'it up
But I'm only dealin' with freaks that wanna cut
Ma, if you agree I want nut
Camcorder, get it played late night on B.E.T. Uncut Uh
Fellas, do your thing Let me do my thing
I mean, do your thing Let me do my thing
Shorties, move that thing Mami, move that thing
Come on, move that thing Mami, move that thing
Hustlers, do your thing Let me do my thing
please tell the deejay  pump, p-p-pump pump it up
I see some haters grillin' I see some ladies chillin'
I see dat girlie I been plottin'to get
She can hop in the web and we can  pump, p-p-pump, pump it up
Okay, we was leavin' We was done
Then she said Can my peoples come
Here we go I see it don't stop
They wanna ride in somethin' where the rims don't stop
Look, baby,you fine but your girlfriend's not
Fellas, do your thing Let me do my thing
I mean, do your thing Let me do my thing
Shorties, move that thing Mami, move that thing
Come on, move that thing Mami, move that thing
Hustlers, do your thing Let me do my thing
please tell the deejay  pump, p-p-pump pump it up
Fellas, do your thing Let me do my thing
I mean, do your thing Let me do my thing
Shorties, move that thing Mami, move that thing
Come on, move that thing Mami, move that thing
Hustlers, do your thing Let me do my thing
please tell the deejay  pump, p-p-pump pump it up
Drah  2 fast
Drah  2 furious
I'm too fast for y'all, man
Drah  2 fast
Drah  2 furious
Oh, I'm too fast for y'all, man
Ahh,you just came home from doin'a bid
Tell me what you gonna do  Act a fool
Somebody broke in and cleaned out your crib
Boy, what you gonna do  Act a fool
Just bought a new pair and they scuffed your shoes
Tell me what you gonna do  Act a fool
Now them cops tryin'to throw you in them county blues
Boy, what you gonna do  Act a fool
Talkin' 'bout traps cops and robbers
It's 9 1 1 please call the doctor
Evacuate the building and trick the pigs
Since everybody want a piece we gonna split your wigs
See, some fools slipped up and overstepped they boundaries
You 'bout to catch a cold Stay the f-- from around me
Ya peeps talkin' 'bout what kinda sh--'s he on
You disappear like poof,b--be gone
You think 1 2 gonna catch me Gimme a break
I'm supercharged with the hideaway license plates
It seems they wanna fingerprint me and gimme some years
They'll only get one finger while I'm shifting gears
I got suede on my roof wood grain on the dash
Sheepskin on the rug Golden Grain in the stash
Hydraulics all around so I shake the ride
We go front, back and side to side
Some punk just tripped up and made you spill your drink
Tell me what you gonna do  Act a fool
Now your carjust stopped on an empty tank
Boy, what you gonna do  Act a fool
If you got late bills and you lost yourjob
Tell me what you gonna do  Act a fool
If you 'bout to get drunk and you ready to mob
Boy, what you gonna do  Act a fool
Let's take it to the streets 'cause I'm ready to cruise
Just bought me and my cars all some brand-new shoes
And the peoplejust stare so I love to park it
And I just put a computer in the glove compartment
With my pedal to the floor, radar in the grill
TVin the middle of my steerin'wheel
It's my car's birthday so we blowin'them candles
More speakers in the trunk than my ride can handle
Got my name in the headrest Read it and weep
NOS tank in the back camel hair on the seat
And when I pull up to the club I get all the affection
'Cause the women love the paint and they can see their reflection
I'm about to take off so "F'"what ya heard
Because my side mirrors flap like a f--n'bird
And for the fools we gonna clock one Then we'll f-- one
'Cause my folk ridin'shotgun with a sh--
You just got hustled for a wad of cash
Man, what you gonna do  Act a fool
Now your friends just smoked up your brand-new stash
Say, what you gonna do  Act a fool
Now them girls up the block still runnin'they mouth
Boy, what you gonna do  Act a fool
If anyone talk bad 'bout the dirty south
Tell me what I'm gonna do  Act a fool
I got my eyes wide shut and my trunk wide open
Did donuts last week, and the streets still smokin'
See, I'm off that antifreeze and my car is tipsy
On the off-ramp doin' 'bout 1 50
Rollin'through East pernium on my way to Ben Heel
Slide a five to thejunkie to clean my windshield
Got the whole crew ridin' and we startin'--
I even got a trailer hitch with a barbecue pit
And now all you wanna do is get drunk and pout
plus your new name is Fire 'cause we stomped you out
And,yeah, we-- trees and bees That's fantastic
So, girls, hold your weave while I'm weavin' through traffic
I kicked to fifth gear and tear the road apart
You'll be like littleJohn "Q'" and get a change ofheart
It's one mission, two clips and some triple beams
I'm about to blow this whole sh-- up to smithereens
Ahh,you just came home from doin'a bid
Tell me what you gonna do  Act a fool
Somebody broke in and cleaned out your crib
Boy, what you gonna do  Act a fool
Just bought a new pair and they scuffed your shoes
Tell me what you gonna do  Act a fool
Now them cops tryin'to throw you in them county blues
Boy, what you gonna do  Act a fool
Talkin' 'bout pot holes in the street just bent ya rims
Tell me what you gonna do  Act a fool
Man, that ain't sticky That's sticks and stems
Boy, what you gonna do  Act a fool
Catch your man with another b-- up in your bed
Ladies, what you gonna do  Act a fool
If the bottle's all gone and your eyes are red
Boy, what you gonna do  Act a fool
2 fast, 2 fast 2 furious, 2 furious
2 fast, 2-- Act a fool