更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
I spoke to Mr. Babbitt on that just this morning.
I'm still sitting on four Lamborghinis
that can't meet the smog emission standards.
How many times you wash out with EPA?
Yes they're finally clearing EPA. Just one or two more days.
Three times? We're really on a roll here.
Four cars three times each. That's zip for 12.
Are you a mechanic or a NASA engineer?
I told you I've never dealt with these Lamborghinis before
yet you assured me you could deliver within that time frame.
Don't tell me that 'cause I'm not listening.
Sir I hardly think that's necessary.
I'll explain that to my swing loan. I'm sure he'll be sympathetic.
I'm into him for 200000. That's three zeros.
I've got all my money tied up in these cars.
If I don't get my money out I am finished. You understand?
You have to understand our situation.
I don't give a shit. I've got sharks snapping at my heels.
They could've taken the car and my business 11 days ago.
I'm under collateral for God's sake.
Lunderstand I know delivery is way overdue.
Fuckin' EPA... whole world is choking on smog
and they're gonna correct the situation
by keeping my four cars off the road?
Babbitt Collectibles.
Have you tried cash? How much can these EPA guys earn in a week?
Charlie it's Wyatt.
- Wyatt. - About the swing loan.
If he doesn't get the money by 5:30 he's gonna seize all the cars.
I'm gonna have to call you back.
You should talk to Mr. Babbitt on this.
Tell him I signed a check on Tuesday
you watched me sign it then you gave it to the mail girl.
Come on! I need this!
Come on!
I wouldn't do that until you talk to Mr. Babbitt personally.
A number for him? He's on the road just now.
He wants you to call him immediately.
Tell him I'm arriving 1:30 a.m. can he leave a number?
What Lenny? Talk to me.
Mr. Bateman wants to back out and take Mr. Webb with him.
They want their down payments back.
They found two cars at Valley Motors and they want to go that way.
Tell him that was me on the other line
the cars passed emissions the EPA paperwork will be here momentarily.
- You paying attention? - I'm listening.
Tell them I'm knocking off five grand on both their deals
because I appreciate their patience.
- Do you understand? - I've got it.
Mr. Bateman that was Mr. Babbitt on the other line.
As it happens the cars are passing emissions...
What am I saying... the cars have passed emissions.
We're waiting for the EPA paperwork... we'll have that momentarily.
And because of your incredible patience
we're going to knock off $5000 on each car.
Well yes you've been most patient.
We really appreciate your patience.
Well thank you.
Thank you.
Ready for Palm Springs?
You still want to go with all these problems?
We're seconds away from closing this deal clearing 75 grand.
Not bad for a couple of phone calls.
Not bad at all.
You know where to find us right Lenny?
Right. I got it under control.
Listen I don't want to be demanding here
but could you possibly say I don't know 10 or 12 words
before we get to the hotel?
Consider it foreplay.
Can you include me in some of your thoughts?
I'm just thinking.
Nothing special. I'm just thinking.
Maybe there's something you're thinking about that we can talk.
If there was something to talk about Susanna we'd be talking.
I'm just thinking. What's the big to-do about me thinking here?
I just feel like I'm going away for a few days with someone.
Call me crazy.
You wanna talk let's talk. How was your day?
- I don't want to talk! - No let's talk!
I feel like you're excluding me. It's not that I want to talk.
One of these again. How did we get back to one of these?
I don't know why I put up with all this.
You wanted to go to Palm Springs and we're going.
But I didn't want to go alone.
I've been sitting in this car for more than an hour and a half...
You want to talk let's talk!
This is not talking this is you going like...
Yeah.
Charlie. This is lenny.
I've been trying to contact you for a while.
I got a long-distance call from a Mr. Mooney.
Your father's lawyer. He's been trying to reach you.
Your father has died. Charlie.
I'm sorry. The funeral's tomorrow in Cincinnati.
He said you'd Know where. I've got his number.
That's not necessary. Anything else?
No. That's it. Listen. If there's anything I can do...
All right.
- Sorry about the weekend hon. - Charlie the weekend?
Look I told you before we had a falling out a long time ago.
My mother died when I was two. It was just him and me.
We just didn't get along.
- You're going to the funeral no? - Yeah.
I'm coming with you.
That's really sweet but there's really no point.
I want to. That's the point.
All right I'm sorry. I forgot who I was talking to.
...for our memory admiration and respect for him
will live beyond the years of his life on Earth.
Let us consecrate ourselves to follow his example of zest for life
dedication to family and charity to all.
And now with sure and certain hope of resurrection
we commend to you the soul of our departed friend.
Just have to go over the details of the will tonight then we're outta here.
Sure I can wait in the car if you like.
Somebody should be watering those roses... they're all dying.
I knew this car my whole life. Only drove it once.
It's a 1949 Buick Roadmaster convertible.
Only 8000 production models made. Straight-8. Fireball-8.
It was the first full year of the Dynaflow transmission.
I know it by rote.
You were his only child.
You came along when he was what 45 or something?
Probably thought he was never going to have a son.
So he had to love you.
I think you're exaggerating.
You were his child his son his blood.
Anyway in these pictures here
he doesn't look like a man who doesn't love his child.
Put that away.
- You wanna hear a story? - But don't get mad.
You know the convertible? His baby. That and the goddamn roses.
Buick.
The car was off-limits to me. "That's a classic" he'd say.
"It commands respect. It's not for children."
Tenth grade I'm 16 years old and for once
I bring home a report card and it's almost all A's.
I go to my old man "Can I take the car out?"
Take the guys out in the Buick sort of a victory drive.
He says no. I take it anyway.
I steal the keys I sneak it out.
You took the car with no permission?
Why? Why then?
Because I deserved it.
Nothing I did was good enough for this guy.
Don't you understand that?
We're on Columbia Parkway four kids.
- We get pulled over. - An accident?
Pulled over.
- What is pulled over? Police? - Yes police.
Can I finish?
He called in a report of a stolen car...
not his son took the car without permission... just stolen.
Central station the other guys' dads bail them out in an hour
he left me there two days.
- He left you in prison for two days? - Two days.
Were you scared?
Yeah I was scared.
Left home. I never saw him again.
Charlie after a year we've been together
this is the first time I've heard this story.
It's strange.
How can you keep all this inside you and not say anything?
When I was a kid and got scared
the Rain Man would come and sing to me.
"Rain" what?
One of those imaginary childhood friends.
- What happened to him? - Nothing. I just grew up.
Not so much.
"And I remember too the day you left home
"so full of bitterness and grandiose ideas
"so full of yourself.
"And being raised without a mother
"the hardness of your heart is understandable as well.
"Your refusal to even pretend that you loved or respected me
"all these I forgive.
"But your failure to write to telephone
"to reenter my life in any way has left me without a son.
"I wish you all I ever wanted for you.
I wish you the best."
"I hereby bequeath to my son Charles Sanford Babbitt
"that certain Buick convertible
"the very car that unfortunately brought our relationship to an end.
"Also outright title to my prizewinning hybrid rosebushes.
"May they remind him of the value of excellence
"and the possibility of perfection.
"As for my home and all other property real and personal
"these shall be placed in trust in accordance with the terms
of that certain instrument executed concurrently herewith."
The last part what does that mean?
It means that the estate
in excess of $3 million after expenses and taxes
will go into a trust fund
for a beneficiary to be named in this document.
- Who is that? - I'm afraid I can't tell you that.
- Who controls the money? You? - It's called a trustee.
What is that? How does that work?
Forgive me but there's nothing more I can say.
Now I'm sorry son. I can see you're disappointed.
Why should I be disappointed?
I got rosebushes didn't I? I got a used car didn't I?
What's-his-name got... what'd you call him?
- Beneficiary. - Right. He got $3 Million.
But he didn't get the rosebushes. I got the rosebushes.
I definitely got the rosebushes.
There is no need...
To what? To be upset?
To be upset?
If there is a Hell sir my father is in it
and he is looking up right now and he is laughing his ass off.
Sanford Babbitt... you want to be that guy's son for five minutes?
Did you hear that letter? Were you listening?
Yes sir I was. Were you?
No. Could you repeat it? 'Cause I can't believe my fuckin' ears.
I was looking for you.
How did it go?
I got what I expected.
This could take a few minutes.
- Can I help you? - Yes I think you can.
I have a problem with a private trust...
- That's a terrific suit. - Thank you.
My father was Sanford Babbitt...
Is this Wallbrook?
Excuse me. Is this Wallbrook?
Excuse me.
Dr. Bruner is still in conference.
Would you like to wait in his outer office?
No we'll stay here. Thank you.
Maybe we're not supposed to be looking around here no?
Good to have you here. Good lucK to all three of you.
$20 starts you all off on a very important match.
In what 1980 comedy film did Goldie Hawn get away from it all?
Private Benjamin.
Excuse me please. I want to watch the TV please.
For whose grandson
was the presidential retreat Camp David named? Lisa?
- Eisenhower. - That's right. David Eisenhower.
You've got another five. $ 10 lead for lisa.
In days of yore. What would a swashbucKler Keep in his sheath?
Whatever this is I don't understand the point of secrecy.
The patient is an old girlfriend of my father's?
I knew your father since you were two years old.
The year my mother died.
I'm trustee of the fund but this hospital receives nothing from that.
That hardly seems fair. That's something we could discuss.
I took on this burden out of loyalty to your father.
That's where my loyalty ends.
And you think I should feel a little of that loyalty?
I think you feel cheated out of your birthright
by a man who had difficulty showing love.
And if I were in your shoes I'd probably feel the same.
I was hoping you would explain my father's side of it
help me understand the right in what he's done
because failing that I have responsibilities of my own
and they have to be met even if that means a fight.
I'm sorry this is not your car. It's my boyfriend's.
My dad lets me drive slow on the driveway.
I'm an excellent driver.
Are you sure that you drive this car?
There's 28 miles on the odometer since I drove it a week ago Saturday.
- Should be more than 28 miles. - Look my boyfriend is coming.
'Course today's Monday.
I always drive on Saturday never drive on Monday.
- Who is this guy? - He jumped into the car.
Well he can jump out.
- I'm an excellent driver. - That's good. Come on.
Why did you let him in? It's not a toy.
He says he drives this car.
Dad lets me drive slow on the driveway every Saturday.
'Course the seats were originally brown leather now they're pitiful red.
You know these seats were brown leather.
- You know this car? - I know this car.
How do you know this car?
Definitely know this car. It's a 1949 Buick Roadmaster.
Straight-8 Fireball-8. Only 8095 production models.
Dad lets me drive slow on the driveway but not on Mondays.
- Definitely not on Monday. - Who's your dad?
- Sanford Babbitt. - Sanford Babbitt?
10961 Beechcrest Street Cincinnati Ohio.
That's my address. What is it with this guy?
- Who's your mother? - Eleanor Babbitt.
Died january 5 1965 after a short...
Who the hell are you?
Wait where are you going?
13 minutes to judge Wapner and The People's Court.
Wait a second I want to ask you a question.
Hey I'm talking to you!
Bruner who is this guy?
Raymond is your brother.
My brother? I don't have a brother.
"...have their dispute settled here in our forum
The People's Court."
"The People's Court."
The People's Court.
Hello. I' m Doug llewelyn.
And welcome to The People's Court.
- Is he crazy? - No.
- Is he retarded? - Not exactly.
- Not crazy or retarded but he's here. - He's an autistic savant.
I don't know what that means.
Some people like him used to be called idiot savants.
They have certain deficiencies certain abilities.
- Yeah but he's retarded. - Autistic. Actually high-functioning.
What does that mean?
It means there's a disability
that impairs the sensory input and how it's processed.
English here. You're talking over my head.
Raymond has a problem communicating and learning.
He can't even express himself
or probably even understand his own emotions in a traditional way.
...and after that. The dog bit him.
I yelled at my dog. The dog laid down...
There are dangers everywhere for Raymond.
Routines rituals... it's all he has to protect himself.
Rituals. That's a good one.
It's the way he acts sleeps eats
uses the bathroom walks talks everything.
Any break from the routines and it's terrifying.
- How long has he been here? - Well I came here in 1960.
No how old is he?
He was 18 or 20 then. I'd have to check records...
- You've been here that long? - That's when I actually started.
'65'75'85... I was almost three years old.
You knew he had a brother you knew I was his brother.
Yes but what's the point?
What's the point? What's the fuckin' point?
Why didn't anybody tell me I had a brother?
What would you have done about it?
I don't know.
Does he know how much money he's been left?
He doesn't understand the concept of money.
He's just inherited $3 million
and he doesn't understand the concept of money?
That is fucking poetic don't you think?
Good old Dad.
Who's playing first? Yes.
The fellow's name on first base. Who.
The fellow playing first base for St. Louis. Who.
What is this? Why is he doing that?
Whenever he gets nervous he does "Who's On First?"
- From Abbott and Costello. - Why?
It's his way of dealing with you touching his books and stuff.
So he memorized "Who's On First?"
Yeah that among other things.
Raymond Ted Kluszewski.
Ted Kluszewski Big Klew first base.
He played for Cincinnati.
'Course he was traded for Dee Fondy 1957.
- Lifetime batting average.298. - All these books. He reads huh?
Reads and remembers whatever he gets his hands on.
V-E-R-N!'Course these people are gonna be here all day.
This is an unannounced visit Vern.
This is definitely not a weekend visit Vern.
He's getting anxious. It's okay Ray!
V-E-R-N this is an unannounced visit.
Put it back. He said not to touch the books.
Not to touch books.
- You like Shakespeare? - I don't know.
- Did you read all this? - I don't know. Vern.
- Did you read Macbeth? - I don't know.
- You read Hamlet? - I don't know.
- The Twelfth Night? - Stop it!
- Yes. - Yes?
You read all the stories that are in this book
and you don't know if you read the book?
- I don't know. V-E-R-N. - You don't know?
Maybe you better put it back.
You don't know. Okay. No Ray take it easy.
I'm not going to... I won't touch anything else.
It's ok Ray. It's okay. Come on. My main man.
Vern my main man. My main man Vern.
It's okay Ray.
- My main man. - Yeah my main man.
Here are your cards.
I'm sorry I didn't know where you want me to put them.
Are you taking any prescription medication?
He likes you. That's just his way of showing it.
When I touched him before he pulled away.
Don't take it personal. He never touched me.
I'm closer to him than anybody in the world.
Known him for nine years. It's not in him.
If I left town tomorrow and didn't say goodbye
he'd never notice.
He wouldn't notice if you leave?
I'm not sure but I don't think people are his first priority.
Hey Ray you want to go take a walk?
Can he hear us when he's like that?
You wanna show your brother your ducks?
'Course it's 27 minutes to Jeopardy!
Don't worry Ray we'll bring you right back.
Practically 26 minutes to Jeopardy!
We'll bring him right back.
26 minutes to Jeopardy!
I won't do it. I won't do it!
First of all because of your tone of voice this commanding...
You're upset. Just calm down.
Raymond I'm going to talk to Susanna alone.
- Goodbye Raymond. - Susanna!
Just hold on. I'll be right back.
No just stay. Just stay there.
Just stay there. Just stand still okay?
That's good.
I'll do it if you tell me why... why do I do...
What?
Why do I have to take the car and go down there
and wait for you again at the gate?
I've been waiting for you for days. Why?
It's for Raymond. The car disturbs him.
- That's why? - That's why.
What are you looking at? The ducks are over here.
I don't know.
Listen our father died.
Did you know that he died last week did they tell you that?
I don't know.
You don't know if they told you or you don't know what dead is?
That means he's gone. He's at the cemetery.
You want to go see him at the cemetery Ray?
I don't know.
Does that mean maybe? Maybe you wanna go?
I live in Los Angeles.
I thought maybe you'd like to see a Dodger game.
Go see the Dodgers play.
- Today's an off day. - We don't have to go today.
Monday. No games scheduled.
Just thought you'd like to go to Los Angeles with me
go see Fernando Valenzuela pitch.
Valenzuela pitched Saturday. Not scheduled to pitch till Wednesday.
- He's gonna pitch on Wednesday? - Wednesday.
I'm not doing anything on Wednesday.
- Yeah Wednesday. - Let's go to L.A.
Come on Ray.
'Course it's a long way to California.
I'm definitely not supposed to be off the grounds for more than two hours.
Definitely have to be back in two hours.
Wait till you get there. The people crowds cheering. You'll love it.
Have to be back in two hours.
- The Presidential Suite. - Dinner's at 6:30 p.m.
To the left is Raymond's room. Look at this beautiful room.
This is definitely not my room.
It's just for tonight.
Have to go back to Wallbrook for dinner.
Little guy! This is gonna be terrific.
Dr. Bruner wants us to spend time together.
We're gonna have fun.
- What did he say? - He said that.
I don't have my tapioca pudding. We have tapioca pudding for dessert.
We can do that. I'm gonna call Lenny.
This is definitely not my room and I don't have my pudding
and the bed's in the wrong place.
You can move it.
- Where do you want the bed? - Should be near the window.
'Course I don't have my books. 'Course there's no bookshelves.
I'm definitely out of books. I'm gonna be bookless.
Here's a book.
Big telephone book lot of words.
Lenny pick up will you?
I got $200000 about to go in the shithouse
and he doesn't wanna answer the phone.
What is it... 6:00 here that means it's 9:00 there.
- No it's 3:00 there. - 6:30 p.m. Is dinner.
It's 3:00 there. He doesn't want to answer the phone?
Orange soda.
Has to be in a can with a straw.
Bruner told you that you should do this?
- It doesn't make sense. - I know what's good for him.
V-E-R-N!
God. Go see what he's doing will you?
- What is it? - What's happening homes?
Everything is fine. Charlie let's take him home.
He's okay. We'll just get him some dinner he'll be all right.
What'd you say... you wanted hamburger?
We have pepperoni pizza Monday night for dinner.
Pizza? You get pizza in the institution?
'Course Monday night's Italian Night.
Hello. Offices of Mitchell & Mitchell.
Get me Stu. This is Charlie Babbitt.
I'm sorry. He's not here.
Where is he? I got a bit of a legal problem.
He's out of town until tomorrow afternoon.
All right I'll call him tomorrow.
No TV during dinnertime. Definitely not.
We can watch TV here. We can. We're allowed.
"Wheel of Fortune!
"Look at this studio filled with glamorous merchandise
"fabulous and exciting bonus prizes.
"A pair of cars for today's busy couple.
"Thousands of dollars in cash.
"Over $150000 just waiting to be won
"as we present our big bonanza of cash
on Wheel of Fortune!"
Room service 321. I'd like to order a large pizza.
Pepperoni right?
I don't want pepperoni.
That's right. A large pepperoni.
- How long's that going to take? - 20 minutes.
Bring some beer up for two and an orange soda.
And tapioca pudding... you got tapioca pudding?
Just bring the closest thing.
Here Ray. Take this. Food is coming shortly.
I'll be right back.
'Course I'm going to be here for a long time. A very long time.
I'm gone for good from my home.
What is that?
I think Raymond is in the room.
What? Raymond are you in here?
Well get out! Get out!
- Go! - Stop it!
Jesus...
Stop it. Go in there with him.
Come on go in there. He's your brother.
He's afraid. He doesn't understand this.
Come on go in there!
Raymond what were you doing in my room?
What were you doing in my room?
- I don't know. - You don't know?
'Course there were noises.
Those noises are none of your business you understand?
Put the phone book down
stop acting like an idiot and go to sleep.
Did you hear what I said? Go to sleep! Go to sleep!
It's nine minutes to 11:00 Lights out at 11:00.
Well new rules.
You don't listen to me! You don't listen to me!
What are you talking about?
I asked you to go apologize. You went and insulted him again!
What am I supposed to do tuck him in? I'm not his mother.
You're his brother. His brother!
They tell you today that you have a brother
and I don't see in your face one little reaction.
I'm not saying joy I'm saying something.
You don't know what I'm going through here.
No I don't know what you're going through.
I don't know because you don't tell me anything.
You just give me lies.
Lies? What lies?
This thing that Dr. Bruner asked you to bring him here this is bullshit.
I know it's not true. Why don't you tell me why he's here?
Because I'm pissed at him. At my father.
You're pissed at your father and you bring Raymond here. Why?
'Cause I got him and they want him.
This makes no sense!
Raymond was left all the money and I got nothing.
$3 million. The inheritance every penny of it.
I'm gonna keep him till I get my half! I deserve that!
What is this?
- Just take it easy. - I've had enough.
You've had enough? What does that mean?
I'm leaving.
You're leaving? You're leaving me now? I need you.
What? You need nobody.
What does that mean?
What? Just take it easy. What is my crime here?
Your crime is that you use people!
You're using Raymond! You're using me!
You use everybody.
I'm using Raymond?
Am I using you? Am I using you Raymond?
- Yeah. - Shut up!
He is answering a question from a half-hour ago!
What good is $3 million to him?
That money is only just gonna sit there the rest of his life.
And you know I need that money!
You need it so it's hardly like stealing!
And when it's over what happens to Raymond?
He'll go back to Wallbrook
or with the money I will put him in a better place.
What difference does it make? He is gonna be just the same!
Only you'll have his money!
His money? That man was my father too.
What about my fucking half? I'm entitled to that money!
You've kidnapped this man!
I did not take him. I took my half.
- Which half? You're crazy! - It runs in the family.
You're soaking wet and you're gonna leave in the middle of the night.
Just wait! My father has stuck it to me all my life.
What do you want from me?
Out.
- Stop it. - Good morning. Coffee?
Yes. That'd be great.
Sally Dibbs.
Dibbs Sally. 461-0192.
How did you know my phone number?
How'd you know that?
You said read the telephone book. Dibbs Sally. 461-0192.
He remembers things little things sometimes.
Very clever boys. I'll be right back.
How'd you do that?
- I don't know. - You memorized the whole book.
No.
You start from the beginning? How far did you get?
"G." Gottsaken. William Marshall Gottsaken.
- You memorized to "G"? - Yeah "G."
A B C D E F G?
G. Half of "G."
That's good Ray.
I like that.
- We hungry? - Tuesday we have pancakes.
- That sounds good. - With maple syrup.
- Bet your butt. - Bet your butt.
They got pancakes.
What is this Ray?
'Course I don't have my toothpicks.
You don't need toothpicks.
That was okay in the hotel last night with the pizza
but in a restaurant you use a fork.
I don't have my toothpicks.
Pancakes keep sliding off. You're gonna eat with a fork.
I don't have maple syrup either.
I'm gonna be without my maple syrup and my toothpicks.
You don't see any pancakes do you?
'Course the problem is maple syrup is not here.
When we order the pancakes they're gonna bring the maple syrup.
Maple syrup is supposed to be on the table before the pancakes.
We haven't ordered yet.
When they bring it after it'll definitely be too late.
How is that gonna be too late? We haven't ordered pancakes yet.
If we're gonna be here the entire morning
with no maple syrup and no toothpicks
I'm definitely not gonna have my pancakes with...
Don't make a scene.
Stop acting like a fucking retard.
What are you writing?
What the fuck is this?
"Serious... serious injury list"?
"Charlie Babbitt. Serious injury list"?
Are you fuckin' kidding me?
"Number 18 in 1988.
Squeezed and pulled and hurt my neck in 1988."
Squeezed and pulled and hurt your neck in 1988?
- Dr. Bruner it's Charlie Babbitt. - Where are you. Son?
It's not important. What matters is who I'm with.
You have to bring him bacK. Do you understand me?
No problem whatsoever. That'll be $1.5 million.
I'm not greedy I just want my half.
Don't touch that. That's dirty.
I can't do that. Mr. Babbitt. You Know I can't.
Just bring him bacK. And bring him bacK now.
This is where he belongs.
I'm his brother. It's not like kidnapping is it?
He's always been a voluntary patient here.
But that's beside the point.
The fact is. This is where he can get the best care.
We're talKing about his well-being.
Let's just cut through the bullshit.
I am entitled to part of my father's estate.
If you don't want to cut a deal I'll fly him to Los Angeles
stick him in an institution out there
and we can have a custody battle over him.
Miss he needs toothpicks.
Could you help him? Thank you very much.
You want to battle me in the courts?
Think about that Dr. Bruner. Think about that.
Or we can cut a deal right now.
I don't thinK you have any idea of the severity of Raymond's condition.
Toothpicks. He needs some toothpicks.
Can we just get him toothpicks?
I cannot. Under any circumstances. MaKe any money deals with you.
Then I'll see you in court.
And the check. Sorry about the toothpicks.
82 82 82.
82 what Ray?
- How much is this? - Toothpicks.
It's a lot more than 82 toothpicks.
'Course 246 total.
Keep the change.
How many toothpicks are in there?
250.
Pretty close. Come on. Let's go Ray.
246.
There's four left in the box.
'Course I have to get my backpack.
Forgot my backpack.
97-X. The future of rocK'n' roll.
97-X\n97-X.
The future of rock'n' roll.
Enough already. Change the channel.
97-X\n97-X.
The future of rock'n' roll.
Lenny I don't care what you think. Did they say that?
You're gonna have to be a lot more forceful with them.
Shut up a moment here. I am in serious trouble.
I can't get to these cars. I can't get the money.
Do you understand that? My loan is past due.
IooK. I' II call the loan officer. Tell him we have a little problem.
Listen. Charlie. Let me talK to Wyatt.
Just listen to me. I'll be in LAX in three hours.
Remember the Buick is in A-3 main terminal.
Make sure they pick it up.
Right. See you in a few.
Will Dr. BaKer. Dr. Andrew BaKer.
Please picK up the white courtesy phone?
Raymond let's go.
Let's go! Come on.
What were you watching?
- I don't know. - You don't know?
Final call for Flight 1559.
Service to Salt laKe City and los Angeles.
'Course there's an airplane out there.
That's right and everybody's boarding.
Airline travel's very dangerous.
It's the safest travel in the world. You're gonna love this. Trust me.
- Now come on. - Oh no.
We're in an airport. People fly out of airports.
What did you think we were doing here?
In 1987 there were 30 airline accidents.
211 were fatalities 231 were definitely passengers.
This plane is very safe. Believe me.
I gotta get to L.A. I don't have time for this shit.
- I don't know. - You don't know?
- No. - Is it this airline?
Is it this airline? Okay fine.
We can... There's an American plane...
American Flight 625 crashed April 27 1976.
We don't have to take American there's a lot of flights.
Pick another airline.
Continental.
Continental crashed November 15 1987.
Flight 1713. 28 casualties.
- This is very serious. - Very serious.
I have to get to Los Angeles.
So you're gonna get on that plane understand me?
You're gonna have to get on a plane.
Yeah get on a plane.
Now there's a Delta.
It leaves at midnight but how's Delta?
Delta crashed August 2 1985.
Lockheed L-1011.
Dallas-Fort Worth. Terrible wind shear. 135 passengers.
All airlines have crashed at one time or another.
That doesn't mean that they are not safe.
- Qantas. - Qantas?
Qantas never crashed.
- Qantas? - Never crashed.
That's... that's going to do me a lot of good Ray.
Qantas doesn't fly to L.A. Out of Cincinnati.
You've gotta get to Melbourne... Melbourne Australia...
in order to get the plane that flies to Los Angeles.
Canberra's the capital. 16.2 million population.
Very lovely beaches.
You and I are gonna get on this fucking plane!
We're not going to take the plane. He's okay!
We're not going to take the plane.
Just relax. He was upset.
We were going to take the plane.
We're not gonna take the plane. We're not going to fly.
No flying.
- We're not going to fly. - No flying.
You tire me Ray.
We're going to drive to Los Angeles.
Okay? Come on.
Ray come on.
No flying.
We're not gonna take the plane. Just grab the fucking bag.
I want you to know you are killing me man.
I got to be in L.A. In three hours it's gonna take me three days.
No flying.
- No flying. - No flying.
'Course I got Jeopardy! At 5:00. I watch Jeopardy! At 5:00.
- Don't start with that. - I've got Jeopardy at 5:00.
- Dispatch this is 109. - Go ahead. 109.
See if you can get another unit up here for point control.
Two more over to you. 10-40.
Come on! Come on move!
Bring some more up.
- Yeah there's a... - Ray get in the car.
Just get in the car! Are you crazy?
We'll be out of this in a second.
That's good.
It's okay. That's right.
We'll be out of here in a few seconds.
That's good Ray. That's good.
There's definitely a fatal accident over there.
We don't need your help. Go on back to your car.
Just a minute!
Son of a bitch!
There's nothing to see here. Get back in your car.
- Yes sir. - Go back and get in your car.
Yes sir. Just stay there by the side.
Ray listen! Just stay there!
Yeah definitely a lot of traffic.
A hell of a lot of work for $3 million.
I should just leave him on the goddamn highway.
I hear you!
Stay in your car please!
What was that... 555 Sam Adam Barry?
What's it going to be Ray?
This is a very dangerous highway.
How am I gonna get to L. A?
Driving on this interstate is very dangerous.
Want to get off the highway? Will that make you happy?
Well you gotta get in the car!
'Course in 1986 46400 male drivers
were definitely involved in fatal accidents.
I got an idea. I got a great idea.
Stay in front of the car until we get off the exit.
You'll get in and we'll take a not-so-dangerous road.
Whatever that might be. Is that an idea?
Give me five. That's a great idea.
Gimme five.
This guy's a fucking fruitcake.
All right. Let's move out!
They've got two more units...
The fire department's covering it.
I'm asking who's on first. That's the man's name.
That's whose name? Yes.
Then go ahead and tell me. Who.
The guy on first. Who.
The first baseman. Who is on first.
Who is? Yes.
After all the man earns it.
Who does? Absolutely.
All I'm trying to find out is what's the guy's name on first base?
No no. What is on second base.
I'm not asking who's on second.
Who's on first? That's what I'm trying to find out.
Get the hell in the car!
Yeah get in the car. Get in the car yeah.
'Course I have to be in bed by 11:00.
Lights out at 11:00. Have to watch TV.
'Course now it's almost 19 minutes to 11:00.
I have to be in bed at 11:00.
We're not flying we're not on the interstate.
We're on some shit secondary road.
I gotta make up some time get to Los Angeles.
My business needs me. I gotta make up some time.
Definitely watch TV
but you have to be in bed at 11:00. Lights out.
Forget it.
19 minutes to 11:00.
This is a good one...
"We don't go out when it rains."
I hope you appreciate this
because my business is going down the fucking toilet.
I should be in L.A.
Instead I'm in the Honeymoon Haven Motel
in Bumblefuck Missouri
because you won't go out when it rains.
It's mystifying. Fucking mystifying.
What is this? Good news bad news?
We passed DOT but failed EPA.
It all ends up the same. I can't get my money.
Yes I'm just stuck in Cincinnati since the funeral.
So many leftover details.
My family is needless to say
quite overwhelmed.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Well it is a shock to say the least.
Thank you. Is there any way I can get an extension on that loan?
Just a couple of days. It would make a world of difference.
We don't go out when it's raining.
What? Speak up.
I bought time I didn't buy that kind of time.
You're gonna have to... how much?
'Course it's 12:30. Lunch is 12:30.
- What do you want for lunch? - Wednesday's fish sticks.
- Fish sticks? - Green lime jell-O for dessert.
Want another apple juice?
Orange soda. Oh it's 12:31.
I gotta go. He's starting to rock and moan.
- Yeah it's definitely 12:32. - It's okay. No.
Give me that gun.
Where is he?
How did you figure to frame Vargas with it?
'Frame'?
Where is he?
'Course there's four fish sticks. There's supposed to be eight.
Eight? There's Eight.
Take a shower Ray?
You take a shower right?
Same thing as rain... you get a little wet.
What do you say?
'Course the shower's in the bathroom.
That's the end of that conversation.
- Go again. - British poetry for 200. please.
The answer at the top of the category.
"ShaKespeare wrote over 150 poems in this 14-line form."
What is a sonnet?
- What is a sonnet? - You got it.
- Double letters for 200. - Top of that one.
"The last word in the Pledge of Allegiance."
- MarK? - What is "stands"?
Stu legally Bruner never established a conservatorship of Raymond?
He didn't figure anyone would show up to contest his authority.
If that's the case I definitely will get custody
- and the $3 million right? - Possibly.
You set up a date for the custody hearing.
Stu I want a firm date and I want it early.
I found that it was an original record.
Because the original song had two verses...
Lenny she hasn't come in she hasn't called?
If you see her or hear from her tell her to call me at this number.
Would you look at that... 1957 Studebaker Goldenhawk.
Zero to sixty in under eight seconds.
275 supercharged horsepower under that hood.
- That's beautiful. - I'm an excellent driver.
You know how to drive?
When did you drive?
I drove the Buick on the driveway when my dad came to Wallbrook.
Was dad in the car Ray?
- And he let you drive the Buick? - Yeah slow on the driveway.
We'll have to let you drive sometime.
You never touch the steering wheel when I'm driving!
Do you hear me?!
'Course I don't have my underwear.
What?
I'm not wearing my underwear.
I gave you a fresh pair of mine this morning.
Not my underwear.
I told you to go in the bathroom and put them on.
'Course they're in the pocket of my jacket.
- Where? - Here.
- These are too tight. - I don't want them back.
These are not boxer shorts. Mine are boxer shorts.
- What's the difference? - These are Hanes 32.
My boxers have my name. It says "Raymond".
When we pass a store we'll pick you up a pair of boxer shorts.
I get my boxer shorts at Kmart in Cincinnati.
We're not going back so don't even start.
400 Oak Street.
You don't have to go to Cincinnati to pick up boxer shorts.
It's Oak and Burnett in Cincinnati. It's Kmart.
What did I say? I know you hear me.
You don't fool me with this shit for a second.
Yours are too tight.
Ray did you fucking hear what I said?
Shut up!
Cincinnati's a long way off.
We're getting further away from Kmart.
You don't have to go to Cincinnati to get underwear.
You have to go to Kmart. 400 Oak Street.
We're not going to Cincinnati. That's final.
I get my boxer shorts at Kmart.
- That is final! - I'm gonna be short-less.
Fuck!
What difference does it make where you buy underwear?
What difference does it make? Underwear is underwear!
It is underwear wherever you buy it!
In Cincinnati or wherever!
Kmart.
You know what I think Ray?
I think this autism is a bunch of shit!
'Cause you can't tell me you're not in there somewhere!
Boxer shorts.
Boxer shorts at Kmart.
These are... these are Hanes 32.
- You're driving me crazy. - Mine are boxer shorts.
We're gonna make a stop and find a psychiatrist.
You're driving me crazy.
Oak and Burnett... that's where the shorts are.
We have to buy them at Kmart Oak and Burnett.
We have to buy them back in...
'Course you're shorts are on the highway.
Let's go back to Cincinnati. Kmart.
Good luck trying to find a shrink in this town.
Hey you! Dipshit! Move it!
You ain't gonna move I'll move you.
Hey buddy! Hey you!
You're gonna get run over.
- You're going to get hurt. - It says "Don't walk."
- Do you hear me? - It says "Don't walk."
Move it.
It's all right. I'm sorry. He's from out of town.
Come on.
- It's all right. - We gotta get to Kmart.
- Come on. - Kmart. 400 Oak Street.
- It said "Don't walk." - It's broken.
It said "Don't walk."
Have to get to Kmart. 400 Oak and Burnett.
Oak and Burnett.
He said "Young man go west. Go west."
And this is the way our country developed
from the East Coast to the West Coast.
During that period of time there was initiated a...
what was known as a Pony Express.
I'm sure you've read about it in the history of the United States.
I may not have the days exactly right or the years
but I'm more or less familiar with the history of the United States.
And I love to tell...
He's artistic?
No. He's autistic.
I'm not familiar with that.
What is the exact nature of the problem?
He lives in a world of his own.
I'm sorry but what's wrong with him?
Do a little of "What's on First?" for her.
Who's on first. What's on second.
They set up a... initial program
where a Pony Express would ride for approximately 20 miles...
What am I supposed to do? There's gotta be something I can do.
I'm not a psychiatrist
but I do know that his brain doesn't work like other people.
What he does isn't intended to be annoying.
If he's getting on your nerves just take a break.
- Spend time away from him. - Sure I'll just send him back.
- Sorry? - Nothing it's an inside joke.
You're telling me I just have to deal with this?
I just gotta deal with this stuff?
Yeah that's about it.
Out of curiosity does he have any special abilities?
Well he's got a pretty good memory.
He counts toothpicks.
They spilled toothpicks on the floor.
He took one look and knew exactly how many there were.
He counted them in seconds.
Are you good with numbers?
I read about this. I want to try something.
- Kmart. 400 Oak Street. - What did I tell ya? After this.
- Ray can we try something? - Ok.
Do you know how much 312 times 123 is?
38 376\n38376.
- He's right. - What?
- He's right. - He's right?
How much is 4343 times 1234?
5 359 262\n5359262.
- He's a genius. - He's right.
He's a genius.
Ray do you know how much the square root of 2130 is?
46.15192304\n46.15192304.
- 2304. - That's amazing.
That is amazing. He should work for NASA or something like that.
If you had a dollar and you spent 50 cents
how much money would you have left?
About 70.
- 70 cents? - 70 cents.
- So much for the NASA idea. - We should go to Kmart.
- What did I tell ya? After this. - 400 Oak Street.
Do you know how much a candy bar costs?
- About $100. - $100 huh?
Know how much those new compact cars cost?
About $100.
In his particular case he's very high-functioning.
Most autistics can't speak or can't communicate.
Do you know what autistic is?
You know that word?
Are you autistic?
I don't think so.
No definitely not.
Lenny shut up. Let me see if I understand.
Very small here.
It's gonna cost me $10000 additional for each car?
- It's very crowded. - Ray please. Just one second.
They want to take out the manifold and carburetors
in order to put in a fuel injection system? Now?
That is nonsense. This is bullshit.
- What are you doing? - Too crowded for a backpack.
Leave this on.
It's gonna cost me $40000 just to meet EPA now.
What? No.
Give me the number and I'm gonna call the conversion shop myself.
That's my pen and that's definitely my book.
Taking your book is not serious injury.
Serious Injury book is red. That book is blue.
Forgive me I lost my secret decoder ring.
- You're already on number 18. - 1988. I know.
'Course that's my book. That's my pen.
It's 12 minutes till Wapner. It's definitely very small in here.
Small and safe.
- You don't want to miss the party. - "What you're witnessing is real."
There's a party in your honor Ray.
When we get to L.A. a little custody hearing.
You know why there's a party for you? Because you're the $3 Million Man.
- "What you are witnessing is real." - Ken Aldorf. Charlie Babbitt.
- Fart. - Yeah I'll hold.
Fart.
Did you fart Ray?
Did you fucking fart?
Man... how do you get this...
- How can you stand that? - I don't mind it.
How can you stand it?
- 10 minutes to Wapner now. - Ken how are you?
Definitely locked in this box with no TV.
It's definitely gonna start. The People's Court.
How could this be? How could this happen now?
People's Court starts on the... they start right on the button.
They definitely start on the button.
I got a problem. I'll call you from our next stop.
We're definitely not gonna make it for the program.
- We definitely have to go. - We're going. Just take it easy.
Eight minutes to Wapner.
Where am I going to find a television around here?
- Eight minutes to Wapner. - Eight minutes to Wapner?
Come on. Come on.
You wanna get in there and see the show?
Want to see the show? Then listen up.
Not another farmhouse in sight. This is it man.
You act weird we don't get in.
You listening to me? I want you to look normal.
As normal as possible all right?
Just put your hands down. Don't rock and moan.
- Four minutes to Wapner. - Shut up and stand there.
Don't rock and moan. Put your hands down.
Good afternoon ma'am.
I'm Donald Clemens from the A.C. Nielsen Company.
- You're familiar with our work? - You mean the TV ratings?
That's exactly it.
You've been selected as a preliminary candidate
to become our next Nielsen family in the area.
My husband's not home.
You'll share responsibility for shaping television programming
viewed by our entire nation
in return for which you'll receive a check
in the amount of $286 each month.
Who's he?
That would be my partner Mr. Bainbridge who does the...
Next. The People's Court.
- Oh boy! - That's it! You blew it.
You don't get to see your program.
- It's finished! - One minute to Wapner.
One minute to Wapner.
I had you in there! You were in there!
Defendants plaintiffs... you had it all!
They are in there making legal history Ray.
- Legal history! - Oh boy!
What is going on out here?
I'm sorry ma'am. I lied to you.
That man is my brother.
If he doesn't get to watch People's Court.
He's gonna throw a fit right on your porch.
You can help or you can stand there and watch it happen.
We like to watch cartoons. Think he'd settle for that?
...then she sees an identical twin.
True. He didn't have his shirt on. The other one did.
But they sure looK aliKe to me.
- Lf it got on his chest... - I want my daddy!
Daddy's not here right now darling.
I wanted to take it off quicKly because it got very cold.
I also confess I was afraid I might burn my hand if I' d taKen it...
Work with me on this one. Believe me I'm gonna take care of it.
I don't thinK she did anything negligent.
- You know that song? - My judgment is for the defendant.
We'll be bacK for the litigants' reactions
to Judge Wapner's decision right after these messages.
- My credit card's been rejected? - Yes sir.
- How much is this gonna cost? - $20 sir.
Thank you.
'Course I'm never going back. It's definitely going to be a long journey.
Just a couple of more days.
Then who's playing first? You mean the fella playing for St. Louis?
It's just another motel. You gotta do this every time?
That's the man's name. Whose name?
Why are you asking me? I'm not asking you. I'm telling you.
Who's on first. I'm asking you who's on first.
Yo Ray.
Ray this is not... it's not a riddle.
You know the fella's name? Then who's playing first?
You're never gonna figure out who's on first base
because Who is on first base.
That's the joke. It's comedy.
Sometimes his wife comes and collects it. Whose wife?
- It's comedy. - Every dollar of it.
You got a first baseman on first?
It's a routine between Abbott and Costello.
When you do it you're not funny.
You're the comedy team of Abbott and Abbott. Understand?
Sometimes his wife comes down and collects it.
Whose wife? Yeah.
Ray you are never going to solve it.
You know why? 'Cause it's not a riddle.
If you understood that if you understood that it's funny
you might get better.
All I'm trying to find out is what's the guy's name on first base?
What's the guy's name on first base?
No. What's the guy's name on second base.
Have you got a first baseman? Then who's playing first? Yeah.
Who's... you know the fellow's name?
Then who's playing first? The fella playing for St. Louis?
Who. The guy on first... the first baseman.
Who's on first. What are you asking me for?
Have you got a first baseman on first? Yeah.
All right Ray. Come on.
We're gonna put the bed by the window the way you like.
We got your apple juice.
We're gonna take the pens and paper put'em on the table...
- Did I forget something? - Cheese balls.
- Yes I forgot the cheese balls. - Definitely have cheese balls.
- But we got them. - I have to have 12 cheese balls.
I have to get my tartar control toothpaste.
I got that a couple of days ago.
Where's my tartar control toothpaste?
Remember when that doctor asked you those questions today?
- How did you do that? - I see it.
I see it.
What's that? Stop that for a second.
Just put that down. I'm trying to talk to you.
When I say stop why don't you stop?
Why do you always have to act like an idiot?
- You think that's funny? - Funny Rain Man. Funny teeth.
What did you say?
- Funny teeth. - Rinse.
Why did you say funny teeth?
You said funny teeth funny Rain Man.
Rain Man? I said Rain Man?
Yeah funny Rain Man.
Was I trying to say Raymond and it came out Rain Man?
You? You're the Rain Man?
Who took this picture?
D-A-D.
And you lived with us?
10961 Beechcrest Street Cincinnati Ohio.
When... when did you leave?
- January 21 1965. - You remember that?
It was Thursday. Very snowy out.
7.2 inches of snow that day.
- Just after mom died... New Year's. - Mom died january 5 1965.
And you remember the day that you left?
- After short and sudden illness. - You remember that day you left?
Was I there? Where was I?
You were in the window. You waved to me.
Bye-bye Rain Man. Bye-bye Rain Man.
So you were the one that sang to me?
What... what did you sing?
What was that song?
What did you sing?
Well she was just 17
And you know what I mean
And the way she looked was way beyond compare
So how could I dance with another
When I saw her standing there?
Did I like it when you sang to me?
Did we sing any other songs like the Beatles?
Scary! Scary bad!
Scary bad!
It's scary!
What... what's scary bad?
Hot water burn baby!
- Water! - Hot water burn baby?
What baby? Me? Me?
Easy. Easy.
Hot water burn baby.
I'm not burned. Look at me. Please.
- Hot water burn baby! - Please! I'm not burned.
Tub burn baby.
- I'm not burned man. - Tub burn baby.
I'm not burned.
I'm not burned. It's okay.
It's okay.
Gotta go to Wallbrook now.
That's why they put you away.
They thought you'd hurt me.
Never hurt Charlie Babbitt.
What?
What Ray?
Never hurt Charlie Babbitt.
What?
Come on it's 11:00 Ray. Lights out.
Never hurt Charlie Babbitt.
Never never hurt Charlie Babbitt.
Right where you like it at the end of the bed.
Come on Ray.
Hi it's me.
Well you didn't hang up. Does that mean we're engaged?
Listen I...
I just wanna hear it's not over. I mean...
I'm scared it's over.
Don't ask me tonight. Charlie.
I don't Know what to say. Let it sit.
That's something I'm not real good at.
There's lots of things you're not good at.
I'll call you when I get back okay?
- I'll see you. - Ciao.
What are you looking at that for?
I spent a couple of hundred on a TV and now you're watching a dryer.
I don't know.
At the shrink hearing we're gonna have to prove
you prefer to watch this little TV as opposed to the clothes dryer.
You understand that? You listening to me?
Turn this off when you're not watching it.
You run down the batteries where you gonna be when Wapner's on?
Yeah the red one always falls the same.
Why aren't you listening to me? You just don't want to listen to me.
You want to go back to Wallbrook is that it?
I gotta make a phone call.
Lenny it's me.
Where have you been? I' ve been sitting by this phone for three hours.
I had things to do. I had to buy clothes.
Clothes? We are in serious trouble. What are you doing buying clothes?
Just take it easy.
I'm in Tucumcari. I'll be there in...
They repossessed the cars to pay off the loan.
The cars are gone. Charlie. Gone.
Bateman wants his down payment bacK. They all do.
That's 80 thou. Charlie.
80000. I don't have it.
You gotta pay these people bacK.
Or it's all over... we're out of business.
Wha. T a. G g t t t
I don't know.
Son of a bitch!
This would be a lot easier if you'd let me put the top up.
We wouldn't have to fry.
Put this lotion on so you don't burn.
Don't start. You want the top up?
- I definitely like the top down. - I know. I don't want you to burn.
Definitely like it when the top's...
It's all right. Just take it easy. It's almost over.
- All right how's that feel? - Very slippery.
Maldonado swings and hits a hot shot through the box
into center field for a base hit.
One run is in. Here's Brenly going to third.
The throw by Davis... Not in time!
Brenly in safely at third base on Maldonado's single.
He held that ball out in center field a little too long. Don't you thinK?
TaKe a looK at it once again.
Treadwell played it way over towards the right side.
Shading him to pull...
Here's Davis.
Yeah. He seems to hold it there just a bit.
Double-pumped. Didn't he? Watch it on the replay.
He loses all chance at a play on Brenly.
Though Brenly doesn't exactly picK'em up and lay'em down.
And the throw into third base finally is a little bit long...
Will you give me a break with this?
Can't.
Ray stop it.
J-7\nJ-7.
K-7? What's that?
What's j-7?
What's j-7? The song's j-7?
Look out there.
No Raymond out here.
"18 Wheels and a Dozen Roses."
What's the number?
E-5\nE-5.
"Cheating Heart" Hank Williams.
"Your Cheating Heart." 'Course that's Hank Williams jr.
D-1 D-1\nD-1. D-1.
"Blue Moon of Kentucky" Bill Monroe.
And the Bluegrass Boys. T-5.
How many toothpicks came out of that box?
246.
You paying attention?
You watching that?
- You seeing that Ray? - Yeah falling on the ground.
Okay. Now what... what do I have left?
Two jacks one 8 one king one 6
two aces one 10 one 9 one 5.
One 5.
You are beautiful man.
- I'm an excellent driver. - You can't drive now.
Are you listening? This is important.
When there's lots of 10s and picture cards left it's good for us.
- Say it... 10s are good. - 10s are good.
And you're going to bet one...
One if it's bad two if it's good.
That's right. Two if it's good Ray.
Now listen casinos have house rules.
The first one is they don't like to lose.
So you never never show that you are counting cards.
That is the cardinal sin Ray.
Are you listening? That's very important.
Yeah. Counting... counting is bad.
Yes counting is bad.
I like to drive slow on the driveway.
You get this right Ray
you can drive wherever you want as slow as you like.
I'm an excellent driver.
Miss Sue Morgan. Please picK up the hotel courtesy phone.
Rain Man let's play some cards.
- You want a hit? - No. You've got 18.
- I want a hit. - Sir you have 18.
- You don't. Hit me. - I definitely want to hit.
- Hitting 18. - He doesn't want to hit.
- Hit me. - Don't!
You took my queen. I've got a 10 I needed that.
- I can't take your queen! - Please don't touch the cards.
- I need my own queen. - There's lots of them.
- There's lots of them? - Lots and lots of them.
Hold on here for a second.
I'm gonna double down.
Queen queen.
Yes sir. You gotta love this town.
I'm going for it Nick.
It looks like it. It certainly looks like it.
Wanna bet one chip or two chips?
Bet two.
What's your secret guys?
We cheat.
This is Sam. Tape table 47.
About 85000.
85000? Did you call the Eye in the Sky?
- Sam did. - I'll take over from here.
- You win again. - All right!
You're doing well. I'm happy for you sir.
What do you see?
Well he's not catching the hole card.
I don't see him using a computer.
He's not but something's not right.
No one in the world can count into a six-deck shoe.
Hold it. Hold it here.
Watch my chips. I'm gonna be back in second.
Go right ahead sir.
We're in the middle of a hand.
You don't leave in the middle of a hand.
We are hot. The Babbitt brothers are kicking ass in Vegas.
Wheel of fortune.
We got Cleopatra and Caesar waiting for you.
"Look at all this glamorous merchandise."
One for bad two for good.
- Twenty. - Twenty?
- It's going to hit on 20? - Yeah definitely 20.
$3000 on 20.
- Definitely 20. - Definitely 20?
It's not your game Ray.
I just lost $3000.
That's $3000 I lost.
Come on a little Black...
No? Easy don't start banging yourself all right?
Maybe we'll play later.
- I'm gonna cash in. - Yeah cash in.
You make me sad Ray.
Twenty.
We won $86000 and some change right?
- $86 500 - $80 000\n- $86500. - $80000.
Refund on the car payments
and I owe...
What did I say I owe to get the Rolex back?
$3500. Six months to pay.
We don't have to pay for the room... that's comped.
I'm free and clear. I'm gonna go take a celebration piss.
Don't go anywhere. Until I get back the sign says "Don't walk."
- Don't walk. - Don't walk.
You looking for a date?
- Are you? - I don't know.
- What's your name? - Raymond.
My name is Iris.
Raymond you like me?
- I don't know. - You don't know?
I think if you gave me a chance you would.
Why don't we try to get to know each other?
Yeah get to know each other.
He doesn't have any money honey.
That's all right sugar 'cause we are just talking.
Yeah we're just talking.
Let's go upstairs. What are you doing?
Getting to know each other. Just talking.
- What room? I'll bring him up. - That's all right.
You want to stay here and get to know each other?
Yeah. Get to know each other. Just talking.
This will be interesting. I'll be over here just in case.
He doesn't seem to like me. Who is he?
My brother. I'm living in his room.
He seems young to be your brother.
He was born August 12 1962.
It was a Sunday.
What exactly do you guys do here?
- We're counting cards. - You're counting cards?
We're counting cards.
- We're counting cards. - What else do you do?
I know you're counting cards. What else do you do?
Are you taking any prescription medication?
Look I'm out of here.
'Course what time is the date?
- Later. - What time is the date?
- 10:00. -'Cause lights out at 11:00.
10:00 daylight-savings time.
10:00? You like her? You think she's pretty?
Yeah. She's very sparkly.
Definitely very sparkly.
Very sparkly.
He did a great job on that suit. You don't realize how good you look.
- Do you like it? - It's not Kmart.
How could you not like that suit? You look fantastic Ray.
- How can you not like it? - It's not a Kmart suit.
I'm gonna let you in on a little secret. Kmart sucks. Okay?
Here you go.
It's the high rollers' suite.
This is for you.
Ever seen a room like this before?
What's up there? What's up there?
You're not even looking.
- Yeah. Bed. - That's your bed.
I had them put it by the window just the way you like it.
- Bed by the window. - Right. Go on up.
Just the way you like it isn't it?
Look at you with all those lights.
Mr. Vegas. You are Mr. Las Vegas now man.
What do you think?
There's a lot of lights. Very sparkly. Very twinkly.
We made a lot of money today. We made a lot of money!
Forgetting the $3000 we tossed away at that wheel of fortune.
Yeah wheel of fortune.
I'm sorry about that. I got a little carried away.
I got a little hot okay?
I'm saying I'm sorry. I just want you to know I am sorry.
I'm apologizing.
I got a little carried away. The money... I got a little greedy.
Want to say something?
I have to be at the bar at 10:00 with Iris.
'Cause I've got to thank you man.
You...
You did it. You did it. I was just there.
You saved my ass.
I was just along for the ride.
Have to be at the bar at 10:00. Have to go to the date with Iris.
Yeah Iris... that's her name.
Big date. Going to go dancing.
Dancing.
Have to go to the date with Iris dancing.
- Know how to dance? - I don't know.
You don't know how? You ought to learn sometime.
Have to learn to dance with a date.
I was just kidding. You're not gonna have to dance on this date.
Have to go to the date. Learn to dance.
Definitely. Now.
You don't have to dance now but I'll teach you sometime.
Definitely have to.
You're not gonna have to dance.
Definitely have to learn to dance for the date.
Sorry I even brought this up. All right Ray. My mistake.
10:00.
You got the only famous dancing hooker in Vegas.
Stand over there.
Come over here.
Now you hear the music?
Just watch my feet.
Raymond watch my feet.
Just do what I'm doing.
Feel the rhythm of the music? We're just moving our feet like that.
Now you're the guy so you're gonna have to lead.
And I'm the date so you want to...
You want to...
Put your left hand up like this.
Don't stop moving. You paying attention?
Don't stop moving. Put your left hand up like this.
Left hand up. That's good.
Don't stop. Just keep moving.
Good. Just like that.
Take this other hand put it around behind my back.
Want to learn how to dance?
You gotta touch someone when you dance.
I'm not going to hurt you all right?
Just put it right there.
I take my hand and put it up here.
Watch my feet Ray. Watch my feet.
The rhythm the rhythm.
All right?
You can't watch my feet the whole time so you're gonna have to look up.
When I tell you to just look up real slow.
Just keep moving.
Okay you ready? Start looking up.
A little more. Keep moving.
Just a little more.
A little more.
All the way up.
There you go Ray. You're dancing. This is it.
Yeah dancing.
You want to close your hand here.
You wanna pull like that.
You're gonna turn me like this okay?
Just turn. That's good.
- This is dancing. - This is dancing.
Don't know about you but I'm feeling a little silly.
That's it.
All right! All right!
Beautiful! You are a good dancer!
You wanna give me a hug?
I just wanted to give you a hug Ray.
Just felt like giving you a hug.
What are you doing here?
- I'm unemployed. - What do you mean?
You don't know about the business?
I know about the business. Come on in. It's okay.
I'm uh glad to see you.
Ray look who's here.
It's not right what you're doing to Raymond.
He's fine.
I know he's fine...
he's in Las Vegas in a suit in a big room.
It makes me sad.
Six minutes to my date.
Six minutes to Iris.
He has a date?
Raymond it'd be nice if you didn't carry that television everywhere.
What do you gotta bring a Watchman for on your date?
The man's dancing.
But what does your date look like?
She's very sparkly. She looks like a holiday.
I don't think I've heard that one before.
Mr. Kelso would like to see you.
I don't know Mr. Kelso.
He's director of security. Would you come with me please?
Sure. Susanna why don't you stay with Raymond?
Right this way sir.
10:01. She's not here.
She'll come. She will.
Congratulations Mr. Babbitt.
Counting into a six-deck shoe is quite a feat.
I'm afraid I don't understand what you're talking about.
We make videotapes Mr. Babbitt and we analyze the tapes
and we even share some of the information with the other casinos.
These tapes suggest that you should take your winnings and leave the state.
Someone has a good day at the tables
and you accuse them of illegal activities?
Is this how you treat all your guests?
All you have to do is close your mouth and go home.
Those are the best odds you're gonna see for a while.
I'd take'em.
Did you want to dance on your date?
There'll be other chances.
Many pretty girls would love to dance with you.
It's gonna be okay.
- I like this music Ray. - Elevator stopped.
It's okay.
Think you could show me the way you were going to dance with Iris?
Yes?
Would you like to dance with me?
- Elevator's on hold. - It's okay. Give me this.
Show me. Show me how.
Yeah. Charlie Babbitt taught me.
Dancing in the elevator.
It's nice.
You're very good.
Iris missed a beautiful dance.
- And a kiss. - Yeah and a kiss.
- Have you ever kissed a girl? - I don't know.
You don't know?
Open your mouth. Open.
Like this.
Like you are tasting something very good...
and very soft.
Like this.
Close your eyes.
It's okay Ray.
How was that?
Wet.
Then we did it right.
Elevator's definitely stuck.
No it's not stuck.
Here.
Fred Astaire and Ginger Rogers.
- Like us. - Yeah like us.
What did I tell you?
I promised you you could drive this is it.
At Wallbrook I drive slow on the driveway.
- This is okay? He can drive? - I'm an excellent driver.
He's very good in the driveway.
Ray get in the front seat.
I'll wait to hear from you after Raymond's meeting?
Don't worry. It's gonna be fine.
- I'm nervous. - I know.
Listen I'm glad... happy that you came to Vegas.
I know.
Ciao.
Ray thank you for the date in the elevator.
It was really nice.
Ciao.
- Thank you for the what? - Nothing. Something between us.
Between us?
Us.
Us Ray?
Here we go Ray. This is your bedroom up here.
'Course there's no bed there. Definitely no bed there.
This is a magic bed Ray.
Just watch and see.
We got the table over here. We got the television.
Went to the video store I got a little surprise for you.
I picked up a video for you.
- Don't start. - I'm not asking I'm telling you.
It's not just another place. This is... this is my place.
That's the man's name. That's whose name? Yes.
Who? The first baseman. Who's on first.
You got a first baseman? Who's playing first? Absolutely.
When you pay the first baseman. Who gets the money?
Every dollar of it. Why not? The man's entitled to it.
- Who is? - Yes.
- So who gets it? - Why shouldn't he?
Sometimes his wife comes and collects it.
- Whose wife? - Yes.
After all. The man earns it.
- Who does? - Absolutely.
All I' m tryin' to find out is what's the guy's name on first base?
No. What is on second base.
- Don't you think this is funny? - Yeah this is funny.
- I' m not changing nobody. - Where'd you see this first?
Dad gave me a book of baseball trivia.
- I' m not asKing who's on second. - Guess it didn't read as funny.
- Definitely not. - We're not talKing about him.
Hello. This is Dr. Bruner. I'd liKe you to call me...
- Yeah what is it? - Oh. I thought I got the machine.
I just got into town. And. As you Know.
The psychological interview is tomorrow.
Yes sir I know that.
I thought we should get together and talK.
I thinK it might be in your best interest to meet me.
When?
I'm at the Bonaventure. How about tonight at 8.30?
Tomorrow you'll meet Dr. Marston
who's in charge of Raymond's psychiatric evaluation.
I gave him boxes of files on Raymond. Boxes.
Well good luck.
This isn't a close call son. It's a formality.
Your brother's a very disabled individual.
You telling me Marston will rule against me?
No I'm telling you it's always been a lost cause.
Then what is this about? Why'd you call me?
Your father put me in charge of all the money.
It doesn't matter whether or not you win custody of Raymond.
I won't have to pay you a dime.
It's at my discretion not the court's.
What so you can't lose?
I can lose. I can lose Raymond.
I care about your brother's life and the treatment he receives.
I made a commitment to your father 20 years ago
and I'm not willing to gamble with that.
What is this?
It's a very big check.
$250000.
And no strings attached. You just walk away Charlie.
This isn't about you and me.
It's not about winning or losing.
I asked you a week ago
why didn't anyone ever tell me I had a brother.
You didn't have an answer.
I don't know.
It's funny I just realized
I'm not pissed off anymore my father cut me out of his will.
You were his friend you probably knew he tried
to contact me a few times over the years.
I never called him back. I was a prick.
If he was my son didn't return my calls
I'd have written him out. Fuck him.
But it's not about the money anymore.
It's about... I just don't understand.
Why didn't he tell me I had a brother?
Why didn't you tell me I had a brother?
Why didn't anyone ever tell me that I had a brother?
I mean...
It'd have been nice to know him for more than just the past... six days.
Come on.
It stopped. It's all right.
V-E-R-N\nV-E-R-N.
Vern. Vern.
Main man. My main man Vern.
V-E-R-N\nV-E-R-N.
My main man Vern.
They got raspberry strawberry blueberry
Pink Caddie whole-wheat Peachy Keen beer nut
Rocky Road buckwheat Belly Buster blueberry.
What kind of pancakes you want?
- Pancakes. - What kind?
- Pancakes. - Of course.
Maple syrup supposed to be on the table before the pancakes.
Charlie Babbitt made a joke.
I made a joke Ray.
Step back a little bit Ray.
Hello?
Why don't you go sit down over there?
This is not a legal proceeding
so there's no lawyers no judge present
just the people who care about Raymond.
Raymond why don't you have a seat over there.
Mr. Babbitt why don't you go to that side of the table.
Raymond right here. Have a seat.
Raymond right here. Take this seat.
Ray put your knapsack on the floor.
This is a good opportunity to be honest with one another...
Ray the TV. On the floor.
I'm sorry.
I don't know any easy way to say this Mr. Babbitt...
Say what? Have I lost already?
No you haven't. I'm not the judge and jury.
I'm a doctor making a recommendation to a court.
I must tell you that Dr. Bruner is a very respected professional.
Raymond's case has been meticulously documented
and Wallbrook is one of the finest institutions in this country.
You've made up your mind. I'll see you in court.
No one's your enemy.
My brother came further with me in a week
than he did with you in 20 years.
I don't think it's necessary to challenge Dr. Bruner.
I'm sorry.
Exactly what happened this past week Raymond?
- Well we got... - I was asking Raymond.
Raymond what happened this past week?
- What did you do? - Counted cards.
Counted cards in Las Vegas.
- Your brother took you to Las Vegas? - $3000 on the wheel of fortune.
He gave you $3000 to gamble with?
Lost $3000 on pitiful 20.
- What else did you do? - Bet on number 20.
- What else did you do? - Danced with Charlie Babbitt.
- Danced with your brother? - He wanted to learn...
Danced with Susanna.
- Kissed Susanna. - Kissed Susanna?
Yeah. In the elevator.
Did you enjoy kissing a woman?
I don't know.
How did it feel?
It felt wet.
Wet?
Quite a trip.
- You enjoy being on the road? - I'm an excellent driver.
You drove?
Your brother let you drive on the highway?
- Slow on the driveway. - He didn't drive on the highway.
- Did he have any emotional outbursts? - What do you mean?
Things they tend to do.
Inflicting bodily harm on themselves...
- Okay a couple of times. - A couple of times?
Okay he had what you call an outburst at the airport
because he didn't want to fly so we didn't fly.
When was the last outburst he had?
- This morning. - This morning?
This is bullshit.
I could tell you anything I could tell you nothing
and you'd never know.
The smoke alarm went off.
He got a little nervous but he's fine.
Don't feel as though I'm placing any blame.
We went out for pancakes. Look at him... he's fine.
You don't have to be defensive.
- I'm being honest. - You're missing the point.
You're missing the point. I'm being truthful.
The point is I'm not placing any blame...
I had a father I hardly knew a mother I didn't know at all
I find out I have a brother and I'm supposed to give him up?
No one is saying anything.
I didn't hurt him he's not hurting me
we're not hurting you so why are you interfering with my family?
- Do you understand? - I understand that.
You do have a brother
but he's not capable of having a relationship with you.
That's your opinion.
Did you spend 24 hours a day seven days a week with him?
You cannot take on this responsibility without professional guidance.
- That's your opinion. - Yes it's my opinion.
There's a couple of things I'd like to go over.
Dr. Bruner states that you stole Raymond out of the institution
and you're willing to trade him for $1.5 million. Is that correct?
My father died. I was upset. Okay? That was wrong.
So last week you were upset and this week you suddenly
found some devotion to your brother
and you want to take care of him the rest of your life?
So in the beginning it was like a kidnapping.
Kidnapping... that's very strong. I didn't kidnap my brother.
But in the course of the week
you came to have an understanding with him.
Yes.
- That... - Yes?
Lunderstand that this sounds irrational to you.
Yes when it started out it had...
Don't feel compelled to be defensive.
- Can I talk? - Yes you can.
I'd like to talk. Thank you.
There's no accusations.
Go ahead.
There's no accusations?
You have to understand that when we started out together
that he was only my brother...
in name.
And then...
Then this morning we had pancakes.
Maple syrup. Maple syrup on the...
Maple syrup on the table.
And Charlie Babbitt made a joke.
You see we...
I made a connection.
I think that's very admirable
but the purpose of this meeting is to determine
what is best for Raymond.
Whether or not he's capable of functioning in the community
and what in fact he wants... if that's possible to determine.
I'm all for that.
Raymond's unable to make those kind of decisions.
You're wrong.
He can't decide for himself.
He's capable of a lot more than you know.
Why don't we ask Raymond. Maybe we can find a few answers.
Raymond can I ask you a few questions?
The doctor's talking to you.
Can I ask you a few questions?
Do you want to stay with Charlie?
Would you like to stay with your brother in Los Angeles?
Ray the doctor's asking you a question
so you listen okay Ray?
Do you want to stay with your brother Charlie?
You do? You want to stay with your brother?
Stay with my brother Charlie Babbitt.
That's what you want?
You want to stay with your brother?
Can I ask you something else?
Do you want to go back to Wallbrook?
Can you make a distinction between your brother and Wallbrook?
Do you want to stay with your brother Charlie here in Los Angeles?
Or go back to Wallbrook?
Two separate things... stay with your brother or go back to Wallbrook.
It's not one thing.
This is your brother. Make a choice.
Back to Wallbrook stay with Charlie.
Can you make that choice?
One or the other.
- All right. - Stay back at Wallbrook.
Hold on. Just hold on!
Stay back at Wallbrook.
All right. You made your point.
Okay? You don't have to humiliate him.
Ray it's okay. It's over.
Stay back at Wallbrook with Charlie Babbitt.
- Stay back at Wallbrook. - It's over.
Dr. Bruner can I talk to you a minute?
Excuse me.
You okay Ray?
You don't want any more questions do you?
I don't know.
No more questions.
Don't worry. There's not gonna be any more questions okay?
No more questions. I'll make sure of that.
Yeah. Main man.
- What? - My main man.
Listen...
I don't know if I'm gonna have a chance to talk to you again.
Because you see these...
Dr. Bruner really likes you
and he's probably gonna want to take you back with him.
You know?
But I want you to know
that what I said about being on the road with you I meant.
Connecting.
I like having you for my brother.
I'm an excellent driver.
Yes you are.
I like having you for my big brother.
C-H-A-R-L-l-E.
Main man.
May I have your attention. Please.
AmtraK train number 36. The Desert Wind eastbound.
Now boarding. TracK number three.
Fullerton. San Bernardino. Barstow. Las Vegas.
Salt laKe City. Denver. Omaha. Chicago.
And other points between.
TicKeted passengers only may board the train.
Hello Charlie.
Hello Raymond.
Wouldn't you feel a little more relaxed in your Kmart clothes?
- Tell him Ray. - Kmart sucks.
I see.
I have the tickets and I'll be on this car here to the right.
Why don't you take a couple of minutes.
See you Charlie.
You made a joke Ray.
I guess I better give this to you.
You're gonna have to carry this now it's...
It's got your cheese balls your apple juice
notebooks pens and...
"Who's on First?" video that you like.
"Who's on First?" Very funny.
I told you it's funny.
Board!
- Better get going. - Yeah. Very shiny train.
Yeah it sure is.
Listen Ray Dr. Bruner only has custody of you.
That doesn't mean I can't visit.
Now I'm coming to see you in two weeks.
How many days is that before we're together?
14 days from today. Today's Wednesday.
- Hours? - 336 hours.
Mystifying.
'Course that's 20160 minutes.
1209600...
600 seconds.
I'll see you soon.
Yeah. One for bad two for good.
Bet two for good.
'Course three minutes to Wapner.
You'll make it.
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：1610169789