更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
Nica?
- Nica. There's somebody at the door. - I'm busy.
Nica, please.
God!
What are you doing that's so important?
I was playing solitaire.
The computer cheats, you know.
Yeah, well, I'm used to that.
- Morning. - Hi.
Got a delivery for Mrs. Sarah Pierce?
- I'll sign for it. - Cool.
You know, you don't look like a Mrs.
Oh I'm...
I'm not. It's for my mother.
Oh, God. I'm back living with my mother, too.
It's just a fucking nightmare, right?
You have no idea.
Wait a minute. Oh, my God.
- I know you. - You do?
Yeah, yeah. It was City College.
The Psych Department, right?
That was me.
Well, when'd you graduate?
I didn't. I never completed my thesis.
On what?
Completion anxiety.
Thought only guys got that.
So, is your mom home now or what?
Yeah.
Too bad.
Well, see you around.
Bye.
- Was that guy hitting on me? - Baby, you're beautiful.
Thank you. But I think that guy was hitting on me.
- Maybe I should go ask him out. - Nica.
He was just being nice.
I'm sorry.
Honey, I just don't ever want to see you get hurt.
I thought you swore off the Home Shopping Network.
I haven't bought anything in three weeks.
Maybe you have a secret admirer.
- You sound threatened. - No. Not at all.
I just wouldn't want to see you get hurt.
Who's it from?
It doesn't say.
Must be some kind of joke.
- I don't get it. - Neither do I.
He's cute.
If you say so.
I'm Chucky. Wanna play?
Alice will love him.
I DVR'd Real Housewives.
I'm going to make tuna melts later. Okay?
Mom?
Oh, God.
Mom! No.
I need an ambulance right away. It's my mother.
I don't know. I don't know. There's so much blood.
Nica.
I'm sorry.
She was fine.
She was taking her meds, she was painting again.
- No. No. - She was fine.
How could she do that, Barbie?
How could she do that to herself?
You remember Father Frank.
Yes. Hello, Father.
I'm so very sorry for your loss, Nica.
Thank you.
Your sister just thought it might be a good idea for me to come.
I appreciate it.
But you know my mother and I both left the church a long time ago.
But not in the eyes of God.
I just thought it might be nice for us to have someone to talk to.
We have each other.
Nica.
We have to pray for her. To be forgiven.
She was sick. You can't judge her.
No one is judging her.
In fact, the church's official response to a situation like this
is not to judge, but to pity.
My mother and I have had quite enough pity, thank you.
I understand.
It was my fault.
I should have seen it coming.
Nica, you cannot blame yourself.
She was supposed to be taking care of you.
- Hey. - Hey, Ian.
Gimme a hug.
- Is that a new chair? - Yeah.
- It's cool. - Thank you.
This is Jill, my new au pair.
- No, I'm just the nanny. - Hi.
I'm so sorry, Nica.
Thank you. I'm glad you're here.
Come here, you.
- I'm so happy to see you. - Me, too.
Did Grandma go to heaven?
Yes, sweetie, she did.
Hey, I have a surprise for you.
That's funny.
Mommy, I have to go to the bathroom.
Okay. Jill will take you.
You show her the way. Mommy needs to talk to Aunty Nica.
Jill, let's go.
I think I'm going to go with them. Okay?
Remember, you don't have to lock the door.
- But somebody might come in. - We won't let anybody in.
But what about you guys?
Honey, we really don't want to see you do your business.
Okay, bye.
So listen, how much is she paying you again?
$400 a week.
That's more than I make.
Well, maybe you should consider a career change.
Hey, I'd be a great nanny. $400 a week!
- Man. - Yeah, but no benefits.
What's your name?
Alice? Alice, open the door, honey!
Alice? Alice, open the door right now.
He scared me half to death.
What is this?
Well, Mom left the house to both of us.
- So? - So.
I think we should consider selling.
What are you talking about?
Nica, this place is fabulous.
It's so much closer to us,
we'd get to see you way more often.
And with your half of what we could get for the house,
you'd be set for the rest of your life.
This isn't about me. This is about money.
Well, you know we've been struggling.
Print media is dead.
Ian's working at Starbucks.
We're going to have to send Alice to public school.
And she so had her heart set on St. Bridget's.
I don't want to deprive my child.
You have a live-in nanny.
Well, actually, that's not really working out.
Barb, this is my home.
Nica, I know this is hard.
But do you really think you can manage here all by yourself?
Mom would have wanted you to be taken care of.
That's all she ever wanted.
We're back.
- You found him. - He was in the bathroom.
Really?
You know, I think Grandma would have wanted you to take care of him.
It was obviously sent here by mistake.
It must belong to someone else.
And Alice, you already have too many dolls as it is.
Yeah, but Chucky's my friend till the end!
I actually think it's a really nice gesture.
Thank you, Aunty Nica.
It's a doll.
What's the worst that can happen, huh?
I like to be hugged.
I like to hug you, too, Chucky.
What's that, Chucky?
Chucky wants to know what's for dinner.
I guess I better get started in the kitchen.
Don't be silly.
You guys are my guests and you must be exhausted from your flight,
please just make yourselves at home.
Father Frank, you will stay for dinner, won't you?
Well, I'd love to, Nica. Thanks.
You're going to make dinner. For six.
Seven.
Well, I will need a chef's assistant.
And Chucky can be my assistant.
Great. Let's get cooking.
- It's really good. - It's the oregano.
- Did you finish setting the table? - Almost.
- Pay the toll. - We're on a roll.
No, honey, don't touch that. Can you grab me the napkins?
The fancy ones from last Christmas.
This smells delicious.
- Thanks. - Come on, Chucky.
Look at this, Nica.
You've really outdone yourself this time.
We are going to sit right here.
- Barb, sit next to me here. - Okay. If you insist.
- Look at this. - Thanks, Jill. Make yourself comfortable.
You brought out the nice china.
Father, would you like to say grace?
Bless us, oh Lord, and these Thy gifts
which we are about to receive from Thy bounty.
- Stop. - Through Jesus Christ our Lord we pray.
Amen.
- Jill? - Thank you, Ian.
- Don't mind if I do. - How about you, Father?
No. I'm good.
I am starving.
Wait.
Your daddy would like to make a toast.
To the chef.
Thank you. I had a great assistant.
- I love chili. - Do you really?
- Yeah. - Me, too. Love it.
- Is there meat in this? - No. Not at all.
It's vegetarian.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God. - What?
This is amazing!
I know. I can't believe there's no meat in this.
It's so hearty.
It's the oregano.
This is just the way my mama used to make it.
Nica, could you pass me the salt?
Thank you.
You know, that doll, it looks really familiar somehow.
Father, come on.
Good Guy dolls were all the rage back in the 80s.
- My brother even had one. - So did mine.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
Oh, come on.
I seem to remember seeing them on the news?
I remember seeing people standing in line overnight
just to get their hands on one of these.
They were right up there with Smurfs and Cabbage Patch Kids.
- Alice, honey, is something wrong? - It tastes funny.
Maybe we put too much oregano in.
Alice, sweetheart, it's not that bad.
Eat it.
Father, are you all right?
I'm so sorry, I'm going to have to be going.
- Oh, my God, Father, are you ill? - Oh, no, I'm fine.
I have an appointment back at the church.
Nica, thank you so much, the chili was delicious.
- Father, are you? - No, please forgive me.
I don't mean to be rude.
I'll see you all in the morning at the cemetery.
Good night.
I'm so sorry.
- Where is he? - This way.
- What happened? - Lost control, hit them head on.
Probably drunk.
No, no, this isn't right. I know him, I'm in his parish.
- He doesn't drink anymore. - You sure about that?
He's my sponsor.
Stanton, you're going to need a drink after you see this.
Jesus Christ.
Steel's got him pinned. He's lost a shitload of blood,
but we just can't tell from where.
Father, can you hear me? Father?
Just hang on! We're going to get you out.
What the hell are you waiting for? Get this shit off him!
I can't make that call.
He's bleeding to death! Get him out!
- Okay, set in. - On my count.
One, two, pull.
This is an oldie.
Oh, my God. Is that you?
- Shut up. - You're so cute.
It's called baby fat.
Look, I didn't say anything.
- Go back to sleep. - Will do.
Look at her.
She's so happy.
What happened to your dad?
He drowned that year,
couple of weeks before Nica was born.
Mom was never the same after that.
Who's that?
Some neighbor back in Chicago, I guess.
What a weirdo.
- Hey there, missy, what'cha up to? - Chucky's gone.
- Not again. - Well, where did you leave him?
I didn't. He's hiding.
Okay, time for bed.
And don't forget to brush your teeth and your hair.
- What about Chucky? - Jill will go look for Chucky.
- I'll give you a hand, Jill. - We're not done here yet.
I think he's hiding under my bed.
Don't worry, we'll find him.
I'm going to be right back.
Are you sure you didn't leave him downstairs?
I didn't leave him anywhere. He's hiding.
There he goes!
I am not in the mood for this.
- Need a hand? - I need a fucking search party!
I have looked over every inch of this house
and I can't find him anywhere.
- God, I've missed you. - Shut up.
You found him.
I think she wanted you to find him.
You know, I haven't been spending enough time with her.
It's like if I'm not working, I'm just so tired all the time.
Life is short!
- Did they always say that? - I don't know.
Listen, little man, what else are you,
telling my kid behind my back, huh?
I like to be hugged.
- And? - Wanna play?
- Is that it? - Hi. I'm Chucky.
And I'm your friend till the end.
That one's a classic.
And it works on so many different levels.
Yeah, the 80s were awesome.
Did you find him yet?
Yeah, we found him!
I'll take him up.
Ian?
Anyone?
Hello?
Oh, shit.
Coming!
See, with her, it's always something.
She needs my help and then resents me for it.
You're the only one who really appreciates me.
You know, I was thinking.
We can get by without the money.
You don't have to sell.
I mean, this is her home.
She's a mess. You can see that.
Oh, crap.
There you are, Chucky!
We've been looking for you everywhere.
Hey, want to play?
I didn't know you could do that.
Playtime's over. It's time for bed.
Can you read us a bedtime story?
Aunty Nica's tired, sweetie. We'll let her rest now.
I'm fine.
It's important that you don't overextend yourself.
Don't you think I'm the best judge of when I'm overextending myself?
- Frankly, no. - Really.
I don't think you realize the strain you're under.
There's no shame in admitting that you need help.
You mean "assistance."
Nica, I am worried about your heart. Okay?
Dr. Masur said I was fine, Barb.
You're at significant risk of it happening again, you know that.
- 13% of all T5 paraplegics... - I know the statistics.
Dr. Masur said that extreme stress,
any kind of even mild shock could bring it on.
And since last night, God knows you've had plenty of both.
Alice, sweetheart, please come down from there.
I'm disabled, Barb, I am not a child.
And I'm perfectly capable of taking care of myself.
Aunty Nica, you're bleeding.
- Oh, my God. - I got it. Okay?
It almost looks like a knife wound.
You must have cut yourself making dinner.
- I didn't. - Doesn't it hurt?
No. No, don't worry, sweetie.
She can't feel a thing.
All right, come on. Come on. Off to bed now.
Good night, Aunty Nica.
Good night, baby. Sweet dreams.
Now I lay me down to sleep,
I pray the Lord my soul to keep.
If I shall die before I wake,
I pray the Lord my soul to take.
God bless Grandma, and Mommy, and Daddy, and Jill.
And especially Aunty Nica.
What about Chucky?
He says there is no God.
- Who said that? - Chucky did.
He said that life's a bitch and then you die,
bleeding like a stuck pig.
Alice. You know it's not nice to curse.
I don't curse, Mommy. Chucky did.
Mommy, am I going to die?
No. Of course not, sweetie.
Grandma died. And Chucky says we're all going to die.
Alice, who really told you that?
- Was it Jill? - No.
- Was it your daddy? - No, it was Chucky.
Okay.
Can't we sleep in with you tonight?
Alice, we've talked about this. You're a big girl now.
It's only a storm.
And Jill's going to be in in a while.
Don't forget Chucky!
Don't worry, Chucky. It's only a storm.
Ma'am, thank you for holding. The package...
Evidence depository.
I'm sorry, you're breaking up.
Did you say "evidence depository"?
Hello? Hello, are you there?
Chucky, I'm scared.
You fucking should be.
Sorry.
We found him.
- She sure loves that thing. - Yeah. She sure does.
But you know, I just called the delivery company,
and they said it was sent from an evidence depository.
As in crime scene evidence?
I don't know. Maybe I heard them wrong. The connection was bad.
I'm sure that's it.
Yeah, but we still don't know who sent it.
I don't care if it was the Manson Family.
Anything that keeps her this happy is fine by me.
She's been so sad lately.
I better get to bed. Long day tomorrow.
- Good night. - Good night, Jill.
Andy Barclay.
Charles.
She's up.
Women.
Can't live with 'em. Period.
Shit.
- What's going on? - Power's out again.
I'm going to go check on Alice.
What about Jill?
- What about her? - Well, come on, Barb.
You're paying her $400 a week to take care of our kid.
Don't you think she can handle it?
Ian, she's afraid of the dark.
It's storming out. She might need me.
Who, exactly, might need you?
Who do you think?
Right now I'm not sure what to think.
You know...
Don't try to implicate me in your sick fantasies, okay?
I've seen the way you look at her.
Ditto.
Ian, I am not sleeping with the nanny.
No, of course, you couldn't be that stupid, Barb.
Knowing that if I could prove such a thing,
I could easily take Alice away from you.
Or I could just check the footage.
What are you talking about?
The footage from the nanny cam.
- What nanny cam? - The one I hid in the doll today.
You are not taking my daughter away from me. Do you hear me?
I am not going to let you destroy this family
because of your sick, paranoid accusations.
That's right. Tune me out.
Let Barb take care of everything.
That's what you always do anyway, right?
You latte-making loser.
What's the word from Forensics?
Won't know anything for sure till they cook his blood.
Hey, you talk to anyone at St. Paul's yet?
Said he was out at the Pierce house all day.
Okay, well, maybe they'll have some answers for us.
I'm going to head out there now.
Alice?
Alice! I don't have time to play games.
Barb?
Barb!
- Barb, where's Alice? - Playing fucking hide and seek.
Barb, put him down.
What is wrong with you?
Look, I know that this sounds nuts, but that doll,
I think that there's something in it.
Wait a second. You know about this?
- Well, I think that I do. - You know what's in this?
Do you?
Why didn't you tell me?
- I'm trying to tell you. - Wait, wait. When did you find out?
- What does it matter? - It matters to me.
It matters to me that my own sister is out to get me.
No. No, no, no, you don't understand, this...
I understand perfectly.
I understand you resent the fact that I actually have a life.
No, Barb, this isn't about anything that...
Well, you know what, Nica?
It isn't my fault. Okay?
What happened to you isn't my fault.
And it isn't my fault that you dropped out of school,
and it isn't my fault that you chose to never leave this goddamned house.
I mean, what the hell were you waiting for, a sign from God?
No, Barb! Just put the fucking doll down!
Fuck you, Nica.
Barb!
Alice! Get down here!
Jill?
Ian!
Shit!
Alice?
Alice, don't touch anything. You hear me?
Alice, you are in big trouble, young lady!
Alice!
Alice, please.
Mommy is just about sick to death of all of you.
Alice?
Alice, you come out here right this minute.
Oh, my God.
Alice.
Alice is mine.
Now she knows
there is no God.
You have your mother's eyes.
And they were always too fucking close together!
No!
Barbie?
Nica.
I'm gonna get you.
Alice!
Ian! Ian!
Ian!
- Ian! Ian! - What?
- Ian, they're dead! - What are you talking about?
Barb, Jill, they're dead, and I can't find Alice!
- No! No! He's still out there! - Who?
Chucky!
Alice! Alice!
I gotta go find Alice.
- Ian! - What?
Ian, if you see Chucky,
whatever you do, just leave him alone.
Chuck... What are you talking about?
Just stay away from that doll!
Alice?
Ian?
Ian!
Alice?
No!
Nica!
Nica, what the hell are you doing?
He did it! It was him!
Nica! Look at me!
Give me the ax.
- What? No! - Now, give me the goddamn ax!
Oh, my God. Nica, what have you done?
Ian. Ian, please. You know I would never...
Oh, my God.
Ian. Ian. Take this.
I need you to inject it under my rib.
Ian.
Ian. Ian, what are you doing?
What the hell have you done with my daughter, Nica?
- Ian, where's Chucky? - You're sick!
Ian, I swear to God, I can prove it!
And so can I.
Hey, Barb, check this out.
RadioShack, 450 bucks.
Oh, and by the way, if you're watching this,
I put it on your MasterCard.
Where are you, Alice?
They'll never find me in here, Chucky.
This is the best game of hide and seek ever.
Just keep your fucking mouth shut.
Chucky, stop cursing.
Say hi to the little woman for me.
Maybe not.
Your turn.
My turn.
You're Charles Lee Ray.
My friends call me Chucky.
You're dead.
No, you are.
Why us?
Didn't your mother ever mention me?
I'm an old friend of the family.
Charles, come over here.
I wanna introduce you to someone.
October 27th.
Okay.
Right against my rib cage.
Soon enough. Cannot come soon enough.
Charles, this is Sarah.
- Hi. - How do you do?
- Her husband, Daniel. - Hello, sir.
Hi, Daniel. Nice to meet you.
And this is Barb.
She has her mother's eyes.
Such a nice, happy family.
But not for long.
You like 'em?
They're beautiful, thank you.
Difficult to find right now. They're not exactly in season.
Anyway, enjoy.
It's gettin' late,
and I'm gonna go pick up Barbie at day care.
No!
I mean, shouldn't we have some time alone together?
What about family time?
Later.
Right now I want to have you all to myself.
Sarah. Sarah, you've had me all day.
It isn't enough.
That's a selfish fucking attitude for a mother to take.
You don't wanna share me with her?
No. No.
Well, what's gonna happen when the baby comes?
Are you gonna keep her from me, too? Because...
that would be very hurtful to me.
And you wouldn't wanna see me get hurt, would you?
Would you?
- Would you? - No. No.
I don't wanna see you get hurt.
I don't wanna see anybody get hurt.
Okay.
I'm gonna go get Barbie.
No! Please, please! Please don't.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
You told them about us?
There is no us.
Why?
Why would you want to destroy this family?
You destroyed my family.
No.
I told you,
I've always had a thing for families.
No!
Especially kids.
You did this to me?
No, Nica, you did this to me.
You and your mommy.
She betrayed me.
Got me killed.
But I knew a way to come back.
Give me the power.
I beg of you!
Took me 25 years,
but believe me,
it was worth the wait.
25 years.
Since then, a lot of families have come and gone.
The Barclays, the Kincaids, the Tillys,
but Nica, your family was always my favorite.
And now, you're the last one standing.
So to speak.
You know, you remind me a lot of Andy Barclay.
He was a whiny little bitch, just like you.
Did you kill him, too?
More or less.
I killed his childhood.
And the truth is, I killed you 25 years ago.
Didn't I, Nica?
You haven't been living.
You can't call this living.
You've just been on life support.
Time to pull the fucking plug.
So you never actually killed Andy Barclay, did you?
What?
You know, it's called completion anxiety.
It's very common in males.
You are a male, aren't you?
I'm gonna kill you slow.
Yeah, no, I get that.
25 years. Must be the slowest murder in history.
I mean, what are you waiting for? A sign from God?
No!
You feel that, don't ya?
You wanna play, motherfucker? Let's play.
Police. Open up.
Help! Help me!
Based on the evidence,
the defendant is declared legally incompetent
and remanded indefinitely to a facility for the criminally insane.
I'm alive, you son of a bitch. You hear me?
I'm still alive!
Please leave a message.
Hey, it's me. I'm on my way.
And don't forget my money.
They never learn.
So who's next?
Next.
Good afternoon.
Three-day, two-day, or overnight?
Overnight. It's extremely urgent.
Fragile?
Surprisingly not.
Approximate value?
Well, my mother always used to say
you can't put a price on love.
Under 250, then.
Would you like to insure the package?
Oh, that won't be necessary.
It protects you and it protects the recipient.
I doubt that.
Perishable goods? Live animal?
Just put "other."
Grandma, I'm home.
Grandma?
And how are you today?
Oh, I'm fine. I'm fine.
- Feeling lucky? - Yeah.
Oh, that's great, Bunny.
As you know, Bunny has won 17,000...
Chucky, you found me!
I told you I would.
Where's Grandma?
In the cellar.
What's she doing down there?
Nothin'.
Chucky, Mommy and Daddy are dead.
Aunty Nica killed them.
But I'm your friend till the end, Alice.
And now it's time to play.
Hide and seek?
Hide the soul.
And guess what?
You're it.
Why do I always have to be it?
Because you're somebody that no one would ever suspect.
Now, close your eyes.
Give me the power, I beg of you.
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：1610169789
- Package for you. - Really?
Maybe you won something.
Must be my lucky day.
Have a good one.
Thanks. You, too.
Oh, boy. A seat!
Get your seat off of my feet.
But what feet?
Hello? Oh, hi, Mom, how you doing?
I'm sorry I didn't call. I meant to.
Yeah, I'm definitely coming for my birthday tomorrow.
No, don't get me anything.
Do me a favor, Ma, no surprises, okay?
Yeah. I'll be there, like, noon? 1:00?
What are you making for dinner?
Yeah?
How's Mike doing?
Well, tell him I said hello.
Yeah.
- All right. - Come on, open up, open up!
Well, I'll see you around that time.
Okay.
Play with this.
Andy...