更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
MOVER: We're here! Time to muscle up.
Hello?
Who's there?
You scared me to death, you mangy thing.
I'm just looking for an old well. Know it?
Not talking, huh?
Magic dowser, magic dowser,
Show me the well!
Get away from me!
Ooh.
Let me guess. You're from Texas or Utah,\nsomeplace dried-out and barren, right?
I heard about water witching before,\nbut it doesn't make sense.
- I mean, it's just an ordinary branch.\n- It's a dowsing rod.
Ow!
And I don't like being stalked,\nnot by psycho nerds or their cats!
He's not really my cat. He's kind of feral.\nYou know, wild.
Of course, I do feed him every night,
and sometimes he'll come to my window\nand bring me little dead things.
Look, I'm from Pontiac.
Huh?
Michigan. And if I'm a water witch,\nthen where's the secret well?
You stomp too hard and you'll fall in it.
Oh!
See?
It's supposed to be so deep,\nif you fell to the bottom and looked up,
you'd see a sky full of stars\nin the middle of the day.
Ha!
Surprised she let you move in.
My gramma, she owns the Pink Palace.\nWon't rent to people with kids.
What do you mean?
(STAMMERING) I'm not supposed to\ntalk about it. I'm Wybie. Wybie Lovat.
- Wybie?\n- Short for Wyborne.
Not my idea, of course.\nWhat'd you get saddled with?
I wasn't saddled with anything. It's Coraline.
- Caroline what?\n- Coraline. Coraline Jones.
(SCOFFS) It's not real scientific,\nbut I heard an ordinary name like Caroline
can lead people to have\nordinary expectations about a person.
LOVAT: Wyborne!
I think I heard\nsomeone calling you, Wyborne.
- What? I didn't hear anything.\n- I definitely heard someone,
Why-Were-You-Born.
- LOVAT: Wyborne!\n- Grandma!
Well, great to meet a Michigan water witch,
but I'd wear gloves next time.
- Why?\n- 'Cause that dowsing rod of yours,
it's poison oak.
I almost fell down a well yesterday, Mom.
Uh-huh.
I would've died.
That's nice.
Hmm.
So, can I go out?\nI think it's perfect weather for gardening.
No, Coraline. Rain makes mud.\nMud makes a mess.
But, Mom, I want stuff growing\nwhen my friends come to visit.
Isn't that why we moved here?
Something like that.\nBut then we had the accident.
- It wasn't my fault you hit that truck.\n- I never said it was.
I can't believe it.
You and Dad get paid to write about plants,\nand you hate dirt.
Coraline, I don't have time for you\nright now,
and you still have unpacking to do.\nLots of unpacking.
(SARCASTICALLY) That sounds exciting!
Oh. Some kid left this on the front porch.
WYBIE. ; Hey, Jonesy.\nLook what I found in Gramma's trunk.
Look familiar? Wybie.
CORALINE: Huh.
A little me? That's weird.
What's his name, anyway?
Wybie. And I'm way too old for dolls.
Hey, Dad. How's the writing going?
Dad!
Hello, Coraline and Coraline doll.
Do you know where the garden tools are?
It's... It's pouring out there, isn't it?
- It's just raining.\n- What'd the boss say?
"Don't even think about going out,\nCoraline Jones!"
Then you won't need the tools.
You know, this house is 150 years old.
- So?\n- So explore it.
Go out and count all the doors and windows\nand write that down on...
List everything that's blue. Just let me work.
Ew!
No. No, no, no. No.
One boring blue boy\nin a painfully boring painting.
Four incredibly boring windows
and no more doors.
All right, little me. Where are you hiding?
Huh?
Hey, Mom. Where does this door go?
I'm really, really busy.
CORALINE: I think it's locked.
Please!
Will you stop pestering me\nif I do this for you?
Fine.
Bricks? I don't get it.
They must've closed this off\nwhen they divided up the house.
You're kidding.\nAnd why is the door so small?
We made a deal! Zip it!
You didn't lock it.
Oh, my twitchy-witchy girl
I think you are so nice\nI give you bowls of porridge
And I give you bowls of ice cream
Why don't you ever cook, Mom?
Coraline, we've been through this before.
Your dad cooks, I clean,\nand you stay out of the way.
I swear I'll go food shopping\nsoon as we finish the catalog.
Try some of the chard.\nYou need a vegetable.
It looks more like slime to me.
Well, it's slime or bedtime, fusspot.\nNow what's it gonna be?
Think they're trying to poison me?
Don't forget about me, guys. Okay?
Good night, little me.
Whoa!
Huh?
Mmm. Something smells good.
Mom? What are you doing here\nin the middle of the night?
You're just in time for supper, dear.
You're not my mother.\nMy mother doesn't have...
Buttons? Do you like them?
I'm your other mother, silly.
Now go tell your other father\nthat supper's ready.
Well, go on. He's in his study.
CORALINE: Hello?
Hello, Coraline.
Wanna hear my new song?
- My father can't play piano.\n- No need to.
This piano plays me.
Making up a song about Coraline
She's a peach, she's a doll\nShe's a pal of mine
She's as cute as a button\nin the eyes of everyone
Who ever laid their eyes on Coraline
When she comes around exploring\nMom and I will never, ever make it boring
Our eyes will be on Coraline
I'm sorry,\nbut she said to tell you the food's ready.
Mmm.
Who's starving? Raise your hand.
Whoa!
We give our thanks and ask to bless\nour mother's golden chicken breast.
Mmm!
- CORALINE: This chicken is good.\n- Hungry, aren't you?
- Do you have any gravy?\n- Well, here comes the gravy train.
Choo, choo!
Huh.
Another roll? Sweet peas? Corn on the cob?
I'm real thirsty.
Of course. Any requests?
Mango milkshake?
- Home?\n- We've been waiting for you, Coraline.
- For me?\n- OTHER FATHER: Yep.
Wasn't the same here without you, kiddo.
I didn't know I had another mother.
Of course you do. Everyone does.
- Really?\n- OTHER MOTHER: Uh-huh.
And soon as you're through eating,\nI thought we'd play a game.
You mean like hide-and-seek?
Perfect. Hide-and-seek in the rain.
What rain?
- What about the mud?\n- We love mud here.
Mud facials, mud baths, mud pies.
- It's great for poison oak.\n- How'd you know I...
I... I'd love to play,\nbut I better get home to my other mother.
But I'm your other mother.
I mean my other, other mother.\nMom number one?
I think I should get to bed.
Of course, sweetheart. It's all made up.
- But...\n- Come along, sleepyhead.
- Wow.\n- DRAGONFLY: Hello, Coraline.
DRAGONFLIES: Hello, hello, hello, hello.
- What's shaking, baby?\n- Hello.
GIRL. ; Hey. How's it going, Loper?
Where's your swampers and chook?
Cripes almighty! How are my best trolls?
I can't wait till summer.\nYou're both coming, right?
- We're already here, Coraline.\n- Gone to Oregon.
CORALINE: Oh.
The mud.
- See you soon.\n- See you soon.
It's gone. My poison oak! It's gone!
Huh.
It was incredibly real, Mom.
Only you weren't really you.\nYou were my other mother.
Buttons for eyes, huh?
Coraline, you only dreamed\nyou ate all that chicken.
Take your multivitamin at least.
You were in the dream, too, Dad.
You had wild-looking pajamas\nand orange monkey slippers.
Orange?\nMy monkey slippers are blue.
Psst! Can you get me some of that\nmagic mud you were talking about?
Because I have a terrible case\nof writer's rash on my...
If the real Charlie Jones\nwants his pages edited,
he better wrap them up ASAP.
Coraline,\nwhy don't you go visit downstairs?
I bet those actresses\nwould love to hear your dream.
Miss Spink and Forcible?\nBut you said they're dingbats.
Mmm-hmm.
Bobinsky. Bobinsky. Bobinsky.
Hello?
I think our mail got mixed up.
Should I leave it outside, or...
CORALINE: Hmm.
Secret!
Famous jumping mouse circus not ready,
little girl.
Circus?
Oh, uh...
I brought this for you.
Huh?
New cheese samples.
Very clever using this mix-up\nto sneak my home and peek at mooshkas?
- Mooshkas?\n- The mice!
Oh!
Sorry. I'm Coraline Jones.
And I am the Amazing Bobinsky.
But you call me Mr. B
because amazing I already know that I am.
Ha!
You see, Caroline, the problem is...\nMy new songs go oompah, oompah,
but the jumping mice play only toodle-toot,\nlike that.
Is nice but not so much amazing.
So now, I switch to stronger cheese\nand soon, watch out!
Here, have beet. Make you strong.
Do svidaniya, Caroline.
Coraline.
Oompah, oompah. Toodle-toot. Toodle-toot.
Hey, Caroline!
Wait!
No!
The mice asked me to give you message.
The jumping mice?
They are saying\ndo not go through little door.
Do you know such a thing?
The one behind the wallpaper?\nBut it's all bricked up.
Bah. So sorry. Is nothing.
Sometimes the mice are little mixed-up.
They even get your name wrong, you know?
They call you Coraline instead of Caroline.
Not Caroline at all.\nMaybe I work them too hard.
Cease your infernal yapping.
How nice to see you, Caroline.
Would you like to come in?\nWe're playing cards.
Still Coraline, Miss Spink.
Miriam! Put the kettle on!
April, I think you're being followed.
It's the new neighbor, Miriam. Caroline.
She'll be having the oolong tea.
No! Oh, no, no.\nI'm sure she'd prefer jasmine.
No, oolong.
Ah. Jasmine it is, then.
Come on, boys.
Are those dogs real?
Our sweet departed angels.
Couldn't bear to part with them,\nso we had them stuffed.
Now, there's Hamish the third...
Go on. Have one.
It's hand-pulled taffy from Brighton.\nBest in the world.
SPINK: The third, the ninth, yes.\nThe fourth, I'm right.
And Jock Jr., Jock Sr.,\nJock the third, the fourth,
and that's Jock's second cousin\nthrice removed.
I'll read them if you like.
- Read what?\n- Your tea leaves, dear.
They'll tell me your future.\nDrink up then. Go on.
No, not all of it. Not all of it.\nThat's right. Now hand it over.
Oh!
Oh, Caroline.
Caroline, Caroline, Caroline.
You are in terrible danger.
Oh, give me that cup, April.\nYour eyes are going.
My eyes? You're blind as a bat.
Well, not to worry, child.
It's good news. There's a tall,\nhandsome beast in your future.
- A what?\n- Miriam, really.
You're holding it wrong. See? Danger.
CORALINE: What do you see?
SPINK: I see a very peculiar hand.
FORCIBLE: I see a giraffe.
Giraffes don't just fall from the sky, Miriam.
Oh, Lord.
Well, what should I do?
Never wear green in your dressing room.
Acquire a very tall stepladder.
And be very, very careful.
Now, was there something\nyou came to tell us?
No. I guess not. Thanks for the tea, though.
FORCIBLE: Toodle-oo.\nSPINK: Cheery-bye.
FORCIBLE: Do you have\nany nice queens for Mummy?
Danger?
Great! The village stalker.
Ow!
I wasn't stalking you.\nWe're hunting banana slugs.
What do you mean "we?"
Ha! Your cat's not wild. He's a wuss puss.
What? He hates to get his feet wet. Jeez.
Wuss puss.
So, that doll. Did you make it look like me?
Oh, no. I found it that way.
It's older than Grandma.\nOld as this house, probably.
Come on.\nBlue hair, my swampers and raincoat?
Dang! Check out Slugzilla.
You're just like them.
Huh?
I meant my parents.\nThey don't listen to me either.
Uh-huh. You mind?
Hmm.
Ew!
You know, I've never been inside\nthe Pink Palace.
You're kidding.
Grandma'd kill me.\nThinks it's dangerous or something.
Dangerous?
- Well, she had a twin sister.\n- So?
When they were kids,\nGrandma's sister disappeared.
She says she was stolen.
CORALINE: Stolen?
Well, what do you think?
I don't know. Maybe she just ran away.
LOVAT: Wyborne!
- Look, I gotta go.\n- Wait a minute.
- Welcome back, darling.\n- Hi.
So thoughtful of you\nto send this nice cheddar, Coraline.
Cheddar? Oh! The mice bait.
Would you go fetch your father?\nI bet he's hungry as a pumpkin by now.
You mean my other father.
Your better father, dear.\nHe's out in the garden.
But my parents don't have time to garden.
Mmm!
Go on.
Oh!
Hey.
I love your garden!
Our garden, Coraline.
Stop tickling me!
Daughter in distress.
Tickle no more, you dragon snappers.
Well, she says it's time for dinner,\nbreakfast, food.
Hop on, kiddo.\nI wanna show you something.
CORALINE: I can't believe you did this.
OTHER FATHER: Mother said you'd like it.
Boy, she knows you\nlike the back of her hand.
Mmm. So good.
I love dinner-breakfast-food.
Coraline, Mr. Bobinsky has invited you
to come see the jumping mice perform\nafter dinner.
Really? That know-it-all Wybie\nsaid it was all in Mr. B's head.
I knew he was wrong.
Well, everything's right in this world, kiddo.
Your father and I will clean up\nwhile you and your friend head upstairs.
My friend?
Great. Another Wybie.\nHello, Why-Were-You-Born.
Hello!
I thought you'd like him more\nif he spoke a little less. So I fixed him.
- So he can't talk at all?\n- Nope.
Hmm.
I like it.
Now, run along, you two, and have fun.
You're awful cheerful\nconsidering you can't say anything.
It didn't hurt, did it, when she...
CORALINE: Whoa!
Cool!
CORALINE: Look at you!
OTHER BOBINSKY: Lady and gentleman,\nfor to tickle your eyes and ears
and making hearts to thump,
I, Sergei Alexander Bobinsky,
am introducing my astoundishing,
stupendulous and amazing
jumping mouse circus!
My name!
It's wonderful, Wybie.
Wow!
Yahoo! That was great!
Very, very thank you, lady and gentleman.
We loved it, Mr. B. It was so... So...
Ah...
Amazing!
You are very welcome anytime you like.\nYou and also your good friend there.
Do svidaniya, Coraline.
CORALINE: There were garden squash\nlike balloon animals and snapdragons.
Oh, and upstairs, I saw a real mouse circus.
Not pretend like the crazy man's\nin our house.
You sure you won't come?
Don't fret, Charlie.\nThey'll love the new catalog.
At least they'll love my chapters.
I did not call him crazy, Coraline.\nHe's drunk.
Well, I guess I'll see you around,\nyou dizzy dreamer.
Dad! I'm not five anymore.
My kingdom for a horse!
Put them back.
But, Mom, the whole school's gonna wear\nboring gray clothes. No one will have these.
My other mother would get them.
Maybe she should buy all your clothes.
CORALINE: So what do you think\nis in the other apartment?
I don't know.\nNot a family of Jones imposters.
- Then why'd you lock the door?\n- Oh!
I found some rat crap,\nand I thought you'd feel safer.
They're jumping mice, Mom,\nand the dreams aren't dangerous.
They're the most fun I've had\nsince we've moved here.
- Your school might be fun.\n- With those stupid uniforms? Right.
Had to give it a try.
How do you feel about a mustard,\nketchup, salsa wrap for lunch?
Are you kidding me?
Had to go food shopping, anyway.\nDad's planning something special.
Grossgusting.
You wanna come along?\nYou can pick out something you like.
Oh. Like the gloves.
Look, Coraline, if things go well today,\nI promise I'll make it up.
That's what you always say.
Won't be long.
But I might be.
I knew it was real.
O THER MO THER. ; Dearest Coraline,
Miss Spink and Miss Forcible\nhave invited you downstairs after lunch.
I hope you like the new outfit I made you.\nLove, Mother.
Wybie's got a cat like you at home.
Not the quiet Wybie.\nThe one that talks too much.
You must be the other cat.
No, I'm not the other anything. I'm me.
Um... I can see you don't have button eyes,
but if you're the same cat,\nhow can you talk?
I just can.
Cats don't talk at home.
- No?\n- Nope.
Well, you're clearly\nthe expert on these things.
After all, I'm just a big fat wuss puss.
Come back. Please?\nI'm sorry I called you that. I really am.
How'd you get here?
I've been coming here for a while.
It's a game we play.
She hates cats and tries to keep me out,
but she can't, of course.\nI come and go as I please.
The other mother hates cats?
Not like any mother I've ever known.
What do you mean? She's amazing.
You probably think this world\nis a dream come true, but you're wrong.
The other Wybie told me so.
That's nonsense. He can't talk.
Perhaps not to you.
We cats, however,\nhave far superior senses than humans,
and can see and smell and...
Shh!
I hear something. Right over...
Hey, Wybie.
She's practically naked!
I'm known as the siren\nof all seven seas
The breaker of hearts by the bay
So if you go swimming\nWith bowlegged women
I might steal your weak heart away
Oh, my God.
A big-bottomed sea witch\nMay bob through the waves
And hope to lead sailors astray
But a true ocean goddess\nMust fill out her bodice
To present an alluring display
Oh! Beware of old oysters\ntoo large in the chest
Let's banish them from the buffet
I'm far more nutritious
You smell like the fishes
Did I hear a banshee?
You're sea green with envy
This mermaid enchantress
No, I, Birth of Venus
- Will send sailors swooning...\n- Will send sailors swooning all day
I can't look.
Ready to break a leg, Miriam?
Our lives for the theater, April.
OTHER FORCIBLE: " What a piece of work\nis man! How noble in reason!"
OTHER SPINK: "How infinite in faculty."
"In form, in moving\nhow express and admirable!"
OTHER FORCIBLE: "In action like an angel."
OTHER SPINK: " In apprehension\nhow like a god!"
OTHER FORCIBLE:\n"The beauty of the world!"
OTHER SPINK: "The paragon of animals!"
Yeah!
Hey, there.
Was it wonderful, dear?
Oh, yeah. They swooped down\nand pulled me right out of my seat,
Spink and Forcible,\nonly they weren't old ladies.
That was just a disguise. But then,\nI was flying through the air, and it was...
It was magic.
You do like it here, don't you, Coraline?
Uh-huh.
Good night, Wybie.
You could stay here forever if you want to.
- Really?\n- Sure.
We'll sing and play games,\nand Mother will cook your favorite meals.
There's one tiny little thing we need to do.
- What's that?\n- (CHUCKLING) Well, it's a surprise.
For you, our little doll.
Black is traditional.
But if you'd prefer pink\nor vermillion or chartreuse...
Though you might make me jealous.
No way!\nYou're not sewing buttons in my eyes!
But we need a "yes"\nif you want to stay here.
So sharp you won't feel a...
There, now. It's your decision, darling.
We only want what's best for you.
I'm going to bed. Right now!
- Bed?\n- Before dinner?
I'm really, really tired. Yeah.
I just need to sleep on things.
Well, of course you do, darling.\nI'll be happy to tuck you in.
Oh, no, thanks.\nYou've done so much already.
You're welcome. And I...
We aren't worried at all, darling.
Soon you'll see things our way.
DRAGONFLIES: What's wrong, Coraline?\nDon't you wanna play?
Yeah! I wanna hug your face!
GIRAFFE DOLL: Get a grip, soldier!
GIRL. ; Hey!\nBO Y. ; Hey!
Where's your buttons, Loper?
You want to stay, don't you?
Going home tonight, robots,\nand I won't be back.
Go to sleep. Go to sleep. Go to sleep.
(ECHOING) Go to sleep. Go to sleep.
O THER MO THER. ;\n...a tiny little thing we need to do.
CORALINE. ; Go to sleep.\nGo to sleep. Go to sleep.
O THER FATHER. ;\nSo sharp you won't feel a thing.
CORALINE. ; Go to sleep. Go to sleep.
O THER MO THER. ;\nSoon you'll see things our way.
Mom! Dad!
Oh, God. I'm still here?
Hey, you!
Where's the other mother?\nI wanna go home.
All will be swell,\nsoon as Mother's refreshed.
Her strength is our strength.
Mustn't talk when Mother's not here.
If you won't even talk to me,\nI'm gonna find the other Wybie.
- He'll help me.\n- No point.
He pulled a long face,\nand Mother didn't like it.
And what do you think you're doing?
Well, I'm getting out of here.\nThat's what I'm doing.
Huh?
Something's wrong.\nShouldn't the old well be here?
Nothing out here.
It's the empty part of this world.
She only made\nwhat she knew would impress you.
But why? Why does she want me?
She wants something to love, I think.
Something that isn't her.
Or maybe she'd just love something to eat.
Eat? That's ridiculous.\nMothers don't eat daughters.
I don't know. How do you taste?
CORALINE: Huh?
But how can you walk away from something\nand still come back to it?
Walk around the world.
Small world.
Hang on.
Stop! He's one of the circus mice!
I don't like rats at the best of times,
but this one was sounding an alarm.
Good kitty.
They say even the proudest spirit\ncan be broken with love.
Of course, chocolate never hurts. Like one?
They're cocoa beetles from Zanzibar.
I want to be with my real mom and dad.
I want you to let me go.
Is that any way to talk to your mother?
You aren't my mother.
Apologize at once, Coraline!
No!
I'll give you to the count of three.
One.
Two.
Three!
What are you doing? Ow! That hurts!
You may come out when you've learned\nto be a loving daughter.
Who's there?
TALL GIRL GHOST: Hush! And shush.\nFor the beldam might be listening.
You... You mean the other mother?
Who are you?
Don't remember our names,
but I 'member my true mommy.
Why are you all here?
GHOST CHILDREN: The beldam.
She spied on our lives\nthrough the little doll's eyes.
BOY GHOST: And saw that we weren't happy.
TALL GIRL GHOST:\nSo she lured us away with treasures.
- And treats.\n- SWEET GIRL GHOST: And games to play.
BOY GHOST: Gave all that we asked.
SWEET GIRL GHOST:\nYet we still wanted more.
TALL GIRL GHOST:\nSo we let her sew the buttons.
BOY GHOST: She said that she loved us.
TALL GIRL GHOST: But she locked us here.
GHOST CHILDREN: And ate up our lives.
Well, she can't keep me in the dark forever.
Not if she wants to win my life.
Beating her is my only chance.
Perhaps, if you do win your escape,
you could find our eyes.
Has she taken those, too?
Yes, miss. And hidden them.
BOY GHOST: Find our eyes, mistress,\nand our souls will be freed.
I...
I'll try.
Wybie?
Did she do this to you?
- I hope that feels...\n- Shh!
OTHER MOTHER: Coraline? Is that you?
Let's go!
OTHER MOTHER: Coraline!
Come on! She'll hurt you again.
OTHER MOTHER: Coraline!\nHow dare you disobey your mother!
OTHER MOTHER: Coraline!
I'm home!
Anybody here?
Hello? Hello, hello!
Real Dad?
Real Mom?
Oh, Mom's groceries!
That's disgusting.
I missed you guys so much, you'll never...
- Oh. The Wybie that talks.\n- Huh?
Yeah, so, you know that old doll I gave you?
Um...
My grandma's real mad.\nSays it was her sister's.
- The one that disappeared.\n- You stole that doll, didn't you?
Well, it looked just like you, and I figured...
It used to look like this pioneer girl,\nthen Huck Finn Jr.,\nIt used to look like this pioneer girl,\nthen Huck Finn Jr.,
then it was this Little Rascals chick\nwith all these ribbons and braids and...
Grandma's missing sister.\nI think I just met her. Come on.
(STAMMERING) Listen,\nI'm really not supposed to...
Whoa!
She's in there.
Can you... Can you unlock it?
Not in a million years.\nBut it wouldn't matter.
She can't escape without her eyes.\nNone of the ghosts can.
Yeah. So I really need to get that doll.
Great! I'd love to get rid of it.
Where are you hiding, you little monster?
- You and Grandma been talking?\n- The doll's her spy.
It's how she watches you,\nfinds out what's wrong with your life.
- The doll is my grandma's spy?\n- No. The other mother.
She's got this whole world\nwhere everything's better.
The food, the garden, the neighbors.\nBut it's all a trap.
Yeah, I think I heard\nsomeone calling me, Jonesy.
Don't believe me? You can ask the cat.
The cat? I'll just tell Grandma\nthat you couldn't find the doll. Ow!
You're not listening to me!
That's 'Cause you're crazy!
- CORALINE: You creep!\n- Crazy!
Crazy?\nYou're the jerk wad that gave me the doll!
Mom! Dad!
Pick it up, Dad. Pick it up.
Dad! Where...
DAD ON ANSWERING MACHINE. ;\nHi! I'm digging in my garden right now,
but leave a message\nand I'll get right back to you.
Where have you gone?
Uh... Don't you only make wings\nfor the dead ones?
Just looking ahead, dear.
Angus hasn't been feeling very well of late.
FORCIBLE: April? Aren't you getting ready?
We've lost our ride, Miriam.
Caroline says her parents\nhave vanished quite completely.
What?\nWe've waited months for those tickets.
I suppose we could walk.
With your gammy legs?\nIt's nearly two miles to the theater.
Oh, yes. Your missing parents.
We know just what you need.
Miriam, get... That's right.
How is 100-year-old candy gonna help?
There you go, sweetie.
- What's it for?\n- Well, it might help.
They're good for bad things sometimes.
(CHUCKLING) No.\nThey're good for lost things.
SPINK: It's bad things, Miriam.
- FORCIBLE: Lost things, April.\n- Bad.
- FORCIBLE: Lost.\n- (WHISPERS) Bad things.
- Lost.\n- Bad.
FORCIBLE: Lost!
Good night, Mom.
Good night, Dad.
CORALINE: Hello. How did you get in?
Do you know where Mom and Dad are?
Mom? Dad!
Help us
How did this happen?
She's taken them.
They're not coming back, are they?\nMom and Dad.
Not on their own.
Only one thing to do.
You know,\nyou're walking right into her trap.
I have to go back.
They are my parents.
Challenge her, then.\nShe may not play fair, but she won't refuse.
She's got a thing for games.
Hmm.
Okay.
- OTHER MOTHER: Coraline?\n- Mom?
Coraline! You came back for us.
Mom!
Darling, why would you run away from me?
Where are my parents?
Gosh, I have no idea\nwhere your old parents are.
Perhaps they've grown bored of you\nand run away to France.
They weren't bored of me. You stole them!
Now, don't be difficult, Coraline.
Have a seat, won't you?
- Why don't you have your own key?\n- (GARBLED) Only one key.
Shh!
The garden squash need tending,\ndon't you think, pumpkin?
(GARBLED) Squish-squash, pumpkin sauce.
Mom?
Dad?
Where'd she hide you?
OTHER MOTHER: Breakfast time!
CORALINE. ; Be strong, Coraline.
Why don't we play a game?
- I know you like them.\n- Everybody likes games.
OTHER MOTHER:\nWhat kind of game would it be?
An exploring game. A finding things game.
And what is it you'd be finding, Coraline?
My real parents.
Too easy.
And the eyes of the ghost children.
What if you don't find them?
If I lose, I'll stay here with you forever\nand let you love me.
And I'll let you sew buttons into my eyes.
And if you somehow win this game?
Then you let me go. You let everyone go.
My real father and mother,
the dead children,\neveryone you've trapped here.
Deal.
Not till you give me a clue.
Oh, right.
In each of three wonders\nI've made just for you,
a ghost's eye is lost in plain sight.
And for my parents?
Fine. Don't tell me.
It's a deal.
What does she mean, "wonders?"
No!
(GASPS) Stop!
Why steal this?
Wow!
That must be it!
(GARBLED) Sorry.
So sorry. Mother making me.
Don't wanna hurt you!
Take it!
Bless you, miss. You found me!
But there's two eyes still lost.
Don't worry. I'm getting the hang of it.
The pearl.
- Thief!\n- Thief!
- Give it back!\n- Give it back!
OTHER SPINK: Give it back!
- Thief!\n- Thief!
- Give it back!\n- Thief!
- Thief!\n- Give it back!
- Give it back!\n- Give it back!
Thief!
- Thief!\n- Thief!
Stop! Stop! Thief! Thief!
OTHER FORCIBLE: Thief! Stop!
Hurry on, girl. Her web is unwinding.
Oh, Wybie.
Evil witch! I'm not scared!
Hello, galoobooshka.
I'm Coraline.
Is this what you're looking for?
You think winning game is good thing?
You'll just go home and be bored\nand neglected,
same as always. Stay here with us.
We will listen to you and laugh with you.
If you stay here,\nyou can have whatever you want.
Always!
You don't get it, do you?
I don't understand.
Of course you don't understand.
You're just a copy she made\nof the real Mr. B.
(DISTORTED) Not even that anymore.
No!
Oh, God. I've lost the game.\nI've lost everything.
I think I mentioned\nthat I don't like rats at the best of times.
I think you might have said\nsomething like that.
It looked like you needed this one, however.
Thank you.
I'm heading inside.\nI still have to find my parents.
Come on, quickly!
So you're back.
And you brought vermin with you.
No. I...
I brought a friend.
You know I love you.
You have a very funny way of showing it.
So where are they? The ghost eyes?
Hold on. We aren't finished yet. Are we?
No, I suppose not.
After all, you still need to find\nyour old parents, don't you?
Too bad you won't have this.
Be clever, miss.\nEven if you win, she'll never let you go!
I already know where you've hidden them.
Well, produce them.
They're behind that door.
Oh, they are, are they?
(WHISPERS) There.
Mom. Dad.
Go on. Open it. They'll be there, all right.
You're wrong, Coraline. They aren't there.
Now you're going to stay here forever.
No, I'm not!
OTHER MOTHER: No!
You horrible cheating girl!
No! Where are you?
You selfish brat!
You dare disobey your mother?
Please shut it!
OTHER MOTHER:\nDon't leave me! Don't leave me!
I'll die without you!
MOM: Coraline, we're home.
Mom! Dad! I missed you so much!
Missed us? Oh, no.\nYou broke my favorite snow globe.
I didn't break it.\nIt must've broke when you escaped.
And cut your knee.
Coraline, I asked you\nto count all the windows,
not put your knee through them.
- But...\n- Well, get yourself cleaned up.
- We're going out tonight.\n- (EXCLAIMS) We got a lot to celebrate.
You're talking about your garden catalog?
Of course. What else?
CORALINE: But look at the snow on your...
What's gotten into you, Coraline?
- So, gonna order the tulips?\n- What's that?
For the garden party?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Dad! So, Ma, invitations?
- Don't forget the invitations.\n- Even Bobinsky?
Mr. B.'s not drunk, Mom. He's just eccentric.
Good night, Coraline.
Oh.
Hello again.
You still mad?
I'm really sorry I threw you at her,\nthe other mother.
It was all I could think of.
I think it's time, don't you?
To set them free?
It's a fine, fine thing you did for us, miss.
Well, I'm glad it's finally over.
It is over and done with for us.
What about me?
You're in terrible danger, girl!
But how? I locked the door!
It's the key, miss.\nThere's only one, and the beldam will find it.
'Tain't all bad, miss.
Thou art alive. Thou art still living.
I gotta hide this somewhere,\nsomewhere she can never...
Out of my way!
CORALINE: (SINGING)\nOh, my twitchy-witchy girl
I think you are so nice
I give you bowls of porridge\nand I give you bowls of ice cream
I give you lots of kisses
And I give you lots of hugs
But I never give you sandwiches
With grease and worms and mung...beans
I'm really sorry I didn't believe you\nabout all this evil stuff, Coraline.
Why did you change your mind?
Well, Grandma showed me this picture\nafter I called you crazy.
It's her and her sister,\nbefore she disappeared.
The Sweet Ghost Girl.
LOVAT: Wyborne! Come home!
Oh, man. What am I gonna tell her?
Just bring her by the house tomorrow.\nWe can tell her together.
We... We can?
You know, I'm glad you decided to stalk me.
It wasn't my idea.
CORALINE: Thanks for helping me,\nMiss Spink, Miss Forcible.
Oh, look, April. Pink ladies!
Actually, it's just lemonade.\nHow's Angus doing?
Oh, much better, dear,\nbut he can't duck his wings forever.
DAD: Here comes a burp.
MOM: Charlie!
Excusez-moi, but that pizza,\nthat was delicious.
- CORALINE: Cold drinks?\n- Oh, yeah. Great.
You were right, Coraline. I really hate dirt!
But the tulips look nice.
CORALINE: Thanks, Mom.
That is possible.
CORALINE: How are the mooshkas, Mr. B?
They tell me that you are savior, Caroline.
And soon as they are ready,
they wish to give\nspecial thanks you performance.
LOVAT: Wyborne, I know where I'm going.
I grew up here.
CORALINE: Welcome, Miss Lovat!
Oh. Hello.
I'm Coraline Jones.\nI've got so much to tell you.
MOM: Here.\nDAD: Thanks.
SPINK: Do you want to pop\na little gin in it, dear?
FORCIBLE: Of course.
pink palace apartments
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：274796078