更多佳片尽在 shop.paipai.com/1610169789
Hi. l'm Lenny.
Oh little buddy did l scare you? l'm sorry.
Wake up. Okay don't worry about it l'll get you out in a jiffy.
Keep holding your breath little wormie.
Yo Lenny.  l'm coming Frankie.
Move it. Pop's waiting.  Here we go. And gotcha.
Okay buddy you're free. Now escape.
Just go. Cry freedom.
You almost gave me a heart attack.  What are you doing?
l was just...
picking you some flowers.
Hey Mom said it's not okay to hit.
Mom's not here.
Don't.
That song gives me the creeps.Whaddya mean? lt's our theme song.
Are they gone? Are they gone?
You sure?
Good morning Southside Reef. I'm Katie Current keeping it current.
We've received official confirmation the sharks are gone.
I repeat: the sharks are gone.
Don't worry
About a thing
Every little thing.Is gonna be all right.
Don't worry
About a thing
Tuna Turner.
Mussel Crowe.
Jessica Shrimpson.
Cod Stewart.
Up next a mother of 800 tells us how she does it all.
But first over to Janice for the traffic report.
Thanks Katie. Slight congestion here on the InterReef 95.
There's an overturned mackerel. Authorities are trying to calm him down.
Get out those shell phones and call in to the boss 'cause you'll be late.
Don't you yell at me. My mother is your mother okay.
Yup. lt's fake.  Fake? l worked eight years on that.
About a thing.Every little thing.
Is gonna be all right
According to the latest Scallop Poll fear of sharks is at an alltime high.
Join us tonight for an indepth report.
How long must this reef live under siege?
Is there no hero among us?
Who can stop this shark menace?
Hi l'm Oscar. You might think you know but you have no idea.
Welcome to my crib. The good life the way the other half lives.
Check it out l got my 60'' highdef flatscreen TV
with 6speaker surround CD DVD PlayStation hookup
and an 8track player for days when you're feeling a little...
old school.
'Cause even a superstar Mack daddy fish like me
has to have the basic necessities.
Yeah like money.
Come on Shorties. Why ya'll messin' with my fantasy?
'Cause you so broke your baloney has no first name.
That's very funny.
Hey Oscar. Over here. l gotta talk to ya.
Be right there. Hang onto these.  Oscar you da fish.
Yo doo.
Yo Crazy Joe.
Now that you live in that penthouse can l be your financial advisor?
That's a billboard Crazy Joe.
You live in a billboard? And they call me crazy.
Hey Oscar. Look who came to visit.
Gotcha.  No. Don't do that.
Shouldn't you be in school?  Shouldn't you be at work?
Right back at me huh? Little smart mouth.
Look l'm on my way. Stay outta trouble all right?
And clean that stuff up.  See ya.
See ya Oscar.
Say what say what
Car wash car wash
Yo what's up fellas? Big O's in the house.
What's up?
Hey. Reef side.
Yo Johnson is it lunch yet?  You just got here.
That's my point.
Hey Headphone Guy.
Lookin' good ladies.  Hey Oscar.
Keep up the bad work.
Huh?
l'm already punched in?
Angie.
Good morning. Can l help you?
One wash and lube please.
Hot wax?  Please.
Kelp scrape? We're having a special.
Why not? lt is mating season and l'm feelin' lucky.
Sykes' Whale Wash. A whale of a wash and the price...
oh my gosh.
Mmhm. Mmhm.
May l suggest a barnacle peel? Removes lines and salt damage.
Good.  Hey Ang.
Oh my gosh. Hi Oscar.  Thanks for covering for me.
Yo l'm sorry Dun. Angie needs to get her freak on.
Would you hold for one moment please? Thanks.
Oscar.  Come on Ang. Dance with me mama.
Let me see it. Tomorrow I will be rich...
Come on.  Oscar. You're gonna get me fired.
Please you fired? That can't happen.
'Cause then l would have absolutely no reason to come to work.
Oh you don't mean that.
Course l do. You're like my best friend.
Listen tell me what you think about this.
This is like the best idea ever all right.
lt's a sure thing guaranteed cash extravaganza.
Bottled water.  Oh no.
All l need is an advance on my paycheck from the boss
and Ang l am out of this place. l mean l am... pschoo!
Oscar.
lnstead of getting in Mr. Sykes' face with another getrichquick scheme
go do something you're actually good at: your job
which by some miracle you still have.
Oh.
l almost forgot.
l brought you some breakfast.  You didn't. Kelpy Kremes?
Your favorite. By the way you're still on hold.
Oh my gosh!
Thank you for holding. Busy busy.
Go. How can l help you?
No l'm sorry. Mr. Sykes is at a meeting right now.
He won't be back till later.
How are my little babies this morning?
You miss me? You doin' good?
Huh? Huh?
You see Sykes
it's a fisheatfish world. You either take or you get taken.
Truer words have never been spoken. ls that it? We done?
Now you and me we worked together a long long long time.
Please Don Lino it's hardly been like work.
You know...  l love that about you.
Let me finish. That l've lived my life for my sons.
Raising and protecting them...  You're the best!
He's the best right? Am l right or am l wrong? Am l right?
lt's all been to prepare...  Right?
...to prepare them...  Sorry.
...for the day they run the reef. Well today is that day.
Luca.
I like big butts And I cannot lie
You other brothers...
Hey boss. Big Butts.
Oi vey!
Long story short from now on you work for Frankie and Lenny.
Capiche?
Lenny? Frankie l understand. But Lenny? You can't be serious.
l'm dead serious. lt takes more than muscle to run things.
Now Lenny he's got the brains. That's somethin' special.
He's special all right.  What does that mean?
Nothing. l'm just sayin'...  l bring you in here
look you in the eye tell you what's what and what?
What?  What ''what''?
You said ''what'' first.
l didn't say what l asked you what.
You said ''And then what?'' l said ''What?''
No l said ''what what'' like what what?
You said ''what'' first.  Now you're making fun of me?
No you misunderstood.
Sorry we're late Pop. Lenny had an accident. He was born.
You're a comic genius.
Look all l'm saying is the kid ain't exactly no killer.
My Lenny is a killer. You hear me? A coldblooded killer. Look at him.
Huh?
That's it! That's it! You are out!
What? [highpitched] Whaddya mean l'm ''out?''
You're fired.
And on top of that you're gonna have to start payin' me.
For what?
So nothing happens to your little Whale Wash.
Welcome to Oscar's crib.
60foot slimecovered tongue with canker sores swimin cavities
and planktonencrusted teeth for when l feel a bit...
old school.
Stop your moaning Oscar. lt could be a lot worse you know.
That's true. l could have this job and look like you.
Who's behind me? Whoever's behind me better give me some.
lndigestion. She's gonna blow!
Wait! Headphone Guy is still in there!
l got you Headphone Guy!
Still think it could be worse?  Yeah. l could look like you.
Y'all funny. Well see if you laugh at this.
Soap in the eye! Soap in the eye!
lt's all right. l'll get you some coupons
a free hot wax and all that. You like that?
All right go ahead big baby.  Thanks Oscar.
All right.
Well look who it is Bernie.  Just the fish we're looking for.
The boss be needin' to see you right now.
Right now.  Ernie. Bernie.
My jellyfish brothers. Booyaka.
Hey what's up man? Man it's good to see y'all... Huh?
What'd you say Ang? Okay.
Fellas l'm gonna go ahead over there.
But don't worry
About a thing
'Cause every little thing Is gonna be all right...
That's not the way you sing that song mon.
Sykes my brother from another mother. What the deezy baby?
Show me dat. What's goin' down?
Hey baby this is all gravy today. Now snap your fin... Snap it.
You're not snappin' it...  Oscar.
Hey don't sweat it. A lot of white fish can't do it.
Would you just sit down okay?  Thank you.
l've been goin' over my markers. You're into me for five grand.
5 G's okay?  5 G's? Man you trippin'? 5 G's.
Oh yeah? See if this refreshes your memory.
That's crazy look at that.
You wrote everything down so you wouldn't forget.
This a perfect example of why you're in management and l'm not.
You go boy.
l have to pay Don Lino protection so everything you owe me you owe him.
How you figure that?  Simple. The food chain.
See on top there's Don Lino. There's me and there's regular fish.
That's me.  No.
There's plankton there's amoebas...
Then there's me?  l'm gettin' there.
There's coral there's rocks there's whale pooh and then there's you.
That's messed up.
So if Don Lino's squeezin' me he's squeezin' you.
What?  Oscar.
Sorry.
Easy boss find your happy place.  Happy place.
There is no happy place with him here. l'm serious.
Okay please. Please just gimme some time.
That's all l'm asking. l'm begging you Sykes. Please. Please.
All right.
'Cause l like you l'm gonna give you 24 hours to pay up.
All of it? How am l supposed to do that?
That's your problem. Bring my 5000 clams to the track tomorrow or else.
Or else what?  The boys'll explain.
Unpleasant.
5000 clams?
You borrowed 5000 clams from Mr. Sykes?
Oscar why do you get yourself into these situations?
l don't know Ang.
lt's just hard all right because l'm a little fish in a big pond.
A really big pond. The ocean.
l'm a nobody. l want some of that.
Mrs. Sanchez?  What?
It's ladies' night Oh what a night...
Ew. No. That.
The top of the reef. Where the somebodies live.
l wanna be rich and famous like them but l'm stuck down here.
Well what's wrong with down here?
l'll tell you what's wrong with down here.
Remember my dad? He worked at the Wash his whole life.
Ooh child...
He was the number one tongue scrubber.
Every year for 25 years.
To me working at the Wash was the coolest job in the ocean.
But then I learned something I will never forget.
Oscar's dad's a tongue scrubber!
Tongue scrubber! Tongue scrubber!
Tongue scrubber! Tongue scrubber! Tongue scrubber! Tongue scrubber!
My dad was the greatest.
But nobody loves a nobody.
l want to be a somebody.
Oscar  you don't have to live at the top of the reef to be a somebody.
What's the difference? lf l don't pay Mr. Sykes back by tomorrow...
l'm dead anyway so...
Wait here.
What's this?
A pink pearl?  Mmhm.
Where'd you get that?
My grandmother gave it to me.
She said it started from a tiny grain of sand
but then after a while it grew into something beautiful.
Dreams can begin small too.
No. No l couldn't...  Take it.
lt'll get you the money you need for Mr. Sykes.
What do you mean you don't understand? We've been over it 1 000 times.
l don't want to have to say it again.
You're really giving me agita. l don't know how else to say this.
You see something you kill it you eat it. Period. Thanks.
That's what sharks do. That's a fine tradition.
What's the matter with you? Your brother Frankie here he's a killer.
Thanks Pop.  He's beautiful.
He does what he's supposed to do. Wipe your face.
But you... l'm hearin' things.
You gotta understand when you look weak it makes me look weak.
l can't have that.  l know Pop l'm sorry.
Lenny. Lenny. Look at me. Look at me.
This handin' over the business it's for you for both of yous
and you're acting like you don't even want it.
l need to know that you can handle that.
All right. Right here in front of me now eat this.
Yeah. Gee thanks Pop.
Here's the thing.
l'm on a diet. l read an article about these shrimps. They're not good for ya.
You know how many calories are in one of those shrimps?
A lot.
lt's true. lt's true and the other thing is
my sister had a baby and l took it over because she passed away
and then the baby lost its legs and its arms
and now it's nothing but a stump but l still take care of it with my wife
and it's growing and it's fairly happy
but it's difficult 'cause l've been working a second shift at the factory to put food on the table
but all the love l see in that little guy's face makes it worth it in the end.
True story.
l'm not askin' you anymore. l'm tellin' you. Eat it!
No. Have mercy.  Pop please...
Eat!  No eat.
Son eat the shrimp!
No please.
Lenny! Eat eat eat!  Don't! Pop!
Put the shrimp down!
Go now. No one's looking. Get out of here.
You're free now go.  Thank you.
You're a good person.
Come on fellas.
Pop l can handle the reef. lt's not a problem.
No. We're gonna do this as a family.
Frankie l want you to take Lenny out show him the ropes.
Come on Pop.  You're gonna learn how to be a shark.
Whether you like it or not.
That kid better show up or he's dead meat.
Just say the word boss.
Carrying a big ol' envelope full of money gonna give it to Mr. Sykes.
Hurry up. This is our chance we don't want to miss it.
You sure?  My trainer friend tipped me off.
The race is rigged. We can't lose.
What's the horse's name?  Lucky Day.
...Lucky Day at 200 to 1.
We're gonna be rich!  Rich!
Top of the reef here l come.
No wait. What am l doing?
Remember what Angie said. Remember what Angie said.
What did Angie say?
Dreams can begin small.
You just have to... bet it all. Bet it all!
And Lucky Day wins.
Five thousand on Lucky Day to win.
That's 200 to one. That would pay a million clams.
Well  l guess that makes me Oscar the millionaire.
The millionaire.
Lucky Day. Lucky Day.
She's dangerous super bad
Better watch out she'll take the cash
She's a gold digger She's a gold digger
She's dangerous super bad
Better watch out she'll take the cash
She's a gold digger...
Nice bet.
You got a name?
You wanna tell me what it is?
Well mine's Lola.
C'mon man! Get your game face on!
So...Lola my name's...
My name is Oscar sweetie.
Mrs. Sanchez.
The hippityhop smooth talk don't work with me.
My bad. Hey so...
Oscar. l was starting to think you skipped out on me.
Sykes! l see you're already on your way to the concession stand.
What are you doing?
Mind bringing us back some drinks? That would be great thanks.
And some of them little wiener thingies.
The ones with the toothpicks?  Don't listen to him.
Let me escort you to... my box.  Your box?!
His box?! You can't even afford the gum under the seats.
He just laid five grand on Lucky Day. l think he can afford anything he wants.
Five grand? My five grand?!  No it was another five grand.
You had the money to pay me back and you bet it anyway?
Hold up.  Gimme that!
Clearly l've made a mistake.  No no wait! Lola!
Look. Deep down l'm really superficial.
And don't get me wrong you're cute but... you're a nobody.
Oscar you cute but you're a nobody.
Wait. Lola. Come back.
l'm not a nobody. l'm a wiener.
You are unbelievable. You're in trouble up to your gills
and still you're askin' for more. Now go on get in here.
Oscar you better pray that this horse of yours comes through.
Bettin' my five thousand.
Hey. Outta my seat. You outta my seat.
Unbelievable.
Sit tight and watch the race.  With your good eye.
Good eye.
The horses are at the post. And they're off!
Fish Fingers then Seabiscuit and Salmonella.
Lucky Day seems to be having trouble getting out of the gate.
What?  Only a sucker would bet on that horse.
Don't sweat it. He does this all the time. He's playin'.
What's this? Lucky Day is now crashing his way through the gate
and he's off and running.
Seabiscuit Fish Fingers...
Please Lucky Day. Go fast.
Coming around the turn it's Seabiscuit by a length and Lucky Day well behind.
And here comes Lucky Day
coming up from behind passing Yellow Tail Salmonella.
You see? Who's your fish now? Go.
Around the final turn here comes Lucky Day.
Lucky Day's now caught up to Fish Fingers.
They're head to head. Neck to neck. Lucky Day's ahead.
l'm tired just thinkin' about countin' all of this money.
Look at Lucky Day go.   We're movin' on up
To the eastside...
Absolutely amazing! This looks to be Lucky Day's big day.
It's Lucky Day.
What happened? Lucky Day is down.
We're movin' on up to the east...
No.
Here's Fish Fingers followed by Seabiscuit Yellow Tail...
And Fish Fingers wins.  Wait. l just want to hold you.
No Get outta my way. Let me see will ya?
Remember your ''happy place'' Sykes.
That's why they call him a long shot.
Yo that was crazy right? Who knew?
Everything's set it's a lock we good to go we in the money
and he trips underwater.
Who in the halibut trips underwater?
And by the way on what?  That's it. That's it l've had it.
Ernie. Bernie. Find the deepest hole in the ocean
and when you do dig deeper. And put him in it.
Sorry kid. lt's nothing personal. lt's just business.
Don't worry
About a thing
'Cause every little thing
Is gonna be all right
This is how you sing it Oscar.  Yeah.
Sykes he like you mon. Him say take it easy on you.
But Sykes is not here. True.
Ernie let me ask you a question.
Yeah mon? Go on.
Why is it that me locks can sting other people
but they have no effect on me or you?
Ernie. l didn't mean it Ernie. l didn't mean it man. Ernie.
Ernie you made a joke. Good one man. Respect.
Bloodfire.
Frankie you know l can't do this.
lf you wanna make Pop happy you've gotta kill something.
Or l could find an old sick fish and just wait.
lt's gettin' around your thing at the restaurant.
You know how fish talk.
This that the other. How you doin'? Boom. Forget it you're dead.
Okay seriously l can't understand wise guy so be more specific.
Specific? You want specific? Be a shark for once in your life.
What am l gonna do?  Lenny forget about it okay?
We do a couple of practice runs baddabing baddaboom Pop's happy
you're a shark life goes on. Capiche?
Okay. Okay capiche.
Bingo.
Right there. Dead ahead. You see it? TV dinner. Don't get easier than this.
All right. Come on. Eye of the tiger.
Frankie l can do this. What if l can't do this?
Then don't bother comin' home.  Good point. All right.
Hit him in the tail again.
l like the funny face he make.  Yeah.
Ernie.  Blow out.
Guys? Guys? Don't leave me alone.
Come on there could be sharks out here.
Oh no. Wait. l'm sorry. No no no. l'm not gonna...
Lenny. Like this.  What?
Oh no.
Just get it over with.
Wait a minute. Do me a favor don't chew me.
l'm not for that.  l'm not gonna eat you.
Don't do the whole head trip thing with me.
Listen to me. Don't move until l tell you.
Ahhh! Back up.
That's it Len. There you go buddy.
That's it. Wave those fins baby. Dig in.
Look l'm just pretending so you can get away.
Now when l turn around you take off.
Tastes just like chicken.
Mmm. Mmm.
Oh no.
What did l tell you?  l'm sorry l didn't get it.
You want me to go now?  Just go.
That's it. l've had it up to here.
Oh no.  Hurry swim.
No Frankie wait.  No! Get your boy get your boy!
Frankie.
Lenny?
Lenny is that you?  l'm here Frankie.
Come closer.  Yes what is it?
l'm so cold.
That's just because we're coldblooded.
Ow!  Moron.
Frankie no...
No!
This is all my fault.
l'm so sorry Frankie.
How am l ever going to explain this to Pop?
Oh no.
Back up. l'm crazy. l be trippin'.
Whoa!
What the...
Don't hurt us. We're sorry. lt was all Ernie's idea.
Oscar. Did you kill that shark?
Uh... yeah.
Exactly how it look that's how it is.
What happened?
You wanna know what happened?
Yeah. You're standing on top of a shark.
Go on man.
Well l'll tell you what happened.
Big ol' shark about 75 1 00feet long.
So he's swimming at me right?
With teeth like razors.  Razors.
And l was like you're gonna come at me like that?
You're gonna come at the ''O'' like that?
Do the muscle thing the muscle thing.
Oh right.
So l told that dude ''You see this guy?'' and l pointed like this.
Well he's got a brother. And he lives right over here.
And l think it's time for a little family reunion.
You see mon. l told you. We were right there.
Pardon me.
Move it!  Oh. Sorry.
She seems so nice on TV.  Oscar Katie Current.
As the first fish in history to ever take on a shark and win tell me:
Does this mean you're now protector of the reef new sheriff in town?
Katie l'm gonna keep it real.
l can call you Katie?  Of course.
Any shark try to mess around in Oscartown is goin' down.
Yeah it's poetic. In the heat I get poetic.
Oscar. Hmm.
Oscar.
Get out of here you barracudas. Any further questions will be fielded by me.
And you are?  l'm his manager.
Sykes with a ''y''.  And l'm his financial advisor.
You want to see my puppets?
Hello.
Could you excuse us for a moment please?
My manager?  Kid you're a superstar.
We're gonna make a fortune.  What about the 5 G's?
Forget the 5 G's. We're partners now.
So what are we talking about?  l'm thinkin' 90 10 split?
That's generous.  You're the 1 0 l'm 90.
l don't think so.  Talk to me.
You get 1 5.  70.
20.  75.
Dude you're goin' the wrong way.
50 50.
You happy?  No. You?
No.  Deal.
My manager and l are now prepared to take your questions.
Oscar are you going to continue working here at the Wash?
Please l barely work here now.
Keep it up kid. You're slayin' 'em.
No. He's slayin' sharks.
Hey that's good. That's good l like that.
Oscar the Sharkslayer.
Whoa! A sharkslayer.
You heard it here first.
From now on any shark tries to bother this reef it's his funeral.
Nomine Patri et Filii et Spiritus Sancti.
I could fly higher than an eagle
If you are the wind beneath my wings
Frankie we'll miss you.  To Frankie.
lt's a terrible thing Don Lino. Everybody loved Frankie.
May whoever did this die a thousand deaths.
May his stinking maggotcovered corpse rot in the fiery depths of hell.
Thank you for your kind thoughts Giuseppe.
Oh and may Lenny be found safe and sound too. Hope he's okay.
Oh Lenny...
Don't worry boss.  l said some things to him...
We gotta find him.
We're searching everywhere. Forget about it he'll turn up.
What's wrong with that kid? Why's he gotta be so different?
Frankie God rest his soul he was perfect. Perfect.
Oh... Luca. Who could have done this?
Don Lino at this most difficult time
please accept my deepest condolences.
Thank you Don Feinberg for honoring my son with your song.
l got some news about the guy who took out Frankie.
Let's... Yeah let's talk over here.
He come out of nowhere this guy.
Calls himself ''The Sharkslayer''.
lra over here.
Sorry. ''The Sharkslayer''.  Where do l find him?
He's from the Southside Reef. That's all we could dig up.
Thank you.
Any requests?  Luca.
That Titanic song?   No.
Get Sykes. He knows that reef better than anybody.
l wanna find this guy. l wanna know about him
where he lives where he sleeps.
He pops a gill? l wanna know about it. Who is this Sharkslayer?
Here he is. The Sharkslayer.
I think I love you baby   What you feel now
I think I need you baby   What you know now
Uhhuh   To be real
Oooh
Your love's for real now
You know that your love
And my love My love is here to stay
Let's get this party started right.
There he is the big O.
Sykes.  Pound that dog. Pound it.
Oscar raise the reef. Raise the reef buddy.
Uh yeah...  Oh yeah. Hot.
Yeah that's pretty...
Come on cabbage patch. Cabbage patch.
Angie you made it.  Wait you're gonna break my gift.
Come on. You didn't have to get me anything. What'd you get me?
What does every bachelor pad need?
A lava lamp? How did you know l love lava lamps?
You know what l'm gonna put it right here next to my other one.
Hey come on Ang. l wanna show you the best thing about this place.
How great is this view?  Top of the reef. lt's amazing.
l know. lt's beautiful right?  Like you...
Like you... your new apartment. lt's... wow. Awesome.
What l'm trying to say is that l'm proud of you.
Yeah. lt was nothing really you know.
Hey... Hey oh you know what wait right here. Don't move.
l'll be right back. Girl you are gonna flip.
l'm back.  You're back.
You know what Ang?
Where l am right now this whole new life l got...
All my dreams comin' true...
ln a weird kinda way...
Well l never could've done it without you.
Oh sure you could.
Well probably not.
Ang. Here.
Oh! Oscar!
l know. l know. l'm just sorry that it took so long.
That's okay.
Bam! Huh?
My grandmother's pearl.
With interest. Now l don't forget anything
and l never forget who my friends are.  Oh!
Ang l...
Oh hi.
l'm not interrupting something am l?
Yes we're talking.  No.
Hey Lola. Wow. You're here.
Oh.
You er you gotta come best my meet friend Angie.
Uh uh eat my best men Wangie...
Your best friend? Oh that's sweet.
So you won't mind if l steal him for a while will you?
So look who's a somebody after all.
Well you know... Sharks!
On the... on the edge of the reef! Th.. Th... They're great whites!
Sharks. Okay everybody go home to your loved ones
spend the last few hours that you have with each other.
Oh...
l mean...
That's the way it used to be around here.
We'd have been all scrambling for cover and stuff
but not since Oscar came to town.
So Lola baby just wait here and l'm gonna be right back.
l'm gonna go take care of these sharks.
Go get 'em tiger.  Woo! Biceps triceps.
All right Oscar.  Go get 'em Oscar.
Lenny.
Where the heck is he? Lenny!
Hey. What are you doin'?
There's a sharkslayer out here. You wanna be next?
Oh yeah...
Lenny? Lenny?
That was close.  Super close.
Don't panic.
Quiet. We're safe.
Oh no not you again.  Yeah.
Ah! What was that?!  Yo! What is with you man?
Shh! He could be anywhere.  Who?
Shh! The Sharkslayer.
There's no sharkslayer out here. Yes there is.
No there is not. Trust me on this one.
Get a hold of yourself man. This is no time to act crazy.
You the one acting crazy crazy.
You're right. l'm sorry. l haven't been myself since the...
the uh...
Don't cry.
No no it's not all that. Just relax.
lt's my fault... kinda... not really... but still. My brother...
You just need a little time man. Look things'll work out.
You think?  Yeah.
So look l'm gonna take off...
And you should just go home okay?
Okay.  Hey good luck dawg.
Wait.  What man?
l didn't catch your name.  Oscar.
l'm Lenny. Hi.  Hi.
Where do you live?
Lenny where l come from fish don't like to get grabbed by sharks.
Sorry.  Go home.
There is no home for me now. Don't you understand?
You too big to be grabbing on me.  Take me home with you.
You won't even notice l'm there. l'm like the invisible shark.
Are you crazy?
Please. l'm begging you. Don't leave me alone.
Put your fins on the wall where l can see 'em.
Gotcha.  Hey. Yo The Shorties.
Oscar.  What y'all doin' here?
Check out my mad burner.  Whoop there it is.
How ya like that?
Hey y'all kids got some skills.
lt's wild style doo.
What did l tell you? You kids shouldn't be doin' this.
And besides it's not safe to be out here at night.
lt is now brobro. You the Sharkslayer.
Yeah brobro.
Sharkslayer?  What was that?
Sometimes l be coughin' for nothin'.
l need you off these streets seriously.
Get your butts home. l'll tell your moms y'all doin' bad stuff.
Let's go make Mr. Sykes puff up.  Yeah.
Bye Oscar.  See ya later doo.
Lenny. Did you see what just happened there?
l know. They think you're the Sharkslayer.
As if.
l don't appreciate your funky tone actually.
No wait up. Hey. l'm sorry seriously.
l don't want you mad at me
and l certainly don't want you to slay me.
You're having a good time? You're enjoying yourself?
Well for your information l am the Sharkslayer.
Oscar the Sharkslayer. That's what people be sayin'.
Wait. You mean you...  Yeah.
When the anchor...
Oh you're a liar.
Hey l didn't lie all right? All right l lied.
But it was a little lie. Come on who's it gonna hurt anyway?
Man l'm not explaining myself to you.
You're on your own.  No problem.
And if God forbid someone should l don't know
find out the truth about the Sharkslayer on my way back...
You wouldn't.  l would.
Uh...  Tssk!
Come here. Of course you can come with me.
But you know you're a shark right?
And l'm a Sharkslayer so we can't be seen together.
You dig dog?  Dig. Dog.
Dog dig. Dig dog. Yeah yo diggy dog.
Just come on.
OK Lenny follow my every move and don't make a sound.
You got it.
Ooh an echo. Echo.
Now batting for the Southside Sharks...
Ow! lt's not okay to hit.
Oohee  Shh!
Ow!
Get your tail in there.  Do you think anybody heard that?
Who was that? Who? Hey. Who's out there?
Yo. Crazy Joe.
l thought l heard something. Did you get that shark?
You have no idea Joe.
That's great. Well gotta go. My show's on.
All right. We're safe. For now.
Ahh.
Hey a bed.
Oh yeah that's good. That's heaven yeah.
Snuggly buggly wuggly.
l love you man.
Whoa. Hold up.  You're my new best friend.
Stop it.
OK you wanna be friends? Fine.
But we gotta lay down some rules. Rule number one:
No snuggly buggly... Whatever that just was.
You got it. Anything else?
Rule number two and this is the most important rule.
ln the event that possibly you get hungry...
Don't worry l won't eat anyone.
lf you haven't noticed l'm different from other sharks.
Let's put it that way leave it at that. Good night.
Define ''different''.  You'll laugh.
l'm not gonna laugh.
That's what you say and then what happens? You laugh.
Lenny l give you my word.
Okay l will tell you.
l'm... l'm a vegetarian.
Hold up.
So that's it?  Tch! What do you mean that's it?
You're the first fish l ever told. l'm tired of keeping it a secret.
And my dad he'll never accept me for who l am.
What's wrong with me?
Nothin' is wrong with you man.
l think all sharks should be like you.
God that's sweet of you to say.
And stop blaming yourself for what happened.
Really?
lf you wanna blame anybody blame me.
lf l hadn't been there in the first place none of this would've happened.
Jeez if Pop knew that he'd ice you for sure.
''lce''. What's he the Godfather or something?
Yeah.  Whatcha mean ''yeah''?
Yeah he is.
Hey. Are you all right?
Man. l told ya.  l'm doing it.
X circle X X double left square right trigger down square square.
Double square. Respect.  Respect.
l've got news for you. The Sharkslayer made me his manager.
So l'm now what l like to call untouchable. You hear me?
Sykes.  Hey Oscar.
Oh! Hey!... Sykes?
Hey there he is. My brotha my player the Sharkslayer.
Whatever. Listen...  Now you'll have to pay me protection.
Sykes. The deal is off. That shark l killed was Don Lino's son.
l know. Ain't it great?  Not if he finds out.
What do you mean? He's on the phone right now.
That's right l got the Sharkslayer right here in front of me.
And he's gonna slay you and all your sharks.
Sykes shut up! Shut up!
Hey that's good l like that.
Shut up Lino. Shut up.
What? Kid he wants to talk to you.  No. l'm not here.
Yeah he's right here.
Hello.  Shut up? Shut up?
You don't tell me ''shut up''.
Hello?  How you doin'?
Give me a pie with everything on it. Anchovies meatballs...
Luca.  Hi Boss.
Why you working in a pizza joint?  Get off the phone!
But l'm hungry.
My guys are coming for you Sharkslayer.
They're gonna tear you fin from fin.
Come on who's your puff daddy? Who takes care of you?
Come on you two we got work to do.
Mon l was winning.  Sykes. You got it all wrong.
They'll write songs about you.
Oh the shark bites
Sykes.   With his teeth dear
Sing it mon.   And then Oscar
Kicked his butt
Sykes man!
Come on.  Maybe l can help.
Hey. Lola? What're you doing here?
You just be poppin' up sometimes places.
Well you said to wait so...
l've been waiting.
Look l don't have a lot of time
for the handclappy makin'thelightsgooff
musicplayinginthedark thing.
What are you afraid of?  Afraid...
Yeah that's funny. l ain't afraid of nothin' it's just... Ooh.
Oh baby you are so tense.
Yeah l've been stressed lately you know protecting the reef.
l do that by myself you know.
lt's just crazy.  lt's too much it's piling up...
Yeah you know one thing on top of the other.
Actually l was thinking about retiring.
You don't want to do that.  l don't?
You have worked your way to the top.
You don't want to go back to the bottom do you?
No.
No way.
You just show 'em who's boss and those sharks will leave you alone.
Yeah you're right.  Lenny.
Psst!
Lenny? Where are you?
Hello Oscar.
Angie. Hey what are you doing here?
What did you forget something?
Oh maybe you forgot your shark.
Hi.
Uh... Shark! Swim Angie l'll cover you.
Quick before it's too late. Go on without me.
Oh stop it. Your pet shark here told me everything.
Dang Lenny why would you do that?
l don't know... l like her.
Thank you. l like you too.
What were you thinking bringing him in here?
No l'm still working out the kinks.
Kinks? You lied.
Everybody thinks you slayed the shark.
Who am l to tell them they're wrong?  How could you lie to me?Me!
Don't take it personally. Come on l lied to everybody.
All right look l'm sorry. l totally betrayed you
but listen l got just one little problem l gotta take care of.
Oh what's that?  Sharks are coming to get me!
And they should. l mean what'd you expect?
You'd take credit for killing a shark
and then everything would be fine and dandy for the rest of your life?
Uh... yeah.
But hey don't you worry about it.
Me and Lenny got it. We gonna fix it.
''We''? l don't want any part of this.
Too late veggieboy. They're lookin' for you too.
Point taken. What's the plan?
This is what we gonna do.   Here's the plan.
You tell the truth. And you go home.
All right look this is what we're gonna do.
We're gonna paint you up all bloody. A mess right?
Then you gonna swim out and meet the sharks before they get here.
And you're gonna say ''Stop. Don't y'all. Don't go no farther!''
''That Sharkslayer's crazy man!''
''He beat me senseless. He's a stonecold killer man!''
Then you could tell 'em l'm huge. Tell 'em l'm handsome.
Throw that in say l'm buff.  You are going way too far.
Actually he hasn't gone far enough.
Exactly. What?
You need to slay a shark and l need to disappear.
Here's what we're gonna do.
Katie Current reporting live.
We've had unconfirmed reports of a...   Shark!
Dadada  Look. It's the Sharkslayer.
Dadadada!
Holy mackerel. Did we get that?
Hey Ang. Oscar's on the TV.
Show me that. Go ahead with your bad self.
Do you hear them Lenny?
They are goin' crazy man. They love us.
They love you. They hate me. Can we switch sides?
l can be the Fishslayer. They'll never see it coming.
Come on man. You sell this you'll never have to go home again.
You can start a new life. Now gimme a growl.
Okay.
Like that?  That was... pretty good.
Let's go.
ls that all? Do you understand how huge my client is? Turn on your TV.
Lenny. Lenny! Lenny!
Turn off your TV. Turn off your TV.
Don't swallow.
Oscar?  No it's Pinocchio. Of course it's me.
Why did you do that?  l'm sorry.
No. ''Sorry'' is when you step on somebody's fin at the movies.
''Sorry'' is when you say ''When's the baby due?''
and it turns out the person's just fat.
This is as far away from ''sorry'' as you could possibly get.
But Oscar l think l'm gonna puke.
No no. Lenny just open up.
Nice and easy.
Are you not entertained?
You can't handle the truth.
You had me at hello.
Turn your TV back on. Why are you turning your TV off?
This reef is huge. How we supposed to find the Sharkslayer?
This is it Lenny. Big finish. Just like we practiced.
The flying fish?  The flying fish.
A little help here buddy boy?
Sorry.  Thank you.
Curse you Sharkslayer.
Yeah and you tell Don Lameo
that l don't never ever ever never
want to see another shark on this reef again. Ever.
Remember this name.
Oscar the Sharkslayer.
You see? You see?
Oscar! Oscar!
Yay!   Oscar boom byeay
Oscar boom byeay
Look at Oscar.
Oscar boom byeay Oscar boom byeay
Woo! Hey... Lola.
Seems The Sharkslayer not only conquered a few sharks today
but maybe a few hearts?
Has the reef's most eligible bachelor been snapped up?
I'm Katie Current here live
watching the Sharkslayer making out.
Hey Angie can you hand me the blue one?
Thank you.
Look who stepped in the room!
Yeah!
Oscar and Lenny. What a team baby. Give me that give me some fin.
High fin. Low fin.
Yo did you see me? l was like...
l was crazy.
When you punched me and the crowd was...
Yeah they ate it up.
You didn't know l had it in me did you?
lt was like an Oscarsplosion.  How good was l?
You was the bomb.  Thank you. Thank you.
And hey hey hey Casanova. l saw your big finish on the news.
Nice smooch lover boy.
lxnay on the isskay man. That's private.
Private? The entire reef saw you do it.
Hey somebody's in a bad mood. C'mon Ang lemme see that smile.
Show me the smile baby...  Knock it off.
What has gotten into you?  Me?
l swear sometimes l wanna take your big dumb dummyhead and just...
Ang what is the problem?
Problem? No problem. l don't have a problem.
Miss Perfect is the one with the problem.
Hey you guys...
What do you got against Lola?  Not my lips that's for sure.
What's goin' on?  l'm gonna stay outta this one.
Why would you even care about Lola anyway?
l don't.  You don't.
No.  No what?
l don't know.  You wanna...
No!
Just tell me Oscar 'cause l'm curious.
Why do you think she's interested huh?
Do you think for one minute that she'd even be with you if you weren't the famous Sharkslayer?
Please don't fight.  Are you blind?
She treats me like l'm somebody.
Would she love you if you were nobody?  Nobody loved me as a nobody.
l did.
Before the money and before the fame.
Before the lie.
To me you were a somebody Oscar.
Now you're nothing but a fake.
A sham. A con.
You're a joke.
Here l come...
Tada! Sebastian the WhaleWashin' Dolphin.
Angie...  No forget it. Just go.
l'm tired of hearing how everything you had in your life wasn't good enough.
lncluding me.
Angie?  Oh Honey l'm sorry.
Go go back and do it again.
Hey come on.
lt'll be OK.
One shot to your heart without breaking your skin
Noone has the power to hurt you like your kin
Kept it inside Didn't tell noone else...
You can't handle the truth.
You've got Shark Breath.
And now you only have yourself to blame
If you continue to live this way
Get it together   You wanna heal your body
Get it together   You have to heal your heart
Whatsoever...
What you kids doing? How many times l have to tell you?
lt's past your bed time. Go on.
Hey. What are you kids up to?
That looks pretty good. You should do this for a living.
You can fly fly fly fly
You can live or you can die
You know that life is a choice you make
You can give or you can take
You can fly fly fly fly
You can fly fly...
Preparation ''O''.
lt slays hemorrhoids like Oscar slays sharks.
Hey Oscar.
Preparation O...
Angie was right. l am a joke.
Hey Sharkslayer.
Why are you out here? All your friends are inside.
Not all my friends.
You mean that little bottom feeder from the Whale Wash?
Forget about her. She's a nobody.
No l'm the nobody.
Oh let me guess. She told you that she loves you.
ls that it?
lt's not like you feel the same way about her.
You know l don't think this is gonna work out.
Wait are you dumping me?
Let me explain something to you.
We're gonna party like it's your birthday
Ha! Young love.
Sugarpie honeybunch
You know that I love you
I can't help myself
I love you and nobody else...
Hey Oscar!  l can't talk. l gotta find Angie.
l need to tell her l love her.
You come and you go...
Way to go Oscar.
lrie. Whale Wash where you...  Gimme it.
Where you get a whale of a wash...  Gimme the phone.
...and the price is very very low considering how good the wash is.
How many times do l have to tell you? lt's ''gosh.''
''You get a whale of a wash and the price oh my gosh.''
Me gets it man.
Whale Wash?  Rhymes with gosh.
Gimme that. Get outta here. Go be useless someplace else.
Sykes where's Angie?
Whale Wash you get a whale of a wash...
lt's for you.
Hello?
Is this the Sharkslayer?  Yeah who's this?
lt's Luca the Octo... l mean forget about it.
Now you follow these instructions to the letter OK?
File cabinet. Top drawer. There's a package. Get it.
That's right tough guy we've got your girl.
There's a sitdown in one hour.
Who is it?  Shh!
Be there if you don't wanna see her sleepin' with the fishes.
The dead ones.
Now nod your head if you understand.
Now tell me if you nodded your head.
l nodded.
They got Angie. And they want a sitdown.
l never meant for anybody to get hurt especially not Angie.
This is all my fault.
Classic move. l've seen it a thousand times.
They take the thing you love the most and then they use it against you.
We gotta go to that sitdown and we gotta save her.
Whoa. Look l wanna save Angie too
but l can't waltz in and say ''Hi Pop. l'm a dolphin.''
Lenny?  And the Sharkslayer's a fake.
Fake?
We're gonna need a better plan than that.
This is a joke right?
Because l told Lino...
Shut up Lino. Shut up.
Tell me that's not Lenny.
Tell me you're a real Sharkslayer.  l'm sorry Sykes l'm not.
But the sharks don't know that.
Will you stop screwin' around? This'll never work. We're dead.
Thank you Sykes. Thank you.
My man Sykes just begged me
not to murderlise all y'all up in here.
Now l might listen to him but then again l might not.
And that depends on the individual behavior
of all the individuals in here individually.
Ain't that right?
Look he's got dolphin muscle.
My uncle Vito got whacked by one of those.
Now which one of you sardines called this meeting?
That would be me.
So this is the Sharkslayer.
l've been lookin' forward to meeting you.
l feel like we're practically family. You know that?
Funny ain't it?
l brought my kids into the world full of love and care
and you took them out.
You know who l am? Do you know who l am?
l'm the Don. The boss of the Great White Sharks.
Hey boss l saved you a seat.
l've been runnin' this reef since before you was born.
And if you thought a guy like me can't get to a guy like you...
Guess what? You thought wrong.
Pah. Man you the one who's wrong.
l barely even know that girl. What's your name miss?
Oh yeah? Well l say he's bluffing.
Marone if l wasn't married...  How ya doin' pretty lady?
Lola. We meet again.
You know Sharkslayer there's only one thing l like better than money.
Revenge.
Oh! l'm in love.
Your sharkslayin' days are over.
And there ain't nothing you can do about it.
Huh? What's so funny?  Ow.
You got nothing. Nothing.
Sebastian take her out.
Can't touch this.
Ohoh ohoh ohoh ohoh
Stop. Oscar time.
OK new rules.
Nobody l repeat nobody makes a move without my OK.
l am the Panama Canal baby.
From now on everything flows through me.
What'd he do? l can't see it.
You don't lose a toothyou don't grow one back without my OKOK?
OK.
lf you sneeze you don't wipe that boogie without my OK OK?
And you don't say ''OK'' without my OK.
OK?
Ohoh. OK thank you all for coming. We gotta go.
One more thing. What's with all y'all living in the Love Boat?
Oscar.  Y'all are supposed to be the mob.
Get yourselves a real hideout. Oscar.
And take a good look Lino.
lt's over. You're old school.
Oscar.  What?
The horror. The horror.
Um... excuse me.
Ang are you OK?  No l'm not OK.
He ate me..
l couldn't take it. The taste was killin' me.
Lenny?
ls that you?
You're alive?
l thought l lost you.
What are you wearing? Huh? What is that?
Boss it's Lenny. He was wearing a disguise so we wouldn't recognize him
but now he's not wearing a disguise so we do recognize him.
Hi Pop.  Are you kiddin' me?
Are you kiddin' me? Are you outta your mind?
Do you have any idea how this looks?
This is the best sitdown l've ever been to.
What are you doing with him? He took out your flesh and blood Frankie.
But Pop listen...  But nothing.
You never take sides against the family. Ever.
Hey Don. Lino. Sir. lt's not his fault. This is between you and me.
What did l ever do to you?
You took Frankie away and you turned Lenny into a dolphin.
l'm gonna get you.
Oscar look out.  Oscar swim. Swim for your life.
You're gonna regret the day you became the Sharkslayer.
Well well well.
Look who's stuck in the porthole.
You still hungry big guy?
Well say hello to my little friends.
Try it again.  Whale Wash
you get a whale of a wash and the price...
Oh my gosh.
All right. You got it right.
Everybody out of the way.
Blow out.  Shark!
Come on Lino it's time to clean up your act.
Pop leave him alone.
All right Lino. Game's over.
Lenny? What are you doing in there?  Sorry.
Where's Lino?
He's right behind me isn't he?  You're mine now.
Whoa!
Let's finish this Sharkslayer.
Oh we're about to.
Thank you for coming to Whale Wash.
OK somebody needs to get me out of the bubble.
Today.
Angie...  The Sharkslayer does it again.
This time luring two sharks into his deathtrap of hygiene.
Oscar you're the somebody everybody wants to be.
The top of the food chain. Tell our cameras how it feels to be you.
Angie.  Oscar get me outta here quick.
l need a head start to get as far away as possible.
Look what you did to him.  lt's a misunderstanding.
Sharkslayer. Over here.
Sharkslayer. Sharkslayer.
Stop!
l am not a real Sharkslayer!
l lied.  What?
And l'm not a real financial advisor.
OK. lt was an anchor that killed Frankie.
l didn't have anything to do with it and neither did Lenny.
lf that was true why did you run away?
Because you always wanted me to be like Frankie.
l'll never be the shark you want me to be.
What is your problem?
So your son likes kelp. So his best friend is a fish.
So he likes to dress like a dolphin. So what?
Everybody loves him just the way he is.
Why can't you?
Don't make the same mistake that l did.
l didn't know what l had until l lost it.
Will you get me outta this
so l can hug my kid and tell him l'm sorry?
Pop.
Come here you.
l love you Son no matter what you eat or how you dress.
Oscar?
Angie?
Angie l wish l knew now what l knew then.
l mean l wish you knew what l knew
l mean before this...
You're blowin' it man.  Mind your business.
lt's emotional and it's pressure.
What l'm saying l just...
l didn't need the top of the reef.
Everything l wanted was right there in front of me the whole time.
Well what about being a somebody?
l'm nobody without you.
You're not helping.
Come here you big dumb dummyhead.
l never told you two this but you're the best henchman a guy ever had.
C'mon group hug.
Sorry man.
Come Sykes try again mon. Don't fret.
Forget it. The moment's gone.
So uh Lino... Uh Don...
We cool right? l mean like the reef is safe?
Walk the streets you know without... aaah! You know.
Yeah we're cool.
Oscar. Excuse me.
You've lost everything you lied so hard to achieve.
Tell me what's next for you?
Come on everyone's waiting Mr. Manager.
All right l just gotta put the finishing touch on my new desk.
Love ya Pop.
Yo dog.  Sykes.
All right partner let's see what you can do.
Sykes and Oscar's Whale Wash is now open for business.
Yo E B. Let's get this party bumpin'.
Yo yo. lt's E and B on the wheels of steel.
Yo Christina. Missy.
How about we have a little Oscarlicious fun?
Yo small tuna fish I'm one big catch
You might not ever get rich
Let me tell you it's better than diggin' a ditch
There ain't no tellin' who you might meet...
Don't try this at home.
A movie star or maybe a common thief
Workin' at the car wash   Whoa whoa yeah yeah
At the car wash yeah   Ooh yeah
At the car wash   Sing it with me...
Hey Angie sorry Pop and l are late
but we brought some new customers.
Hey how ya doin'?
Wow.
OK guys come on in.
This ain't no place to be if you're planning on being a star
Let me tell you it's always cool
And the boss don't mind sometimes if you're acting like a fool
Working at the car wash...  No snap it. You're not snapping it.
l'm snapping it.
A lot of great whites can't do it yo.  Yo?
Yo what's up?  Up with what?
Yo yo yo. Yo yo yo. Yo yo...
You say ''yo'' one more time
l'm gonna yo you.  Sorry.
OK doo l pimped your hide.  All right.
Hey. You think this is funny?
What am l a clown to you?
Car wash
Sharks in the water Make theirjaws lock
When I swim through the grim I'm too hot
You can make y'all bets Y'all small tuna fish
I'm one big catch   Sharkslayer
Bow down player...
What you got?  You don't want none of this.
You gotta be kidding. Break it down fellas.
9 to 5 I gotta keep that fat stack comin'...
You got served.
Workin' at the car wash
Hey yeah
At the car wash yeah
Come on work baby work it Sing it
At the car wash   Hey yeah
At the car wash yeah
Come on work baby work it Sing it
At the car wash
Workin' at the car wash yeah
So come on come on come on come on
Now keep it comin'
You may not ever get rich but hey
A Shark Tale exclusive
Ooh hey
Get your car washed today
亲，有空的时候可以来交流电影哦 加我QQ：274796078
Hello? Hello.
Oscar? Listen baby l know l was a bad girl
but come on you'd have to be crazy not to take me back.
Did someone say crazy?
Taxi.
Hey taxi.
Hello.
Hi. You gonna eat the rest of your popcorn?
Eurgh! Too much butter.
Hey a nacho.
You're not even halfway done yet.
What? You see this guy? He hardly worked on the movie at all.
Always on the phone. Yakkin' yakkin' yakkin'.
Man have you guys seen what's playing next door?
Stinky.
What you doing? Go on get outta here. lt's past your bedtime.